good morning gamers it's another
beautiful day in the Minecraft isn't
that right everyone ow damn it that it
aah
why are you near my meatball
don't wait I love you meatball the man
you seem to attract a lot of bad people
what is it with meatballs and batteries
IKEA tower looking beautiful of course
moo-cow are you trying to escape both
cow
please anyway today we have a lot of
things to do we have a lot of missions
to complete
isn't that right Sven bro basically I
want to build a little house for my
little horse he is I feel like he's not
getting the love and attention that he
deserves
he's sitting in here with these other
disgusting things Jurgen deserves of his
own house right Sven just like you got
your own house
you're gonna leave at least the Serbs
are stable oh my god get out of my house
all right don't escape Jurgen don't
escape I need to make this safer so that
Jurgen never disappears again it's my
heart cannot handle it anymore
isn't that right Sven don't worry son it
won't be as it's fancy as your house it
will just be less stable how tall does
it have to be for me to right now okay
oh my god this is the most annoying
place well you guys are in my face you
smell
no wonder Jurgen doesn't like it with
you guys oh my god you're good no I'm
trying to build here it's gonna be the
best stable you have ever seen in your
life I couldn't even finish that
sentence with that Oh God Sven and his
perverted ways though happens I do have
fence there we go
I mean already looking low-key kind of
cute that's adorable
now you're breathtaking Jurgen your bath
oh we should lit up with Lantern that
would be so cute I don't need that many
uh can I make these back it's for a good
cause it's for a good cause it hurts my
soul
it's for your again okay it's for your
again buy a t-shirt so I can afford this
oh my god that's so Kat Kat what the
Frick you dude oh my god I didn't know
you could hang them that's adorable
yes are you kidding me I'm one short
damn act it's for your again it's for
your didn't do it for Jurgen
it's Merrigan purgin oh my god I'm one
short
I'll never mind yeah burping oh my god
oh there's kick oh you know what would
be cute having like a little caldron
caldron are they expensive ah I'm not
making that noise for your kin though I
have these stones
[Laughter]
[Music]
guys all right I can enter now aah
like wouldn't it be cute if we had this
little there's already water perfect
look so he can make a drink drink so he
can make slurp slurp can I ride the
llamas I can't okay we're gonna have to
try and I don't want to ride you aah
[Music]
all right I'll push you then cheese out
no no cows can end oh god this is an all
cup
you're gonna zone ready escaped get out
yes this is for Jurgen only you're
getting smoking oh but it's don't go
back in gosh
this is why we can't have nice things in
Minecraft get out oh now it works let's
go there you see then then there bone
you can stay oh look look how cute
Jurgen has a little friend in here on
don't ever speak to Jurgen again that's
right Maya look he has a cute little you
can drink water now
ok that's freaking adorbs and I don't
care what anyone says ok so you may
wonder why do I have this ugly wall here
well I wanted to try out if I could
build like a hidden door the thing is
like because now when I ah that when I
ride out with your again smart again it
doesn't work it doesn't work I couldn't
make it the war we like no they're just
they're too small for your again so I
want to make like an like a piston door
I think because Pistons are fun get away
from here some so when me and uragan got
an adventure we hit button door open and
we go out and it's epic fun time okay
let's do that I don't know how to do
that let's figure it out right Sven
let's use our peepee poo-poo brain okay
okay so first what we have to do is we
have to cook a steak I need I know I
have okay I have three sticky pistons I
think I might need more I need these and
I need a lever probably a new axe
I don't mind my anvil broke I'm so low
on steel fine you know what fine this I
have a lot of diamonds okay I think I
think I can spare to make an axe what
level am i 27 I'm freakin rich
freaky
all right and chaunt min time what do we
get what did we get what do we get
efficiency 3 ok I guess I'll take it
dude can we talk about how I'm fully
diamond can we talk about that you guys
want to talk about that I'm gonna talk
about how rich I am why don't I have so
much diamond no steel because how will
this work let's test it out on neutral
ground
I don't know how sticky piston work but
I think what they can do is they hold
they hold the block that it's listen I'm
a Minecraft veteran I think I know
better than you so don't even
Stevens Mead and how does this work does
it come back it comes back that's epic
so the idea then here again if you could
just stay over here oh god it's gonna be
annoying no one goes near your again no
one goes near Yuri of why can't you
leave us alone
no you cannot enter you shall not pass
god I hate you all leave us a lot leave
us leave us leave us are you asking for
it you're asking for it you're asking
don't come there you will you'll get
Frigg okay one two three
no no ah I'll kill all of you oh my god
you freak
already extremely annoying wait a minute
can we even go through this Jurgen is
too fat sorry you're again yeah you
better art you're just showing off now
you're just showing off so that means we
need three more sticky pistons damnit
I'm poor
don't worry about the yelling Sven it's
literally poppy has a tough day at work
how did you get through oh my god
pistons yes it's only one it's all in
one sealed so we actually can't afford
it I think I have slime yes I do with
the squeeze of lemon and lime okay slime
no piston sticky piston one
okay and then one two it's better be
cool these better flippin dipping skinny
dipping bald Pippen get away from him
yet again it's evil okay so this will go
here I realize this whole contraption
needs to come further back god you're
annoying if it wasn't for water sheep I
would get rid of all of you all of you
would go by buying just so you know just
so you know I think I freaked up again
for the third time it's my freak day a
birthday I mean today thanks for all the
birthday wishes why do I said that
that's a lie okay did I freak up again I
cannot freak out three times
I've never freaked up here that sucks
we got to get rid of Lanford okay so
this is how it look like when the doors
are open then I just need to wire it
somehow I got your thank you thank you
keep telling them to leave hopefully I
can make it as clean as possible I don't
really get how redstone works I'm still
like I don't know so I make it go under
or above or bow that does not activate
it what maybe it's better if I go
underneath you just hit me with a gate
okay hit me with a gate gosh okay I'm
almost done I'm almost done if you just
leave me alone let me think what how is
that connected
[Music]
sound like an you know what this game
makes zero sense
look how much space there is your only
oh my god they gave this back are you
kidding me I don't understand redstone
how did that okay I don't understand red
block clearly but it works no no my
wiring
[Music]
ah oh my god yeah haha so why does this
not kill and you know what all right
let's just try it out now oh yeah let's
uh hide the ugly okay here again we are
riding off I guess I needed to close as
well I just oh my god peace and quiet
I've been listening to this sheeps for
so long I mean I did loose a little bit
over the aesthetic maybe I should spend
some time oh my god get down from there
yeah they're escaping
oh you're so annoying
cool literally one cow is like you're
again not you too okay so it will work
like this boom we're out and that's it
that was that was what I go and then we
come back hit the switch Jurgen is safe
and sound and he has water it's perfect
do you like it here again he loves it he
said he loved it I heard him Oh about
cow
damn it
was trying to get rid of the boat my god
please don't make a big deal out of boat
cab please just that's right Sven today
we are actually heading out on adventure
because when I went all across the sad
I discovered a jungle I know I never
went like inside it but it's time to go
I think I know where to go find it okay
let's go yeah come on Sven and uragan
it's adventure as always I forgot a
leash I need to bring a leash there's so
many things you need to think about in
Minecraft at least if you care about
your animals it becomes a whole
different aspect of the game because you
can't go without really glad I spent
half the episode trying to build a
freaking redstone it's fun I like it
look it's cool
I think it's cool I wish I was better at
hiring the hiding the wiring and stuff
if you guys have any tips like let me
know Sven is with us sorry I wish this
wind could go on the horse on the air
again that'd be so cute all right well
this is a good time for me to shout out
represent calm sighs PewDiePie we now
have minecraft merged that's right
support the series support Sven support
uragan yet we look epically cool at the
same time all right what else could you
want in life
so the jungle is like really far north
this way gotta make sure Sven is still
there but get a pufferfish it's doing
great today you look really good today
buckets of puffer fish son doesn't like
puttan spenders didn't like pufferfish
it reminds him of when he was in the
bucket a lot of people have been saying
that you can actually put the ender
dragon in a bucket and a lot of people
are also bunch of lying sniffles all
right where's this freaking jungle I
don't like water 360 over the water it
never works with 360s all right fine
here come here cheap and showmanship
team Tom Jim Jim Jim Tom come on come on
you're against then we have adventures
we're looking for jungles what are we
gonna find in the jungle
I don't know that's the fun of mine crap
I haven't even been in snow places yet
or they're like yetis it's Bigfoot in
Minecraft Sven I remember I saw Fox for
like half a second and I was like ah
there's water oh I don't remember
I just remembered North can we do it and
then we can it that the jungle we found
the jungle kiss van there it is and
turtles are they virgin hello Turtles
where are your children I will not harm
them I just want their shoots all right
we're gonna have to put the leash on you
again let's go I think you can find like
parrots and like other animals it's a
whole new world
Jurgen and Sam is having epic times when
we have to be extra careful this is on
exhibited
what is this what is this is dope
what about bamboo brick yeah I can make
shampoo now oh my god
there's shampoo and my can I climb these
oh my god
ow oh my god I can climb I got a I got a
go on top man
I got ahh Oh fine
oh ok I see I see I see it isn't called
you again thank you thank you
damn this is cool I could decorate my
Japanese house with these bamboo that's
so satisfying my dot it's thick in here
dude I can't even see myself ah what was
that don't be scared you're again nearly
choked myself I don't know like what's
in the jungle like this doesn't look
very jungle e I assume oh there's melons
in I mean cactuses why am i lagging so
much haha
you want some fine we take a little
cactus break here you go Sven here you
go you're again alright we're gonna have
to do the old technique I don't know you
don't love this here again hey you can
stay with pufferfish oh gosh it's
getting dark soon no I should have
brought it I should have brought it are
you okay there you're yet should have
brought a bed now we're gonna be in the
jungle at night oh I hear them
get him your head spin that's my boy hey
yeah that's right
baan Gaeng good job Sven is that what I
think it is do you see this man no not
the melon whoa the parrot in a temple at
the same time friend look it's a blue
it's a blue one it's a blue one jigeon's
hello I am your friend we're bringing
you home how do i how do i tame a parent
oh my god it's so cute I love you
oh my god eight oh my god they will sit
on your shoulder
oh my god I'm free I have some seeds
here I'll give you my seed oh you like
that okay he likes it yeah what's your
name then Klaus Klaus okay Klaus okay
luckily there's like melons here which
makes bling bling bling bling bling long
long long melons is you like melon seeds
Sven MIT cloth you're making creepy
noise oh he loves me does that mean I
did it or that you just liked it
he's sitting right knees closes with us
my god I'm lagging like crazy freak off
he's he's sitting on my frickin is he
sitting is he sitting he's blue - yes
yes yes that's so awesome we win at
games and this I'm to like it for a
jungle I had like a piece computer but
minecraft is just too much look at this
van
look at this Klaus I mean you crazy he's
crazy here have a little more no where's
the entrance doesn't that look scary
there's gotta be an whoa found it okay
gamers spend you sit here Klaus you you
keep looking sexy whoa I got the green
how this is awesome I can farm this okay
this could be a trap I don't like this
yeah yeah you sit there sit there
everyone said don't buy feelings that's
all you got to do here don't die I
really want this mossy stuff I could
make like cool slippery alright there's
definitely traps in here I know how this
game works but look o it's Slenderman
hello slender sorry is this your house
come in it Kuniko minutes like okay I'm
gonna have to she believed it alright
cool nice knowing oh god there's a
little boy what are you guys
where'd you go oh god there's lepers
what where is he oh god he's angry you
man Oh freakin oh my Wed me stop am i
I'm lagging listen I need your pearls we
caught them dude you suck oh nice
whoa they all get stuck in the bamboo no
sir are you making is he making spend
noises that's sir okay all right we got
to be careful here practice caution
there's lepers okay I really feel like
this hat has to be something or it's
just like a random generated speckle it
is maybe yes okay then there's
definitely something here why are there
three levers oh god I'm scared
hello that's a dispenser they're gonna
shoot what is that that's a trap oh my
god how do I get past the trap what is
this
hello did I do something hello oh where
did that go
sound like over here alright let's keep
it how do i how do I do the trap whoa oh
oh okay be careful oh I I think I'd be
activated no and steal I really need
steel and bones for some happy day I
thought ID activation yeah you can shoot
me now you can shoot me now but you
can't shoot me name no it's IKEA bird
it's IKEA bird said yes I want to
explore a little bit more
see what we can find is the bird like
how fast is the bird not very fast
well what is that huh that's the cocoa
beans the cocoa pocos but how many of
these Fricker's are gonna I thought it
was the burner that made the freaking
noise I thought I was like dude he
throws me okay alright I got uh I got to
give seats away as well how do I know
the help of mr. Mellon man okay he seems
fine freakin melons dude dude you could
uh yeah you could be like cool tree
houses and stuff so I'm here don't hurt
him so I think with the cocoa beans you
can actually make Brown by it's like an
actual jungle you safe Oh got it
I thought IKEA bird died he's a good is
a good war I guess freaking creepers why
are there creepers in the jungle answer
me now
why is that the same temple or another
temple are there villages in the jungle
maybe that'd be cool kind of finding
like a town in here oh my god I'm an
actual child
we're never cool if there was like
villagers in the jungle wouldn't that be
awesome son and IKEA spent Klaus his
name is Klaus get it right gamers and I
stand on the out never mind
you snake God is annoying navigating oh
my god they're all oh my god two of them
don't think so oh that shot though that
shot though come on
what if creeper is just like us I'm
walking in the wrong direction
why does Klaus sound like no he makes
creeper noises or does he warned me for
it it confused me so much the first time
I think he does it to warn me that's so
awesome
Klaus is awesome alright we just got to
find uragan and bounce one dot under B
beep
[Applause]
[Music]
hello hello what do you want feathers no
seats what does he like what does pandas
like bamboo they like my boo you like
bamboo oh my god we're making new
friends guys this is awesome thank you
really chug that down huh can I even
tame a pan that you make some no sense
alright just finish it
oh my god you're really chugging that
down aren't you
wait pandas have different personalities
that can be lazy worried playful
aggressive weak or brown what that's so
cool
so I don't think we can actually tame it
so I'm just gonna go ahead and do this
mean does he follow me is he like a cow
that he follows if I have bamboo how do
I make them follow me
here have another one so I definitely
got the lazy version of the pun that my
god you are not moving are you so I
can't put the leash on him how do I make
him come
can you move at all or is he stuck maybe
stuck in there
bamboo I'll push you all the way back
home buddy is he following me now ah
research is actually moving now yeah I
got bamboo you want this can I ride him
what can I do what can I do with you
lame alright I guess I can't tame them
whatever we have a real panda at home
okay we don't need fake pandas just
gotta find uragan now he's in a hole
somewhere oh god where did I put him oh
look at the bird floss very hello you're
again
here here's a treat oh nevermind he
doesn't want it okay now how do I get
out of here this is probably the easiest
way can they teleport this far Oh God
alright oh my gosh
I think nope oh oh he's warning me again
oh my god
don't go in there here again I think not
oh he's using hacks oh my gosh whoa is
that it's a Triton guy we're going for
it we're going for it
they're dangerous is freaky Sven I need
you in hold right now oh sorry sorry
oh my god I'm alone Sven damn savage did
Jurgen I hit him like a million what
we's online Chiba
that's good though yes did you drop it
damn it
get him Sven get him Sven kill him kill
him kill him spend showing show him what
you got spend freak him up real good
Sven nice job Sven cool so it's raining
it's raining here but not here my craft
makes no sense gosh can the Sun come up
please woah
it's a village guys Klaus were you
flying backwards I saw my high jump oh
yeah kitty damn it
I don't have enough fish one day will
tame a Kia Tim Keanu Reeves 26 potatoes
you're crazy
get out of my face give me this I want
this I think we're gonna have to start
preparing for the end game like getting
arrows and stuff like that because I
think we're getting pretty close not
gonna lie
knock on wood how do you make terracotta
stuff can I just steal an iron golem
question mark I mean this village kind
of suck let's get real here
oh sorry son what in the world happened
here can I steal you're coming with me
we got a lot of new friends today okay
why make an iron golem they're expensive
you can't just steal them I can't tell
if this is bad or good but you Rick
we're bringing you a new home you're
gonna live you're gonna live nice and
stuff we have like we have stuff listen
I built two of you two of you are out
there so okay I didn't know you had to
put a leash on that this time we're
gonna have to I'm gonna have to be with
a bridge cuz I don't think he goes in
water you're against Merrigan how fast
can the iron golem go I want to see they
oh that's right you better run boy you
better run me and the boy know where do
you go oh my god come um no aah
oh you've done it now get back from
there
where's where's your leash third I need
other artists come here come back here
you're in the pity pie again you're in
the bro gang what look did you not
freakin hear me - I don't care you don't
have it same this is not a democracy you
don't matter is what I'm saying you will
pay for the crimes of water sheep
someone has to me and the boys storming
area 51 run ow
could I bring Klaus could I bring him
with me when I fight bosses and stuff
like that did I tell you to stop running
ah
glorious meatball where's my IKEA power
there she is
and we we ride in
and we close up that was awesome
oh yeah where did the leash go no one
knows hey Walter sheep there's someone I
want you to see this is your new a you
stay here protect water sheep that is
your duty you can't hear me I said
protect water shame you can't protect
water she who is what there's y'all my
god idiot
pack it up alright gamers thanks for
watching another episode of minecraft
letsplay hope you guys had fun we made
some new friends today that's awesome
thanks for all the lovers report if you
want to check out the merch link is in
the description and that's it for me for
now smash like and subscribe oh yeah
what what you never played super
simulator you know it's fun right I'm
not supposed to give my opinion but give
it a try and then you can tell me if
it's good or not not convinced yet okay
I'll cut you a deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]