good morning gamers today today we say
goodbye through its little friend Jurgen
the second you know the first Jurgen
Jurgen one at least that was your fault
technically that was your fault but this
I can't blame on anyone isn't that right
mushroom cow thing this is all on me
isn't that right spending close IKEA
bird what are you even doing there I
should not have let Jurgen to go in the
mines I didn't even think it was
possible there's only one thing left to
do let's say goodbye I can't keep doing
this
I can't keep losing the ones that look
jörgen deserved better but at least at
least he died happy
[Music]
look at that spen is devastated he
refused to leave the boat IKEA bird says
the same I'm all alone one year again is
one year n't enough but 2-yard against
that's not right I can't even afford a
proper burial
come on Sven we got to go pick his
favorite flowers Daisy
David was his favorite Oh Mike that is
mine with taking flowers now's not the
time
Libra is a lot
get him spending that strike not today
oh my god getting a bit intense here I'm
just trying to pick flowers geez sex oh
my oh my ha you are one tank you know if
there's anyone that's never gonna like
never gonna go it's vain I'm just trying
to pick flowers that's literally all I
want
here we go this this is his favorite
flowers one day when I'm rich Jurgen I
promise I will get you the full diamond
that you deserve
but until then Jurgen second
rest easy buddy Macias in Angola that's
right you're again one day we'll all be
together
don't worry but now you are with your
brother okay I know this is kind of a
downer to start an episode but the show
must go on spend we must continue our
adventure that's what's that's what
Jurgen 1 & 2 would have wanted I imagine
it oh my god please not today Sven I'm
sad too but something has to be done
[Music]
sorry now I know there's other Jurgis
out there but I'm not ready for another
Jurgen Sven I can't do it I do remember
something from the very first few
episodes there he is hey buddy
me and Sven are looking for a new
companion are you available you're busy
you've literally been here since episode
1 what are you doing here have some
wheat how's that taste good go away it's
not for you he does like it's fun I
think he likes it I think he likes us
another no no na wa nani desu ka' tell
us donkey son how many times I have to
do it please love me I have no one else
but hey can I ride you you don't like
melon ok well this might be for the
better listen I got a whole supply back
at home just fall just come with us my
god you eat like a horse I'm literally
out I just have to sit on donkey oh ok
we're just chilling huh
he loves me your name Sui hold the
Swedish names are running through my
brain hold up let me get you a Saito let
me get you a sable first oh my gosh
we're under attack not now
for yogurt
[Music]
get them speck
I've demoed
or should I name him I'm really
struggling Bernie it's not a good name
Bernie the beast you're officially part
of the bro gang he's so slow burn a oh
god Barney hey Bernie there's there's a
couple of people I want you to meet
first of all this is Jurgen - this is
Jurgen one this is IKEA bird this is
where what the Sheep used to stay um
hopefully you won't disappear
Bernie hopefully you won't just go
places without asking oh how about that
are you actually staying okay we're
gonna gather up fruit in some food but
because it's time to seek revenge I
don't know about you guys but I'm I need
to kill something then you're gonna have
to stay hold down the fort
he's trying to make acquaintances do I
have a nametag
can I put an armor on Bernie oh my gosh
I never thought of that
it's a horse armor I doubt I doubt I can
no just don't die on me Bernie please I
know this is a bit unprecedented there's
a there's a city but I can access oh my
gosh are you kidding me all right don't
be afraid Bernie I made it safe I'll be
right after you are you
are you Bernie
okay he's fine Bernie's fine everyone
welcome to this is a bad idea okay
Bernie I forgot some stuff just don't go
through the pours Oh Bernie
I need weed fast okay
I have obsidian I could get some more
where's Bernie there you are okay let's
go Bernie
we are literally too fat there we go oh
okay
hopefully this should be safe right god
I hope this works okay so now we're
gonna go through at the same time Bernie
don't worry it's fine it's fine
the raid has started it's killing time
Friday for you again ah kill oh my god
why did I do this at night kill them
back off pissants how is there so many
the youngling stop running child
that's right Bernie no one messes with
this where's the Raiders that's right
here Bernie there they are there's no
time for emotion stay there in the name
of jurgen i smite thee hey Iron Man
where's the Raider oh my gosh are you
okay down there
careful not to fall here let me give you
a hand there they are that's right I put
a fence around to stop Raiders imbeciles
cowards hey don't shoot Bernie Bernie
sensitive that's what I thought there's
one more remaining one more remaining
could they have spawned like down here
what here dummy you shoot if you dare
any less in the last word coward
for yoga oh god it continues
eat up Bernie the battle continues oh
these are strong careful yeah oh you're
a bum full of dummy dumb aren't you ball
of dummied up your elbow derby dumb hey
don't shoot Bernie Bernie's innocent
Bernie three's 360 Bernie knows so it's
apparently 2015 why won't you die he's
taken hostage you're doing great Bernie
proud of you these Raiders stand no
chances
oh look they're rich where are they
attacking front oh gosh they have the
giant horse we will kill it with bow oh
gosh run bad egg why you will never be
young again ah run [ __ ] yes we got your
little Jurgen Baker again is that a
Raider it is come at me coward I got to
say this is a lot easier than last time
Bernie we're too strong
hey thanks for doing nothing by the way
oh oh run Bernie
ah I can't do it anymore you will pay
for this whoa whoa what is he doing
string oh gosh oh my gosh she fell down
she says are you kidding me now out I'm
out of arrows
why can I just pull the one out of my
body yes Oh God don't push me down I'm
scared I'm so scared get the total
[Music]
this is the worst day of my life you
cannot get any worse than this for
Jurgen won Jurgen - Bernie both cow and
water sheep oh I only had one come back
coward
add the power of baby in my hands and
thus the battle is won but we lost
Bernie but for what cost
we lost Bernie I can't celebrate I can't
celebrate without my main man we're
gonna have so many epic adventures
together me and Bernie now I can trade
cheaper with the with the villagers but
does it even matter you're telling me
this guy's charging 26 as discount for a
bell when I can just steal the village
Bell high IQ a bird Bernie didn't make
it back the pay
I mean absolute agony it shouldn't have
been like this and so you're again I
mean spend on those we say goodbye to
another hero
it's made of dirt well he was poor okay
it was poor this is what we hear this is
what Bernie would have wanted I knew him
since I was born
okay I knew him better than anyone he
bobbed art it's really getting full up
in here
[Music]
clearly I don't deserve a horse clearly
I don't even deserve a donkey there's
only one option left to be my fellow
rider in the night you're my companion
spend not Rider it's different I know
there's someone here come on we're easy
it's gotta be at least one here he is at
last our last rider in the night that's
right what's your name how do I ride you
I know I can right hey what's your
problem got to feed him first
did you like they let me ride you oh oh
yeah oh yeah this is what I'm talking
about
this is it that I've been looking for
your name is peepee poo-poo
that's right Sven peepee poo-poo we're
gonna beat the ender dragon together and
we're gonna finish the legacy of Legends
peepee poo-poo is gonna live forever
peepee poo-poo we'll never die peepee
poo-poo it's my hero you're my hero
peepee poo-poo that's right who's my
peepee poop would I see you you're
mighty people now oh my god peepee
poo-poo how do you even do that
peepee poo-poo fine you know what I
understand you don't want to disrespect
mr. peepee poo-poo now you go back in BB
bubbles stop
how are you so good at athletics all
right until we build a proper place for
you you can stay with us you can stay
with us spend spend one at a time please
you can't use too fat you can't get it
mic off
I actually have extra funds eep-eep
eep-eep oof ooh there's invaders in our
house while we kill them peepee poo-poo
let's get a BB boo boo boo boo we did it
people before we destroy the invaders
aah
right this way people right this way
stay there span it's too dangerous
more invaders you did it pee pee poop
what we did it we destroy the invaders
that is it me or is peepee poo-poo
faster damn people we fascist Frick wait
so apparently I can make people poo poo
faster by holding the carrot on the
stick
oh my god I'm boosting him faster peepee
poo-poo faster
I don't need your against I have peepee
poo-poo
okay here's fake peepee poo-poo fake
peepee poo-poo okay here's what we're
gonna do I lost too many people I lost
too many loved ones me and a peepee
poo-poo are just gonna ride in a
straight line and no matter what we're
not gonna stop okay we're going on a
pilgrimage no matter what we're not
gonna stop people poo Quinn pewdiepie
forever faster people should all your
against be forgot and never brought too
like peepee poo-poo and gherkins might
peepee poo-poo is alright
calling me PP poopers well write forever
in the name of Jurgen our pilgrimage can
never be stopped
we will amass an army an army of people
poppers that will never be stopped join
us in the name of Jurgen only pigs only
peepee poo-poo coward this is like that
episode of Forrest Gump oh look it's
Bernie's girlfriend hello Bernie sorry
sorry about your boyfriend join us
join us join us fellow peepee poo-poo
listen people deal with grief in
different ways this is how I choose my
battle oh hold hold
what is password faking what this
password wrong password Oh what this
password wrong password assemble VP boo
boo all without password permission
has to be destroyed the password is your
against Merrigan mergenberg and target
player again okay remember it and don't
tell anyone
password you're correct follow us
together we are strong together we are
unstoppable
oh god TV bloopers run baby people whose
ahh
be people never dies peepee poo-poo too
strong
infinite health baby purple for your
yearn for yogurts will good retreat to
Ikea tower when the curtain comes we
will be ready to strike and we are not
afraid
together we are strong I need someone to
DJ for me sell hold up and why it's so
hard for me to find DJ's all right
you're coming you're coming back home
with me buddy I'll gosh the carpet huh
what is happening now he's not the time
oh go go before she sees this how is he
not going through oh my gosh that I
actually okay here we go
you're our new water cow which means you
have to DJ for us I need to lighten the
mood a little bit
yeah that looks good what do I keep the
CD I think this plays roomy brofist no
he doesn't think on first friend he
didn't go through the portal in II spend
you absolute mad lad get up I'm tryna in
the episode go back now then you need to
go back you don't belong in this realm
you're too pure for this world please
like honest man okay gamers
spen kinase have been a hard episode
it's been a tough one
we met some new look friends and then we
lost some of your friends been legends
true legends always lives on as long as
we remember them in our hearts thanks
for watching another episode smash like
and subscribe and get some mature
convert see you guys tomorrow
hi what you never played super simulator
you know it's fun right I'm not supposed
to give my opinion but give it a try and
then you can tell me if it's good or not
convinced yet okay I'll cut you a deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]