eat the toilet paper so it wipes on the
way and good evening everyone my name is
Peter and I don't mean to brag but I
have a very large brain just like the
person who wrote this god-awful reddit
post so today we're gonna explore more
people with big brains and perhaps you
might find that you are big brain as
well I love this one you don't have a
skeleton inside you you're a brain you
are inside a skeleton you're piloting a
bone mech that is using meat armor I
never felt more powerful I mean
technically you're not wrong big brain
very large brain I bet this guy can whip
out a cobblestone generator in half a
second my god so we're all an anime
Mecca that's so cool
to be honest it's not premarital sex if
you never get married baby what
I've been lied to a new scientific study
claims that fertility is hereditary if
your parents didn't have any children
chances are you won't either
it took me a second but big brain that's
I understand this isn't minecraft it's
funny how we we tend to mimic our
parents behavior what you okay I got one
for you guys here's one for you big
brains what smells better than it tastes
a nose I get it
I was like what is a nose smell like oh
you can't spell advertisement without
semen between the tits nine-year-olds
write that down things I wish I didn't
know okay this is not big brain get out
of my sight so I met a cute guy at the
bar last night dance with him says he
doesn't have a girlfriend we exchanged
snapchat look him up on Facebook and he
doesn't have a girlfriend
he has a wife the gray
everyone knows the smartest people in
the world
Socrates Stephen Hawking's Einstein they
all had very large heads Einstein's
brain weighed only which is less than
average adult male Einstein had small
brain small brain here's one for you
youtube lovers what's the best way to
download a YouTube video screenshot each
second and play it on PowerPoint small
brain
hey if the public bathroom door is
locked
don't forget to try and repeatedly open
it and give the person using it and
paralyze be expected
it's like when you're waiting for the
elevator and the the button is clearly
lit up but someone comes in anyway and
decides to click it for you
the door is locked stop trying out but
it I'm having a ship cut in your tennis
balls in half allows you to store two
more balls in each camp thus saving
space small brain very small my brain is
so tiny this is another typical problem
with capitalist America why can't they
just they can clearly fit more tennis
ball but they chose not to disgusting
people will stop showing you pictures of
their kids if you whisper are freaky
under your breath when you look at their
focus ah
wow what a fantastic tip that had that
is so helpful yeah I like that one only
a fool would buy IKEA furniture instead
just download the instructions and keep
emailing their service department to say
that I'm missing a piece until they ship
me all the pieces over a six month
period
Swedish break this is an old hack
everyone in Sweden does this come on
don't waste my time being vegan has been
so freaking easy
I literally just stare at the Sun and
I'm full thanks photosynthesis I mean I
never tried it so maybe it works
ah if you are behind someone at an ATM
late at night let them know that you're
not a threat by giving them a gentle
kiss on their neck see this is the kind
of stuff that I wish people taught me
when I was growing up it takes 45
muscles to frown but only 10 muscles to
smile frown all day lose weight get
ripped gains
[Music]
damn Brian you've been working now yeah
right now I actually feel it damn I will
actually get a big break my forehead
will be massive
the games apply garlic to freshly open
cut or burn to immediately intensify the
pain thank you this is so helpful oh god
I've been barely injured garlic please
what does that help okay here you go
ahh I keep a fruit sticker on top of my
head so that if cannibals ever eat me
he'll have to peel the sticker off first
giving me time to escape how to learn
anything ten times faster I speed at the
video times 1.5 so that I can learn 15
times faster damn oh I'm sorry
you read books I listen to audio books
at ten times the speed oh I'm sorry you
listen ten times the speed I listened at
five RT books at the same time in twenty
times the speed it's quick it's easy and
it's free pouring river water into your
socks why would I do that
LMI it's quick it's easy it's free you
[Music]
can apply that to anything really buying
thirty five words it's quick it's easy
it's you got the point if you ever feel
alone watch a horror movie late at night
with the lights up you won't feel so
alone anymore
thanks Satan you're the best when a baby
on board sticker is a little faded and
beat up you know the kid is at least a
year or two old now and the car is safe
to ram I think I remember that one
I think I keep that one in the memory
bank thank you very much poke your
finger in someone's mouth while they are
yawning to establish dominance big brain
weight might sell was does it to me I've
seen this one I got a go pregnant in
high school so I told my parents
getting bullied and removed modern from
require modern solutions that is awful
by the way just so we adjust so quickly
that is not big brain that is despicable
brain same thing actually firing tip
profiling tips knees on your knuckles
before a fight in order to inflict
poison damage damn hell big brain very
big very large brain oh oh here's a good
one if you touch your pee-pee while you
watch you can pretend like you were
having oh oh that took me a long time
okay hey oh my god taking a little
weight off your check luggage that is
actually big brain I like that we can't
do that in I think European airports
they keep them like dang in how to get
over your fear of the dark as soon as
you turn the lights off starts touching
peepee poo-poo 'i know monster was to
see that while doing it
stare at the corner and whisper tenderly
this is for you
I always thought about like in a horror
movie if someone just does something
really crazy to throw the monster off
but I think this one takes surprise
that's extremely large brain not even I
would think of that mr. president Jesus
well that explains it if you count their
wine snug confuse them by using this
move oh my god
life hack pause and say you can show
yourself now every time you're about to
leave an apparently empty room someday
there might actually be someone there
and they will be really impressed I've
been doing this for 29 years so far
nothing happened very large brain now if
you have the biggest brain of them all
you will be checking out represent calm
/pd primer it is epically big brain we
don't have any big brain merge stuff
Spanish cool thanks for watching gamers
smash like if you enjoy
subscribe and remember to just take like
life love big brain my friend is so big
I don't know how to speak how do I make
outro place what you never played super
simulator you know it's fun right I'm
not supposed to give my opinion but give
it a try and then you can tell me if
it's good or not not convinced yet okay
I'll cut you a deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]
Swedish prey