today we're doing something different
today we're talking about someone in a
positive light yay first time on this
channel Keanu Reeves everyone Internet's
new favorite character everyone's
favorite badass good guy I know I know
it's I've done a lot of videos but I've
been digging a little deeper into Keanu
Reeves and it's some pretty fascinating
fun stuff that we can go through
together let's go I'm sure you've
already seen the abundance of memes that
happened during the past couple days
Keano has taken over the internet but
what makes kion R so likable why does
everyone love this guy number one Yano
always knows what to say in any
situation Keanu will have the perfect
answer what is your secret for always
staying down-to-earth
well I mean gravity I like how he laughs
at his own joke - yeah what do you think
happens when we die Keanu Reeves I know
that the ones who love us will miss us
[Applause]
John wick chapter so good so how does he
get this wisdom well of course
Keanu Reeves number two reason why so
likable he is immortal everyone knows
this it's as a nun indisputable fact at
this point look at this portion this is
early 1500s portrait of a man the gang
signs a gang Steinbeck a lot of weird
finger things you tell us kyon oh it's
late there Lilly you you have a likeness
in the eyes yeah no the mustache and the
beard and the cheekbone and everything
yeah we have the same forehead ish I I
think there's a website called Keanu
Reeves is immortal calm there des this
canneries is immortal calm here it is he
doesn't age here's to prove the website
has been updated 2077 still has an age
even here how old is he is over 50 and
the paparazzi referred to him as young
man that's right young man I know you
turned 50 last month an unhappy birthday
but it's hard to believe looking at you
madam maybe I'm getting older or you're
just very very youthful but you I would
never he does Nate number 3 Keano has a
very sad paced
sad Keanu was a meme that appeared a few
years ago before meme review was a thing
what there were memes before meme review
what the Freak this was in the era of
memes where people just found a picture
they thought was funny and everyone just
photoshopped it that was really it I
look how many counters look how sad he
is next to sad panda legends say that
Keanu is still sitting and still sad
sipping that JPL when I was digging on
the web about you I came across this
about you
this phenomenon the sad Keanu oh gosh it
was a couple years ago yeah oh man where
people picking fights with you sitting
on a bench eating a sandwich looking a
little bit sad and it became like this
crazy thing on the internet what do you
think about sort of media attention yeah
I don't know I didn't think of that as
media attention he was funny people
worried about your welfare um no I think
that's lovely
but oh the I think it was people started
to do funny things with that sad Keanu
obviously side account it was a meme or
whatever but it doesn't work in a way
because he ah no does have a sad past
there's his clip on Facebook that adds a
hundred million views talking about
Keano sad past
[Music]
you
so apparently Keanu was born in Lebanon
okay how many people watch me from
Lebanon and his father is half Hawaiian
and his name Keano means cool breeze on
a mountain I don't know if that's true
but that's what he says
Keanu is such an exotic name but that is
your real name
yes sir that is my name yes is it from
Hawaii yes it's a Hawaiian name and it
means cool breeze over the mountains is
there anything about this guy that isn't
cool
god damn it Sookie oh no leads clearly
suffered through a lot it's almost like
people fetishize his past in a way like
oh he's been through so much and a lot
of it is kind of exaggerated as well but
I think what's important is that yes
he's gone through a lot but he hasn't
let that define him or destroy him and
that's what him is impressive about it
number four am i counting correctly his
lung okay I looked into his interviews
and I found this clip and it's so
bizarre but Sandra Bullock she so that
was her first big break with you yeah
and I asked her because everybody had a
crush on you
if she had a crush on you then and this
is what she said I think how sweet Keanu
Reeves was and how it was really it was
hard for me to like really be serious
like he would look at me and I'd be like
never dated really there was just
something about me
not sure I think it's true no he never
you never intimidated not at all
yeah there's nothing to intimidate I'm
not that yes you are
but we're but I think we're probably
friends for that long because we didn't
yeah right is that how you do it that's
how I maybe that's why he didn't want to
be with you
and it is reacting to that click look
how happy is obviously didn't know I had
a crush on her oh I can't believe you
both had crushes on each other and you
you were so scared okay well I know I
mean you ever had a romance with
somebody that you did a movie with um
sounds like yes I mean whether it's
whether it's before or after I mean if
you wait until it's over
sure yeah but that's so that so that
chemistry was real because he all really
did both have feelings like that yeah it
was super sentai dog yeah yeah I mean
she's so what's such a wonderful person
no look at this cheap Trick's end and
he's like oh no
ICI accident I don't want to look
goddamn you Alan don't do my man piata
like this no I believe she's in a
relationship now you the window closed
you you you had a chance you rest
assured Sandra Bullock husband is
sweating profusely right now John wick
is coming for you
and then I looked into my fish over this
the interview of him talking about
Sandra well they shot this film and it's
so sweet she has a nice nice such a
wonderful energy about her and her in
life and she's just wherever she goes
and she really gives and wants things to
be springtime Jordan company
oh and she's a really great actress too
no she is no but she is no again I mean
that the thing that's cool about this
film I mean it's cast really very well
and the actors are really good and you
know she's she's brought a very you know
she's been fighting the the this the
direction of just being like you know
they complete damsel in distress okay
how do you do not make a move on her
Keanu Jesus Christ my god well all of
this aside pass and the non happening
romance this is what led Keano into just
becoming social class when Kioto acts as
John wick he is John wick okay in every
single film he is John wick the matrix
training for John wick that love story
movie he's still John wick okay he just
gotta he's clearly such a badass and
have such intense respect for his craft
got a reefs really well
that's funny you can tell Keanu really
cares about giving you an experience
that is special in the film and actually
putting the work and effort into making
that happen he does all the action
himself or at least as much as he can I
love movies gosh I love movies I love
watching them and I love making them and
this brings up to the number 5 which is
Keanu and money there's this question
movies have made so much money three and
a half billion dollars entertain
entertain right yes that's right that's
right
everyone is so obsessed with money
apparently it was reported that he
donated 80 million of his 114 million
earnings from the Matrix sequels I
looked around it doesn't seem like it's
100% true but he definitely is a very
giving person he has donated a lot a lot
of money and he has also said himself
that money doesn't mean anything to me I
made a lot of money but I want to enjoy
life and not stress myself building my
bank account I give a lots of way and
live simply mostly out of a suitcase in
hotels we all know that good health is
much more important and I think that is
an important distinction of how you look
at the world and how you look at money
and I and I really really respect that
then coming to number five the point
number five is counter Rives and public
when he did the matrix it became such a
smash hit success that people were
obsessed with this film inevitably Keanu
Reeves who is the main star of the film
I found this quote in an interview where
he talks about the matrix becoming a
cult hit and he says he was asked about
the film and it was he surprised that it
became big and he says yes somewhat I
want to make something clear I am NOT
Jesus I am also no prophet or lone
fighter that will save the world
I find it frightening how many people
believe that being acquainted with me
would solve their personal problems
that's simply not so but I'm
participating in the next two Matrix
films with enthusiasm I don't know if
he's joking or not or if this is how his
life was actually changed that people
looked at up to him as some Messiah I
could be reading into this wrong but it
is interesting with the kion Owen and
and the public you know there was his
viral clip of him being in the subway
by the way you're not slick when you're
sitting there with your camera like this
is this is how you look like by the way
he clearly just want to live his life
like everyone else and I I can't relate
to that in a lot of ways but when you're
that famous this is inevitable that
paparazzi and living in LA you get
recognized
look how hidden he is we will still find
him look how many cameras you know that
moment when your bike doesn't start it's
a bit frustrating imagine being that
situation with a dozen cameras pointing
at you
and some guy across the street choked it
you need to choke them but yeah it's
like okay got it
god what an awful situation like if you
don't get the bike running what do you
do you're just gonna be stuck there with
all the cameras
there's my nightmare oh yeah
who was that that was John wick he's
also very nice with fans which I do
appreciate taking selfies
please you're one of my favorite doubt
[Music]
oh you might imagine you're flying
across the country you're tired you just
want to go home and then you may with
which leads me to the final point
stop asking Keanu Reeves for pictures
okay
I'm sure and listen I want to speak for
him I'm sure he doesn't mind but I feel
like I'm speaking through Keanu he just
want to live normally and not be stopped
every moment okay this is what Keanu
Reeves woods okay anyhow after this
video went viral where he says you're
breathtaking the guy that yelled you're
breathtaking from the audience was
offered the game to get it early and he
said no thank you
I would rather if you donate to charity
instead so in the spirit of Keanu Reeves
and making this video I wanted to donate
all the profit that this video makes to
the leukemia Research Foundation it's
working on her donated a lot of money
because his sister went through leukemia
she survived it took my granddad and I
thought that could be a nice ending to
it and have a nice Keano effect of doing
something good I know everyone once
ochio Reeves he should be how should me
review or whatever that's not why I made
this video I'm genuinely just fascinated
by the guy so it doesn't matter okay
that's it bye what you never played
tuber simulator you know it's fun right
I'm not supposed to give my opinion but
give it a try and then you can tell me
if it's good or not convinced yet okay
I'll cut you a deal the game is
available for free and that's a great
price
[Music]