[Music]
don't worry it will grow back
so i've edited the hair background
g-fuel is celebrating me coming back
with 30 discount my god have i missed g
fuel they don't have it in japan and i
forgot to ship it
so i ran out after the first week not
good my god have i missed it
get the pewdiepie flavor 30 up you're
welcome gamers that's a great price
but you have to enter code pewdiepie
meme review
[Music]
i'm not going to sit here and lie to you
guys the memes this week
are absolutely garbage okay
just so we're clear just so the
expectations are set
but i do think it's important that we go
through what the memes are
as part of culture as part of
understanding the world
our first meme okay actually this is a
good meme
this is from nepesta who is a
speedrunner
why he's been running this
square square game what is this game
called it's called an impossible game
isn't it
and he had this reaction where is it
me me beating tuber simulator
jesus christ
[Applause]
absolute degenerate behavior yes i know
but the good part about this is became a
meme
i'm joking by the way these are not my
opinion anything i say
not my opinion just so we're clear so
people started making their own edits
out of this
this one is good
i like this one because i actually saw
some people thinking that was his
reaction to playing the practice round
there's more there's so many great ones
here's the black emoji speedrun oh man
i mean that's pretty fast not gonna lie
damn come on boy that's impressive dude
oh come on come on come on
me that's literally me when i do the
black emoji speed run all right here we
go guys
all right all that all of them all of
them god there's so many
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is this is on par with that
what is that one i swear i saw it
somewhere oh here it is
yes the two titans of reactions to video
game
imagine screaming at a video game
another legendary action to the bank
gamers uh there's also this one
uh pp island speedrun world record
that's pretty good
all right here we go come on come on
castle bar come on
come on yeah yeah yeah yeah where's the
castle bar
there it is
[Applause]
well done well done 12 seconds that's a
new record
when you ask the pretty girl for nudes
and she sent them
that's such a bad meme imagine spending
135 000 attempts
135 000 and becoming a meme instead
this is a friend of nepesta who said
that he had 135 000 attempts
117 verification streams
an hour long so over 300 hours spent
in the level alone now that's gamer
dedication
who said video games doesn't call
violence
so for that we respect you in the past
good job you did it
well done
you did it
approval i would say what do you think
out of five that's what it gets
[Music]
all right tell me honestly what you
prefer regular music
okay regular music or penis music
answer right now in the comments you got
five seconds if you never heard of penis
music before
just let your ears are going to melt but
i will play it for you anyway so just
be aware that i did warn you okay don't
say pewdiepie didn't warn me that my
ears melted because of peepee music
sorry god damn it i hate this meme
but damn it's good
[Music]
question mark god damn whenever i hear
pp music
my peepee just goes
[Music]
that's what my peepee says so so this is
an actual song rubber band by jackal
quinston
wait uh okay let's move on this is a
meme
this is an actual meme i mean if patrick
bateman likes penis music
then if you don't like it you have the
wrong opinion basically
when the pp music comes on
it's like that moment where you're not
the club and you're like i can't vibe to
this
it's all this commercial garbage every
single time on
on the radio adele ed sheeran
lady gaga when will they play the peepee
music
and you know all these cringe-ass kids
who say they like death grips
thinking that they're so quirky and
unique as if they aren't already
mainstream
they don't listen to pee-pee music like
i do all right they don't vibe to the
penis music they might say that they
like it
but they don't actually understand the
new ones
the texture the sound oh i'm sorry your
ears already melted you can't even hear
me right now
pp music not everyone can handle it not
everyone can handle it not gonna lie
but my pee pee go hey que pasa hey
holmes
blaming some of that bp arms shut up
shut up son i say son turn that penis
music up if you're republican you listen
to me
or is that republi i don't know the
flags penis music
all right okay all right it's a whole
genre basically
i don't buy you but this makes me want
to suck i'm not gonna lie i'm not gonna
say or lie to you
disappointment you've allowed yourself
to be defined by a single genre
penis music you see what i mean you get
judged for liking
something that holy sh
my g fuel matches penis music do you see
this
are we gonna talk about this does that
mean i'm drinking penis music
in this music yes
all right okay grande uploaded this
thank you grande thank you so much
now you're you ruined the grande i'm
sorry you get this
i'm just kidding god damn it oh my god
it does not get less annoying geez
[Music]
penis music has always been there it's
one of those genres
but you always wonder like why have i
been listening to ed sheeran all this
time
all right just a side note all right
lady gaga just uploaded this
in song and it's like why would you
listen to this if you can listen to
peepee music
why would you listen to this garbage
this commercial garbage about
love and how you want it wasn't she in
that movie
where they literally made fun of this
huh wasn't that the point of that
film
whether the one with bradley cooper were
there like when she becomes this
commercial artist that just sells out
and there's whatever is poppy or
whatever
i get it it's catchy it's i like it i
vibe to it i'm not gonna sit there and
lie
but like what is this can we stop it
just stop it all right all i want is pp
music
all i want to do one day in society i
will turn on radio and i will hear pp
music and nothing else that's all i want
or drain gang that's okay too
male 1 genitalia
oh that's funny nice one cyrillic
has he done one nope disappointed
all right all right that's enough penis
music thank you penis music gets a
uh six i don't know six out of penis six
penis
so last week we reviewed bernie sanders
memes great am i right
next we have a new bernie sanders meme
because someone took a photo
of bernie sanders when he was not aware
and it says
it's this guy i don't know if he's the
one that took the photo chris carr
first class flight and first aboard
socialism has been good
to bernie sanders who is this in right
that took a photo bernie
i'm not a bernie supporter necessarily i
don't even know what he wants
this is a non-political show but why
would you take a photo with someone just
to write them out let the man fly
in first class he looks like he's at
least 200 years old
he looks older than the world's oldest
guy did you guys see that recently
this is turning into pew news this blew
my mind so this guy
took the price right and 112. and then
recently
four days ago this guy took the record
he doesn't even look old
jewish duty i'm telling you and
we children were brought down from the
attic
and put under the dining room table look
at him
he looks less old than bernie sanders
does how is that possible
you chris carr all right let the man fly
first class
second of all you notice how he's
coughing on a flight is that a little
suspicious
i think it's a little suspicious now i'm
not going to say what i think it is
because the video will go
clearly but i think we all know what's
going to happen to bernie sanders yeah i
wonder what kind of zombie bernie
sanders would turn into
me hitting my feet from the
now a lot of people added theories okay
what's he listening to
space mountain by mikhail
me trying to hit my jewel secretly nah
of course he's listening to
three-way the golden rule obviously he's
listening lasagna
come on we all know it all right bernie
meme gets the two i don't know i just
wanted to bring it up
i think it's important next meme we got
two more alright gamers
two more dorito this one is important
this one is important okay so here we
have in spanish
the suffix ito means little like poquito
right all right capicho que pasa et oms
understand the word dorito
means something like little doro
implying the existence here
the existence of a bigger and legendary
snack called
doro a huge doro dokunideska
why would they call it that if there
wasn't one it makes sense right
these are the things we really need to
focus on in society these are the things
that truly
truly matter danny
where does it end where is the giant el
devo
despacito that means there's a giant
despot
oh my god all right like life's meme i'm
not gonna rate that because that's
garbage
here's an important question where will
you be during the random ship event
it's coming it's coming area 51 already
happened
world war iii already happened the virus
thing that i can't mention the name of
already happened but what truly will
take us all out
the random chimpanzee we have here a
graph of places with highest chance of
random
chimp event as you can see it's not
looking good you can't hide anywhere
people doubted the earth and said that
we'll never have a random chimpy went
well you'll just wait and watch they are
disguised among us waiting to rise up
the random chimp event is near this is
so random cringe humor by the way
hey are you sleeping yes now shut up
what if you're not prepared for the rent
what if
that's it that's it what if enjoy some
fierce
random chimp event that's all i drink
every day
actually i got some in here i feel it oh
god oh god
listen up kid the random chimpanzee
he was trying to warn us he was trying
to tell us of the god damn it
smash like on this video if you are
prepared for a random ship event
check out the merch support channel g
fuel drink it if you like drinking
and i see you gamers tomorrow thank you
and for every comment about my hair a
single hair will grow out so don't worry
just keep commenting about it