James Charles where are you we have to
play minecraft my sister hi sister - mr.
Fisher is back in visit team sister
Pfister its back and we're gonna win
this time I'm taking over the Minecraft
universe you're gonna have to help me
get my very first kill in hunger games
minecraft today okay I feel like what's
just jumping right and then Charlie is
jump in - yeah let's do G we can do
either minecraft Mondays hell or oh geez
it's up to you wait wait I feel like I
have to tell people the pros because the
pros might not know that James Charles
is an epic minecraftgamer you have to
carry me here cuz like I'm terrible okay
because we already played on the
Minecraft Mondays but they didn't in the
first three seconds every time what oh
we should like okay so for those two
guys who know Felix that I played on
this fun tournament called minecraft one
day a few weeks ago together
I ended up winning in the end but it was
a chariot winning we don't have to be ok
so we are going to run where are you
where are you James
okay I see we're directly across you're
gonna see you're gonna run to your left
towards the bar oh I see you okay just
right legs barn
there's no barn oh I see it okay okay
run that way they recognized me they
were looking at me I don't like this
your skin isn't disguise for some reason
I think you didn't put on the sky slowly
damn it
okay just choke a barn somebody hit me
James
oh I'm first sample it doesn't open
James Bible open either weapon where are
you right here I'm so scared where are
you
stop punching me where are you I went to
the barn James oh my god I got a chest
that way I don't have a check you said
go let you said go okay okay I'm by
their weird windmills okay I know where
you are basically in the back of the map
there's a bunch of like teepees all
together and maybe to get to those okay
this is the longest I've ever been alive
yeah it's over jail there's a team here
oh all right P I got a freaking sword I
got a sword don't be scared this guy
just gave me thank you how could they
kill James Charles doc no don't even you
know what are you still in the game
yes I'm still in the game I delegate we
need you disguise you so if we can't
follow you off this bar oh that's why I
didn't see you
yeah you weren't disguise yeah that's
the point James there's no time I don't
know where to go oh okay I'm going for
chest in the middle I don't see no don't
go for tessel them at all
oh my god boys you appear laughs to your
lofty left left left left just walk out
just walk out like get out oh yeah oh
god this guy oh I see I see it I'm right
behind you great okay this is the game
James you have a weapon you have two
weapon okay kill him yeah don't worry
I'll tank them there's a chest up here
Freck I died this is so sad
[Music]
James Charles fan X do you find are you
the baby I am the baby ill okay so in
this map okay see over this way right
here see how there's not like white hut
I seen it behind there's a lot of baby
shows so okay so it's not white building
right there um there's a chest in this
building over here I know for sure
okay this weapon heck yeah Oh sword run
James Charles I'm running oh he's
chasing us
of course he is that's other don't worry
James Charles I'll freak him up so I
have to punch the Timothy oh whoa that
was a pro-gamer move Oh get him James
okay I'm a little Aeon two hearts
get up James are you I'm right behind
you Felix I'm gonna blow into
smithereens
we're so bad okay
that's we're going Felix this way don't
turn around turn around I'm right here
okay we're going in this way towards -
hi it's behind the this hill okay I'm
nearby where we're going do I go to the
Red Barn or not I guess what I bar
behind that cactus that's like straight
back behind you there's a chest if you
want to run right to it and grab the
fake guys like them but I'm ready to
break oh I see the fake heck that yeah
there's a man lad just go like that like
back towards the edge of the mouth are
you by the pumpkins and stuff yeah yes
Rick how do you know where everything is
I'm gonna give you this helmet wait come
here
spit it out
now we're gonna win a melon and a helmet
hey let's cross the river oh we could
get the double chops - okay
it's not you do the turning toward teen
oh no Tom okay you feel like okay
there's somebody over here where are you
okay on the other billing I'm in the
other billing
get him James sister face-down knows I'm
right in front of you I got this
connected wait no what I don't know
the minecraft gods are not happy okay
all right where are you okay behind
right now
so we're okay I see it where all the
chests in this stupid gate I found one
of our chests yo dude I got I got TNT in
a chair its gaming time okay hey behind
you behind you James Charles coming
James yeah wait you die I've been I
haven't be honest I haven't been trying
my hardest damn girl was a you know I am
down [ __ ] damn [ __ ] sorry get a chest
as fast as you possibly can yeah I got a
bow but no arrows this is total crap all
right I don't know the chest come on
right here
damn [ __ ] is gonna die die
oh you're gonna get game Don
you're gonna get game Don you're gonna
get game done they're so fast how with a
gamer stop pushing me oh excuse me I
keep forgetting that I'm supposed to
spam this run how's that run how's them
go off the hill they're dead okay
[Music]
kidding me I have an axe and they don't
die what is this game Phyllis
okay so literally we're gonna go this
way there's a James
when you say this way I have no idea
what you're talking about
hey okay so this is me right here funny
you okay
so we're going the same exact way we did
last time right okay there's a chest
behind there and then we go learnt that
hail to the left towards the bottom yeah
and then uh huh right when you get like
over this little Hill right here huh
yeah the left of this mountain whereas
the oh dude I'm right by the cactus
it's gamer on oh god I didn't go for the
Chesapeake on until they just hold it
okay yeah go go go I get the chance is
my chest old dude I got leather pants
James chance this out of the state of
loss right here I'm right here behind
you go through that tower or that like
oh man okay I have a sword good yes
commanders gonna go put the same thing
keep going yup keep going no q4e this is
me but I always lose you Craig he
already has boots prepared to die mother
wait we need to get you weapon first I'm
a weapon for your feelings oh okay oh I
died no what do I die so fast
get him James okay I flogging oh my god
oh you did it
okay are you spectating me yeah I guess
I'll look like that
no you don't have to it's fine James
Charles just said I suck at minecraft
it's the worst day of my life fun
playing with me we get to play for two
seconds I thought maybe like we were bad
because minecraft Mondays James leave
the game fine
are you doing jumping yes I'm jumping
yes okay so you go directly to your left
cuz the white thing is right there the
thing is right there okay I gotta live
in okay where do I go Jean to that to
that building that I've said about last
time I have absolutely no memory James
Charles okay I found James Lee this is
the good building get the chest I don't
have a freaking weapon okay I have an
arrow I do okay stay here
okay okay save right here stay right
here stay in here okay so I hope hence
okay all right
here take this oh wait take this you
have weapon
quickly get him Kjetil go let him go let
go there's a guy right here oh and it
will say James Charles panic out you
kill them get stone
you stole King James Charles okay let's
go let's go
no no no I'm not brushing over this hey
we better test please brick your fan
account James Carr James Charles is fan
that's a video title we need to get more
items over here there's somebody over
here you go as and left leg all right
wow he's good hold on he's good he's
terrible he's terrible get him jack what
what snacks been disrespectful
disrespecting respectful I almost got to
kill those so I think this is good for
improving my own fan ecology all right
we need to find more of your fans to
kill them games no go to your left your
left your left there's no chests it's
rigged you dead yes Josh Josh I'm sorry
it had to be done wow dude there's a
chest here how
oh I get it John Oh guys gonna get that
shoot okay feel like we're gonna brag
okay I'll throw snowballs on there oh
he's really bad
oh just kidding wrong advice you're bad
you're bad [ __ ] you bad ah thanks Jegs
help help help James Jones where are you
oh this I just like come on what ah
James did you fall to the trap dibs
Josef me Felix
Jake so help me please today I have a
sword this orange spot I have a sword
are you falling into the trap no that's
a new mistake okay that was good that
was a good game I gotta kill it
I gotta kill him I would kill as many
fan of cancers I goddamn please Nana
skincare hardcore I know Ellen talk okay
right here keep going keep going
okay no I'm right here in front of you
to your loft chill out chill out chill
aft hey I have a lot done for you are
you yes are you I went right behind I
gotta kill okay where are you yes I'm
hiding until I find you I mean this big
big big big big baby baby big very big
large building with no freaking loot in
it um go back home to spawn okay I'll oh
okay I got a stick and sugar and Robbie
I think we got okay I don't think so I
don't think so tapes back up back up
James
oh my god oh god oh god oh god oh you
got him yeah
James Charles that's good this is what
I'm talking about my feeling Kyle just
as good a welcome for us I'm I'm on I'm
on three l3 hull yeah one melon will dip
one melon would be okay
I have its acts the same thing here just
take the sword inside cuz it's a little
better that's all things Charles we are
almost top ten okay this is true let's
go down we are gonna win this
wow I love this I'll rip your works here
are items so somebody was here oh
there's something right there right
there around shoot oh no he just ender
pearl dawai avenge me he's gonna end up
rolling guys come on James
yes Daddy
James Joyce I keep playing our units
party here she's like yeah you're gonna
keep playing oh wing Oh way he
trash-talk the city
you suck kid almost kill you 10 adult K
bye
he will find out they got killed by
James Charles on and it was recorded on
YouTube got'em your top 10 James you're
already amazing you're doing so good so
good freakin up the zou toys more like
though no toes get the MTA
that was close he's literally leaving
channel anyone anyone here happy
he's eating cake James I don't have any
arrows he splits by the way be careful
nice you can't play James Charles like
that no one plays James Charles like
that did an epic let's go no judo more
like no Snoodle yeah they're teaming
wait that's cheating
they ran James they ran their what are
you doing Golden Apple time okay alright
we're pulling out the big guns Oh James
Charles got arrows he hit two times
James Charles running away James Charles
oh he knew he went in the water he
freaked up I didn't know one chance and
make my sword stronger that I was I was
just about to say yes
looks like I won this this is it this is
the moment he goes in to v1 we were
he's on fire is on fire oh we missed Oh
a mace keep getting m1 is right behind
you and the others on your right No
but you're still alive oh I think night
stop teaming you have virginity how did
they know James Oh help us out the other
guy wait where are they
right behind yo put the where's the
other guy I don't know shoot okay
oh there's three people in this area
[Music]
James Charles No Oh ROM 0 K is king yeah
get up James James run he's gonna hang
on
he's got out strafe strafe oh god he's
far away that was pro gamer
[Music]
you make the night with soldiers with
Stefan match Oh God
focus you can do this
oh he's fat by the TNT oh he's low his
love James Charles James Charles James
Charles James
[Music]
James Charles is about to sacrifice one
of his most loyal sisters we have
gathered here today thank you for your
sister service this is so dark you're
gonna burn sister sisters still alive
wait I'll push her it I'll bury you it's
a sign from God what a trooper that's a
true sister win this one James let's
just communicate let's do this easy win
come on okay all right I know we have
one this actually might be an easy win
all right let's get it I'm right here
doing range oh sorry
[Music]
I got it I got it yes the Festa this is
for sister what are we doing why oh I
see all right now I couldn't do that I
couldn't I could have just killed James
Charles I'm not fighting you I'm never
never kill a gamer
wait wait wait for real all right James
Joss I'm so I'm so glad we finally won
again
dave says they're paster guys check out
James Charles link in description he's a
real gamer as you can see I didn't I
didn't catch what you said but yeah rate
this a thumbs up okay