name review last week Elon Musk and
Justin roiland hosted meme review a
legendary episode what do we do now I
don't know we've never gotten this far
how do you follow up an episode like
that you can you just can't accept we
will I have a secret plan in mind for
another bonus just wait
but first it's meme review time let's
freakin do this - like a pure excited
when it's Steve Urban's birthday and
nobody seems to be celebrating this is
very sad but but the pipette out out of
nowhere comes Google and Google knows
what's up commemorating the legacy the
legend Steve urban very nice thank you
google very cool but oh no no oh no no
we can't just let things be positive we
can't just have nice things
Pizza that's right Pizza everyone
decided to take the moral high ground
and as a response to this Google header
PETA posted this Steve Urban was killed
while harassing array the mental
gymnastics of this organization he
dangled his baby while feeding a
crocodile and wrestled wild animals who
were minding their own business you know
who should be minding your own business
PETA I you you shut up today's Google
Doodle sends a dangerous phony message
well I can't even read this this is
giving me brain damage
everyone dislike that no one likes you
PETA
this is why people don't care about
anything you say someone replied Steve
Irvin didn't have a kill rate of 80
percent you do he didn't donate seventy
thousand to a convicted arsonist you did
and he wasn't in bed with eco terrorist
networks again you so take your
self-righteous BS and shove it that's
right Peter now the meme community is
not happy about this the mean community
heat disrespected Steve Irvine on his
birthday everyone like Hitler but even
Hitler care about animals or something
he probably did
next mean PETA when animal abusers set
up dog fights PETA when chrome changes
is logo to honor Steve Irvin how could
they hey you're a fairy you know to
grant your wishes I wish I could talk to
ponies Steve Irvin was a hero
you can come good meme great me there's
one way to properly ridicule and shame
someone it's through memes there's no
other way okay
shame on you PETA Steve Aaron's memory
the whole internet preaching need things
Peter have done to have animals Wow look
nothing when I kill a deer my parents
family of deer Pete that you have to die
now am ill - oh God it's time to go wish
I had a good organization no stupid baby
no one likes you Peter just crawl back
into whatever hellhole you came from
okay no one likes you
no one wants you I'd like that one
kidding clients that have that farts
really badly
good analogy Felix thank me Irvin hasn't
been on a date since losing Steve I have
already had my happily ever after next
beam Elon Musk memes they just kept
coming I swear my whole reddit it's
filled with nothing but Elon Musk memes
at this point I guess he likes dark
humor I guess hey man the video didn't
get demonetized so I assume YouTube is
fine with it a dear lying dead in the
pool exists nobody if not must I love
this picture it's goddamn beautiful
Petey pie with the sub gap it was
literally one and then rose up to 10 K
uh-huh I think it's 100 K now thank you
very much this has to be one of my new
favorite laughing reaction yes so
when you tell a slightly offensive joke
at the dinner table you your brother the
guest the dot hey stop it stop it with
the dolphin jokes Elin
this is not a dolphin you're drowning
the oh god he has air pods of course he
has air pods in he's a billionaire my
god dark sense of humor can be dementia
warning well then I guess we all have
dementia on this channel let's get real
here yeah definitely my favorite Rick
and Morty moaning can't stop laughing
Thank You Justin roiland for hosting me
and review with me so this was a plan
all along I knew it I freaking knew it
teacher why are you laughing me nothing
my brain elem dusk hmm what are you
laughing at nothing
Elon does oh god damn it teacher what
are you laughing at me nothing my brain
in a mask teacher why do you laugh in
there me even the dust - all right Jesus
you know I was kind of disappointed that
Elam didn't like this meme of himself I
was like ah what a shame
you know I used to think these were
actually funny but then I started seeing
them on myself it's not funny okay it
and I'm saying it genuinely teacher what
are you laughing about me nothing Felix
smell bird stop just stop before it's
too late
you don't want to mess with me boy what
are you laughing at huh what are you
laughing at nothing oh yeah whatever
what is this Felix Kjellberg this is
racism at its finest I mean it's the
worst what are you laughing about
nothing my brain Felix
KJ over Jesus Christ so bad the eland
meme gets it there okay the eland dear
memes 10 out of 10 baby but the e1
teacher meme format
[Music]
what are you gonna do about it cry piss
your pants maybe hmm
next meme another pity pie related meme
of course I'm gonna bring this up
evidence shows that vaccines don't cause
autism anti-vaxxer
what the is that events are posts to me
pretty good meme Treaty of Versailles
exists
Nazi Germany what does daddy when your
girl wants you to touch her but she's
too big bombs are regala what good means
these are great memes he's a fantastic
meme no remains when they see a meme
with no caption can I pay my best damn
alright now as a final mean of this
week's meme review we have a meme that's
been sitting lurking in the background
for quite a while and it's kind of
taking on many different shapes and
forms and I don't really know how to
summarize it but I'll try my best to
explain this god-awful atro shitty name
Ricardo Ricardo started off with tick
tock trolls okay here I am basically
trying to watch some some tick tock
videos and then out of nowhere this
fricking guy comes in and I'm like I'm
not gay I don't like this
it's basically the skedaddle skadoodle
your dick is not one it's basically that
level of tear okay first you get annoyed
but then it happens again and and you
just look at him and you're like oh god
him he's smile his eyes he's dams
his bandana his warmth he's existent and
you know I'm not gay but if I had to
pick between the tic-tock girl or
Ricardo I'm gonna have to think really
hard about it at least the eternal
struggle between good and evil
tick tock girl versus Ricardo well
Ricardo is stronger I have to say that
he has more muscles so I think he's got
the win on me
okay that's pretty good hey shut up
I'm on skype with someone sorry
beautiful you were saying oh stop it
Ricardo we are sitting here inventing
and playing little dota shut up guys I'm
talking to the cutest girl ever sorry
babe you were saying ah kpop with guys
no thank you
Ricardo
[Music]
I don't really understand this meme I'm
gonna be honest why have people spent
hours editing this stuff I don't know
like what is this
[Music]
well now we understand where he gets his
power from Ricardo meme gets a zero just
because they need to stop just stop the
Ricardo me please I'm begging you
I think I've proved my point here today
cuz I'm not gay okay I don't like men
now of course to the big surprise it's
going to top LMS and Justin roiland as
bonus me who could it be
3 2 1 game review in case you guys
didn't get the memo today is bring your
kids to work day so I brought mine
alright but before I host meme review
I'd like to do a moment of silence for
all our fallen Bros in the war on T
series first me so here's the thing
cutie pie just gave us a cluster of
means yes spending 7 million dollars on
a dead giving cutie pie 7 million mm I'm
sure they did put this in their way
giving p25 7 million little paying
subscribers Oh giving to you by 7
million dollars yeah well I need a few
years I'm not Logan portal I don't have
that kind of heart cells sevens a little
high I may be like for about 7 maybe
like it for now you have to give me a
subscriber count'
give him his dollar per subscriber
another penny person is subscribed cool
cool alright we'll just continue the
illusion that I'm filthy rich
I guess you're the lucky oh I didn't
make this vid what whoever made this
meme doesn't have to I know how to dream
you come on let's go what mr. Bies now
the top right actually are we allowed to
say that mr. B's spends hundreds of
dollars buying cutie Pie's peers can
give Ben Shapiro to host me review mr.
B's am i joke to you okay just kidding I
never really wanted to host I don't want
to look like the leech like that's why I
only did all this but I get barrage by
tweets every day so uh why are ya one
week she loves me one week she hates me
both weeks should get a diaper seems
like the simple fix
yeah dude that's how big jungus came
along he was just sick a shot in the bed
and so you just tell my god I gotta help
hold it in and you just blew up that's
funny cuz that's like an eight or nine
for me we got it next mr. B's PewDiePie
putting in know everything it's pretty
accurate up until he started
live-streaming it literally it's
something that's like hey do be like
that but seriously it does kind of hurt
when you put a lot of effort into the
board campaign a few pies the next day
or whatever just like I don't care if I
get past I don't really care about being
number one and they just like ah but we
do we care game review I am NOT a racist
but that's how every racist person
starts up everything they say I'm not a
racist
but there's so many things I want to say
I just can't I'm not as savage as
PewDiePie
you know like he would probably say
something slightly racist here t-series
mr. Bies PewDiePie I mean it's true bow
down survive
what yeah he's one of the most
attractive men yeah I
that was a long time ago active woman I
don't know I don't really like names
like this please
my name is terrible and this is why I
mean it is true ruins the entire me you
didn't have to explain it here will crop
it up the good part that's how many yeah
this the meme should just VIN this it is
boom problem solved okay all right I
think we have Tula Super Bowl ad TV but
no key mysteries supported the most by
spending a lot of money for PT pad same
QT five hundred thousand times that
helped me indeed if I receive eight
hundred thousand plus subscribers first
off I don't think I ever tweeted that I
think he did no I never tweeted that
that is a fake tree but anyways let me
clear it up a little bit
basically when I said PewDiePie hundred
thousand times I said I was going to try
to buy PewDiePie yet the game plan was
to sell stuff to PewDiePie shirts and
hoodies like this make a few million
dollars off of it and put that towards
the end that is what I planned on doing
and that is why I said that but after I
uploaded that video we ran into some
complications I learned that there's a
really good chance of Superbowl probably
wouldn't approve the yet like there's
some marijuana company that didn't get
approved even though they offered like
ridiculous amounts of money for the
Superbowl and so then I had a dilemma do
I sell stuff to peopIe shirts telling
everyone I'm gonna take all the money
and put it towards a Superbowl ad and
then you know make a few million dollars
but then the ad gets declined so then
I'm stuck with a few million dollars and
then yeah obviously I give it to charity
but then people would be even more
disappointed I didn't know I just I
didn't know if they would reject or
approve yet so I never went through with
the idea of selling this like really
hard with the promise of buying a Super
Bowl ad so after that we decided to make
these shirts and the blankets and get a
you know seats right behind the
goalposts to promote them because they
said we're gonna do something at the
Superbowl and we didn't want to not
deliver anything just what we written
that yeah so this meme doesn't have
accurate information so it's labeled
inaccurate
does not get it ready next during like
Oh God oh man the pain is so great that
a woman can almost imagine what a man
feels like when he accidentally kills
the dog in Minecraft
Hertz with your minecraft dog falls in
lava I may not be able to relate to a
lot of these memes but this one Timmy
right here do twelve-year-old me woof
yeah I vividly remember my minecraft
eyeballing a lava one time and I just
like got so sad about it to wrap this
meme review up I'd like to plug
something PewDiePie send me a message
say I could plug whatever I want at the
end and I really want to plug grande
because he actually helped us make some
of these billboards he's been a strong
fighter for PewDiePie he's very good for
the meme economy he's really helpful you
know keeping the GDP up you know
quarter-over-quarter
and I'd like it you guys wanted
subscribed him so he could make more
memes so PewDiePie could react to him
alright brothers that's it for me review
i'm your general i'm gonna go back to
fighting t-series appreciate you guys
having me on thank you peter pie
honestly if anyone else was the number
one most subscribed to youtuber they've
probably bring it up a lot or if they
got an argument say be like