hey it's me and she's back if we won
how does it feel spent a long time Sachi
berry dance I thought why don't we
answer some questions it's all the time
people are like Oh what is happening
reminds me is she hiding in your
basement is she having a pug factory
what is she doing how his mind said
doing and what is Ramon said doing well
first of all green your your place to do
yeah I was working and then you were
just saying we're feeling that yes first
question how often does mine say I get
recognized by now we don't leave the
house don't leave the house now what
it's really like in busy days are busy
times but if we do now when it's like a
weekend for example I think maybe a few
times a day but not as much here
usually when someone recognizes me or us
they'll come to me first and then
they're like and they blue lagoon yeah
the person came to me they seemed to
make an effort even to be like Oh Marcia
I love Marcia so much my tastes the best
youtuber keep-away favorite spread to
put on brain I knew that what is mine
nothing and chef Davidi the kid that you
put on the connect you brat and that's
how you need baby Jess ok kids
[Music]
Felix easy way you should do your voice
hearings even our child beautiful same
thing to the ranch to the ranch with the
child
he got your expression right that's 99%
of the time you looking at me like this
have you both learned Japanese yet
nihongo best guy no I just been
listening to like a part it's like a
audio or something but yeah we will
learn we will get on it how are not game
Maya I need seen them in video oh great
they are dream is sitting right there
because I don't worry he's behind that
he's pastime oh yeah it's been a long
time no one's here the time of the
channel - oh here's a good one
doesn't Marcia have legs - two - as in
as well yeah moving on hey they're
saying they're proposing to march in
Japan are you guys planning on getting
married there or in any other countries
you were born we thought we thought
about everywhere on the planet bases I
really like the idea of eloping and
going to Japan but the more I looked
into it it's hard complicated we didn't
know what we were getting into it's like
oh you can go here and we're like well
what happens over there but we have
decided and it's a secret
do they know no it's a secret mm-hm
maybe in Argentina Japan trip when when
Marcia
soon my gf very soon are you jealous
will you please mark this camera to film
use instead of yours
we are your welcome internet what's
wrong with my camera look at this
quality terrible cold
no I'm not gonna sit here you need to
produce my video
yeah we'll invite any other youtuber to
the wedding
how've you been we're keeping the guest
suites very very small severe youtuber
annoying violin that means we hate you
hi this is from sweet bliss clearly a
fan of Sweden why did you move from
Sweden and have you ever thought about
moving back here why did we move minds
yeah we wanted a place where we could
both speak and be independent because in
easily you would have to mean a means we
do not have to read news yeah so you can
seem like a pretty in between times and
middle ground basically but we really
cherished the time we had in Sweden
because that's what we got my and
yeah that's it was a humble beginnings
in Sweden that's what I think about
going back to Sweden yeah but I think if
that happened he will be in the future
house dog how is done he's great he's
doing great
he sleeps during the day doggies lying
unlikely he's very cute he's asleep Saul
the time I play with him next car maybe
you don't like that design you don't
like this design uh it's cool maybe not
on a car
what will your white host mean were you
well first we have to get married that
is the requirement I have to be married
to everyone that holds me Shapiro's what
was your dream job it's a king yes I
think it's a boat I wanted to open a
boutique and it was mostly for fetching
I'm petite steel spec boutique still
stands maybe a my shop in the future
this video was sponsored by my shop I
wanted to make video games oh yeah but I
had no idea what that meant I was like
yeah sure and I realized that youtuber
because I'm the more important one how
do you feel that much after quitting me
the first two months when I first quit
I really miss it a lot mm-hmm you missed
one making video anything but also
sharing things I feel like I still share
them but I miss being able to have a
platform what I could speak about
anything I want it in the same way but
at the same time it has given me what I
wanted which is the time to focus on
something else so it's good to have that
feels good man can you speak Italian
Felix can you see by l'italiano molto
bene same a dragon pounder I am boy
William Pizza wouldn't be saying yes
yeah
see they really seem a mite yeah you get
burglar
one day okay this is one is for me but
you should read it for me thank Mary
killed bread one Bret - and my skin all
right this is easy kill nice yet mang
bread one Mary branchy
what are some of your favorite games to
play together off camera well we don't
play any games we play Yasha get
together on camera we play pokemon card
inj then some do you games we play we
usually place where she beans overcooked
is good night Bros Smash Bros is good Oh
Drummond fine Drummond fun that's really
fun all that game yeah that was fun of
course new tech of games my favorite
central for video games save the coupon
code that's it feed pipe 20 that's
humility will you propose mine to the
second time in Minecraft and any chance
recording it well as you can see I've
set up a computer here - yes time to
play minecraft imagine if a creeper was
are like priests explosion tells us the
affiliate median life now you're
basically best oh really oh yeah oh yeah
that is my answer
female wall man Hugh Mann person what's
her dishwasher very late next once the
joke here was that I'm the one who put
everything in the dishwasher they
thought it could be an educational
moment here for everyone here but you
can learn that man can use the
dishwasher - okay I use the dishwasher
all the time you're more of a hand
washing the guns and there's nothing
wrong with that nothing wrong with it
maybe before we were married I would
shame but now I've educated myself this
is from enemy Maine
Joey who's your wife my oh my I don't
have a wife
you are like my future life you always
have girls practice okay it will be fine
if you set a name
hey you got a question from Isaac do you
really think he's the one
I mean maybe you've got betterment aside
but I have a job and regular ice
one-size salary yeah but they smaller
than money you know my charm and good
looks like being funny
dude I was rated top fine mind Sam
here's a tough one if you could marry
Elon Musk would you choose him over Mars
yet or already engaged sorry Marcy on
this is the reason I put it on camera
because I want people do you want more
cuz that was all the questions okay bye
well well well well Thank You Marcia
that was really smooth for being here
look but also for being my future one
everyone is invited to the wedding
security check your inbox everyone that
subscribes are invited it's gonna be
late we're not giving out any details
right you're just inviting but you're
inviting you won't know when where or
how they make sure you smash like
subscribe and also months yet the floor
is yours millions of people watching
what do you want what is he putting you
on the spot
smash night subscribe bye old emerge