hair short hair short oh let's hear it
can't wait to read all the comments he
looks like ask the same haircut I had
when I was baby that's so funny
you guys are so clever alright let's get
him to the memes I'm ready
[Music]
I miss IKEA / what that's actually
pretty cool not gonna lie though he's
just vibing them come on look at it I
was wonder where he went
where did I care where oh no wait a
minute IKEA bird is dead
belongs in a museum alright last week I
said it's whisky week so here we go we
got whisky themes and for next week I
got a new theme I'll announce it at the
end of the video next theme is whiskey
me a 9 year old whisky I'm skating 20
bees chase car for two days after queen
bee gets trapped in boot sorry to ask
but who counted the bees that's a great
question
how many bees a lot of bees no that
doesn't sound good many bees mmm do it
twenty thousand twenty thousand publish
it yeah here it is paradise fetus
innocent infant q2c child juvenile
preteen confuse teen troublemaker team
existential adult responsible adult mmm
mmm the evolution of PewDiePie has come
full circle next next up I'll go feed us
alright from now on it's fetus pie this
video guy recommended because I went on
a break and then I guess like in 2011 I
wanted a break too so let's see this
how's it going everyone
PewDiePie here and welcome to my very
first non gameplay video it's gonna be a
really boring video
sound so stupid how's it going guys
nerd you're a nerd no one likes you
you're not that bronze learn English
you're not even speaking English just
warning you but it's also an important
video cuz I because I no one cares god
damn look at this fan art holy moly
hey they got my favorite whiskey right
there and I got Centauri whiskey right
there and they got a very bad virus and
no legs
that isn't they even got the coffee malt
whiskey dude I got a freaking jet pack
more whiskey they're so cute
alright this is Leonardo Vincent and in
damn it belongs in museum ten out of ten
they look like a couple in Pokemon who
wants too bad I have the power of
lightning why is that that's not
supposed to be off alright this looks
more dramatic I like this this is
dramatic means from now on yeah me and
Marcel want JoJo's I know it's no big
deal
do I still have mine hold up let me get
it I'll show you guys some tricks
they call me yo-yo master
about anyone can do that
a link
this is how I got mark here by the way I
just like ate Italian good
I'm on stilts by the way it's heart of
metal main
[Music]
no that's why I'll show you
ah while I'm at it
G fuel you can buy it right now for 30%
off if you enter the code PewDiePie go
ahead and do it there's a new doom
flavor which is spicy and I hacking love
it all right back to your dramatic memes
whiskey theme you know why because
you're not allowed to drink y'all
nineteen-year-old laughs in European
laughs in Swedish hey hey
most of the Mars scenes in the Martian
2015 were actually filmed on earth this
is what it drains the soul of cinema
every time they use suggests using CGI
instead of actual props and actual
settings it's upsetting when you're
there yep when your mom chooses your new
haircut the irony here is that my mom
never let me cut my hair short she
wanted me to have it long which is good
on my mom because I look way better with
long hair
clearly I just never had it short so I
thought I kind of want to just see how
it looks like and surprisingly hairline
is fine I didn't notice so now I know
this this is good and if you notice here
as well even better it's the fact that
my forehead is huge which basically
means my brain is large how did that
break all right traumatic memes it is
you sync your phone gently PewDiePie
what do you make what you guys want to
try some mains tomorrow
all right just imagine that you're a
salt you're a salt shaker yeah yeah no
you're you're the salt in a salt shaker
okay and I am PewDiePie okay
okay hey hey there whitey you look a
little salty there I want to lick you
yeah that's right I don't care if you're
big or small I will get you out of there
but be sure don't be scared it's going
to be okay you will get out of there
just dramatic
memes continues remember that kid from
strangers things
this is him now feel old yet do you feel
old yet hey YouTube videos in 2050 if
you buy these videos in 2050 we finally
have 4k should I start shooting in 4k
will you guys be quiet then cuz I'm
happy to do it I don't care
the problem is sight I'm just gonna
blame side for this one for no reason at
whatsoever it is size fault size fault
thanks I'm sorry I think things I'm
friendly appreciate you making memes
upside down knowing pewds is on PC
checkmate liberal alright that's not
worth it alright not worth it
me can I go to the bathroom teacher it's
may me no it's March
boom says the bird Boehner English when
it's whiskey week American 19 year old
European night in Europe I drink to that
I'll drink some spicy doom G fuel for
30% off today friends are like a
trampoline I always wanted a trampoline
friends are like a trampoline you have
to go to someone else to enjoy it
because there was always that one friend
that had a trampoline there was always
that one friend that was way more
popular than everyone else
only because they had a trampoline let
me just say it straight out so it's
crystal clear for everyone if you had a
trampoline the only reason you had a
friend is because you are the trampoline
owner people don't want to be around you
people just want to jump on your
trampoline and yes the trampoline is a
metaphor for your balls
I don't think Sony is going to reveal
the PlayStation 5 in February February
29 smart brains made with brains they
should have posted this at 11:59 come on
no balls no balls Dave dear I was so
stressed I forgot to say I was the one
who recorded Polish cover of bit lasagna
in Brighton series okay not gonna lie
he's just vibing and polished uh very
nice but like what is he saying I don't
get it
I don't speak slowly pots polish that's
a language the guy on the left is the
voice actor for trevor in GTA v and
that's his son why does his son look
like his 9 year old grandma way imagine
his son playing GTA 5 and in the final
mission he choose to can't leave now
that would make him a Malfoy again I'll
take it back I bet you that's what he
did
Felix hairstyle before a break Felix
hairstyle now you guys think you are so
clever don't you hope you feel good
about yourself how did you die I was
hugging my best friend though I mean
what what killed you I don't care I was
hugging my best friend oh oh I was not
ready for that
oh why can't girls during puberty oh my
god I hate everything boys during
puberty oh I miss my hair already can we
get a moment of silence in the chat for
my lost hair can we gather like for each
like my hair will grow out please guys
can we do it
math teachers on the first day of school
we are four parallel universes behind
array yeah that's true they're always
like that oh we're so much behind
oh yeah well why don't you count faster
dumbass is this what he meant by whiskey
theme nice that's cool come on give me
my whiskey I literally the only reason
I'm a whiskey thing was like oh I was
hoping things would send me whiskey
right like some company would be like
what we can that's smart actually the
Sun Alexander the Great Diogenes
lie back down that's great I didn't
expect any Diogenes memes I appreciate
that that's fun really a big thanks to
all that everyone that support those
kind of videos that I do because I think
YouTube wise they make no sense they
shouldn't exist but people like them so
that's what and I like them so that's
why they exist hammer man is here very
nice
got the same form you know it baby five
million subscribers in six months five
million subscribers in a month five
million dislikes in two days
five million repost in an hour big brain
brain large Paul Mikoto Yoda I don't
know if that's what he says reddit after
two hours of scrolling I've seen enough
I'm satisfied ready there's 10 seconds
later oh my god this is so freakin
relatable don't we all just do this oh
my god it's me ha ha ha holy moly it's
me bro you see this hairline it's
straighter than you this celebrated
before PewDiePie came back this
subreddit now Toby H 3 alcoholic sorry
Toby sorry about that I'm sure things
will work out at least you still have
your hair Toby not gonna lie they look
similar this is what happens gamers
that's just what happens I mean not to
go after Felix hair but that's the thing
everyone had this haircut when they were
a kid already if I had it as a kid I
wouldn't have to do it now I would be
like alright cool I did it redbull may
give you wings but whiskey gives you big
PP sure let's go with that
oh hey YouTube King Felix everybody like
that
nice see I got skills I don't know what
to say I can use anything as a yo-yo
just look I got all the skills if anyone
dare challenge me in the yo-yo back
though I imagine you you just challenged
me in your battle don't do that
don't do that stop it guys I'm gonna
need some video requests by the way
since I'm back marci hosting low I hey I
want my review this is my favorite since
I've read it it's whiskey that's funny
huge puppy s'more yet I was waiting for
that that's good
that's a funny in you mean template my
god the Super Girl fans were so mad that
I dare to criticize your show watch it I
think I actually said that at one time
oh god no good meme I laugh at this you
know how I got this hair line I pour
whiskey on it everyday you just dab a
little bit of whiskey it all blooms like
a flower garden daisies yeah rocket oh
yeah you think you can yo-yo well yo-yo
you step out of this one
no wonder he's 180 centimeter god this
is so annoying
alright I'll explain this I can explain
this hold on so you think this is the
soul but really the way the foot goes is
is like this it goes all the way until
the bottom there's no soul that's how my
feet look like on the inside so it looks
it looks like I just don't want other
people to feel bad that are short that's
why just so we clear
hey oh that's nice thank you I like his
new look yeah I think now it's a little
too short I think if I grow it out a
little bit it'll look it'll look better
they look better it's okay
appearance isn't everything this is
something that people judge you by
someone made a CD with all my hit
singles I really appreciate the
placement of that that's great breaking
news if you call the police I will come
I will have to say out of all bad things
happening in the world one thing I
appreciate is that if I'm really bored
in a line somewhere it is kind of funny
just to call for the sake of it
just to see people's reaction I was at
the post office and I had nothing to do
there's taken forever and you just just
do that's all you have to do and all the
sudden really if you cut down a tree you
must plant two more even musk three take
it or leave it
oh he did three so I already said that
so I actually own some credit for it
being epic that's awesome I like how I
actually take credit for that they're
saying stuff and then there's action to
take an action oh I'm so good thoughts
I'm getting robbed how the video
actually went so I thought it would be
applesauce applesauce oh you know what I
update my secret word its applesauce now
I realize I have to keep updating it
because people are gonna follow right
secret word if you ever meet me there's
applesauce if you save math it's related
to science I'm gonna be like cringe all
right you want to selfie a cringe guys
I'm gonna need some video requests by
the way since I'm back okay fine 500
likes might say will host oh I
that's a promise I've never said that
that's a lie eight-year-old me watching
my friend drunk because I replace his
apple juice with whiskey the fifth time
classic oh yeah I kept saying classic
the whole video like that's a classic
that's a classic right there another
classic it's doomed flavor G fuel for
30% up Master Skywalker there's too many
of them what are we going to do shop
shop talks to a girl for literally 10
seconds my mom oh my god yes why either
guys are really dumb and we can't pick
up cues and when a girl likes you and
moms are spot-on or it's literally this
means I'm curious what your thoughts are
on this let me know it took me 69 days
and it looked amazing
very nice oh here it is look at that
from the freaking skies bro that's cool
yo your master 64 me and the boys
drinking apple juice instead of whiskey
since we're not own enough apple juice
will suffice it's okay
red it should have a do you want to go
back where you left off button how do
they not have that yeah seriously
oh my god I stand that's a fact I stand
with that I've been recording these way
too long this is a very long episode
thank you for making it to the end
I appreciate you and now you know the
secret word as well which is obviously
very important about information now if
you want to support your channel
remember to check out the merch I
appreciate subscribe if you haven't
already for whatever reason and next
things look the why not to be confused
with lawar you guessed it trebuchet so
if any companies that are trebuchet
manufacturers or want to send me a
trebuchet and you want to get some promo
hit me up my business email is in my
thing and or just post on the subreddit
ok that's it see you guys tomorrow
Adel hey you know what big peepees do
they play PewDiePie's pixel ings of
course pixel ings is a creature
collecting game I'm the primary
shareholder over a Brazilian players
have downloaded and it's got a perfect
score it's safe to say it's the most
popular game of all time
PewDiePie pixel aims it's awesome deal
with it
build with it
[Music]
you