Nicci why everyone it's me another day
Jesus Christ
another day another video just cuz I'm
out traveling doesn't mean the video
stop I know that's why we had this
amazing new set up that is not cooked to
close-up at all this is nice and
intimate aren't you enjoying this stream
fails that's what we're talking about
today I never done one so I can't really
relate to what we're about to witness in
this video good job Felix but here are
some epic stream fails of not just
people making mistakes but getting
trolled epic style by the viewers which
again I cannot relate to cuz I've never
been trolled by the viewers I am just
too smart for that
it just not happen and I want to start
this off with the reason why I'm making
this video because it's my favorite clip
of all time a life and just thinking
about it poor innocent girl just wanted
to play Minecraft
I couldn't find a better quality why is
it so bad and someone in the chat I
can't believe how you could sink this
low
it's super worthwhile hold the pickaxe
look at lava push Q someone comments
it's super worthwhile look at lava and
press Q okay oh poor pickaxe she threw
it right into the lava this is so sad
but wait I guess I mean to me why okay
why it only works with oh I'm so I'm so
stupid so the person comments again I
can only imagine I don't see the chat it
only works with diamond pickaxe the
first pickaxe you sent into the lava
that's too cheap you need to throw in
the other one you gotta you gotta
appreciate when you acknowledge that
you're really stupid and then you do
something even more stupid now I don't
afford this girl I would do the same
thing to be honest if I wasn't so
goddamn smart never I have I been troll
and Winnie the Pooh if Tigger was like
what would okay alright
shout out to my boy Nicky gears oh my
god Jesus Christ Felix what are you
doing read this message I'm forcing it
stop singing
why did I fall for that Jesus Christ you
could get a third person with keel just
don't do on the horse it's a bit buggy
just don't do it on the horse in console
it's a bit buggy press Q in the console
[Laughter]
how could you be so stupid
I would never fall for something like
that this is the reason I don't live
stream this don't do it on the horse
it's a bit buggy well played yeah I
guess my dick see wreck what's up it's
funny when they realize right after
what's up my bro I just shat my pants
let's get this bread guys on dammit like
Dixie or something
you gonna do that old art do a special
attack hold our do special attack it
resets the game Jesus Christ is such a
dick mo oh my god
I kind of want to just make a game for
streamers and have one button that just
flips everything up Weis is funny it's
really not funny but it's also hilarious
huge huge load of sick
my mom's here no can't you sub another
day some another day load of seamen they
don't got it mom I don't know who that
is
there's this some troll just having to
explain that to your mom as well that
just makes it 10 times better
oh is this huge nog can you imagine
having that conversation with your mom
just sub another day please god damn I
can't tell if this is one of the things
would I just meet think think it's funny
or not just because I can see myself in
this situation and it would actually
happen to me and it is the only reason I
don't scream anymore because I'm just
getting cybernetically bullied just
kidding okay I would never fall for your
foul tricks these bunny fools I swallow
come come great how did I poke the thing
is like you're streaming it's so hard to
it's so hard to be streamer gay you just
don't understand but your your focus is
so shifted on so many things already
like it's not just a game but also the
chat and trying to understand what is
happening really got to be good at
multitasking so then when people catch
you off guard with that kind of mess
I get it okay hey look it's forsen space
ah
you fool for seven what's happening
precious space proceeds to masturbate
what the [ __ ] Sarah there is no donation
that there's no he already raised it
what are you saying it's out donation
there re subs tiger harvest thank you
for your sob gully lord thank you for
your five months crispy thank you for
your four months
Travie oh man thank you for your six
dollars i'm tim son I don't notice
anything Mike Hawk Meredith shut up to
my dick just want to interrupt this
video and give a huge shout-out to my
pothole I love woody doesn't register
either it's equally funny and no one no
don't do it g4 for some chunks why he
doesn't work
oh god oh no three zeroes in 1g oh and
1g do your y'all's codes are [ __ ] busted
make sure you're typing the right thing
dude oh I don't know I feel about this
not a third time please try X please
this is a great compilation by the way
I'm sure every Chad there's gonna be
like I already saw this video I know but
it's funny okay
his vent ro it's about hold on mutters
like that's the song you like she says
she says oh my goddess I hate that
goddamn sound I hate that goddamn sound
smash like if you got trolled as well
let me know so I know who's a headphone
user and smash like twice if you have
the razor PewDiePie it falls just so I
can know if you're a headphone razor be
the PI user god damn why ever did that
two questions this time one of those
medical related and the other ones not
which one do you want first the non one
first let's know that is just me talking
yeah does it smell like what oh no dog
dr. Murphy please yep
what's that sorry what's up dog why is
up dog funny it's the lamest joke of all
times and lamest dad you ever crafted
you get hit by an up dog you might as
well just end your career right there
please be quiet and dedicate 30 seconds
to his favorite 30 seconds no take off
your head that's nice for a 30-second
silence
oh my god they said only use me blade
the mud them were afraid to guy that
only uses is played you guys remember
those days or is it just me
okay sips I'd just like to say I
appreciate everything you do and think
you're a very attractive man and I
aspire to be just like you one day nice
just kidding you [ __ ] Virginia so
disgusting I hate this so much
whatever yeah read a nice comment on
YouTube and like oh this is so nice
finally like a really nice comment I
haven't seen those in days literally
years I can't remember the last time I
didn't go and send something nice in
general with my name regarded to it and
then you and you keep reading in this
like by the way check out my channel in
like god dammit
my couch is hairy even what excuse me
Mike who cheese hair even what say that
again
Mike who cheese hearing it's time to
stop please I don't know I don't know I
I literally don't know anything I don't
know what's happening Oh someone wrote
it oh my god
Oh God it's not funny this is so
childish and stupid but also it's
hilarious and I love it
dr. Murphy again sook undies don't do it
don't do it dr. Murphy please no don't
answer going to see those Deez Nuts I
really appreciate the people taking the
time out of their day just for that one
moment just for that one moment of epic
trolling that's it that's all the time
we had for today streams fails epic
trolls if you're an epic troll stirrers
leave a like just so I know if you are
and also check out mercs link
description I think you will like it
very much and now I'm gonna go and
explored
Nihon everyone bye bye tuber simulator
it's now so relevant that it's got a
brand new minigame crania drop the crane
and get fresh items only available in
the washing machine like game and you
say there's more of course there is new
knowledge perks new quests and new picks
links and legs guys length