Jacob Zuma Oh
have you heard of this guy the Sue's
face ring a bell what if I say his name
is Jacob get lay II Lakeisha Zuma now do
you understand well this man is the
former president of South Africa and
here you can find him breaking it down
[Applause]
a quirky figure you might say well Zuma
has all kinds of history history that
involves accepting bribes corruption
fraud racketeering you know I was just
just one of those it doesn't matter if
there's one thing for certain of our
Jacob Zuma and that's one thing numbers
is Jacob Zuma's number one enemy okay
let's watch one of my favorite clips of
Jacob Zuma one of many we announce that
our membership figures stood at 769 810
700 haha listen properly I am I'm
talking hundred and sixty nine thousand
eight hundred and twenty was that it at
the end of the and seventh and seventeen
thank you
you know without the seventy Indiana I
would really have thought he didn't know
what the hell he was talking about
seemed we can follow that let's just see
if we can what should I use in text on
stood yet as I've been hundred and sixty
nine seventy six and eight hundred and
you mean six one six nine million eight
hundred seven hundred I am say another
nine and sixty nine certain 2820 oh I
see okay so he started he started over
here it still doesn't match and 7th and
seventy members down from 110 100 I come
on cut him some slack all right why
should he know how to handle numbers
it's not like he stopped rising at oh my
god you think America was dealt a bad
hand okay think of South Africa but he's
so funny and quirky
he does dancing but wait there is more
oh god there's so many more oh this guy
just keeps grabbing numbers from
everywhere
whatever you think he's done he decides
another thousand another million it
doesn't matter come on you know it's not
like a five-year-old could do this
better
[Music]
is key
hahahaha 769 810 700 the number of
babies shall be positive was reduced by
sixes percent from twenty four thousand
two thousand eight two eight four two
eight point two two to eight hundred
point twenty the numbers Jacob what do
they mean
eight point two to eight point two
hundred the numbers dropped from twenty
four thousand to eight point two to
eight point two hundred if anyone knows
what that means let me know I really
like these news clips because they have
a translator and they just don't know
how to translate his ineptitude
[Applause]
megawatts this guy is talking about nope
you know it's no coincidence that
they're Doomsday Clock is what how close
is it it's two minutes that's fine
doesn't matter maybe just maybe we need
to be more careful with who we vote for
in our democracies Wow
where did he get that number that's a
great statistics vicaroo by two hundred
and three thousand apples I think it
couldn't handle figure between seven to
eight hundred this continent is the
Asian continent in the world not
separated even by a river
the rivers that are there flow with the
continent they don't cut it how can you
have a Potter all continents put
together will fit in into Africa
oh wow fun fact
fun fact time all the continents fit
into Africa you know he's not wrong he's
not just the master of numbers he's also
a master of the fun facts all continents
fit into Africa as you can tell here
this is one of those illusions where it
like it wouldn't work but if you try it
you can see it clearly like USA has so
much space North America has so much
space left in Africa and if you take
Europe there's plenty of space from
Europe as well if you cut it out it yes
you can tell here it all fits into
Africa all right this guy is a president
over country Jesus Christ how are we
alive how one video he is literally the
scene from washing powers $1,000,000,000
it's literally the living embodiment and
the Zulu Zulu I don't know what a
billion is in similar some buffoon this
was none season is that true is that the
actual translation that can't be right
but you might not believe but it's money
that can't run away run away billions
has been stolen from governments okay
this is very concerning
[Music]
now apparently Zuma has had such an
impact that other people are affected by
this there's a conspiracy going on
called the Zuma virus that makes people
not able to number look at the
translator here but my favorite one is
this one I don't know if this is even
real problem or a problem rising rupee
red pepper deep problema popping crab
open up Oh peep peep you can tell how
done the translator ladies she's a lady
professionals been financially all
professionals I'll give you one thing
though he has a contagious laugh and I
think he knows thank you very much if I
can laugh because I would always laugh
answer to answer you sure not stalling
Thank You mr. president it appears that
you are very well advised by your
Minister of Health because medical
experts say that if you want to live a
long and healthy life then you laugh
everyday life I ever heard you know some
people who could not pronounce cancer
they've now led Konza con song this is
guy actually roasting people how they
can articulate Jesus Christ cons I
really miss him he used to steal so much
money from our tax papers he's one of
the clever ones he might be stupid but
he still managed to take a lot of sa
money Jesus Christ dude apparently God
lately Casa means one who smiles while
causing you harm well isn't that ironic
Julian onziema
thank you for coming in thank you good
morning here Zoomers brother d you ugly
I'm not sexually active right now so
what did I enjoy this lately choice by
choice me I've just not I've chosen not
to engage doesn't that make you gay why
doesn't that make me gay I am I am ill
and attracted to a female so who is gay
oh god I shouldn't laugh it's a sad oh
well good morning why are you gay
straight to the point
some male and attracted to form a so
whose Oh God
alright well that's all you need to know
about Jacob Zuma
if you enjoyed this video smash like
subscribe we got a hit a hundred million
come on bros since I still have you make
sure to check out epic merge represent
coms - PewDiePie support the channel and
I see you guys tomorrow what you never
play - birthday maleta you know it's fun
right I'm not supposed to give my
opinion but give it a try and then you
can tell me if it's good or not not
convinced yet okay I'll cut you a deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]