oh my god Becky burrs no I wanted to
join I'm like no I can't intro completed
welcome back
Wow we traveled so far what are we doing
we're like a mountain now Oh climbing
very epic I'm gonna go up here and see
what the hell is up here hey hey sorry
thank you swore so now I have to fight
you on top of mountain to show Susan I
am not actually bad nice she's like I
give you good ads don't worry she's like
I put you on trending please do every
day alpaca I'll get the left word those
wild alpacas they're wild epically oh I
want one we don't have any saddles maybe
we can ask them from are you spinning
like the other pepper baby up to
badlands
okay how about this we put them in a
hole so we can just grab them later okay
I think this one likes me Holy Bull okay
go in the hole no stop climbing is yours
in the hole yet bro no I hate what mine
is in the hole I just spitting on you
Jack I'm sorry
don't you get what a bit thing on Jack
he's in the sand I don't have a shovel
did you put in a hole yeah of course hug
oh you're on you're on this note that's
easier yes stay the whole stay in the
hole you don't need a dad we're your new
puppy hey sorry we're come on my god use
your tiny hands why it's too fast he
can't be stopped there we go there we go
push me put him in look great oh my god
you pushed him out I did not I did not I
think they will despawn just so we're
clear right no no this is gonna work
perfect staying home we'll find you guys
because we care little it'd just to make
sure you same okay and I get sacrificed
through what their Oh - golden
alpaca my inventory oh it's a mess
really
I have like five things
can I give you some yeah please here's a
gold nugget did you get all this sweet
seeds ready God Lord you're like a
McDonald's I'll take it
mutton apparently okay pet dolphin in my
game got me too why can you not Bowl cry
don't know I trapped one before he died
flower biome no I'm special no never
mind it's not it's regular I have a
flower island in my game special am i
special yeah yeah you're special
did we just emigrate to new world
because I feel like that's what we did
even though it's equally bad pretty much
we left Scandinavia we need new accents
I kill you at me look at me when to
reassure it is very Arabic Rasha
oh my god kill skeleton skeleton too
scary skeleton too bony like him
everyone my family because we don't feed
okay no go F go back wait why is it long
string in this guy what is that oh it
hasn't loaded yet wow look at in it
looked really cool dude I don't like
this do you like this no I don't like
anything of what we're doing I'm trying
to figure out oh let's go to spruce
place I like the Spruce place we could
have had like seven storey house by now
rich kill the wheat Oh help me please
they'll put a spell on you I don't even
know who you are please help I'm about
to die I heard that please help I'm
coming please help my sword went out
well they have a pickaxe I'm an axe I'm
dying I'm gonna die
no I'm gonna die I'm serious you're not
I have one hell you're not gonna die the
witch is dead we need to sleep otherwise
we won't respawn sneeze
like uh do you have arrows everywhere I
saved you though you did bro thanks bro
no problem three hours too late
Corinne three hours later okay boss
Enderman oh god there's okay
I don't should we go back what are we
doing I don't know keep pushing forward
okay let's go to the spruce okay I'm
there
I have diamond pickaxe I really don't
want to lose this we have to kill sheep
if you see oh we need to sleep Jack we
need to sleep or there's a village here
we can sleep in the village hurry follow
me sweet
Oh God wait there's one of these who
tiny dago's okay watch out for our
berries they hurt my string they sting
like tears from your eyes oh god you
have special technique of jumping I
didn't know that makes you go faster I
got okay oh god wait where the hell do I
respond I told you brah we were supposed
to sleep you died outside wait I have to
sleep I have to sleep otherwise bad wait
do we have to sleep at the same time
three two one sleep there's no beds I'm
sleeping that's not bad I'm sleeping
well funtime I can't sleep where were we
fuzzball series is me dying three
diamonds cool cold not sleep okay what's
it that's awesome sleep before here
Panthers bro you're missing out bro okay
wait I was sleeping that I will dream of
you and maybe that will make you
teleport
if I if I sleep okay I'm sleeping I'm
dreaming up jack
oceans oh look good morning top of
morning top of money okay - 727 - I'll
make a boat are you actually gonna walk
no I'm gonna sail I'll walk it all of
this I respect I respect this delight
you need stop guy I wanna make bread oh
yeah I can't make bread I think this is
a cool place I like this place
yeah awesome yeah it's so cool I mean I
can come back if you want Jack you're
not gonna believe what I just found
right not one not two seven hundred
potatoes oh my god it was so worried the
sacrifice that's why I thought we could
emigrate to new planet just like even
MUSC good when you plan it
yeah marce it's like hey Mars hello
hello Mars it is me hello it's me hello
okay wait what's your coordinates oh I
see okay
- 729 it's a backfire no no it isn't
I've gone further maybe I'll just go
through the nether and dying lava five
times again oh my god
see it's funny because I could joke
about it now now that it hasn't happened
I I did the exact same thing in my own
playthrough again whoa there's armor
racks what I went into the nether and
forgot sorry timing I rented that a
nether and forgot Slynt and steel so I
had to use a gas - no and then he
disrupted the lava and I died me oh my
god I have a problem Jackie you keep
dying Oh horrible you're gonna love this
I built like one two three four five six
houses Wow yeah it's great built or
stoled does it matter stealing them is
better okay a stone
I stole awesome I love stealing people's
houses jumping in stealing all their
stuff sleeping in their beds
I like how I was so amazed by our place
the first time and then
as I oh but there's nothing else I like
the spruce area though it reminds me of
the four fjords takes yards back in
Bjork
yeah you're kirik they say they say you
Bjerke enough time you become a say once
you've York you never go yeah the arcane
the way you speak Jack the words remind
you of the motherland that's nice
my mother's land I'll make sure that if
I ever meet her I'll talk like this to
her
oh hello hello do you understand she
likes me up
Felix Miyama okay what's so good to meet
it's big bouncy baby
he's don't meet her in the wedding all
right speech speech speech hello Swedish
I speak like this so you understand me
what're sheep water sheep I don't even
know what half of the stuff from your
series is watch the episodes I just keep
getting secondhand knowledge from
everybody I expect anything you say that
like it's a normal thing in the game
what do you mean she's a sheep that in
the water don't make me talk about it
it's too painful
okay I get it sorry you lose enough
water sheeps I break any man I'm not
scared of no man but that water she okay
I'm at 700 700 - ham bro no - mm - 700
oh yeah - - I love this area
we should fence this city so we can
protect and sleep that is what Vikings
did this is what we do we take their hot
babes oh my god nice babes here steal
their house that's why old Scandinavian
so attractive we picked out all the good
ones does that mean we become prettier
and prettier
I see but then why you ugly Oh
god oh my god can't believe can't
believe he just said that to me what if
I find something like totally epic and I
come to you and we make epic if we find
a horse that we tame they we can give
them both armor cuz I have to iron
armors for horse or horse yes for horse
[Applause]
wait that's not the armor you were gonna
give me is it because you think I'm a
horse I'm trying to make the potatoes
into a heart but it looks like fork haha
but understand what I'm trying to get it
don't ruin surprise every time an
Irishman looks at the potato it looks
like a hurt yeah I I can see that I like
how at the start of each episode I
complain that we don't get enough done
and then I die and I spent the whole
episode
I killed cow now sorry cow hungry so you
were vegan oh they are vegan cows
oh good you don't know if vegan cats
it's just another thing like water sheep
no actually never I brought up water
sheep
let's talk about water sheep you never
go back you never forget the pain hey
there's a bunch of sheep around me
though that I can kill for freaking beds
because I kind of need the meat as well
see why progress in Minecraft when you
can just steal other people's progress
I make bed and I sleep make bed and
sleep oh good night world okay good
night good night sleep sleep I sure hope
green boys thinking about me always
where is he
it's almost like he's speaking in my
brain but why he had to die I'm here
massacre ha ha ha oh I smell potato is
you it's me it's my deodorant oh my god
okay oh thank you Tony for me I don't
just play yeah for you and follow me
good d-bag
you can take two potato potato
and also look soft potatoes I know you
like yeah I don't know how many times I
got it it's the gift that keeps on
giving
thank you the keeper gave it this
village is massive like look it goes all
the way even up here jeepers what should
we call the village they all have eye
patches I know they're like blacksmith
kitty so cute I think we're in a pirate
village pirate blacksmith's a Viking
village pirate Viking not eating the
bread that you gave me telling you man
my brain just turns off just as long as
my my crab pick egg is okay pickaxes go
on forever that's really part of our
problem right now we really need you
like tame wolf
we need our dogs foxes here but we need
a leash for them so sad you can still
breathe them oh no they have a baby
already the two babies make them more
baby oh wait they need to mate with
someone else
yeah it's just a mom with two babies ah
dummy mom oh look he's with us now oh if
only we had a leash we're two leads we
could have two foxes now my god that'd
be so cool
maybe we could build house build a
mansion right in the middle of all their
houses
yeah on top of all of theirs yes wait
which is who has the biggest house if we
build a house on top of like a two-story
house back here I haven't built anything
you know while I'm down this one seems
good I'll get some wood at least now you
don't have to worry about dying as well
I always worry about dying in this game
wait there's no lab around is there hey
how about we just use this house right
in the middle the hill from what else is
out yeah I just build on top of it I
like you thinking
these are gonna have to go
not offense you know like those now it
looks like our house in the middle of
the shop shop shop I'm doing some
renovations cuz I think it has Marcie
blocks all we need to do up the house a
little bit angry I agree
maybe we can add a floor to it pop up
morning cuppa morning disco hello what
happens when you ring the bell we did
the old runaway wave creatures attack
you can ring it and they all go into the
house oh my god they cool they went to
our house excuse me yeah row when in the
same building am I gonna have to commit
a murder
don't do it jack I know it's tempting
but you've been for young murder he has
a sweeping edge iron sword for 11
emeralds
how many emeralds do before this is so
sad but he have six soft potatoes for
one whoa arthropods it's four against
spiders and son bane of arthropods two
and knock-back one for sixteen emeralds
yeah I never traded with the most type
of villager hello Hey boarding iron Oh
gets up here bro hello you know sit see
me I do okay oh these blocks are not
gonna do they have moss all over them
how did you guys live here with mold
just go Stan it was one of those guys
Fang yeah we definitely improve this
place absolutely you're welcome so much
we should be lately hey watch this
[Laughter]
bounce out of the bed yeah you can oh my
god you are babe get out get out
we should probably sleep actually okay I
got this one there's one downstairs go
okay go oh excuse I'm here masa guy yeah
get out of my house Jack I don't know
how to tell you this I'm making my own
house haha I wonder why I want our house
come on let's be lured together
I don't want to steal other people's
house we can be the mayors of this town
that's true and then they'll have to
listen to us we ring the bell every
morning we start the morning we top of
the morning to them how about we make
like a reverse tower so it's skinny on
the bottom but Jake
antek on the top like my peepee just
starts at one block Oh see now the good
idea come then then two by two or yeah
yeah maybe we should go in the mines
then there's a mine there down here
where's the mine here perfect oh oh oh
Gollum hey bro you want to help oh my
god
trying not to hit you nice oh my god
sometimes the moms lag and then they
just attack you even though oh sorry
yeah that's okay bro I see her Enderman
possible in Minecraft and they're men in
Minecraft I was so shocked the first
time I saw one and then it's like oh
they're everywhere
yeah I had no idea what it was yeah work
pillar house for us that'd be cool if
you can employ them me like Hank yes but
we're not under contract
we have no Union to protect ourself we
have to unionize and became papers
please Olsen
maybe the diamond pickaxe is like your
thing like Voldemort like your
attachment to life my Horcrux
your Horcrux yeah yeah that's it that's
why you haven't died yet cuz every time
you mention to your diamond pickaxe
somewhere last second so what are you
doing in your mine crying right now I
redid my entire castle oh it looks
awesome giant Irish flag on top oh you
finally got it nice I got a girlfriend
for my dog Oh
me too bro except boyfriend it's pretty
nice
what's his name Spence boyfriend so
original give him a name bro he's not
person's boyfriend's feelings yeah why
it's such a badge months for pets on
YouTube well I've got a comeback through
mine Kyle oh I like that do you hear
that yeah what did you do I was building
stairs so you get in and out of this
hole and a creeper came up behind me
okay I got a few mats if you want to
start building see
that's it's just sounded like fortnight
all of a sudden again oh is that a
foreign I think yeah do the metal mats
whoa you make excellent entrance
entrance to cave thing Wow I can fit a
whole bus full of children down here
that's the plan bus full of children go
down the hall there's a cover up these
holes as long we take their taxes and we
put it back into city we make it good
look everyone nice place we give back to
people if I'm bad before anybody else -
fine fine dibs
I feel like they just looked at
Squidward more like yeah that's you know
spongebob is in the game right have you
done an ocean temple yet No then you'll
see spongebob well it did make a
character based on Slenderman and just
called him Enderman I like a challenge
that's good enough
good job dude me and fire do not
cooperate yeah should we do it like this
where we build only in the edge out and
not like yeah so it's like a reverse
pyramid on yeah that's it
you just be like Tony Vista how do we
get on it we're gonna have to build some
like mega stairs going into the front of
it ooh
so how about we like leading from this
pathway we have stairs oh it's one thing
yeah but we can we can change we can
make it more Center we Center this and
then we have like badass like Imperial
steps going all the way yes and then we
hollow out some of the middle of it and
then go up into the middle and inside
we'll have a bunch of parrots and a
jukebox and they will be a priority yeah
take a little long there I'm so bored
that I just didn't fully grasp the full
concept of it uh-huh yeah all right I
got blue screen again from playing
Minecraft this is the fourth time we
could make a piston door we can keep the
symmetrical shape of the
you can still have an interest coming
from the bottom ooh yeah like that this
became our new mine I like that build
this whole entrance thing this is just
for now this is just to steal rock I see
the other one is ceremonial we borrow
from earth too late nom nom nom so what
if we burn down village build our house
the only thing that will be just to be a
temple of fire spit out flames
we brought fire to your village I'm just
happy that we're doing something that
doesn't have all you dying
that just doesn't involve us talking in
a Swedish accent foreign oh I remember
back in the day when I did like the
montages right yeah what I was trying to
create those moment as much as possible
like I went always having that in mind
just because oh yeah got it okay if I
exaggerate a little extra head then
perfect for the mountains later when we
completed it everyone be like how you
built that you must have used created my
meatball people say that about my castle
it was even saying as well like oh I
built it using creative I mean survival
because I tripped myself up thinking
about creating so much whatever was
gonna be like he did it he said it
exposed draw alert I want to see this
from our other spawn I'll be able to see
it from space
Chinese wall and upside and peering me
they're having a party might a few yeah
we're doing last time okay break it up
you guys break it up go home actually
work I refers to go polish touch people
in a party 2009 their outfits look like
Dutchman's I guess so right mix up touch
and where's the sound of music recording
Austria that's very different it's the
same country it's gonna say maybe we
should take out the block at the very
bottom so it's a floating permanent OSE
are you holding up the pyramid
oh my god it's up of my head jack big
brain my brain
how do you get in now is how you answer
maybe you could build a water elevator
underneath it
see that's what I wanted you to do now
it looks like it has it pooping pooping
pyramid no it's gone now alright no more
of it
speak no more of this and then when it's
done we steal the bell and we put it on
top of her so that we can just burn and
we snipe all the villagers what are you
gonna keep see pictures of you with
peepee poo-poo written all over I feel
like I don't even need to watch your
series at this point everyone else will
just give me all the information
baby boom that's all you need to know
see you good was he a good pig it sound
like you died in the winter fight no not
really
either die PB read a poop no either die
irrelevant or live long enough to play
Mike oh all this I can't help it if
minecraft is legitimately fun I recorded
minecraft today and then we're recording
now and then later on another livestream
minecraft you got to do it been getting
cobblestone are you lost old man
I think he's senile come on follow me is
he down there he's down here but don't
worry I save you it's too dark I can
barely see him get out where's the
entrance if you're not out in 10 seconds
I kill ya to be to war swore it's always
that thing you never know what you're
gonna build in Minecraft and then
suddenly personally genius stroke of
genius I think I have one of your access
by the way I did realize so good man
sure he's caring sharing is caring and
building is the best part of Minecraft
oh yeah dude likes it haha surprise
second stack
who are you surprising myself hey has it
been windy for you in Brighton yeah yeah
it's wild I I got those like rent-a-bike
things uh-huh and I went to sharpen them
and then the freaking wind like keeps
blowing the bike sideways as I'm going
down destroy
see I was gonna go with the pedalboard
and then I looked at the weather and
this is like yellow warnings not that
bad and then just a storm hit and I'm
like okay this is the wind stops I've
been waiting ok so we have one standard
in the middle here oh you should make
for everything has to be symmetric yeah
I like it though it's very pleasing to
the eye okay anymore so peasants you're
all a bunch of fools poor a basket no
glory
there's not even any like subtlety to it
anymore it's just poor weak small break
me big top of Egypt so how do you get
out of it pyramid and how do you guide
it that's something we figure out later
you pick up the trace hello did they
they they invent how to extinguish fire
first before you mending fire I don't
think so alright I never thought of that
you're just blowing my mind right yeah
probably the demise of humanity it's the
fact that we always invent stuff before
we figure out how to put it out
yeah the safety measure comes second
yeah destroy first rebuild second I'm a
fool jump to trees stay with the
peasants oh I saw you jump that was
happening they're having a pool party
stop stop go back to ring it up stop
break it up back to work build our Tower
yeah help build the tower build our
tower is an affront to God I feel like
we have to take down one of their houses
if we look at that house it looks better
without their houses I'm gonna destroy
the ones around the tower should we blow
it up do we still have that TNT on you
use it to drink kill me what you never
played super simulator
oh no the Golem stood in the fire what
are you doing idiot what happened he
stood in the campfire and almost died
he's and though he's walking to me like
Oh died
I feel bad now I go slowly did they heal
themselves or I don't know this it looks
pretty cool but I think I should double
up the stairs or triple in the
excessiveness is happening but you spent
a long time building your house
yesterday yeah you get that a trip like
I have to finish this no matter what
matter you put something in one place
it's like I wonder what that look better
it's like oh my god it looks way better
I have to change it all now yeah that's
what I'm doing that I feel like doing
bro it has to be done bro see that looks
better
oh how should we lit it we got to make
sure we lit it symmetrically as well for
now I'll just put stuff in the corner oh
that yeah that's one in each corner
onions level mm-hmm yeah good
you think both Smith will be in this
rewind he's in the new rewind yeah yeah
this is him reacting to him going yeah
yeah that would actually be pretty good
double yeah good self awareness on
YouTube spurt maybe we should put beds
in the ground outside of it so we jumped
YouTube is watching right now what write
that down write that down write that
down
sorry what we think I'm saying we should
jump off the tower into beds oh oh yeah
we can do that oh they're shooting how
they killed our Angolan today yeah means
I can grab his iron that probably means
we sleep sleep sleep I'm going to make
it I have to make it to this house we
still have to figure out how to get in
that's tomorrow's problem tomorrow's
prob
tomorrow's Shawn and Felix today is just
big brain ideas yeah we invented before
we figure out the countermeasure exactly
to err is human
and also arrogance and all other bad
traits do you think a dog has ego no
just human I just realize this is gonna
sound very big brain the more we build
then more we need where are you you must
have so much yes but yet the more we
build every layer requires however a
number of mass of block more yeah could
I have some because I don't have any
thank you I worked hard for this
all right all right I respect it just
let me just I want you to know I respect
you dizzy boom do we not have enough I
don't need to regret it now
dude we should put a campfire in the
middle and smoke will come out of it it
looks so good
how do you make a campfire I keep
forgetting you need like there's one on
the ground just steal that one yeah but
it it becomes charcoal and when you take
it oh you need cam tax you need a flint
in the middle so oh it's his coal oh
cool Oh to the mines it's called right
there next to it to the left rock wall
with tons of coal in it oh my god I
could just jump to this area up here now
and jump to tree break my ankles morning
jack I always die in this game okay so
if I put the campfire you heat yeah I
just love how this thing is in every
shot of anything I'm doing gigantic it's
beautiful we should name it to Burt our
to bird tower wait does the smoke
actually come out I don't know is it I
can't see the top no oh a hole here Oh
more puppies did you dog
Oh lots of poofy oh yeah look at this
dang that's awesome
smoking kills Felix kills the YouTuber
just don't jump down at the hole don't
jump that way home oh yeah we diabete
them there wait what if we smoke signals
oh okay gamers my craft is the best game
I got this game check out Porter for
next spy gamers by gamers remember
pyramid remember pyramid think of it
when you sleep at night
the power of the pyramid well you
haven't tried to Bruce emulator citizen
e after 50 million outros flash
oh yeah nah go just go it's still
relevant just download it