hey it's me another video another day
another video
you know how only skin youtuber in Cisco
Oh guys I've been making videos for
three years every single day boohoo hey
every single day I don't take breaks
is it even eight years how long have I
been doing this mother flippin nine
years let's begin the why everyone's
favorite show
leave your entry in already closed I am
honored to be Army General of the nine
year old army and I'm ready to host meme
review I am blue shirt kid well anyway I
think it's safe to say that anyone that
gets a hundred thousand uploads will
automatically get to host a meme review
blue shirt kid put on your finest blue
shirt because it is time to host meme
review meme review with such hostess
Elon Musk and blue shirt
I mean I'm doubt I'll be in touch of
blue shirt kid check out your DMS never
forgotten blue shirt kid I am also on
the side of PewDiePie because I don't
like t-series personally so he found me
in a bad mood I can just watch him to
feel better so hold something sweet that
was such a great video I really enjoyed
that
not the hero we deserve but the hero we
need Captain Marcia everyone damn an
actual superhero with not the flat ass
am i right path sexually of you now I
would normally pick on people's
appearance but I don't like brie Larson
asked me anything
I'll be answering it on my youtube
channel alright blue shirt kid relax
you're getting meme review and that's
final alright where did you buy the blue
shirt that's what I want to know I like
how this guy just got like instant
internet fame could you lend me the blue
shirt lawful good neutral good chaotic
good cluttering this is actually very
accurate they did a good job getting all
kinds of people yeah
my god is my whole dreaded taking over
my blue shirt kid animate Netflix had it
tasted incredible what about the manga
did you know that the bones in your
fingers are shaped like penises
of course why else do you think I eat G
fuel with my fingers
cuz I'm gay I'm gay son I like dick if
you can't figure out the name of a song
just upload a video of you singing it to
YouTube and they'll copyright it oh my
god
modern problems require modern solutions
I'm pretty sure this would work someone
should try this my final attempt at
posting here spend two months making it
I just want Puetz to see it now this guy
went all out
it's another beautify anime
well goddamn
look nice holy Sh
damn what's that a double men crybaby
reference
dad yeah that's also the fact if we do
like animation it should I should voice
acting Swedish hey call me and ah yes
guitar down a little back just DISA
thought pigs your sampling rate is set
to 420 I fail to see any problem with
that that's the problem with the
Whittier quality of your camera should
be able to change it to anywhere in the
settings well goddamn Oh
turns out it's stuck on 420 listen I'd
really try my best
Oh to fix the quality but this is pretty
much IMAX cinema quality so I think you
guys should be satisfied with the
quality of this video no stop
to celebrate International Women's Day
tag the women creators who inspired you
Gloria Borger that is so nice
I really appreciate that Thank You
rollick that's gonna make her day that's
for sure this is my second fan art this
week why are you crying it's awesome
thank you very much what is this an app
good 12 + 12 + to download the app I do
know that someone made a website I think
it's like pew news yeah look penis dorks
it looks legit about hosts look at all
these hosts Michelle Obama hahahaha so
they have all the topics we discussed
that's funny
leave it write it down as well holy
someone spending work well done he needs
to host me review nobody
pity pi sub reddit basically the new
king do I even need to be here every
month you guys pick someone else that
you prefer I get it okay everyone money
is hard to get and should only be spent
on necessary stuff mr. Bies what the
kiss had even supposed to me I still
understand where mrs. B's get all these
money from drug cartel please tell us
mr. piece I want to know pity pie in you
laugh you lose hey look it's t-shirt kid
again when your kid asks you why there
are twerking videos recommended to you
okay first of all because of the
algorithms it's good meat that's a good
meme right there
Felix laugh at our memes but never up
but sometimes I do okay
I'm just not logged in all right crime
or shut up spider-man your face I made a
huge toy with oh my god oh yeah what I
fix it what chair launching whoa that's
incredible guys check out lost in the
fold I link in the description only 135
subscribers I pause the 55 minute while
my YouTube was lagging big mistake oh my
god he's taking over me was just charged
hey broach on May 31st we should
celebrate bride's birthday for his hard
work editing dude's videos now hold on
just a second here this is a track I've
known Brad for I don't know how many
years now and every year I try and
figure out when his birthday is because
he will never say it I know more or less
the timeframe because his mom just
appears out of nowhere and Brad just
goes yeah my mom is here sorry and I'm
just like why is your mom here hmm
oh it's birthday time but Brad will not
tell anyone when it's his birthday
how did you figure this out it's this
posted by secret fry this is a trap how
did this random reddit person know
birthday nice try Brad and I returned to
the dungeon from when's pewds keep you
that's right bread nice try there's five
minutes before mrs. Gloria hoga no oh my
god me telling my friend why my meme
with 1.8 thousand our folks didn't get
into the why okay first of all because a
brad petition for blue shirt kid to
become CEO of the YouTube Jesus correct
oh my god when your friends ask you why
you only have four subscribers okay
first of all because of the YouTube
algorithm kids are dumb and changed my
mind
I changed my MA my god med Puetz in
iceland used his camera
- that is not my camera then - you're
facing tab better-quality
yeah what's out he lives in it this is
Bali yeah when your parents ask you why
there's hentai on your recommended okay
first of all because of the YouTube
algorithm
I just noticed it's been lasagna all
along that's right everyone oh my gosh I
didn't see the GQ I was like oh yeah
it's another one of these
Oh G fuel ten out of ten very nice why
you push the ad just drink G fuel
pathetic for legal disclaimer please do
drink the G fuel and don't inhale it or
any other ways to eat it
thank you now I will continue my habits
pewds i'm 1.8 meters also pues bullying
you were the chosen one you were
supposed to destroy TV series not carpet
strikers dr. Phil to the range okay
let's get this done
Sony TV now it has been three days and
all my dr. Phil videos are still claimed
except the ones I private 'add thank God
now I expect Sony TV to remove these
times immediately or else I'm gonna drop
a diss track on you Sony
you've seen what happened to T's series
their company is never going to recover
you don't want to make this enemy
sony/atv remove their claims immediately
damn to new milestones we hit 89 million
subscribers and lasagna it's my most
viewed video in incredible I remember I
have to skip an upload to work on
visuals on am like oh god I missed one
upload this is terrible I think it paid
off I'm so proud I can't believe this
channel is still peaking after nine
years it's crazy thank you guys so much
for all the support it genuinely means
so much to me smash like and I see you
guys in the bye bye tuber simulator it's
now so relevant that it's got a brand
new mini game
crania brought the crane and get fresh
items only available in the washing
machine like game and you say there's
more of course there is new knowledge
perks new quests and new pixel inks and
legs guys like
you