what's up everyone its main review time
and you know what that means it's time
for some below average entertainment but
first oh I forgot contact lenses and now
I look like my papi that's better
let's get into the freaking games let's
just get into it
next meme let's get a really good meme
in here let's get a really good one
hamburger and hand hand hand hand hand
burger hamburger is a meme now everyone
it's finally happened congratulation to
everyone that invested in the hamburger
fast-food stock market it's finally pay
off time cuz hamburger is a meme
hamburger I'm going to McDonald's do you
want it handled that relatable moment
where you're part of the Avengers and
Thor ask I'm going to McDonald's do you
want and a hamburger so it's like if you
can relate to this video right freaking
now what flavor you ask hamburger this
originated from youtube poop who had
sonic saying hamburger Thank You YouTube
food hamburger my god will this
reference be seen in the sonic film it
remains to be seen it good sentence
Felix thank you hamburger so why is
everyone saying hamburger is everyone
just freaking lost their minds
what is the Frick is happening
millennial humor is so weird what if you
wanted to go to heaven but God said
hamburger I think this is another
existential question that we've all
asked ourselves at one point or another
I mean what would you do
literally what would you do I don't know
what I would do I would just say
hamburgers well probably and hope for
the best
hamburger
is that a hamburger hamburger what has
happened we used to have you gone the
knuckles god dammit why the Frick is
hamburger a meme it's not even that
funny of them food I can name at least
five at the top of my head
chicken tikka masala what the Frick kind
of name is that shirt Buller oh wow
sounds way funnier
I love hamburger say it Yoda oh my god
who's gonna say it and it's African I'm
South African I know accent though cuz I
was raised here handbook these
compilations completely ruin the joke
because you know exactly what they're
gonna say at least if you're scrolling
through Instagram or whatever you don't
know exactly what meme it's gonna be but
you want you sit through a compilation
and it's like they I'm just waiting for
them to say hamburger
hamburger hamburger you know if it
didn't say hamburger then I would laugh
all right you need to surprise me at
least goddamnit Felix why are you so
salty night huh are you being such a
hamburger because I want to goddamn it
and you can't stop me you see what I
mean you know what enough for this I'll
show you some good memes nobody fish in
a grocery store now that's funny
come on oh you oh I'm sorry one more
hamburger compilation memes sorry
alright sure do you want hamburger
company
okay that one was good I did like that
one okay sorry hamburger I take
everything back you're so funny
I love you so much like this this is a
funny meme he's holding it with his has
cheeks
he's dummy thick all right guys serious
question time no more jokes no more
playing around serious question time
okay you're ready to answer question you
have three seconds to answer alright you
get either 500 euro but you have to
delete your Facebook account forever I
absolutely will I'll take it easy next
one okay okay I realized that one was a
little bit easy how about this one you
are very attractive to the opposite sex
but you are also very attracted to the
same sex and your skin is green
[Music]
food for thought okay all right I
realize these are a little bit easy
questions I got the better one for you
coming right up you only get two seconds
fans through this one you die all right
you die but but fortnight dice - oh god
damn it is so easy just kill me
you have one second to answer this one
all right Instagram dies but reddit is
always in light mode no freaking dude
Luke my ice will die these are so she
can I get one funny thing meme this week
Jesus Christ all right here we go
bowling alley memes you heard about
these you're heard about bowling alley
means remember you were bowling as a kid
in the animation what we may more fun
than the actual game nobody the bowling
alley screen when you get a strike
nobody bowling alley TVs win again this
is a good me thank Lord thanks Lord
Almighty
nobody did bowling alleys came in
defense legit I would have more fun
looking at the goddamn screen than
playing bowling who likes bowling anyway
alright let's get another good meme in
here dank memes kills memes faster than
PewDiePie what that's break ice what
that better you think you're a sunny
with your little jokes you're not funny
you're gay and I mean that in the best
way possible
brofist if you're gay to the screen at
the bowling alley
you can test right I cannot I don't know
about you guys but I kinda wanna go
bowling now I kind of bowling yes that's
smash like if this is completely
freaking accurate when you're an
animator who gets hired by falling alley
I'm gonna make some weird freakin [ __ ]
who made these that's a good point
actually if you're a bowling alley 3d
model design creator hit me up in the
comments with the likes just so I know
if you're there
nobody bowling alley screen may get a
strike
that relatable moment even this joke the
novelty wears off pretty quickly doesn't
it nobody the bowling alley screen when
you get a strike sweet dreams are made
of these good mine to piss on me a chase
of lyrics just so they can't copy strike
it it's fine it's called innovation
learn what it is UMG
the bowling alley screen when you get a
strike
click loop and then play there to hit
this is humor
all right you stupid Millennials you
stinky Millennials we their silly dummy
dumb humor
this is humor right I don't care about
your obscure and burger all right what
do we got
damn all right did we get to see the
strike there it is man
that's it ten out of ten we'll play
bowling never again light-skinned Monta
posted this clip on Instagram oh all
right the rat right hood Edwards when
they see a ranked I think we can all
relate
[Music]
what's he gonna do now I take everything
back
goddamnit oh damn eight Oh No and
they'll stop hand boo boo stop the
goddamn hamburgers handle you want to
see another hamburger meaning my goddamn
life oh hey is it gonna mine it is gonna
dare ahead hey come on
some of these are good I'll have it to
you guys your little editors with your
little Ann deeds you think you're so
good Oh a very sexy man that Ricardo
okay that's good
absolutely this has been the last meme
review ever I'm sorry I forgot to tell
you guys but it's over I'm Mary ham and
I'm just canceling all the shows I'm
sick of it I want none of it anymore and
I see you never again fine
what you never played super simulator
you know it's fun right I'm not supposed
to give my opinion but give it a try and
then you can tell me if it's good or not
not convinced yet okay I'll cut you a
deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]