minecraft means you love them I love
them let's watch them yeah watch till
the end of the video for a surprise now
that I'm a Minecraft channel I can
finally understand
minecraft memes so I asked you guys on
Twitter send me your best minecraft
memes let's see if we can make a scout
that today welcome to minecraft edition
ok he's found diamonds
what is the twist a creeper don't dig
down Hey look nothing uh stop stop
he's gonna jump in isn't he okay that
was a rollercoaster they had us in the
first half not gonna like I think they
had me in every half I never felt so
literally trolled smash like if you got
epically troll that funny but at the
same time it was the first time we saw
creep up I mean a zombie in a minecart
it was funny damn Mike I've looked
different back then we call the Sun is
every didn't there get the fraps this
has to be documented no one's ever done
this no he's gonna die at it these are
always so good this is my video game
minecraft veteran you know that you can
jump off a high point in place of water
right before you're only pros can do it
take any fall damage ash such welcomed
through the life of an idiot I can laugh
at my own jokes cuz I don't remember
them the mental lag is brutal
that's the sad thing I was actually
trying can't wait for Minecraft in 4k
damn knotch come on you just make it
happen since I play Minecraft now I get
this joke because it's not actually
Minecraft it's Spyro
don't miss another minecraft set Lionel
bring it to me
[Applause]
he had no loot are you kidding me
I don't believe they see I understand
these joke now it's the eye of Ensor I
get it I get it I'm part of you guys I
understand the job so that funny but I
get it
see now I can truly appreciate this
cursed image now that I play Minecraft
please kill it
what do you think I don't like what are
sheep let's get real here please stop it
I don't want to see your curse imagery
stop it no don't do that your pee-pee
poopoo creeper oh man how did that even
happen
damn creepers of Nashville's damn proud
of himself for making tons of gamers
suffer SM edge I appreciate that
minecraft air pods as well I think this
is more of a meme that I'm I can truly
appreciate it it's like wine I don't go
wow this one tastes good it's more like
that's good I like that I like this me
[Music]
[Laughter]
since Petey pyres now become a Minecraft
youtuber I felt it was finally time to
become a Minecraft editor this is now a
Minecraft page from now on smash like on
that one thank you very cool just don't
mind straight down no oh my god
I guess trolls epically oh okay that was
good
fine that was good brother lock is just
great dude got my freshly enchanted
diamond tools and um my eyes are going
black on the surface hey every time
ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba only true
gamers can understand this moment only
true gamers can understand I understand
like now that I play Minecraft I
understand the pain that this man is
about to get inflicted upon himself No
don't you just go this way yeah even the
trees in the background
Oh force mad it's not hey that's alike I
like that one that was good
what can I say sometimes you guys have
good memes all right next one 7777 peace
out sucker
god I'm 77 he's not sucker that's good
like half of the Minecraft memes is just
falling or a creepers only true
minecraft gamers can understand me hits
Pigman by accident all Pigman in nether
buenas Dias this is like the only thing
I haven't messed up yet in Minecraft I'm
pretty sure I just jinx myself
yeah I drinks myself it's gonna happen
normally I'm like Oh Pigman I should
attack them minecraft big brain I'm not
gonna cool Felix good you want to tell
us any more pointless information next
game oh god not Sven memes I can't
handle it okay that's all that guy I got
this is sad little late I feel that you
laugh you sad
Hey Dolan got one it's all items you
just have to take a risk
[Music]
it's a good mean I have seen it already
I'm sorry darlin come in the side dock
son but like before I got it but now I
truly understand like I bet she thought
she jumped into lava or something like
crazy water Shh
the quality is so bad I can't see what
is that she closes it order very nice
house water she I knew it he's invading
other people's world in dark souls
that's funny oh I see this skills around
the corner don't go down that's amazing
10 out of 10 smash like and subscribe I
know we're in like it's clearly people
reposing other people's content whatever
it's never stopped me before
the Wi-Fi password is on the back of the
router the back of the router yeah why
do they always make it so freakin
encrypted so that's the language of the
enchantments okay see I get it now this
is a minecraft mean I get it I don't buy
you guys but I get it smash like of you
and subscribe and buy the merch if you
get it I am wearing them out it's just a
little chilly today okay just myth just
to make sure just to make sure kpop fans
be like oh my god which was why does
villagers exist and why did they give me
nightmares
I developed an AR app from your
microwaves and put it on the Brighton
Beach what the actual free curry oh my
god is the pier that was literally there
yesterday I didn't see it
what oh my god they're entering what can
you guys imagine why is the Swedish flag
not working
that is weird
what their sheep gets the revenge of
Kitty plank yeah that's creepy no not
the balance I got ya I can't believe
everyone has my freaking world no my
Diamont
what song is that oh my god it was this
literally foreshadowing for after Jack
Black does this mean Jack Black is water
sheep stop it so then do something worst
guard dog oh listen PC etiquette stop
don't don't you dare touch IKEA tower no
delete this right now grande what is
this what flag is that no too far too
far water ship is Norwegian it all makes
sense now
no don't touch that
[Laughter]
brah brah I'm shaking not y'all yet he's
already suffered it up it even has my
freaking contraption dude how not cool
man
not cool guys I fix Australia ding their
boat I get it that huh
thanks guys I finally understand the me
thank you very much thank you so much it
took a while but I finally got there
only gamers know the real struggle and
sacrifice when you're suffering from
success that's a decent mean I gave a
chuckle I'm still I still got my health
bar though I we're still doing that no
it's minecraft ok how do i how do i tame
a parrot
hey look it's me again come on how did
he live through that oh my god oh my god
[Music]
ten out of ten editing what's your name
is beautiful
oh he ate the compass so Marty McFly
Williams F's in the chat for Marty McFly
Williams boys good night girl I see you
tomorrow
good night girl I see you tomorrow
I get it because you're not supposed to
just go in the end reporter I get it 90%
bug free 10% of bugs good mean I get it
if I didn't play my crime probably would
not understand why sister think I'm very
confused but it also made me laugh and I
don't know why hey look it's me
immersive Asian maybe edition question
mark in the future of course Grande this
video is not for the faint-hearted well
the last one was painful enough okay
let's watch it stop stop
Oh God
hey at least you got ha ha ha okay sure
what else could he possibly do to annoy
me is that obsidian yet okay great
I feel like the Hakeem starts screaming
meme saw that play hates now I truly
know what keemstar was screaming about
well playing my track oh my gosh you
can't melt obsidian crinch what now get
biscuit nugget in a biscuit Hey look
what I didn't know that worked what can
you possibly do with redstone
[Music]
of course how was that even possible
that made no sense guys see I played
mine crab and I can I can honestly tell
you guys this makes no sense
you can't just summon the wither he's
from call of duty black ops everyone
knows that stop using my world how did
this happen
get out gosh damn it
don't touch the vein don't touch don't
you dare okay good good damn it my mom
my dad see there it is there's a
screaming team sir he lives in all of us
see everyone loves minecraft it brings
people together it makes you have a good
time and not worry about all that petty
BS look at that if they can get a long
before cap minecraft then we all can
thank you so much for watching this
episode smash like subscribe by the
merch which I am wearing and I see you
guys next time bye what you never played
to purr simulator you know it's fun
right I'm not supposed to give my
opinion but give it a try and then you
can tell me if it's good or not
convinced yet okay I'll cut you a deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]