[Music]
welcome everyone to Scot the new further
adieu
the rule is I think I ran out of intros
I don't know now let's just jump into it
that's right case that's what we do for
here on this channel has T series foetus
yes first of all round of applause I
thought it was the end game last week
but we're still in it and we're still
kicking it now I'm a day ahead now just
a day ahead so it would be very awkward
while I make this video very happy and
very cheerful and then somehow he series
is passed out of nowhere I mean they're
they're calling in the cavalry and all
cancer all these Indian celebrities
going hey I'm not paid to do this and
I'm not paid to say this but subscribe
to t-series oh and there's definitely
not a gun to my head but subscribe to
t-series look at this you can make India
win
I don't care they're calling the Indian
celebrities pathetic ok
I barely relied on help from anyone now
there's got a little sidetrack we're
supposed to laugh at means but yeah ok
let's just jump into it ok warning guys
warning Captain Marvel spoilers coming
right up if you have it recorded record
I've never seen so many people being
pissed off about me rating a meme 10 out
of 10
it is the meme that keeps giving I
absolutely love it Ricardo lives forever
Ricardo immortal the immortal son of the
immortal God
Ricardo his name will echo ins for
centuries and above next meme this is
getting weird we have already shown this
but it's a Ricardo take my heart you got
a legit put a bar here like anything
with Ricardo gets to monetize if you
show his dong so I apologize for that by
the way that was a note for my editor
but you deserve to know she's answering
f finger no but she's effing answering
the phones at Walmart no I don't work
here but the phone's ringing and ringing
and I know how it feels to be on that
other end and nobody answers that's
kinda sweet I like that Walmart we need
to find whoever's responsible when you
definitely heard a noise in your house
but you're too afraid to turn around and
flip did turn any sad day to a happy one
look at that dog it's absolutely
terrified okay I feel like that could be
mean here's I feel bad for this
eight-year-old Poland brother he doesn't
deserve this ridicule that will follow
him for the rest of his life I just
realized I haven't had the green screen
film what the hell is this oh my god
very nice moving on have you lost the
challenge oh my god I haven't even been
paying attention to my health bar this
looks like I'm fine I'm you order your
GP oh by the way edge of the code
pewdiepie to get 10% off pretty good
deal moving on no you stupid he's not
mad it's not mad if it was mad you know
he would have won that's right well you
never looked at your own face just the
ultimate me where this would have been
if we pulled out a mirror yes sir just a
little feedback for the future
moving on looks like we're off to the
west coast to find some more leaks Phil
what are you doing in Minecraft sweat
fair Swift damn bill is living the high
life did you guys see this flex seal did
their farm sub - PewDiePie Phil swift
declares that in order to assist PT pi
he will saw T Series in half
Thank You Phil Smith very cool oh my god
I don't know about that one not a Scot
the for me at least I'm sorry try next
time maybe but it turns out I am
undefeated in this challenge obscure the
duel already
I just can't lose it's crazy peopIe
versus two series ahead the check
whole milk
saku-dono car years and you cannot deal
on it's costly to couldn't okok goddamn
right cuz konoka to no boots no mr. Lee
what is t7 technical boy come on Subin
[Music]
oh my god holy [ __ ]
oh my god absolutely beautiful and that
makes everything worth it that's
hilarious
god damn it how do I look like okay okay
Selena Gomez okay I mean both human good
joke critics thank you next meme
everyone check culture to another let's
see this wave son this is crazy
oh good memes man we had some good laps
today don't we we have to do something
god damn it oh god I say kids don't have
God are they gonna add another layer now
this is the kind of real enthusiasm when
I asked for a broker just kidding
you broke your screen for nothing how is
your screen not broken yet
pounded real for once final give me your
orders broke fit ah ah damn that fit
good I'll buy a new monitor sirrah I'm
sorry into the mouth no that was
beautiful I want to hear that again into
the mouth nice this is great
it just makes me smile good thing this
isn't try not to smile allenge
what does he see Ricardo Ricardo I love
him
a spirit home I see home god damn what's
with the Swedish crossover under Ricardo
memes like botton on and then now they
played by obviously I have we can't show
the autofit it weirds me out a little
bit that's it for me for now hope you
guys enjoyed this episode smash like
subscribe and it always this is not the
real merch guys this is not the merch
you have to buy this is the merch
I know it's a bit disappointing compared
to but okay this is the new Burch check
in a hug and I see you guys borrow a
bike what trooper simulators becoming
relevant no no don't leave no please
sponsor eagle please do something yes
this game is still relevant
god dammit
[Music]