everyone knows movie theater food is so
expensive one skittles
what why we're gonna show you how to
sneak candy and snacks into the movies
without being caught but here's the
twist
this is not your normal movie theater
security and each theater is equipped
with the most insane security checkpoint
that we're gonna have to try to get
through without being caught and by the
end of the video whoever has the most
amount of candy confiscated they will be
ejected from the fever
literally the first feeder you're
sneaking candy into is protected by a
vicious guard dog and i want to sneak in
as much candy as possible in these
skittles here
you're the worst at opening bags to
sneak by candy and i have a genius way
of getting it inside these stuffed
animals what i've got a way better way
to sneak it in devin i've got
oh bella are you kidding exactly so
belle you want to tell them our master
plan of how we're going to sneak you
down
all right so i'm going to pretend that i
have a baby bump because i hear dogs are
very protective of pregnant women
back it up literally i'm going to have a
booty that's voluptuous
what yeah i'm going to waddle right in
there man dog won't even look he'll
sniff sniff
nothing to see here just a sweet booty
you guys are insane that's
never gonna work but this is definitely
gonna work so first we gotta find the
perfect pregnancy belly for bella here
so i think that was a nice shape and to
all the stuffed animal lovers out there
i'm sorry
i actually needed to stay attached a
little bit but this is perfect not to
one up you devin but it's all the
basketball lovers out there yeah i am
sorry
let's go all right here we go
oh my goodness i don't feel too good
right now
i'm not as strong as i once was getting
a little like bomb
there we go it's now storm breaker mode
so here we go three
two one two there we go that's what i'm
talking about so bella we are now
in business come on over oh wow okay
thanks let's see will that work
hey there yeah i mean for a basketball
it's relatively convincing so for mine i
just have to remove some of the stuffing
so i can fit a ton of candy into here
all right we've lined the inside of the
basketball with a whole bunch of rice
krispies treats that way the dog will
not be able to smell all the other candy
how's the tiger going though it's going
great so now that i have it empty it's
time to fill it up with candy all right
well the next thing i got to figure out
is my booty
and more importantly what i'm gonna put
as my booty implants we'll try and
cantaloupe and this little thing it
gives me a little bit uneven but hey
it's nature
that's gonna go down your pants bro i
don't think so man i think i can get it
or here we go boom
haters gonna hate i think i'm a hater on
this one how does it look
could that pass no no no no no
oh no all right guys i'm gonna go for
the global booty right here so i think
that this would be better
intergalactic right here i feel wrong
having to open the globe up this way
knowing where it's about to be but
it just gotta go there we go i feel like
this is one of the best halloween bags
ever so
what are you doing there's a hole in my
booty all right
i'm done i can't do this anymore so well
it's been a pleasure
what is so well you mean farewell i'm
confused
all right but you know what though i
don't want to see candy until i'm back
sorry
welcome back the quantity of candy i am
putting in this thing
is insane i've already used half of my
table over here all right bella i'm
gonna try to take that belly to you so
if you want to put it on for a second do
it really fast yep three
oh snap that was good okay here we go
this is the worst painting i got you
guys okay there we go
this is so hard i don't want to get it
running out of tape i think i'm not
doing much to help this at all even
though this is like my diy oh my arms
stuck all right
part of my diy here we go okay my arm is
stuck
all right well you know i think we
should find a better way of securing it
right now let's go try to sneak into the
first movie theater this isn't
convincing
yeah this isn't gonna work bro we'll
clean it up the first thing we're
sneaking candy into is protected by a
vicious guard dog it's time to sneak
into the theater all right we were here
to see
what do you mean
sir i'm gonna start with you okay all
right yeah start okay tank's gonna have
to sniff these stuffed animals okay
why well why is there so many dude what
are you doing why i got somebody's
stuffed animals going to a little movie
man what do you mean it's not a little
movie it's a scary movie
i see i i'm with you on this one i think
this is super suspicious
he's gonna have to check those out for
all right we're gonna want to take a
step back
i'm looking at you i'm looking dead in
your eyes you might have candy in his
eyes
sir good job he's gonna have to sniff
these stuffed animals
okay oh jesus oh okay then all right
he's
oh
so what are you expecting three weeks
three weeks she's
uh how many months 18. 18 months
pregnant this wow
fully developed brain is going to be
next level algebra out the gate
if she can just go into the movies would
be great thank you so much
a little funny could you take a little
turn around and do it slow for me all
right well let's just uh
do a little turn just a little wow oh
stop stop
right here that doesn't look natural
that's what you call 15 squats a minute
man
i think he needs to sniff your butt my
dude i'm just i'm with my body
this can't be theater appropriate this
is outrageous
this is outrageous yo give this video a
thumbs up if you also think that this
no more questions thank you very much
bye tank all right cool let's
hop inside thank you hey we were able to
sneak the candy in theater number one
but sneaking into theater number two is
gonna be way harder because it's guarded
by the candy crushing car wash it's a
spinning nightmare designed to dislodge
the candy and send it flying so right
now try to get devin and hide our candy
for the next theater we're going to try
to sneak in as
many gummy bears as we possibly can and
the strategy on this one is to hide them
in plain sight so i'm going to make arms
and legs out of gums i'm going to make
gummy clothing so right now we're going
to cut a little hole in the inside so i
got to get this over my head all right
so i filled this
hand with some gummies trying to remove
the plastic hand from it
here we go here's the hole let's see if
we just try to this is so hard dude
trying to fit through this thing here we
go okay yeah all right here we go i'm in
okay
yeah oh hey here we go first part of the
gummy shirt is not what that doesn't
look very convincing i mean this doesn't
look like
like a shirt like fashion oh it's almost
yeah
oh dude why is it so floppy
i feel violated all right so i got the
gummy hand now it's time for the gummy
leg all right did you do that time for
me to put over here we got oh whoa
so i got this tube that's filled with
gummy and then i'm going to fill this
with some candies now time to draw the
logo here we go get out of here
boom that's one g oh oh that actually
kind of worked fly
you literally almost hit me it's a
little bit dirty but it works look at
this
he's a floppy man yeah there has no
bones
why do you do this to me every time add
them comment down below such like
not nice things all right don't comment
down below a floppy man he's
he's not a floppy man all right time to
pack this in with some candy so it's not
a floppy leg can you not do that like
directly in my ear do you like it as
much as his hands
no you should slap me with it every time
you have them comment down below
something that's not
super nice i get to slap you with this
hand devin is the most
wonderful brother of all time who
doesn't hold me hostage he's
amazing i don't like that hand do you
know this i'll put it back okay for now
all right so my gummy shirt is almost
done once i'm done filling up this leg
i'll have one gummy leg some gummy shoes
and one gummy arm yep and then it's time
to see if we can sneak through the candy
crushing car wash dude this shirt is so
sticky there's no one around this car
all right wait wait wait right there
boys what i'll be taking care of things
here from now on oh
my name's rico and i have a perfect
candy contraband record that's not about
to change today
what even is this oh this is our candy
crushing car wash my friend i brought it
special from flagstaff arizona people
it was handmade by my grandfather but
sir
oh i'm sorry what happened
sir there's an orange footprint for each
of your feet why don't you hop on
okay yep there you go very well done
two feet down now you hold on to the
patented gripper well i'm way too cool
for school so i'm gonna keep my arms
crossed
i would prefer sir if you put both
regular sized and colored hands
on the stick there definitely i'm glad
you pointed that out but
my hand did fall asleep on the way here
that's why it's blue oh wrapping them
together that wakes them up
i'm sorry it hurts too much do you want
me to do no no no no no no no i'm good
he's clapping together no what do i do
all right no no it's already working
it's magic
see this is what we call a centrifugal
force discombobulator
you have to disorient
you're supposed to do that that means
you're done i'm done
thank you wait a minute
we know where he's at his whereabouts
are known
you broke it how can i it's not broken
it's performing exactly as it's meant to
sure thing all right i'm just gonna use
this as like a as a gondola thing from
yes yes
i think i'm doing pretty good on this
all right okay that's perfect now
we need you to go through the crusher oh
gosh
no way this seems like a terrible also
from five staff i gotta walk through
these are there we go three
two we've been fighting subscribe
challenge we will see if you can
subscribe to the channel and turn on the
channel post notifications in five
seconds you're ready here we go five
four
three two one done if you're able to do
that comment down below keep your squad
right now and let's go for it all right
here we go three two one oh this is
uncomfortable oh
geez okay it's like tickling but like in
a very kind of painful way okay and i'm
through that
i'm good to go right yes sir apparently
there is no contraband candy to be had
here i hope you enjoy your film see you
later
since the next theater is guarded by a
giant mystery wheel we have no idea what
we're actually up against so we're gonna
have to get creative with the diys
i am gonna make a baby out of candy i
don't even wanna know how that works
nobody is gonna suspect
a cute little baby all right for me i'm
gonna attach candy all over my body to
my arms but the backpack is gonna be lit
so i got my suit here and the first
thing is i have to make the head of the
baby just gonna pour it in here like
this
all right here we go pull the seats bam
there we go
that's what i'm talking about i gotta
say i think your method might be a
little bit better than my method even
though i'm like a full-grown person i
think the baby's actually working out a
lot better so
bro yes i mean they're not gonna suspect
a thing let's suspect a thing and
done all right so the candy arms are all
in place whoa bro look at this
whoa whoa whoa whoa you feel intimidated
no yes actually yes so you're using a
baby i'm using
a backpack i gotta undo my backpack i'm
all right dude i can't bend my elbow get
out of here this baby needs a diaper how
does this work man how does this work
i don't know this is the perfect candy
to put in the diaper cons just look at
this gloriousness
i don't think you're looking bro sorry
about that you're not even paying
attention
what you've covered my entire baby i
don't have dexterity man this is the
perfect candy for the diaper are you
putting up you're not hiding a babe ruth
inside the baby's diaper oh yes i am
dude that's disgusting
can you imagine you're gonna be in the
theater you whip out your baby first of
all next thing you know you whip this
diaper off you'll reach in grab that log
yeah and you eat that long exactly
you're gonna be in jail
look at this dish he looks so
look at his little legs this circulation
is not
happening oh i need to put a face on
this baby too man
what is it called little bro there yeah
a little brother
that's that little bro there you're
gonna be the worst uncle ever ready for
the face reveal come on that's three
two one he is a little bit scary he
looks so disturbing all right guys so
the last thing i gotta do is fill up my
candy backpack put a hoodie on and then
it's time to sneak past whatever the
mystery wheel throws at us dude i am so
excited to see this movie with my baby
girls
hold up there boys to see if you are
clean of any contraband candy spin the
mystery wheel once
whatever it lands on that will be your
test that's that sounds good
all right father man you're gonna have
to give this thing a big spin you ready
here we go three
two one okay there we go
but lucky for you mike here is a six
degree black belt at guard joust
so you're in for quite a while all right
gentlemen
on the pole i didn't think i would ever
hear that in my life but all right so
here we go sir under your shirt is that
a spongebob plushy hyper realistic cake
filled with candy
no copy that standard question take your
weapons thank you
good luck to you sir appreciate it if
candy is dislodged if we discover any of
that you are out of the theater do you
understand i understand and there is no
such candy on me you can guarantee that
sweep the leg i want a clean fight
no funny business find that candy three
two yo we're planning something super
special for you but we need to know
if devin and i created a challenge for
you how excited would you be to play it
comment down below i'm hyped if you want
in
candy fight in three two one fight
michael oh the furious barrage of
probing blows looking for weakness
only getting angry
i'm gonna need you to open that backpack
yeah come on man this is not good
oh no oh no you did it oh hell care yeah
you better run
that guy is unbelievable you're right
yeah he is your turn
can i just like go in you think just
like go right in no one is exempt from
trial your weapons serve thank you
sir right gonna be put your morals aside
this is about candy all right gentlemen
on the pole
candy fight in three two one hold on hi
i know you're not gonna hit it baby
there's no way where you're gonna hit a
baby
i can't believe the baby actually worked
and i won this round the next theater is
gonna be the hardest one yet we'll have
to strike a pose and attempt to fit
through these hilarious cutouts but if
we can't we'll be falling into a painful
bed of legos
sneak candy through the hole in the wall
i'm making a candy filled jacket as well
as a taco hat and i'm making a candy
filled baseball bat and wig i'm gonna be
filling this baseball bat with a whole
bunch of candy so to start i'm gonna
drill a hole in the bottom of it
yeah all right it is all hollowed out
and now it's time to fill it up with
some good candy i just got a jacket i'm
gonna put this
inside the jacket on my shoulders like
this now we can sneak in a whole bunch
of candy without them knowing anything
gonna put a shoulder number one in here
like this
this is great man that's why i want to
get huge shoulders down because if i
want to take a nap you should just take
your neck wherever i want wait a minute
devin what
taco thoughts yeah how are you gonna get
it with a baseball bat that makes no
sense devon with the baseball bat's
gonna look like this he's gonna be
coming in
super sus i hope i don't look like you
right now because you are
definitely getting caught so right now
let's go give it a shot taco tuesday
yeah taco tuesday you represent taco
tuesday
don't do it okay they don't like taco
tubes they don't like it very much yeah
what's gonna happen gentlemen is we're
gonna start pulling this wall
okay we're gonna strike a pose i'm
trying to fit through the hole
can you demonstrate the pose full space
mike
wow i mean that was great that's
incredible i don't need your
transportation
whoever can't make it through that hole
yeah is getting pushed into this pit of
super painful legos
okay let's activate it in three two
one
[Music]
[Applause]
tuesday shame
but thanks trying to sneak candy you
know hey yeah can you believe this guy
check out his shoulder can you just
shoulder i hope you rethink your life
choices where do you think you're going
taco
i don't think
have you seen this one good luck that
was a partner exercise man holy cow mike
or i could definitely make this work on
our own but
if you require assistance no i'm not
saying assistance i'm just saying you
may get it yes
you are not unshamed but you are allowed
to go into assistance
thank you so much no no no okay so so
here we go we gotta stand over here
like that okay all right hold the wall
test commencing in three here we go
ready to go
hold on turn okay what are you doing
what are you doing
oh
what do you think that looks like
popcorn to you that that's a popcorn
that's oh
here it is the final security checkpoint
and this is going to be near impossible
to sneak candy through because it is an
insane obstacle course filled with axes
spike balls and a whole bunch of other
insane things so devin right now let's
go make our final candy sneaking
contraptions the final theater is gonna
be the most difficult one to sneak into
so we're gonna try to sneak in the most
difficult foods for me an entire plate
of nachos and i'm gonna be sneaking in
an ice cream sundae
under this hat devin's got a little
helper in there up
that was me all right so now that the
shenanigans are done i'm going to put my
hat down and this will be the bowl that
i use to sneak in my chocolate sundae
see you're using a hat devin i'm using a
hat right here this is what's going to
hold
all the chips and we're going to put the
cheese and the ties let's scatter some
chips around the exterior here it's a
pretty classy way
of sneaking some chips in as long as my
head doesn't go back when i'm in the
obstacle course we will be good i'm
gonna need a broom
leading calling to the rescue whoa
bro you're about to like foot sweep me
what you call a goal
here that's how you sweep off a mess
watch and learn all right so i got the
chips and next thing i need is some
beans for my nachos popping one of these
in here dude
it's gonna be so delicious in the movie
cleveland how to get a top hat what is
this yellow thing but that's how i'm
gonna put it in the hat so it's not just
on my head oh that would be weird yeah
that one's got a hot noggin so that
would it would melt pretty quickly bro
you're using
pinto beans yeah to be completely honest
i thought i bought refried beans
don't come at me man we're gonna have to
scoop to dupe some pinto beans in dude i
have to wear these
yeah i'm gonna have to wear these shoes
you decided to do oh yeah
go get your bean juice on beans down in
the shoes bro oh my gosh
dude you're gonna smell like a bean it's
gonna be food flavored this is all sorts
of nasty man i'm not looking forward to
this all right so now i'm gonna dump
these crushed up oreos
in here oh yes that's gonna be so
delicious we are on opposite end of the
spectrum here man cause yours looks
amazing and my tie
is soiled with bean juice man the last
thing you need for nachos is cheese
we're gonna use this right over here
we're gonna suck up some cheese
yeah i'm gonna get this whole container
in here all right so here we go we've
got the cheese and then if you can just
hold the tie in place for me for a
second
three two one
that is the sound of delicious food
being prepared so there we go
here we go the wages like sex all right
we've got everything we need to sneak in
the final meal so now let's go tackle
the obstacle course dude my head is so
cold his head is super cold
hello there there's something wrong with
the ceiling yeah
what is this must have a leak in our
tortilla chip line oh yeah
you have a tortilla that's how it works
it's a movie theater of course we have a
tortilla chip oh
yeah have you ever been to a movie
theater all right gentlemen let's set
some ground rules
yes the first thing you're gonna do is
go over or under the hurdles of shades
dude
wire on them what are you guys doing
pointy stingy shave
then you go backwards through the
swinging axes of shame backwards bro we
can't see what we're gonna do
exactly exactly once you clear those you
go through to the wrecking balls
of demolishmation yeah of shame
all right gentlemen are you ready i'm
ready man run the course let's do it
mike man the ball man those balls all
right gentlemen
last time yeah and remember if we see
any candy or snacks
you're out here you're not gonna see
anything by me all right three here
two one go for one oh
my god i'm gonna decide to go under i
think
oh yeah
it's coming from somewhere all right so
i gotta make it over this one here okay
there we go boom
all right hey welcome hey do this bros
right here
it this does not pass regulations this
could not be saved
you guys even work here
[Music]
bro i knew it since devin lost it is
finally time to eject him from the
theater in the most disrespectful way
possible
all right
okay here we go yeah you know what i'm
not a professional i don't know how to
launch people out of cherries but my
friend dwayne he is a professional yeah
professional dude is this a profession
that's a professional see dwayne says
it's professional let's do a little test
right now without depending all right
here we go let's launch the chair devin
this is going to be you in a moment all
right no
three two one go for it
oh no oh my goodness oh no
did you see the chair yeah that chair
didn't make it man it's lost a couple
limbs clearly this is way too dangerous
to do with an
actual person so we're not gonna do it
with an actual person we're gonna use a
dummy over here so again do not try this
at home and now let's launch this dummy
out of the chair
and all the jokes aside do not sneak
candy and snacks into the movies support
your local theaters if you want to see
another video click right over here you
got five seconds here we go
five four three two
one done love you bye