coca-cola bottle rocket Oh fine bottle
glasses blue so let's go hit the window
it's not good watermelon smash oh man
you chose not to try the viral tire
crushing experiment if you thought that
water mode was crazy
just wait to see what happen we do with
the car bro what are you doing Oh dad
this car stops and says it's making sure
the brakes work I will man will hop out
here's the deal we're each gonna be
setting up a roll of objects running it
over with the car and see which one
reacts the pass and that's who's gonna
win this round we have a whole bunch of
lined up right now by the way do not try
this at home I can smell it yeah I mean
you're gonna be quite the 3d shop look
at the ground
that looks pretty satisfying pretty
amazing to be on a silly-string dude we
shouldn't have brought out the nice
cameras for this video you've made a
terrible error
why didn't we go to next level that was
close like he barely heads up before you
go again hurry dude I can't see this you
know how close I could have been to you
almost getting blasted dude yes my next
up here we go let's go over the Ben &
Jerry's right now oh we gotta like oh my
gosh it's like literally all over the
lens well hey at least the lens and
moisturize its exfoliate or this next
one Devin here is called curves hi
guacamole right side the guacamole that
looks actually pretty delicious have a
chip man takes plate oh good what I'm
gonna use my jaw and I'm not do that ah
here we go let's run over my beautiful
full
you're on the jello so keep going way
too far all I want let's just do
compression under the Capri side well
there you have it that is my role of
tire experiments and so now heaven it's
time to see it yours
and beat mommy I'm gonna pop it in right
now and let's see if your lawn or your
seat is so high bro you're like I want
to see out of the car yeah I built a
special ramp for you I went diving come
straight that's already off to a great
start is actually bury one right
constant you got straighten out the
wheel here oh yeah go this way a little
bit like that here you're like a
terrible backseat dad just go go turn
turn the wheel turn the wheel you want
to drive oh you're gonna keep going oh
we're good we're good that was close all
right this silly-string kanji icons the
takis into the foam or next Oh icon just
go straight go for it
next up is some grapefruit go for it Oh
chips then we got these things you got
you sing Oh baby's workout you got the
chickens bro stop stuffing another
chicken put something alive under the
tire for a second no cannot do the
housing alive all the cans you comment
down below whose line was more explosive
and remember the loser gets all a whole
bunch of glitter jumps all over the
experiment drunk with a whole bunch of
Coca Cola and dropping a mega Mentos
into it and of course they had a giant
Coca Cola bottle rock goes literally fly
and here we go shake it when the Coca
Cola bottles I've got a great way of
adding it into this drum right here you
55 gallons so I've got an axe do not try
this on him to 100 we'll see we're gonna
shake the bottle again that's the issue
is that you're shaking it up into the
close-up of my eyes man you will see you
just a wild passion like a primitive
dude
me no look the acts on the sign no it
says do not try this at home
hi I've got this soldering iron here
it's very hot so do not try this at home
nothing I'm just I'm basically burning a
hole in the bottom so I can connect all
these coca-cola bottle I even goes gonna
crack open the top of the mint oh my
gosh this is up this is tough how does
this thing work it's got military-grade
lock on this thing see even you can't do
it man usually if you having to figure
this stuff out for this that's a lot of
Mentos man Baba sailor don't try this at
home except I don't know how or why he
would 3 2 1 are you the Wonder is the
blenders of London blender is a blender
ah all right here we go let's took
forever but I've actually blended up all
the Mentos into this like dough looking
stuff here man this took forever so here
we go here we go let's see oh man all
you gotta do to finish up my vile
experiment just fill this thing up with
55 gallons of coca-cola and then shape
this into the perfect Mentos shape and
I'll be ready to go and all I gotta do
is add these electric parts attach these
bottles and add some fins and that's
gonna fly all right we got the coca-cola
Rocky now it's time to see if he's got a
lawn I am very skeptical about this Evan
cos we have rocket blast once before
yeah there was some slight cheating that
happened yeah yeah it didn't even really
work so we're gonna put this on right
all right so cons I'm gonna have you
hold the remote here we go yeah here's
the remote what part do I not cut any of
this doesn't clear what are we touch
what do I talk I gotta move on what
about touch yeah there yeah all you're
gonna do is rotate this when it's time
the wheel the wheel brother we have not
the trigger no not the figure whatever
you do do not pull the trigger so I'm
gonna pull the trick no no no not at all
so what you're gonna do cause is the
moment I pull this it's going to release
the air pressure and then what are you
gonna do pull the trigger against your
better judgment Devon I just cannot stop
myself from party you've really know to
press a while
whoa okay nothing happening guess what
happened nothing I guess we're good all
right I heard something in the distance
I don't know probably follows my
imagination ha pull it again pull it
again don't worry Hale don't know so you
don't move the wheel a little
adventurous for me is pulling the
trigger like nothing's happening yet I'm
gonna be way cooler man that's kind of
boring are here as they want to scoot
back but the issues I'm in the Sun as
you guys know I sunburn very easily
I'm have to take a knee all right Ultra
back there you go three two one it
worked okay okay hey let's go laughing
there we go wait wait hold hold hold
holy cow oh my gosh that was absolutely
ballistic bro I can't believe it man
okay
we didn't even lunch I think mines gonna
be even more explosive so right now
let's do it oh dude I did my shoes bro
it's finally time to test this massive
coca-cola and mentos explosion I had to
go back to the drawing board a little
bit actually glued all whole bunch of
Mentos together I've also added some
baking cleanser dust coming out of it
College that's baking soda no it
actually reminds me of one of those hair
nets that you wear when you make food
you know Wow okay that's a lot dude
that's what you called dandruff I'm
gonna be hopping out and that balcony up
there and I'm gonna be dropping this in
from be eating it beating it as hard as
I possibly patent into the bucket night
all right time for me to go up right now
let's do it what am i peer review the
mega mentos drop in devon how's it
looking down there man this is looking
exactly the same as it did before
prediction scale of one to ten one thing
nothing happens and I missed the Mentos
it just doesn't you get the bucket or
yeah and B the fact that guys in the
past the house where do you think this
is that well I think your deeps are
pretty on point cons thank you no I
would have to say I think it's gonna
guys her up I think this is gonna be
absolutely huge and phenomenal.i time to
do this I gotta say I think it's been
one of my greatest accomplishments ever
Devon forget America's Got Talent it's a
mega Mentos at coca-cola man
three two women three-second like Josh
do you like this video in three seconds
you ready here we go three two one
come on three two one
I got a whole bunch of it barely did
anything I think that was just the
impact of you throwing it in I've got a
backup good you held the GoPro oh wow
all right why Meena is fizzing up but I
think it mostly was didn't you chucking
in it no good comment down below whose
coca-cola and mentos experiment turned
out cooler and remember the losers
getting glitter jumps all over them at
the end of the video so right now we're
on the next experiment for this viral
experiment of crazy right now let's
clean this up cuz we're making only way
bigger one so right now let's go I
ripped out the zipper III don't have a
zipper anymore see the thing is when
definites the restroom and it nightmares
what my elephant toothpaste explosion
I'm using a watermelon I'm using this
horn I've never been out or but it's
time for me to be out
orbed euro and it's gonna get even
cooler I'm full or black I really did
turn into it you're committed to this
orb life I go back to normal cause this
is I gotta find if I hey hey whoa whoa
this is high or not you're or can't be
in front of this orb
you're not even in the or forming you
across the board not even an organ this
is a cylinder it's gotta excuse me
that's not water
I don't think that's water this is water
acid why would we have a giant 300
gallon thing of acid no I've never done
that before
no but you see that blue nastiness
you've got on my watermelon yeah there's
only one way to get blue nasty off of my
water bucket blue nasty op watermelon
dude like feet just water no Johan whoa
what are you doing okay dude dude dude
dude this isn't even the thing you're
not here to destroy a watermelon bro a
watermelon
oh no this is what you call year we go
3-1 I mean you did not come down you
know strike right here we've got a can I
think this will be the perfect way to do
it so get a place right here if they're
gonna use the grill on top not to broil
it
I broke the drill I wonder how that
happened I have no idea dude I am mixing
up this paint I'm making a sweet Hydra
dip I have my orange bag it's actually
not normal or crystal or it's just a
normal week okay any more can be turned
into a crystal orb that's why I like
orbs so much and that's why you can see
the future inside of it activate the
future telling magic or telling we must
speak the ancient tongues over the salad
mission master arugula salad mix to
mentor arugula salad mix a nice sauce
[Music]
whoa I thought the future would be way
cooler than that we're talking about man
I love arugula salad that's a perfect
future for me now it's time to dip the
orb 3 2 1 oh you dunk the watermelon
into its own the surprise it looks bad
are you good time to cross the
watermelon here so here we go is gonna
go ahead like this gonna try something a
little bit unconventional and probably
really doesn't sound like I don't have
anything
there's no hide your dipped stuff in
there let's run out get those all in
Devon right there it's so casual how's
this all on Devin right there I think
that's for me all I got to do here is
just hold on my watermelon got it all
prepared it's time to set off the
explosions let's put the masks down to
use with a bird mode third mode that is
enough here we go yep okay well I think
I went a little bit too stream on that
one got to go find them yes just in
YouTube star Devin key is stuck in the
crevasse yes his wench went deep that's
cute all right guys we've got great news
I found out you just tore my suit man
I'm on tour horns now yeah that wasn't
from the piggyback ride that was from
his journey to the crevasse
alright so here we go it's just like
this here Oh hide up hold up hold up
hold up hold up hold up that's not where
the issue is there we go boom no gaps
down if you were a department store
you'll definitely be the gap here we go
nice down time to go for it again do not
try this at home three two one
and smells so good too if you like yours
about to be double the explosion alright
here we go
3 eyz you can subscribe to the channel
and turn on the channel post
notifications in 5 seconds you ready
here we go 5 4 3 2 1
done if you were able to do that comment
down below keeper squad right now and
let's see how this goes 3 remember the
loser has a massive glitter jump at the
end of the video but right now we're on
to the next experiment you challenge us
to combine the eruption of the coke and
mentos experiment the explosive flow of
the elephant toothpaste together to see
what happens so right now let's dig some
holes here wait hear that yeah love is
that yeah well I will insist that let's
give it one more here we go to fix that
up and out right now let's go first
thing we got to do is plug these holes
in the ground with a whole bunch of soda
so he was gonna pour this in over here
like this oh it's overflowing okay well
there you go oh boy here we go cheer to
the good life yes you know your boys are
living their best life in the wilderness
[Music]
got me a fire breather right now oh wait
a second what she's gonna add in the 7up
now I wouldn't add it that way if you
know I mean I would just adjust the
position of the button oh and we're
height wise it's not enough just oh yeah
yeah does that help
now it's time to get ready for the
elephant toothpaste we've got the soap
here got a min for my first one I'm
gonna go for distance why you and height
I'm going height I'll go if you want me
to spot you know I got ants why you want
one leg that doesn't seem it all the
right way to go man cuz I'm making it
dramatic and I said we're going for the
color over here teamwork makes the dream
work
that's a lie my fingers blue I'm turning
into a smart alright guys welcome to our
YouTube channel is called degradable so
uh yeah here we go you're ready three
two one here we go in school I gotta say
the rainbow colors definitely turned out
nicely not gonna lie I was hoping for a
little bit larger on mine all right
Devon now it's time for yours yes the
yours have the more explosive reaction
so here we go Matt Sam I'd here we go
three yeah detain me the video called
with Devon and I text the word cool to
8100 right now so pause the video text
the word cool to 80 100 200 matically be
entered into it and let's go for it
mine's bigger this is definitely big rat
it's like a galaxy that's what we get a
lot bigger than mine you didn't comment
down below whose combo experiment up the
coke and mentos and the elephant
toothpaste turned out cooler mine or
Devon's comment down below right now
time to clean all this up and Ron in the
next experiment it's finally time for
the glitter playa here's the thing this
punishment is the worst game we put a
GoPro on the front of the bowl Oh yo
guys oh hi yes the losers are nervous so
here we go yeah yeah take it from before
you were getting blasted for sure
hitting at you're definitely totally one
thing that we do now when regardless of
who do we tarped everything because we
only want the glitter going all over the
loser eggs not on our yard easy guy we
want to go in on this I'm not the loser
dude
you definitely LOX let's settle this
right there I'm gonna take this back
okay coke and mentos yes okay I got to
start with that one first
why dude it's the best one I think like
my rocket was really really good it
didn't I think like your things pretty
clear though with yours with yours
yeah I actually fly though doesn't as
bad as just throwing a hunk of mentos
into a butt excuse me and nothing
happens a cool-looking giant mentos not
just all hokum I mean the slush did look
cool but they didn't react at all fine
on that one I will give it to you okay
guys ever get to take it that's some
we're gonna go for the tire crushing
yeah the same man strongest show their
defi mine were popping off they were
exploding everything looking great mine
was really bad nothing yeah it was so
thank you what about the elephant
toothpaste do you mean you had you
watermelon one and then I had you know
the one with the bunch of holes I think
my watermelon geyser was absolutely
awesome boys shot up went everywhere it
was pretty quiet
it was pretty typical he'd done that
before but mine I've never done that I'd
actually took a lot of time cutting out
those holes so I'd appreciate the win on
those my I do I do have to say what kind
of exploding octopus and way I describe
it yeah so there yeah I guess that was
it all comes down to this the tiebreak
yeah the holes in the ground with coke
admit doesn't yeltsin truth but just
sodas and I have to say why are we doing
this one as a tiebreaker like the least
definitive one of yeah I was definitely
a game of inches or millimeters yeah all
right so yeah if it's a game of inches
or millimeters I think I don't think so
man I think I think I think Mama's
pretty good play if they don't really
you know if you were to hear to replan
so you would notice
yeah bats is one different class yeah
yo move jab me in the stomach right now
okay I don't get jams in the stomach how
about this young man
yes I think you did we all take one for
the team ah yes fun for the team you
objectively lost this is not for the
team let's make it seem like a circus I
guess I gotta just hop in that mini full
of shame with the sandbags of sadness
sadness they're very sad hello just like
you right now cuz you're about to get
quitter blasting just hop in there why
do I give you all the mini pool of shame
so the next step is I have to pump this
thing up with air I got another idea
hold this real quick hold those things
alright see you try to maximize there
you go yes had to do something wrong
this is terrible I've kind of feel bad
now actually I kinda want to put this
down oh now you feel bad I'm soaked
that's struggling I'm struggling his
hold the band okay
nice thank you okay go buddy go teamwork
make the dream work
what's next got my earplugs over here do
not want glitter in yes so poured forth
but not leave oh this hurts man okay
[Music]
Oh
dude look at that it was like I got a
scaly ileum and I have absolutely I am
so not what here well bet is the glitter
bless ya I'm a double oh right now what
is your favorite pilot screaming your
loves you do another version of wannabe
nuclear grandma here
bye-bye come on floor three two one oh
boy