hey where you going was exactly um too
early in the morning right now and I'm
off to Vegas once if everyone is calling
ski and welcome to the Thursday of law
now give this video a thumbs up if you
saw me in Vegas on America's Got Talent
now for those of you who don't know I
don't know what in New York City but
today I wanted to talk about the values
experience first of all I'm just very
grateful for the fact I even made it to
Vegas now I'd only just ever been done
before on the show but I'm going to show
you some exclusive behind-the-scenes
video footage that I took in Vegas enjoy
so if everyone's Colman's key here
Daly's hotel they see we just got
transferred out of a room because the
room smelled like rotten cabbage and so
the room was also there's no way we're
gonna get was sleeping in actually being
transferred to another room right now to
make sure I'm pretty excited about my
dad's over there in the business oh
gotta go
sup song ski day to Vegas in a long day
a lot of being on setting everything but
in Ex the hotel room
this is day three of Vegas week and
today basically found out our face so I
guess what's actually happening is I'm
actually going to be uh I'm performing
in Vegas but they're working on my hacks
got to go through a stage run-through
today had a good time and just preparing
for the big show
I don't even know what day this is
Wednesday here in Vegas I just performed
and got the thing so they's like the
guys are they weren't supposed to
respond at all when I was up today like
they totally responded they were totally
into it and it's like they kept the book
afterwards they're trying to figure out
how it worked and I'm just super psyched
is like everything went totally
according to plan I had a blast with it
living the dream that 16 here in fake is
performing on this stage and you know
what happens in here is what happens
from here you know I'm just super
exciting I was like I didn't have like
any adrenaline on stage or anything it
was just kind of like I don't just feel
like super like their housing I was in
the moment everything but I just didn't
feel like the first time at least I had
a crazy amount of adrenaline going
this time I felt totally bare and now
the Adrenaline's kicking in I'm like oh
what happened in that so at the end he
was walking behind Todd and I together
and she actually like she stopped by and
she usually doesn't talk to anyone
because like oh my gosh this your dad
and all the stuff so it was it was super
cool so yeah living the dream
so if everyone is calm key and this is
day I don't know what the heck I'm so
lost this has been one of the most like
intense weeks of my life Vegas week and
we're heading out of our hotel room
today I think it yes I'm going through
to New York Radio City Music Hall will
be the youngest magician ever in the
history of that venue to ever perform
there which I'm pretty pretty psyched
about and so basically I was checking
out today I'm gonna hang poolside a
little bit and so when we get back the
real work begins definitely give this
video a big thumbs up if you enjoyed the
behind the scenes footage now I got to
keep the actual envelope that heidi klum
sign and she sat on it so I'm pretty
excited about that
now I wanted to get back to copy the
book I used on the show Mel B took him
home I guess she inspected it further
still cannot figure it out luckily she
brought it back the next day and gave me
the original copy of the book I used on
the show the other thing conceits the
page with the word draw on it and it
fits perfectly so the book just thank
you to AGT for letting me keep these it
was great meeting all the other
contestants everyone who works on
America's Got Talent is super nice
the judges are amazing in the cannons
the bomb on July 23rd I perform live in
front of America on the Radio City Music
Hall stage fun fact that will be the
Yelling's magician in the history of
Radio City Music Hall to ever perform on
that stage now for this next show I need
your help jeepers please continue
spreading the word on Facebook Twitter
Instagram Tumblr Ustream YouTube
everywhere this is the Colin key take
over I need your guy's help
thank you so much my fans for all the
support you guys are amazing now give
this video a thumbs up if you're excited
to see the live show and of course don't
forget to subscribe to this channel
once you get a calm key thank you guys
for watching peace Collins mmm Collins
performing today man it's time to get up
let's go ahead we got right now yeah you
got your smile eh you performed my god
no no no we're not late we're not like
I'm all dressed