what's up you guys will see some magic
yeah cool check it out so here what
we're gonna do is just pull out actually
I've never seen a card scam before okay
I mean your first card scam no money
involved but check it out
you tell us works this is all memories
it going this with your fingers so we
have the ace of spades and this will be
your car because we'll end that right
there and then my card here will be the
lesson ace of clubs so a little bit
lower and how this works all right I'm
gonna switch these cards out you won't
even feel this happen all right this
happens crazy fast ready there's one
rule about this this is all memory let
go oh my my target you got the ace of
spades I've got the ace of clubs you
cannot turn the cards over this is all
memory and watch let's see how you
holding a little bit looser we're going
right there watch we go one two now did
you even feel that happen no no okay
that's how fast that literally happened
to see I've got chicken I'll get the ace
of clubs and I'll turn over watch you've
got the ace of spades and I'll teach you
how this works okay in case this ever
happens to you I'll teach you how to
defend against it basically what the
what the scam artist does I'll take the
ace of clubs and basic what I'm doing is
I'm pushing this card in and then
pulling this card out and that right
there that's the move this I think I've
been doing this for about two years now
just every day of my life dispensing I
have no life that's what I do what
you're gonna do is this time memory only
I've got the spades you've got the
club's memory only you guys can help her
out spades clubs watch one two three
four four switches memory only don't
turn them over which ones on top the
clubs are the spades you can help her
out clubs clubs on top so clubs on top
spades on bottom turn them over