three two one yummy bunny wait no no I
tell the guys that let Adam go in our
previous to gummy versus real food
videos a bummer was the most requested
thing the devil's got some big bunny
[Laughter]
right now number two reintroducing the
ability to either keep them or switch
them so Devon right now you want
keepo or switching one session i want to
keep it oh alright here we go 3 2 1 this
is suggested by mega Helton so shout out
to you if you want to be the Instagram
keeper than we can be shattered out in
one of these videos
check the description down below to find
out how but bro not cool
no oh my gosh dude I know horrible
experience with lemons I just got lemon
juice in my eye toward the insane yeah I
didn't like that at all
no alright little the RFP so Devin I
think you guys eat yours first and then
is it good mmm is actually super sweet
okay no it's not alright here we go
bro you've got a squeeze it into your
mouth just licking it isn't anything
either that or actually like biting off
a chunk of it oh come on liquid yeah
then on this spider bro okay and then
squeeze it right dude you're actually
crying all that birds
Brogan's ish thank you thank you
bro oh I thought I was helping but Oh
again and to finish it off
oh I didn't say all three bro
tap out Oh pop out okay let's go this is
my second discriminant this one smells
funky funky funky funky funky bro they
done of this area just smells really
gross my turn right now I give you the
switchover keep them I've never had good
experiences with switching em I'm gonna
keep it I don't want to get whatever
this is horrible look at these tiny so
cute there's some I don't look like
normal eggs though no those are like not
hard-boiled weather let me smell weird
no we had a pickled pig's foot nothing
was nasty cold eggs pickled eggs is that
the month that's gotta be a thing how is
that a thing it's like two of the worst
bells hard-boiled egg combined with
pickles no you gotta eat that Devon
right bro I'm doing it you gotta do both
with the same time bro not just one I
don't fit that in my mouth yes you can
bro just to it this what yes you can no
I don't believe in you okay bro
is he getting high ones go jump this up
and then the other one right all right
here we go three two one good but first
we've got a challenge for you guys we
want to see you can subscribe to this
channel turn on the channel post
notifications and give this video a
thumbs up in seven seconds here we go
7 6 5 4 3 2 1 done you could do that
comment down below keeper squad right
now
a lot of people who are able to do all
through those things in seven seconds
but right now no more stalling Devin all
right daddy both of them here we go one
diet over here man we just found out
that these eggs are actually six months
expired
why would you feed me then am I gonna
die I'll do the next round you were
jealous so we bought the five-month
expired pickled a smelled horrible this
stuff smells even worse ten times worse
whatever this is smoked so disgusting so
this is Devin's turn you can either keep
them or switch them what would you like
to do the trouble is the whole house
smells terrible and I can't tell if it's
coming from here or from that one but I
think I'm just gonna switch it your
Swift I had good luck with switching all
right here we go
I really hope I got the gummy 3 no short
meet oh my gosh dude you're about to eat
a predator of the ocean poor shirt dude
white walking towards me pull up and you
get a good whiff of the stuff the worst
thing about the smell is there like a
sharpness to it you smell it and like if
you like it cuts your nose like on the
inside like oh so I'm gonna get my shark
right now oh dude oh yeah sure this
bridge oh yeah I'm sure that's great oh
my gosh yeah we're gonna back on the
back so far yeah I'm sure they're okay
so like all the best part the deal yeah
just keep rubbing it in don't walk on
there I'm not looking forward to this
all right here we go oh my god three two
one yo what
bro this is great what yo this tastes
awesome and sniff smell though if you
inhale any smell do Oh smell it tastes
great but the smell like once you walked
it in through your mouth there's just no
filters is no filter it's just oh great
it did I believe me it tastes great it's
just the smell okay alright bro it is
your turn do you want to switch them or
do you want to keep them bro you know
I'm always feeling big drawers let's
switch a bro alright major go
cow-tipping yeah these are awesome
they're so cute I'm gonna play a game
right now this is the opposite of
cow-tipping that's called cow flipping
here's how the cows lift works Devin you
throw it up I throw it up if you get all
of them in a row and new rule we have to
do it another 15 seconds over here we go
are you a yellow let's get stuck my
fingers get so difficult
here we go oh my gosh here we go
[Music]
okay all right your turn right now do
you want to keep them or switch them you
know I've had a really bad what bro I
have no idea I'm just gonna I'm just
gonna stay who's gonna keep it why here
we go three this is leading up to the
finale after this one is the big one
you're all waiting for the snake but
right now you're a joke are you great or
what yeah yeah oh I can these are slugs
I have never done this before bro I am
I'm Tommy gone wrong I like this one I
cannot do this what dude bro you've done
spiders you've done sardines like how
much worse is a slug I can't even
describe how gross there's no I'm not
eating this bro I draw the line at
whatever their fancy word for a snail
it's a slug Oh an escargot
it's a soggy is that a cargo it's a slug
okay if you get one skipped that means I
get one skip coming up in the future in
another video at any time right is every
four slides if slugs come up with other
videos dollar then you can do it this
run is the worst ride we've ever done
first of all too real slug I ain't even
that say the balls II feel like the
cheapest gummies
there's not even gummy this crack that's
not there like a hybrid yummy yummy and
a hard candy I am very very disappointed
and unsatisfied with this round but
luckily there's one more round which
hopefully will I will satisfy us let's
go here we go the final round of welcome
all been waiting for
a snake three two one right but first
you want to feature it in our next video
comment down below and let us know what
are some real foods you want us to make
into giant gummies but right now let's
do this three two one
yo what are they little mates yeah these
are some well no do we know how the
first one way you have a giant gummy
bunny bunny so - they probably smaller
three two one