here we go I'm tightening closed jerseys
are open above ah there we go perfect
hot in this hoodie man whoa
and we are ready what's up everyone it
is collin ski and welcome to magic
mondays today if actually got something
very special i've got some special
behind-the-scenes and video footage from
when i got to do magic for the judges on
America's Got Talent but this footage
was never aired on television so I
thought you know what why not to do that
as my keeper is an awesome a backstage
look at what happened at the judges
soiree
enjoy
[Music]
ironic part seven what I was very
poor joke everyone even shows with
hammer I won't come once in that part
was the camera
[Music]
I'm not gonna look all right here okay
put it down you all see it tell me what
it is okay I have to what this SV secret
ownership this is a misleading Tibetan
word we use for cards realizes this
which call a line all right I want you
to lie to me how you're gonna be the
first one to license to look at me okay
I'm going to show you this card all
right and you're gonna say
this is not the car ready for this look
at mommy a lot yes okay this is not the
car for pull your hand there's one oh
yeah no I know here all right already
look at my hand for us one by one I
think all right here we go Melvin same
thing you're like look at this say this
is not my car this is not my
I'd say they pull your hand light just
say it's not my party
[Music]
Howard this whole time one of my tools I
would actually lying to you
this last part laughter that's a nice
what should I tell watch watch go one
two three
so yeah and if you guys enjoyed the
magic and the judges reactions please
give this video a huge thumbs up our
maid service never comes to clean our
room so our room is a disaster at the
moment also don't forget I'm on tour
right now I'm actually in some creepy
hotel it's been proven this is a haunted
hotel so if you guys want to check out
last week's vlog I need a whole vlog
about I'm gonna put like the link over
here if you guys are coming to the tour
make sure you bring awesome calm key
t-shirts homemade is the best of course
and also I may bring like signs and all
that kind of stuff no I had my first
show yesterday I'm gonna post a little
video clip right now I'm going to yell
at them with ridiculous word you can
think of stealers give me an absolute
blast I would love to see you guys on
tour I'm gonna be doing whole bunch of
meet and greets if you guys are excited
for the tour please give this video a
big thumbs up now make sure you guys are
tweeting me hashtag calls key on tour
for all the latest updates meet and
greets all that fun stuff once again you
guys I'm Colin's key thank you so much
for watching this week's magic Monday's
I'll see you again soon
peace
[Music]
got some mints like a mouse till I knew
this Oh first ride