what's up you guys know I love dummy
foods and we giant dummy were right here
and that's you guys know I've got a
love-hate relationship with sour food
and today I've got my friend Karina
Garcia here and we're gonna be making
the first-ever
world's largest sour gummy worm it's
gonna be crazy and we're kicking this
off right now with some toxic waste so
Karina here ahead toxic waste before no
I have yeah doing nothing to be scared
about this stuff is like not not to be
worried about at all we're first gonna
eat it and then just kind of like just
see how it tastes and then looking like
DIY add it to the gummy worm dreaded
with us yeah wanna get like a little bit
kind of stuck right hand high five good
luck - there we go we've now added the
toxic waste to the gummy worm I am NOT
looking forward to taking a fire god
you're so intense what's the next item
you want to go for I think we should go
for oh that guy's going to toxic waste
which is horrible
- warheads which are like bad so guys
fun fact you see like this little like
weird coating it has on it
that's malic acid this is the most
intense part of this entire thing my
machine is off this gummy worm with the
malic acid so this is kind of like I
guess our first tasted it so here we go
we're about to eat this but first I've
got a challenge I want to see you can
subscribe to this channel turn on the
channel post notifications and give this
video a thumbs up in seven seconds here
we go you ready for this seven six five
four three two one done it you can do
that comment down
keeper squad right now I'll be replying
to people who are able to do all three
of those things in seven seconds but
right now ready for this ah plus let's
talk about birthdays and then we'll go
over the whole handful man you ready
three two one go three and go for the
label two one I'm just trying to get on
like Farina's level when it comes to DIY
bird life hacks and like Ursulines
videos are insane so I don't know why
but a ton of you guys suggested for us
to do these super sour warheads drops
I've double these ones they're horrible
I think I can so that I got both at once
here we go oh oh
three two one go to the next one okay so
I'm kind of at a loss for what to do
next but you guys really wanted us to
try out this stuff here sweet tart I
choose sour all right so hold out your
hand so I will I will dispense them to
you I'm like a PEZ dispenser right but I
have it hardly wait look these could be
sweet they could be sour targets they
could taste like parts enough
[Music]
yo I've never had these before so the
salad either going steals in a way yeah
there is nothing sweet about those sour
cards
Brina what are you feeling like sour
patch kids all right
do you like sour patch kids that'll be
great oh yeah just kind of doing all
ones and guys I gotta give it up right
now this is Karina's first time ever
doing like a sour video and she's
crushing it thank you for cheese like I
know it's a 3 2 legged one my tongue
burns they feel that you feel like it
doesn't so great I have a question for
you huh you're not a crybaby right no
singing nearby except what I have to eat
there's a hair on it that's gross it's a
white hair it's like an old lady here
that is not your hair your hair is
luscious this is not Cheers
see you on the other side
[Applause]
[Music]
alright next I want to choose crybaby
bubble gum bubble gum I feel like that
wouldn't be sour
alright I'm already tearing up I had
these one time they were the worst out
of the ante up swing leave will mess up
your whole life I'd say we do three
because I don't want to die are you
shocked 3 what helped me to 1 these are
the worst so we're gonna pop these on
right now I thought they were getting
regular gum but they are terrible no
these are so these are the worst because
the sour coating on the outside is like
the first thing oh and then you get to
the inside like for this next one I kind
of want to go I don't know what to do
because my taste buds my mouth is just
so destroyed I've never actually had
this before it's a sour spray rain I'm
gonna do it by second and I think you
should do as many as you can in five
seconds so let's see who wins
okay five four three two one done okay
that was horrible
alright so I think we're gonna do one
other one with one final coating I gotta
say I think she got more and more more
in than I did that's for sure
so now we're coming down to it guys
we're almost at the final round but
first we've got some soda next it's like
there's a little pizza malic acid in my
throat that's like there's like beating
my throat up right now usually
apparently likes our sodas so
got the sour green apple I got sour
cherry
it's called Death Valley this one's a
Jelly Belly this one looks good
Mike it's called Death Valley look at it
it's like these like bending Cowboys on
the horses like like you're those
delicious mine was like like some guy
was like in Death Valley trying to drink
this out oh no it's like smoking the
Cowboys for yours are amongst us and
they didn't work if I could describe it
that experience imagine my tongue is the
desert cracked and broken
oh and imagine this is a hot lava and
scorched me man I'm happening you want
it yeah you guys want to dribble yours
on my side I think mine's already got
enough a little smidge more that sound
soon Ansem are a similar does not sound
fun all right
this here is the final one I'm about to
add some malic acid and then take a bite
of it so I'm gonna grab a spoon folda
malic acid oh my god it's like sugar for
people who love sour things basically
it's like it's it's the the core
ingredient of just like every sour candy
so we're about to take a giant spoonful
of this but make sure the moment this
video ends go like the video that we did
on Karina's channel we made the most
lime I've ever seen in my entire life I
mentioned you go subscribe to her
channel she's been an absolute trooper
for doing this video here we go
you go for you ready three two and then
we have to eat this little snake filled
all the stuff what's the real food you
want us to turn into a giant dummy but
right now you cook your end I'll grab my
end here we go I'm trying to get a
toothpick oh my god you think it's tough
bro horrible three here we go torture I
forgot I forgot how care of myself in
you weren't here I forgot oh my god so
that know me so you guys know Chuck
gonna take it right now like I'm you
gotta show her some love man she
wouldn't so much back our video now
[Applause]