over the first-ever magic Monday's
basically every one day I'm going to be
putting up a new a magic theme de video
sorry Hayden see there I wasn't just
watching my video or anything so yeah so
hi it's awkward what's up everyone is
columns key and welcome to the second
ever magic Monday first off I like to
thank all of you for watching last
week's magic Monday so please give this
video a thumbs up if you're excited for
the second week now last week I asked
all of you to comment what kind of magic
you want to see for the next video no
Megan Penna said I want to see some
Street magic so that is exactly what I
did I went to a festival I filmed some
magic enjoy except everyone is calling
key this is a 4th of July party that I'm
at sided whip out some cards and do some
magic
so
I've got a few
normally have additional I tried to find
car and that's kind of boring it was
craziness for me right here okay what's
good over here so you can see it
right
King apart sorry Washington he's happy
or either one you like that
all
so real
take the five right here
Oh King you didn't see when I should
have switched out the cars watches way
to five five like that
so the girls : ski had a great time here
that delightful festival that you guys
for watching so please hit the like
button if you enjoyed that video
subscribe to this channel that way you
are the first one to see all of the
latest videos so comment below let me
know what kind of magic you want to see
me do in next week's video alright guys
that is it for this week's magic Monday
once again I'm calling ski thank you
guys for watching
[Music]
whale