hey oh okay well last video we asked you
guys to let us know what should we do in
sumo suits and you guys had a ton of
crazy ideas but right now there's better
get up right now let's get into it get
someone else
hell no well pay ah we're kicking it off
with the most requested one of all and
that is a sumo suit battle how this
works whoever can push the other out of
this orange circle first wins a sumo
battle - gonna take your corner okay
into the ring and begin I'm hit
Devon won now we're on to the next way
victory is mine a lot of you wanted us
to try yoga poses and so we're going to
be choosing the three most popular ones
that you guys suggested the first one is
called the downward dog this is where
it's supposed to look like and this is
what it looks like with sumo suits Devon
high five for good luck ah all right
here we go five high five here we go
three two one quick I think I did it I
did it good
what alright next pose next pose dude oh
did I just kick you yeah I'm sorry
next up is the chair here's what it is
supposed to look like and here's what it
looks like in sumo suits Oh Devon arms
up uh this is dumb three two one now go
for the flames and for the last one
we're doing a group yoga pose it's
supposed to look like this but here's
what it looks like if you can't even get
up here we go alright gonna go up like
this all right you ready Rock can't
reach over my belly I'm just gonna have
to jump
alright three oh gosh two-to-one but we
got this we got this we got this one
more try all right Kai
are you ready yeah great - what ah
Oh busted my leg next up it is never too
late to pursue your baseball career so
Devon's gonna pitch it I'm gonna smack
it that way
nope that way bro you got to use two
hands if you want to hit a home run bro
okay yeah there you go my arms don't
move I guess my whole son feel like I'm
the one who's really gonna get hurt in
this this is gonna go like like a half a
foot all right you ready yep
three two proper form one oh all right
toss it bro
huh I got it well that was strike one
here we go here we go three two yep
one hey I was like wait for the wine no
that's strike two
all right ready yeah all right let's go
hey do one Oh what did I say I feel like
I'm the one who's really gonna get hurt
in this next guys want us to jump rope
but first you get a challenge we want to
see you guys can subscribe to this
channel and turn on the channel post
notifications in five seconds here we go
5 4 3 2 1
John you do that comment down below keep
your squad right now
you good yeah let's jump rope here we go
you'll design no difficulty so all right
three how that we can do that one oh
look it's literally just hitting like
what what happened bro oh my god next
one
what did you say it right well he back
there so like it instead just throwing
the football with other be kind of
boring Devon's gonna try to kick it
you're a field goal at the bush or the
shrub whatever that thing is he's gonna
kick it there give me the football Devon
there you go thank you
alright so we're gonna set this up I've
watched a lot of football I know how
this goes the guys go like this yeah
alright ready three get a good kick
Devon two one go
No my leg do what happened did it go in
the gulp oh yeah
do that I did yeah oh it just bounced
back to my abs wait why are we up try
this one more time here so remember
Devon the main goal you have to get the
ball in the bush here we go
okay good hole let's unna fingers
retract my hand
there we go three I'm really going for
it to go one no I appreciate how
confident you guys are in our juggling
abilities but I really don't know if we
can juggle in these sumo suits but if we
get latrise in any one scoop that way a
little bit all right here we go three
two one no I already lost it gone my
belly gets in the way alright that was
round one and now it's on to round two I
fell over anyway
Stevie dope yeah that would help him
boom as he's trying to get up and the
show must go on
alright well I think that's about the
best we can do hey Devon hey catch huh
well that went just about as badly as
you'd expect so hey you're finally up
again oh I just haha let's go into the
next one for some reason you guys
thought to be hilarious for demantoid to
have a pool noodle battle in sumo suits
Oh Devon owl which ninja are you i am
french fry
sumo guy and I am the Christmas you a
wrestler so whoever whoever is forced to
leave the mat birth they lose and begin
Oh
[Music]
oh yeah I'm doing Christmas sumo for the
win so next up we are going to have a
tug of war battle but as you can tell
instead of pulling on the rope
we don't wanna destroy our hands with
rope burn we've tied it to ourselves and
ended up looking like really connected
by an umbilical cord all right here we
go three two one go huh
those what what are you using your hand
wait what are you doing what are you
doing but I'm getting dizzy
that backfires oh well good one that was
a really good tug of war battle at all I
feel like everything we do turns into a
sumo battle I wonder why I guess we call
it a draw
yeah just a draw I'm exhausted eh
alright this time we have real badge and
we're about to do the same thing we did
with a pool noodle battle same rules
apply I'm joking I'm joking I'm joking
what do you guys want to see how dizzy
we would get if we put the bats at our
forehead put them on the ground and then
spun around them a whole bunch of times
and so I think like we're just gonna get
dizzy all right I'll take this corner we
can spin around 20 times then after we
have to walk in a straight line got it
ready yep three two one go one is you're
so hard to
whoa Road wait we're still spinning yep
uh-huh I thought we were go no go on
down down down so you're still going
struggling here we go yeah here we go
why does this always happen I'm gonna
take a little nap guys I'll see you in a
couple of minutes by three hours they do
magic hands
oh okay help me out you've seen
gymnastics you've seen sumo suits you've
seen us in sumo suits and also lots of
doing gymnastics and now we're taking
the two things putting them together
sumo suit gymnastics
it's gymnastics in sumo suit gymnastics
difficulty level a thousand easily we
begin with these forward roll got to get
down I will be the judge I can't get my
head above whatever these are here we go
1,000 yeah whoa lore has it it can't be
done it's called the handstand in sumo
suit this is unprecedented mind blown
right here we go three
- what yeah
hahaha I would say a score of yes we got
a kid spread the legs on the way up so
that now that dream help I'm going to
try it one more time this time instead
of going legs apart cat kicking up into
it which is again Lily would happens
like kick this leg up and then this suit
like with this leg by bottom leg out
from under view that's just one console
just happen here we go you're that siren
that's a potentially dangerous this
could be you although they're your
clothes you've got this bro yeah oh that
was actually bra yeah David you know how
dangerous that was
well that's not even wearing my helmet
right now Olympic crane 20 I'll see you
there
here we go the grand finale the belly
flop balloon contest we can be popping
the balloons with our bellies but if you
guys want to be featured in the next
video comment down below what is your
favorite gummy food the keeper of the
week is Jesse congratulations if you
want to be the people we check the
description down below to find out how
Devon f3 balloons I have two red
balloons
we each have a trampoline we're gonna
one by one pick up the balloon place it
down belly flop where we can pop them
all first they win ready Devon I'm so
ready bro
may the best sumo suit dude win three
two one be good I got a different
scratch okay you are not mine oooh nice
run away run away no hold on oh no I got
it I got it I got it it's so far away I
can't reach it
look Oh glass one there's no flow out
there we go
you're ready you're not even in the
running bro you're like you're gonna be
trying to beat me buzz what for losing
okay alright last one here we go
three two one hello cheer I'm coming in
good oh no wait wait don't worry we'll
talk about it later
[Music]
[Applause]