hey guys so as you guys can see I
finally moved in it needs to need some
work don't worry guys it'll look a lot
less dirty hopefully soon that's a lie
it's probably gonna look the same just
just get it started
that's not the off button I just covered
the lid there we go
dear Ryan can you make a man's not hot
parody pretty sure I could do that this
part there's actually words in here I
thought there was no words the dingo
tingles mmm tingles yet done now you
don't know which one is it you're done
now or you don't know boom boom you
don't know gonna hear that again the
tingles
[Music]
you don't know you don't know I don't
know dear Ryan can you grow your beard
back you look like a [ __ ] without it
good do not dear Ryan can you fart in
front of your friends
this one supposed to be difficult um I
mean if you don't fart but hit your
friends you're not real friends there's
a bunch of fakes actually that could
just be our group of friends we're
pretty disgusting but guys fart in front
of each other all the time it's it's
funny to us for whatever reason it's not
gross any most times we have Barney for
my girlfriend's easy well unless didn't
know you were here
nothing I just I came to say hi hi I'm
Ryan Higa and every single year of each
second of the day
horrible acts of sexism are being
committed by men who don't even know
they're committing them it's called
sexist party many men don't even realize
that by holding in their farts around
women you're not only depriving them of
the joy that is farting but also
systematically teaching them to hold in
their farts in front of men everyone
deserves an equal opportunity to
experience farts and if we truly want to
create equality amongst men and women
this is one very necessary step we must
take we have to do better so please join
the movement and do your part
have a heart sponsor a girl and just
fart thank you
[Music]
you know what no I didn't come here just
to say hi I came here to do this
[Music]
that's when I realized they were letting
me into their group and she did laughs
we pass gas and a knew right then I had
to build it fitting so I just lift up my
leg clench my Pistons as he met out of
big old dear Ryan can you please stop
using this voice for all of your dear
Ryan's I have no idea what voice you're
talking about dear Ryan can you turn
Gucci gang into a country song coochie
language can whoa
this song is a lot more cursing than I
knew they say only heard it on the radio
so I didn't know it was so vulgar spend
10 racks on a new chain my love do
cocaine we got to change that but could
we change that to my grandma loved to
use cool canes there we go that's the
one that's one down Oh Graham ellipses
cooking King my teacher called it tutor
II I feel dirty I can do this we just
clean up the lyrics a little bit easy
[Music]
pollen cost more than your and your mama
living in a pen still have some hope in
the jet PM my grandma's enemy meds
done of is poopy new to me and from a
teacher call for some tutoring bottom
red bottoms cause allergies F your
airline and your company fee for
Christmas like some cigarettes got an M
to be on all my project give me out the
plane I'm a red and yellow purple jet
now little pump line in a private jet
everybody scream in a fresh get little
phone still selling them
they'd all Marvis if in our tech f ll be
get a kitty wave which again panting
rats on a brand new neck chain my
grandma loved to use cocaine by no bo
any rain rather go and buy something
called all fans google ball fans now I
know that means gonna change don't know
what half these words mean hoes and
drugs and money or something
all I know is the title is Gucci game
[Music]
[Laughter]
so leave your questions in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video
[Music]
so please join the movie I'm can dizzy