hey guys I just wanted to thank each and
every one of you for helping us to reach
1 million subscribers I mean I had no
idea that we were gonna go what are you
talking about you didn't do anything
whoo I'm our diesel for shizzle - off
the hizzle drizzle i got you over 20
million views yeah but you got removed
and what about me have to be ninja was
the first one to make 1 million views
how is this possible where are you guys
coming from so what I had over 20
million views you're only getting there
now at least my video is still on
YouTube you did not just go there I'm
gonna pop it down with the rap all right
I'm looking on people get a welcome do
you wanna join us
shut up shut up teas we're supposed to
be thanking the subscribers not fighting
over who got the most views so then you
tell me which one do you like better had
to be ninja or had to be gangsta hmm hmm
huh be ninja the gangster I mean Jenny
and Jenny neither I liked how to be emo
yes anyway we're just here to thank all
of you guys were helping us a room what
now I thought I was your foot hey what
are you doing get away from here get
away yeah yes what though no balls were
hurt in the making of this film
ah