when you ask somebody what do you want
for Christmas you all have that one
friend that gives you that smartass
answer and says something completely out
of your price right now is your chance
to give a smartass answer back here it
Buzzbee you compiled a list of the ten
most highly requested gifts that are out
of your Pricer and how you can still get
them in the cheapest funny way possible
okay Merry Christmas man
is this just cardboard yeah but it used
to be a boxy now it's an Xbox what is
this it's exactly what you asked for
MacBook why'd you give me a picture
Ariana Grande
well look at what she's wearing what fur
yeah cuz I know how much you wanted that
Ferrari I know how long you've been
waiting for one of these so oh my god
diamond ring yep biggest one I could
find what are you smiling about
oh is that yep
fresh new pair of Jordans beats by Trey
Rolex I didn't even know you knew how to
sell oh it's not sewn I needed it it's
exactly what you asked for remember I
don't recall asking for the letters O
and E yeah but you did ask for a
Nintendo II I know how much you love the
movies so here you go it's a DVD frozen
not funny Ryan you know how much I love
that movie come on it was just a joke
maybe you should just let it go
can you stop can't just be serious for
one you know I only wanted this movie so
we can watch it together oh no don't
worry we can still watch it the DV is
actually in there we just have to be
careful when we're cracking the ice
because we don't want to scratch it we
don't want to be watching it and then
halfway through the movie it freezes
forget it
come on gee it was a joke you know what
if you're not even going to try I don't
even know why I bother okay okay look I
was gonna wait until after the joke but
here I wasn't gonna not get you what you
wanted for Christmas
sometime I know here let me go put it in
where's the TV yeah about that um I kind
of to sell it for all the puns in this
video I need to buy materials what we
can still watch on your macbook wait
where's the where's on the match oh you
know what this MacBook might be frozen
to rosin too