hey guys so breakups are one of the many
tough things that people have to go
through and there's a lot out there and
how to deal with it or how to cope with
breakup but there actually isn't that
much and how to break up with someone
and if you've ever had to do that before
you know that sometimes breaking up with
someone can be even harder than getting
broken up with especially if you still
care about the other person which is why
so many people end up using the worst
breakup tactic of all the text message
breakup as most of you know this is one
of the absolute worst ways you can break
up with someone and I know from personal
experience that it is just the worst
feeling ever it's downright rude and
college unless of course they did
something terrible to you and you don't
care about them anymore but if that's
the case you've come to the right place
here are a bunch of other terrible ways
to break up with people and then you no
longer care about hey you ready what
right do it a class we don't have
chemistry anymore exactly why didn't you
flush looks like a turd in the shape of
a C's oh that's cuz you have to tilt
your head to the right now what do you
see just looks like a u now don't you
see I dumped you today you must be
popular on Twitter with all those people
following you huh then how do you
explain all the people I've been seeing
behind your back Oh actually could you
not stand on my right side why cuz I
realize that you're actually not right
for me and it's time I left you is that
hair in a jar yeah it's a part are you
watering it no we're watering we're
growing apart man am I tired are you
tired no wait
well I mean you have been running
through my mind all day I think it's
time we took a break
and done and just put this above you
real quick what is this and why did you
keep the e red oh just to let you know
that I'm already over you know our
relationship is like a broken mirror
it's better to just leave it alone than
to hurt ourselves trying to fix it and
also if you look into it you can see how
much more crazy crackhead you are why
did you tell me to meet you at the gym
if we're just going to sit here oh you
know just to let you know that we're not
working out all right what about this
people they don't see anything I don't
think it's working huh
you might be right maybe we should just
see other people's what are you doing
obviously not you anymore hey can I ask
you a question sure do you like this
movie I get it I know what you're gonna
do what you're gonna break the DVD and
say that you think we should break up
good one what no I was just gonna show
you this and tell you to look up
seriously what you did this whole thing
just to break up with me just to make a
joke no I'm a relationship that's so
little to you that you can make a joke
out of all of this then I have nothing
to be sad about because it was never
real to begin with gee look honestly I I
didn't want to break up with you earlier
and I didn't know how to do it so I made
up all these stupid breakup jokes and
then I realized breaking up isn't tough
at all breaking up is easy most
relationships end because people just
give up on them and I know now
I'm not ready to give up on this not
just yet
either now I'm ready so thank you guys
again so much for watching if you want
to see bloopers and behind-the-scenes
click them on the left if you want to
see the previous video click the one on
the right and if you want to see the
last plenty video we did 10 plenty of
Christmas gifts I think or something
like that click the one in the bottom
see you there
or here or and the bloopers or in the
previous video see you I'm probably not
gonna be there