ever since we came over - my life's
never been the same
who's they used to bring me happiness
joy now just seemed meaningless dump
I wrote a poll the pain that lies
beneath the sphincter of my dreams show
them not art they'll tell thigh of thee
or else the nothing feels right what to
do say it wasn't you alright yes it is
true I am now the number two most
subscribed person on YouTube for some
reason a lot of you guys are more upset
about it than I am
don't get me wrong being number one on
YouTube was such a great honor but how
can it be sad when I just hit 4 million
subscribers wait what play the happy
music yeah yeah that's the flashback
music great anyway so I know I've been
mixing in apples for a little bit and
the reason for that is because I've been
sick in fact I've been sick for a while
now yeah you thought I was gonna do the
same joke for the fourth time no it's
been a while guys I grew up I'm mature
I'm an adult moving on the real reason
why I've been gone for such a long time
is because I just got done filming for
my first TV show appearance that's right
I'm gonna be on a TV show called super
ninjas on Nickelodeon I'm not sure how
much I can say so if this video does get
removed you guys know why right drugs
they take everything away and I already
know what you guys are gonna say in the
comments all Ryan you are such a sell
out you do the mainstream media thumbs
up if you agree and if the 302 view is
you I was actually supposed to play the
lead on a TV show but the reason why I
turned it down is because they wanted me
to remove my youtube videos so before
you call me a sellout think about it
like this I will never ever sell out you
think I'm selling these $3.99 teehee
bands in the store section of kitv.com
for money no and do you think that my
shirt just magically changed into this
new top-of-the-line new release tank top
they can only be for if you
comstor just because i wanted to send it
to you you know I would never do that
because I'm not a sellout but seriously
buy my stuff anyway all jokes aside I
just want to thank you guys once again
for helping me to reach four million
subscribers even though there's a lot of
you I still appreciate each and every
one of you thank you guys so much for
watching and supporting my videos this
bump or or or punch if you're a hater
and I'm not gonna stop hosting videos as
long as I don't get sick with Bieber
fever
Wow hey 1 minute later in the video
right didn't I tell you to stop using
that joke well you know what one minute
earlier in the video Ryan I don't have
to listen to you anymore oh oh yeah
you're in the past I'm older than you
this is a weird video it's been a while
guys let me let me get back into it
until then Shane Dawson exit
to