oh hello there I didn't see you come in
my name is Ryan Higa also known as Ryan
but you can call me Ryan Higa for sure
and I'm a professional badass for years
I used to be that guy
that God that people made fun of for not
being cool enough I'm not taking any
chances my poor Rick Grimes from Walking
Dead and fresh Karl so I created this
program to help you to help you yeah
yeah weak sensitive not bad ask people
to become badass people so that from
this day forward whether you got ten
twenty a hundred feelings inside of you
none of them will ever get broke again
double negative Ryan Higa also known as
aka represents step one get it through
your Helena wait that's step one five
steps to be badass step one get through
your head in order for others to believe
you're a badass you have to first
believe you're a badass so let me ask
yourself this do you ever feel like I
don't not not look like a badass even
though you never not should not feel
like you do not look like badass like
exactly the answer is no don't I
backwards I don't know
now take a good look at yourself right
now if I were to hold a mirror up to
y'all right now you know what you'd see
a weak skinny
cheap tripod from Walmart holding up a
camera but if that camera were to take a
picture of you right now and you were to
upload that picture to iPhoto or some
other picture editing program using a
hustler would you really say that this
is you this is what a badass looks like
no cuz you are a person not a picture on
a piece of paper you're a man even for
you women out there you're a man recap
step 1 get it through your head and
let's move on step 2 stop being a little
right now you're a little you're soft
easily proved yellow-skinned as much as
I hate seeing the B word I might use it
for M passes y'all a bunch of bananas
right now if you want to be a real
badass you can't be no banana double
negative never show weakness
you ever feel pain you must never show
it again real badasses never cry even in
the most painful situations imagine a
poor example you walked into your
brother's room causing you to step on a
lego and now you're trapped don't you
ever cry for help all you have to do is
use the figure-eight maneuver and figure
it out you accidentally poured all your
milk first and realize you ain't got no
cereal left don't you tear a breakdown
in crime so you'll always go
on sale it's no big deal get your bike
are don't you dare lean get up that's
right then brush yourself off limp to
the nearest electronics store and get up
just because you can and last but not
least people keep telling you that your
puns are not funny and yet you see your
puns all over Facebook and 9gag other
website I thought even given you grin so
what do you do
don't you dare complain about it in a
video you create a pun that's so
ridiculously stupid that there's no way
someone else could take credit for it
how you ask just by making mints you
take a mint coffee imperfectly so it's
just right put it in the fridge and boom
next time someone tries to steal your
bad punch to show them what you made
copyright infringement so again to recap
step to stop being a little and also
don't be a banana and let's move on step
move on nobody got time for step 3 step
2 took too long
step 4 have a montage at some point in
every badasses live he or she needs to
become a man quickly by having a montage
a manly montage Mari all you need to do
is do a bunch of manly things and slowly
get better at it until you become the
manliest a man while being accompanied
by some hardcore inspiring song because
today I'm gonna be making a man out of
you that's right our hardcore inspiring
song comes from none other than the
movie line
[Music]
[Applause]
Ryan what'd you just say that Disney
song
step 5 live on the edge true badass
lives their lives however they want
badass has never played sing hey make
sure you throw that as soon as you light
it coz that fuse burns pretty fast
badasses never follow the rules yeah
that's not a joke there's nothing badass
about drinking and driving don't do it
and always recycle most importantly true
badasses never look at explosion
especially not the explosion of one's
mind yeah
now beat that that wasn't more badass
than you touching the magical green ball
didn't even put your whole hand on it so
yes it was fine watch me drink and drive
they're not even old enough to drive
yeah but my future self is
oh no I'm not gonna do that where'd you
get that anyway give me that
come on future me please please a sign
it's not a joke there's nothing badass
for drinking and driving don't do it
get in and put these on I think god that
was a dud
could I put my finger off oh yeah and
always recycle
click here to watch my full Milan cover
reflection
[Music]