if you ever posted a video on youtube
you know that there's a bunch of people
called haters they go around and leave
me comments and video responses to you
so on behalf of all of the nice
youtubers out there this is a message to
all of you haters well as always saying
this is a message to all you haters out
there I mean I know I don't have any
haters you know nobody hates on me
nobody hates nigahiga you know excuse me
I don't like your accent
I mean well except for her I hate you
you know and him you're so gay I can't
stand your videos I hate every single
one of them you know why cuz you're
Asian um your lip sticking sucks can't
sing I I don't like it that your eyes
are never hoping when I'm talking to you
really to me you know we depend on
people and I want to throw a rice bowl
at you and hit you in the face the ninja
glare was the worst song I've ever heard
in my freakin life yogi who ever beat
you
I'm just kidding you don't hate comments
they don't even bother me anymore
in fact sometimes it's pretty funny
they're all like open your eyes your
stupid Asian and I'm like what and I
know I said this before but if this is
not open to you
you better open your eyes all right so I
was getting a little off-topic I'm just
gonna give the message right now for all
you haters out there I know that you
guys are probably only leaving these
comments because you are bored or
something and maybe a lot of you are
going through a hard time right now but
trust me if you stop hating and start
loving you will go places in life but
overall I appreciate the fact that you
guys even comment on my videos and I
really hope this video doesn't offend
you because I want all of you haters to
come back and leave more comments and
finally for all you haters out there
remember I love you
and if this video does cause me to have
you been more haters and you just I
always know that there's someone that
will always love me my mom right mom get
out of my house