hey guys it's a lot of you guys already
know but I used to be a huge gamer
almost to the point of addiction I'm one
of those people that once I really get
into something I go 100 percent I get
super into it well in the past few years
I actually haven't played many games at
all I purposely stopped myself from
buying games because I I mean I was like
a drug addict if the game is in my house
I'm gonna play no matter how hard I
tried to even if someone hides it for me
I'm gonna fight I'm gonna sniff it out I
guess that would make me more like a dog
actually but like a drug addict dog in
the drugs are games and it's a gaming
dog what what am I talking about like I
was saying before I so rudely
interrupted myself haven't played or
gotten into gaming in a very long time
up until recently it's right I relapsed
I mean it's definitely not as bad as
before but I once again gave in to my
demon that is gaming and even though
it's been a while I think because I was
so into gaming in the past that once I
started gaming again it was it was just
like riding a bike I went through all
the stages that most gamers go through
in less than a week but you've ever
really got it into a game you know
exactly what stages I'm talking about
Stage one is like when you first start
playing and you're all like I can get it
I'm just playing for fun oh I died haha
who cares
stays chewed you're like I kind of got
it this is starting to get fun yeah each
three got it down I'm starting to get
pretty good Stage four I'm really good
actually a while Stage five I'm damn
good this is getting serious this is not
a game anymore
and of course stage sick this is not a
game anymore what are you doing if
you've ever really been into gaming you
know exactly what I'm talking about
don't even try to deny it isn't there's
nothing to be embarrassed about it
happens to the best of us the best of us
anyway if you guys don't already know I
make these videos off things that really
inspire and after such a long time
playing online has really inspired me
not the games but the people the gaming
world can be the most fun place ever but
at the same time if you're gonna join it
you also have to deal with the most
annoying people ever the thing is when I
was playing video games a few years ago
it was already bad it is worse now there
was always the same types of annoying
people but now there's just more of them
and that's why today I'm gonna be
talking about the most annoying gamers
on the internet Makoti it makes way more
sense to say most annoying gamers online
when Marvel just sounds dumb Makoti and
because I already know I'm gonna get
comments about this before I get started
I know a lot of these examples are gonna
be geared around guys and it's not meant
to be sexist at all I know gaming isn't
all
girl keepers - all right but these were
inspired from real personal experiences
and majority of the time if not all the
time it was a guy and let's just be real
there are more guy gamers and there are
girls at least for the games that I'm
gonna be talking about it's not sexist
it's just the fact I sounded bad it's
not that wasn't sexist I what you I'm
scared
gender equality control so this is the
most obvious one so I'll just get it out
of the way and this point everybody
knows what a troll is you don't have to
be a gamer to know what that is the goal
of a troll is simple to upset or anger
other people there are trolls everywhere
but in gaming they're the most
successful not only can they annoy you
with words but in a way they can also
annoy you physically like they can
actually ruin gameplay by doing things
like purposely blocking you so that you
can't move anywhere or friendly firing
when you hurt your own teammates and of
course you can't forget that trolls also
love to verbally annoy you as well
pretty much all just use the same nine
year old tech like mocking everything
you say in the stupid voice for saying
the lamest your mom jokes dude you got
any flash banks flash bang your mom dude
that's gross your mom's gross I don't
even have a mom your mom is okay the
best mom is the best mr. talkie mushroom
this next guy I call the shiitake
mushroom because mushrooms are a fungus
and that's exactly what this guy is
talking fungus that is a menace to the
game like the troche you're talking
mushrooms aren't trying to ruin the game
for you they take the game serious so
serious at the moment something bad
happens they be into shiitake the entire
rest of the game I actually think these
guys are even more stupid than the
trolls it's almost every single one of
them uses the exact same unoriginal
overly use insults and phrases every
single time get ready man bro speak
English you chinese mo get shrekt gotta
speak English UK mother Sookie murder
you would hate us yeah I'm from the US
but I'm not gonna lie the majority of
these shiitake mushrooms that I came
across
90% American but I also could just be
the server I play and so or maybe that's
just because I can't understand the
other languages but you guys can let me
know the noob caller if you don't know
what a noob is by now then you're a noob
right there is exactly when new colors
onobu someone new to the game and new
cars are people who absolutely must let
you and everyone else in the game know
that he or she gender equality is a noob
or at least plays like one and new
crawlers are kind of like YouTube
comments they look for every single
little mistake so that they can call you
out on it well this is so fake in 6
minutes and 36 seconds you can clearly
see the fishing line they messed up they
were clearly wearing a different shirt
earlier did anyone else notice that he
spelled the word wrong in the title for
the new colors yeah we did that on
purpose
so who's the noob now that's right
you're the noob no the afk people who go
afk or away from keyboard may not sound
like the most annoying thing in the
world but when you're playing a game
online and you're playing with other
people going afk mid game is not just
annoying it's really rude but if you're
not gonna be playing go play
single-player go play with yourself
that's what she said
or he as well if you're gonna play
online you're playing with real people
so commit to it imagine going afk in
real life like say if you were on a date
so I mean what was it like oh boy AF can
when you're driving your friends hey
where are we going I think we just
missed the time or even going afk when
you're vlogging the excuses guy this guy
is so damn good and so good at
everything that if he ever loses or gets
anything wrong it's never his fault ever
he always has to have an excuse for
losing that's everything but himself
it's cuz my team is so bad another team
is definitely hacked my computer lags so
much it's cuz I'm so drunk right now
it's cuz I'm high because I let my
little brother play okay or or sister or
sister the desperate guy so like I
mentioned before there's a lot of girl
gamers but in my experience you just
don't come across in as often in fact
most of the time it's guys so what a
gamer girl reveals that she's a girl by
either talking on the mic or her
username or profile picture or whatever
that's when these guys come out the
desperate guys and these guys are all
the same they do whatever it takes to
get the girl's attention but just in
slightly different ways first off you
got the suck ups they go out of their
way to compliment every single little
thing she does well and cheer up for
every little thing she does wrong
nice job best kill I see all day order
you got the trihard guys these are the
guys who try to impress the girls by
saying how good they are at this game
normally but this is just their off days
yeah this is a this action Matt low
level account I have three high ranking
accounts like challenger low believes
not really and of course just like
anywhere else in the internet you got
the douches hey hi I got two words for
you what let the mic abuser I mean it's
pretty self-explanatory these people are
the reason why the mute button was
invented and sometimes they're not even
doing it on purpose they're just
annoying by accident they're unaware
that their mic is a little too close and
we can hear every single breath that
they take they get a little too into the
game so they start shouting which like
blows the speakers and your headphones
they top in the phone or like to anyone
else in the room with their mic on so
that we all have to listen to it and of
course my favorite of all is a mic DJ
the guy who was likes to play music for
everyone there is my keep your music to
yourself the bossy guy now one guy on
the team that always gets so mad at
everyone else because they're not doing
exactly what he told them to do he
thinks he's so much better than everyone
else in the team and we all should be
following his exact orders all right
Derek you know peel off cover left
that's your area
don't let anyone through Sean peel off
to the right I'm gonna flank straight up
the middle meet at the rendezvous point
Roger Roger Roger
on my mark
[Music]
no no no Jerry it's right fine newsflash
bossy guy you're not my boss isn't that
something it's a reference to something
I think it is I think I just made that
up and I make a movie one day that's
going in stat [ __ ] standards are
people that only care about their stats
they do whatever it takes to have a good
score but have no consideration for the
team whatsoever and last but not least
and one of the most irritating the rage
quitters when things aren't going their
way they just quit but these aren't just
regular quitters exactly how it sounds
they're quitters with you don't know
what that means you're some examples and
realize that peace of food won't come
off the dish rage would just hide your
shoes and the laces came untied again
rage quit you didn't get to complete
your entire poop and now you have to
keep wiping over and over and over rage
quit
think you got something on your face bro
oh it's just Nutella well learn how to
eat Lube agree not to go wash myself off
you can't just move out of the way are
you seriously mocking me right now mom's
gonna mock you Hey look what what the
hell is that a fact
you see annoying gamers are like a virus
the more you come in contact with them
the more likely it's going to spread and
create even more annoying gamers until
well that's all there is left so please
won't you join me the gaming world is
already a dark place as it is
let's end this vicious cycle of hate
help us prevent the spread of annoying
gamers by spreading love and happiness
and joy Wow thank you you know if you
didn't do that I I would have stooped to
his level I would have shot him I would
have friendly fired I would have became
an annoying gamer too and this vicious
cycle would keep going hey hi I got two
words for you what gender equality so
thank you guys so much for watching if
you want to see bloopers and behind the
scenes click to the left and you want to
see the previous video fits the one on
the right and if you don't want to click
either of those and just sing along with
me
[Music]