hey guys so I play basketball at a
public park a lot and I was kind of
inspired to make this video and there's
not just ages at this part there's every
ethnicity that goes there black white
Indian Hispanic pretty much every single
race you can think of have you've ever
been to a public basketball park you
know exactly what I'm talking about when
I say there's a lot of racist jokes that
goes on there and for some reason most
of them are targeted towards the Asian
for example when we're picking teams
they'll point at me and say give me
Jeremy Lin over there and obviously I
don't look like him it's just the fact
that I'm playing basketball and I'm
Asian and there's two ways that I could
easily take that I could add their act
really offended and say damn bro that's
racist or I could just make a joke out
of it and make it seem like it's not a
big deal which is what I usually do and
it works or another example I would have
passed the bond got stolen out wouldn't
be surprised if one of my teammates said
hey come on you gotta open your eyes bro
because Asians have small eyes right or
even if they were to pass the ball and
got stolen by another Asian on the other
team they would say something like oh my
bad I thought you were the Jeremy Lin on
my team what you agents look alike
because we all look exactly the same
right or even sometimes when they ask me
the score so Jeremy Lin what's the score
and I'd be like she's not sure but I
thought all you Asians were supposed to
be good at math well no but actually I
think the score is seven 200 or what
nothing that's the score Oh Oh to seven
well you mean it so to seven no no it's
all to seven two O's what
double-oh-seven sad part is I actually
said that joke at the park once and the
reaction is probably the same as you
guys you know nobody nobody laughed
anyway this is probably another
unpopular opinion that I should keep to
myself but I'm not going to I'm just
gonna be completely honest with you guys
I personally do not get offended by
Asian stereotypes anymore because if you
really think about it stereotypes not
just ages stereotypes but all
stereotypes from other ethnicities are
somewhat based off of true and rather
than getting offended by them and trying
to deny it I think it's a lot better if
you were to accept the stereotype so
that we can break through them instead
now before all my fellow Asian people
attacked me for this opinion just think
about it I know that most Asian
stereotypes aren't hugely
over-exaggerated and they definitely
don't apply to everyone but in general
stereotypes come from some truth and
that's why they should be offensive to
you like for example when I say Asian
stereotypes I know one of the first
things that come to mind when you look
at me is that oh he's Asian and we all
know the stereotype for Asians is that
he has a little well Sony or Yamaha or
some other kind of type of Asian stereo
and you're absolutely right I have a
little Sony stereo right
my point is some of my fellow agents out
there I used to be one of those people
that got insulted by Asian stereotypes
and I used to deny that they weren't
true but the thing is that's never gonna
work
Asian stereotypes aren't going anywhere
because they are based off of true
rather than being offending and trying
to deny stereotypes I say just own it
and poopy belong don't give them the
satisfaction of being insulted for
example one of the most common Asian
stereotypes is that all Asians have
squinty eyes obviously it's an
exaggeration and it doesn't apply to
every Asian but statistically it's true
agents have smaller eyes it's not even
an insult to me in fact it's better to
have small eyes we can get away with
falling asleep in class and if a
professor or teacher were to tell us to
wake up and open our eyes we can say
well that's kind of racist sir okay that
was kind of an insult but I'm Asian so I
can another common Asian stereotype is
that all Asians are good at math now I
don't even know why Asian people get
offended by this one it's a compliment
and again I know the stereotype doesn't
apply to everyone I mean I can name five
Asians off the top of my head that
aren't good at math Sean and Greg Derek
me but for the most part it's true
cystic aliy most Asians around the world
are good at math I think you guys pretty
much get the point but I'm gonna name a
few more Asians have poor English yeah a
lot of Asians - but for those people
it's because English is their second
language in English for their first
language they would sound just like me
and I'm good are their foes not Asian
people my English is that is all Asians
are bad in sports so all Asians are bad
if sports try saying that the jeremy lin
he's so good at dota you don't even know
Asians only eat rice okay this one is a
little racist because it's not true at
all we also eat the noodle all Asians
know martial arts no not all Asians know
martial arts but most martial arts are
from Asia even if that's not true for
everyone why wouldn't you want people to
know that that's cool
kung fu kata take kendo judo Aikido I
can understand why that's a stereotype
Asians have bad teeth okay this one is
an insult because teeth are supposedly
beauty and basically you're saying in
Asians are bad teeth they're not
beautiful I mean but let's be real for a
second you can't really get offended by
this about 50% of all the Asian kids I
knew had braces the other half were
either really lucky or they still do
need braces again don't get offended by
it just own it yeah I got messed-up
teeth but I can get braces what you
gonna do about your face okay you don't
want to say that but that was just an
example all Asians are Chinese know just
because somebody's Asian it doesn't mean
they're Chinese that's like assuming all
white people are Irish or German or some
other type of white and just for the
record because I know this is gonna come
up in the comments I'm Japanese which is
completely different from Chinese like
Jeremy Lin he's trying
do I look anything like that no I'm Way
buffer than he is that's another
stereotype Asians aren't both look at
this huh you see that mountain right
there you see these guns you can't make
fun of you who make fun of yourself I
made a joke about it earlier but one of
the most common stereotypes that people
use as an insult is that Asians have
small well wieners at least for me I'm
not afraid to admit it I got a mini
wiener right here his name is Marley and
he's my miniature wiener dog who's
actually been sitting on my lap this
whole time right next to my little
sausage I believe they're called Smokies
not sure why they're called that
probably cuz they're so small and you
have to hold it like a cigarette not
that I would know how to hold a
cigarette I don't smoke but that is how
I hold my little penis penis isn't dick
you know my little dick dick isn't
Richard Richard is in Richard marks one
of my favorite pianists of all time he's
such an inspiration I always keep a
picture of him right in my left pocket
next to my vagina and last but not least
regions can't drive this is one of the
few stereotypes that I have no idea
where they came from it's not
statistically true personally I'm not a
bad driver I only got into like three
accidents so far and got pulled over
maybe like three or four times for
speeding and running a red light stop
signs you know the common things that
everybody gets oh and of course the
really common driving mistake that
everyone does you know when you put your
armor on the passenger seat to help you
look back cuz you're gonna reverse and
then when you press the gas you realize
you're still in Drive so you have
forward so again I don't know where that
stereotype comes from because it happens
to everybody because even in basketball
attorney Asians are great at drive the
best you know I've been making fun of
him this entire video but Jeremy Lin is
an excellent driver I mean all he does
is drive cuz we all know he is
definitely not a shooter Oh Jeremy hey I
didn't know you were in here you don't
think I can shoot what no I did pretty
sure you just said I can't shoot there
was no obvious joke they give me the
ball where did that come from who passed
me if I wasn't a shooter could I do this
[Music]
even after all that you still can't make
a single I can't shoot so thank you guys
again so much for watching if you want
to see bloopers and behind the scenes
click the one the left if you want to
see the previous video click the one on
the right and once again thank you so
much to Jeremy Lin for being in this
video and also for breaking down the
stereotype that Asians can play
basketball I mean I I can't play
basketball I mean I can I'm just not
that good well yeah at least Jeremy's
good in DotA and basketball I'm not that
good at dota either