alright boys we got one of Jake to loot
kill survive most importantly you're the
last team standing even if that means
it's just one of us left wait so which
objective exactly what you said we all
have one objective but you mean like
four so who is this guy again uh he's a
friend he just hasn't played that much
pub G yeah this is my first time all
right you brought a new girls our
chances
hey we were all noobs at some point plus
he's a gamer he'll catch on quick yeah I
play games you play games what kind of
games you play well I I have a level
seven town hall and clash of clans oh my
gosh clash of clans various all right
look we're going at look at the bat
I say we're gonna know about I say no
don't worry but we trust this drop drops
or poor Tinky Tinky advice video what
happens in a Perez to noble
now where's the new
yo we gotta go now where you think we
are fools right there the water tired by
rostov let's loot those houses right
there cuz I think we're in North
Hollywood because that's Burbank places
don't exist
oh boy you think it's trouble go north
plane one horizontal yeah let's go get
in please get in okay let me see one
time did I do it yes
[Music]
and there's nothing in here keep looking
why are you guys ready to go yeah I'm
good I got a scarf
ranae's boosts I'm ready to go huh right
where you at here I'm here all you got
was a pan that's all there was not for
this whole time that's all you found
I checked the whole room don't worry
about it there's gonna be other house we
gotta go let's go
you got pretty good gear moves about to
move so let's head south you guys what's
so bad about the blue anyway I mean wow
what the hell just don't touch it now
you never heard the song
Dumbo D don't die who's coming in all
right well we got ten left and we're
four of them so if we stick together
with you just got shot in the face are
you still alive it's only an m16 and I
got a little too help but it's your face
how is that gonna help
I don't know we're good all right let's
go what do I do
just shoot something
I got you stay still they still go just
go five more seconds
Oh
damnit I was headed Brian what are you
doing moving our bodies go kill them
there go the hosts we're not ghosts this
is the death camp
Brian what are you doing yeah he's
shooting at us because he thinks the
death cams are Coast and he just used up
all his ammo right last guy right there
revive me it'll be to be won a much
better chance how much to get over there
I don't have a smoke look gonna reload
in second all right we're done that's
your chance
now what are you doing sorry sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
nice good job all you gotta do is revive
me now just press is it not the click
button look get him up the last guy you
can still I don't have any ammo let's
move my mind oh right looting this
alright what is the flip this again see
you now know how to type
[Music]
what the hell that was seriously awesome
hey let's play another one how do you
leave again you said it was escape
button escape button lanes a lot third
space bar I wear this alright let's go
again