alright guys I've narrowed it down
countries all over the United States
I've been taking out the best of the
best
destroy best crew and now that we've
been training for months and months we
are now harder better faster stronger
never oh ah so who's with me
I am rave
you guys are dead
do you know who we are we're best
friends forever like a serious matter if
we practice the sixteen times
alright are you trying to embarrass me
no that's that's the opposite of what
I'm trying to do then what the hell are
you proud of yourself you're proud of
yourself because now we have to do it
again
you know where you are we're best crew
too early no don't you cry don't you cry
ha around Punk don't you cry what are
you a [ __ ] girl you're gonna be like a
little [ __ ] girl just crying yeah you
suck those tears up
you suck them up stop them up all the
way harder it should be all the way up
okay we're good so we're gonna do this
again
right right you guys are they're dead
you know we are what our best crew who
are you bumblebee extreme step team
what are you doing I'm stealing them we
don't do that we're working on boobies
hey why you guys do here oh you know
exactly why we do here what what are we
going
oh you know exactly why we do Arnold you
know exactly what we're doing who is
that
oh you know exact
those with me Oh