yo what's up my name is reine and this
is Braves dad's place for kitchen Dan's
badass like and I'm looking for dancers
enjoy my hella epic dance crew so if you
can dance like this then come on down to
raves dance please for kids you can
dad's badass leg and we'll teach you to
dance like a [ __ ] cat
for the simple payment of $8,000 a week
not only when we teach you the moves you
know like the head spin
or the turtle and you also learn these
moves as well the cartwheel the
handstand
the one handstand the no handstand the
camel toe the whale the worm a worm on
dry land
and who could forget the slug see y'all
thought that Quest Crew was dope we'll
check out my crew best crew so why are
we called best crew uh duh Oh be extreme
step team so leave your craziest coolest
or latest dance move and if I like it
I'll approve it and then you can join my
crew oh I thought of that and that's
what you're gonna be running from reign
peace Oh