i swear
when they dance i just cannot you have
to look at their hair
they're still watching kate this whole
time how does that
do that i don't get it i mean they don't
even
speak korean do they like how can you
love something so much that you can't
even understand
what's there to get man it's a group of
really good looking asian guys that can
sing
and dance well i mean we're a group of
good looking agent
well i mean we can sing
dancing is um no no no
well we're all asian yeah right yes yes
you can learn to sing and dance you
gotta learn to be asian
what makes them so different though it's
because they're all like
dog caterpillars they got rows of abs
nine wait why don't we just do that then
do what
why don't we just make a group why don't
we why don't we make a k-pop band
yeah yeah yeah no no no no no guys look
you just said yourself we
can't sing or dance well i mean we can
all throw in ourselves
yeah yeah yeah right yeah but that
doesn't negate the fact that
we can't speak korean wait david's
korean yeah he's korean dude you're
super korean
i'm pretty korean wait but can you speak
it
kinda okay how do you say girl you have
beautiful eyes
yojan
yo how do you say how do you say like
look at us sexy guys
sexy
david how do you say like hey girl
dude girl is yoja
[ __ ] is dawn
yo you already know capital b
with a lower case
foreign
oh you thought we couldn't dance
m
foreign
wait what's wrong
i kind of have to go poop that's
disgusting
and so immature
not science
don't size