[Music]
yeah Kumiko tanka involtini gavage
itachi uchiha pages or el gol de los
Angelino George my boy economy of
birthday silane mr. Mendoza teaching the
funda to Cabo
Oh :
all right fandom name group color new
song so we got to figure out today easy
why are we doing this again that's what
we need in order to be a kpop fan since
who everyone the comments I help fandom
in fandom name is basically what the
fans called himself my old like Justin
Bieber fan as a call of believers don't
we already have a fandom name the DJ
army according to the comments that's
already taken by some other group called
like behind the scenes or well since our
first and only song is about poop again
thank you for the demon what maybe
something like uh k poopers yeah yeah
that make sense I don't care that's
pretty cool but um do you think the fans
would like being called poopers yeah
okay yeah most of our fans are girls and
girls like poop jokes so cool alright we
got to find the name next thing on the
list we got a group color I'm just gonna
throw it out there I personally like
silver I could use silver right but
that's like second place what gold is
first silver second gold gold doll I
would get it gold
y'all saying you know you know not me no
no I don't know what you're saying so
what color do you want to choose gold oh
me too
okay well we have two for gold two for
silver and Jun be our tiebreaker I'm
fine with either guess which one you
prefer yeah which was better gold or
silver obviously gold right you go and
you pick one you 88 can we do both yeah
I'll do why not actually I never really
thought of that before you I never seem
to color yeah and we can have like the
glowsticks that tape off your cards like
it has a silver and gold option and we
can have our logos like we yeah yeah
yeah god that is the dumbest idea ever
silver and gold doesn't even go together
who's gonna buy these glow sticks I'm
not putting my money for that garbage
man you know what we'll just come back
to it because it's not that important
what we really need to figure out your
song we haven't had a song since last
year well whatever it's about I better
get some lines in this one because you
took all the lines last time obviously
I'm the leader
you're the leader are you kidding me I'm
obviously the lead
have you not read my twitter feed
all say you read the comments there like
everybody's least favorite not because
you hog all the line okay I'm pretty
sure JUnit everyone's least favorite I
don't care about being the leader I just
better be higher than June okay I think
I'm about 2nd place because I like
silver what silver you just said would
you like gone now you're flip-flopping
but all of a sudden okay all I know is
I'd better be higher than Mary okay on
the barbie on the bottom all right all
right
okay we're not gonna get anywhere like
this there's only one way to figure out
when you leader and how we make a song
with everybody in it equally and we just
see what happens okay but what's the
song going to be about exactly what
we've been talking about this whole time
who's it going to be
oh my god that better not be the name of
the song that is so cheap okay
[Music]
repend okeyday our coffee store
boomerang attitude I go country got
anything
I'm gonna draw one of us will rise the
rest will fall
[Music]
oh did you a hot guy out
no Jackie
can I see can
Dickens mother
we're gonna break out me the rest oh
please we got it can Tony
John Johnny targeted go yeah you wanna
go hyung Jionni are fancy youngsters on
a goal on the Easter song wait a minute
it's already happening No
[Music]
he's got a key
yes June month I ain't I
we're gonna break down cigarettes away
[Music]
what is live to me
Oh God
ah
[Music]
Jen everything you wait what are you
guys doing why do you look like that but
then we're happy for you
we really are ever since you left the
group you can't really talk to the rest
of us
yeah we just be doing all we can to get
by but only been one week well that's
been a really tough week yeah yeah seven
days a long time why are you even
talking to the traitor he wants us you
let us know all that you're talking to
the manager in your little contract why
is it here actually that's exactly why
I'm here
[Music]
this pretty much guaranteed me fame
money and everything that we've been
working forward together as a group but
it says I have to do this alone without
you guys which is why I felt the need to
come here and do this
[Music]
what's the point of fame and fortune not
would you guys
[Music]
the hell are you thinking
and now you're gonna take it the money
and shared it with them I'll tame and
rip this man comes alright now we're
going to put this back together or it's
like we could tape it and glue I have to
glue in the car for you oh well you're
taking a lot of pieces that you know
it's not good play or do or don't
suppose vixen told you gold and silver
to match hold it
idiot Oh
Oh and so I signs outside science on
regular tree why what did they only tell
you alright guys there it's good let it
go
guys it's in my email I can print out
[Music]
[Applause]
breakup is allegedly
luckily
[Music]
gonna break out MIGA less complete
[Applause]
obviously I'm the leader
oh yeah cuz you have all the line that's
good yeah
what am i doing it over don't know