do you write can you make a boy bad
music video about games we got asked to
do something very similar before but I
think it was about um posted sandwiches
[Music]
yep that's what it was there's a small
part of a bigger deer Ryan I remember
because so many of you were commenting
about how you wanted the full version of
this song you guys are commenting more
about that small part that dear Ryan
than you were about the rest of the
videos so that was shocking guys I
recorded the entire song in my closet
using a very cheap microphone and using
stock GarageBand that it comes with
every single Mac and it sounded awesome
so yeah I just try probably sort of put
it on I it was just kidding in the so
bad we were trying to parody basically
90's boy band it's back in the 90s way
if you are alive then didn't seem cringy
then but you go and watch them now it's
a straight-up big old-fashioned
cringefest why do that you'd have to say
it like that
I am so off topic back to the video hey
guys I probably should have comment on
this first but as you can see the vlog
room has finally completed crazy of
Shawn and Dana
they actually surprised me and created
this whole thing without me knowing what
it was gonna be and I love it they have
a second channel video coming soon
showing the whole thing anyway so now
that everything is set and I'm all moved
in we can finally get back into the
swing of things I know I know we've been
a little slow on posting videos lately
that's you know carrying over from last
year as well it's completely my fault
not only because of the whole moving
situation getting messed up but also
because well I I don't know how else to
say this but I I relapsed again um it's
hard for me to talk about as some of you
guys already know I have had a very
dangerous addiction to well
[Music]
I've had a dangerous addiction to it
when I get stressed out I okay find this
bit is not funny addiction is a real
thing I know see this is just paper I
don't actually smoke this was root beer
and well this one's real as you guys
know I kind of do have an addiction to
energy drinks but you know what's the
big deal nobody ever gets hurt from
energy my chest
the real dangerous addiction I relapse
into was well gaming too much energy
drinks and I know I know a lot of you
think that this is some kind of joke
it's not when I get really into games it
harms every aspect of my life because
I'm one of those people that you know
when I get into a game I get really into
it you know because it's fun my eating
patterns changed because I forget to eat
a lot of times I skip meals when I'm
playing games free time that I would
normally use to work out or go hang out
with people in real life go straight to
gaming I'm constantly sleep-deprived
because I keep pushing myself making
four hours is enough sleep three hours
so you still feel okay - it's not that
bad well the sun's already up so I might
as well stay up I mean I got these I
don't really need it I'm sure a lot of
you gamers have very similar experiences
maybe not all of you but one of the
biggest things that gaming can take a
toll on relationships because more than
anything gaming takes away your time and
your attention and that's one of the
most important things you need for a
relationship so if you're a hardcore
gamer and you want to have a
relationship really think about it
before you get into one you're probably
gonna have to sacrifice something things
are gonna change
I'm not saying it's not possible to have
both there's always a balance but trust
me something has got to give and it's
just not gonna be the same so unless
he's behind for a little bit just
protect me okay I'll admit it I did
forget that I agreed to go shopping with
you today but um in my defense I do
recall saying I didn't want to really is
it that much to ask you spend a few
hours with me together well I mean we
spend tons of hours together why does it
have to be out shopping like
need anything new we own that we have
groceries it's not about shopping it's
about spending quality time together
just you and me except all you want to
do is play your stupid little games
their stupid friends why can't we just
spend quality time together here doing
what playing your games well yeah I mean
you just said that it's not about what
we do it's just supposed to be
g-g-gee come on alright guys I'm back
let's do this even though you probably
don't want us to here we go again
[Music]
so muted my mic ever fought all night I
realize that
is really much spending time and why
[Music]
inside a room controller just for you me
no makeup to impress just like a
[Music]
to
we're suffer just for you
- yeah my friends might be mad we first
added to the chatty but give it a run or
two and you see we all got each other's
fast run to dip there's no more room in
us what Lobby house it up just for you
Oh we'll just give there a clue
[Music]
by that
on a completely unrelated note and I
just saw one thing here what's up man
thank God for
[Music]
voiceover just for you we can live the
dream if you if you be my player
come back he's ready to hop on it takes
the guys who are you playing with uh
yeah what's going on here
yeah we can already started I don't
think I got a text from you or any of
the other what is it what what is this
you guys starting another group without
me
yeah I mean look we kind of noticed that
your kta has been well let's just say
pretty average lately yeah I might have
dropped a little it's only because I've
been working so hard like one of us has
to pay for the virtual currency and even
then you didn't need to start without me
there's still room for one more
well yeah you know believe it or not
ever since we kicked Derek out dude he's
been practicing and he got really good
so you replaced me with Derek yeah wanna
go shopping what I want to go shopping
so leave your questions in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video
[Music]
[Laughter]
even then even then they like some speed
[Music]