what color is the dress is it black and
blue or white and gold or maybe a
different color altogether scientists
have tried to science it theorists have
attempted to theorize so what is the
true answer is suddenly infamous
question find out next on an all new
episode of brain gum hello welcome to
brain gummies and today we are gonna be
solving the mystery of the ever so
popular color changing dress but before
we do that it's important that we warm
up our brains a little bit first I have
my volunteer here named Ryan and he's
gonna be participating in brain ganas
aha that was the first test did you
realize Ryan that we actually already
did the intro sequence and that was the
second time we showed him how yeah I
mean that just happened right before you
introduced yourself see just like Ryan
here your brain is not warm enough to be
ready for such a difficult question such
as what color is the dress so what we
need to do first is warm up that brain
with a little brain ganas you see if you
thought the title sequence was gonna
start again then you were completely
wrong on to our first game it's called
the math psyche so this is for all of
you at home just follow along I'm gonna
put up a number of fingers behind my
back but before I reveal what that is I
want all of you at home to pick a number
in your head got it
good now add five to your original
number whatever number you're at now
subtract one and now add two now
subtract your original number that you
started off with because the number
you're at right now is the exact number
of fingers I have up behind my back
that's right six welcome to brain ganas
our next game is called the Train Saw
Massacre I'm gonna be using my volunteer
Ryan but I want all of you at home to
follow along so Ryan if two trains are
on the same track headed towards one in
the train a is going 50 miles per hour
while train B is going 50 kilometres an
hour
assuming there's no wind and both trains
left the station at the same time what
is most likely to be yelled out by the
passengers on train a is it a all of the
above B help C no or D let go
how am I supposed to I guess see so
close the answers B C and D actually
would have been correct if we were
talking about train B because it's
probably filled with foreigners being
that they measure in kilometers however
the question was about train a measured
in miles brow which means most of the
passengers were Americans and those are
not what Americans would say in that
scenario I mean even with that that all
that's left is the letter A all of the
above and there's nothing else above it
so wrong again the answer is actually a
all of the above you have to think
outside of the box with box you see the
correct answers were e who cares F this
is so dumb G this needs to stop because
if it doesn't or a to try I couldn't
even see those though so that's not
really fair right you have to see the
full picture Ryan I mean after all this
is brain gummit and finally we have our
last game it's called what do you see on
the screen probably one of our simpler
games all you have to do is tell me what
do you see on the screen Ryan um the
letter A wrong the correct answer is a
color red oh I thought you were talking
next question what do you see on the
screen now do you see the color blue yes
wrong again the correct answer is the
letter A but you're the one that has the
next question what do you see on the
screen now well I see the letter A and
it's colored grey grey spelled with an A
or with an E does it matter not really
okay I guess with an A then wrong the
answer we were looking for gray with an
even still wrong what the correct answer
we were looking for was the letter A
colored a light black I don't think
that's even in however if we were to
darken this gray colored a to the color
black what do you see on the screen now
okay you said that that was the color
black correct and nothing physically
changed in the image from the last one
right indeed okay then the answer has to
be the letter A colored black Ryan that
is absolutely wrong what the correct
answer was a ninety degree rotated
unfinished drawing of pac-man eating a
tic-tac next and final question god what
letter do you see on the screen now what
letter correct and nothing to do with
the color right indeed and it's awesome
stupid answer like an unfinished drawing
of pac-man
actual letter in the English alphabet
that is correct okay this then it has to
be the letter a wrong the correct answer
was an extremely zoomed in picture of
the letter B okay but the letter B is
made up of a bunch of A's so technically
my answer wasn't wrong this time right
wrong again the B is not made from a
bunch of aids then what is it made of
then unfinished pac-man drawing no son
of them and finally now that your brain
is warmed up and ready we'll ask the
question once again what color is the
dress well now that your brain is
prepared you can finally see the full
picture and I'll answer your question
with another question is the dress even
a dress people assumed that it was
addressed when really if you do what
I've been telling you to do throughout
this entire episode and see the full
picture you'll see that this infamous
dress is actually a shirt it's a shirt
how it all makes sense why you have me
doing all those stupid exercise this
whole time everybody was arguing about
the color of the dress but when you look
at the full picture the true answer to
the question is it's a shirt wrong what
the correct answer is actually a
seriously you made me and the audience
go through all of this and you're not
only gonna give us a serious answer I
did answer it the answer is a that makes
no sense what does the letter A have
anything to do with the color of the
dress well not the letter A the answer
is a you have to see the full picture
remember you have to think outside the
box the answer is actually a
all of the above yep and the next time
somebody asks you the question what
color is the dress all you have to do is
say a all of the above who cares this is
so stupid this needs to stop because if
it doesn't if it doesn't then what two
trains see now you're on the right track
so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see bloopers and
behind the scenes click on the left if
you want to see the previous video click
the one on the right and so I know you
guys are already gonna ask the colors
that I see are actually the colors