the age of consent is 12 in the
Philippines
oh I smashed his Porsche door into
another car door and I felt so bad the
rate that we're growing everyone's gonna
die so Ryan could have wrote more Paco's
car went down yeah we're starting this
podcast a little late today drew Clabby
clapper ready just get into it
welcome back to another episode of mouth
to peel podcast welcome back to another
episode we are joined here today with
Paco Leto sitting in the moderator seat
and we have Dara leaky holes
what's sitting in the guest seats eric
is back we have Ryan Higa and I'm the
host seat
yep yeah hot seat I don't know I never
knew what that meant the hot seat really
you know what it means now no we're
gonna like it's like like our knee drill
you want questions yeah all like being
interrogated yeah yeah we're in the
interrogation he would technically be in
the hot seat because right here in the
hot seat today well I mean we're all
talking I'm asking for questions
that'd be nice having you talk more yeah
people don't know this so Derek I mean
you've seen him in videos and stuff he
just got back from China he has been
gone you haven't been in a video for a
long time it's been like a month month
and a half or so yeah but Derek was in
China dancing for the Jabbawockeez yeah
it was fun I basically took a small leap
from arch PC and I started doing
rehearsals in Las Vegas and we're
preparing for our show which was like
pretty much like six weeks over MGM Co
tie which is in China Macau that's a
part of China isn't it cult I know Macau
yeah well I'm sorry go tie is like
saying like the city Macau is like the
town yeah yeah okay so it's a town in
the city that's where you want yes vote
aye yeah that's what we would say to the
taxi drivers cuz there's two strips
right out there so like Vegas strips
yeah there's like a downtown Las Vegas
yeah so when you would tell someone
especially
you didn't speak the same languages and
we would tell him like em gymkata cuz
there was two MGM properties and they
would try to take us to the other one oh
he would tell him coat I so you were
living out there for a bottom little
over a month right yeah pretty much like
six weeks we did the shows we're the
first team to ever have residency out
there they've never had like a team or
an act that stayed on the show or stayed
on the stage for that amount of time
right everyone's always done like
one-off performances or like you know
quick show here and there and then they
leave but they never had one group just
stay so we were the first and just to
give background for people that might
not know Derrick is a before he started
working with us editing and stuff he was
actually a breakdancer and you were in
the job walking show here yeah I guess
yeah he's also a world-class dance
world-class break dancers loan
internationally to perform they laid
real competent like hop top-ranked b-boy
yep but he don't talk about it cuz he's
trying to be all modest and stuff but um
yeah and also he's only the quietest
people in the group extremely modest but
he's actually very physically talented
and can pretty much pick up anything
physical that he tries yeah you guys are
freaking kind very kind shut up honest
dude take a compliment just I mean that
was just people know yeah but it was fun
though I mean we're you know we did the
show seven shows a week we had double
shows so we did two shows a day
sometimes the crowd was like sixteen
hundred people the first show was
probably like the most nerve-racking for
me right because uh they want to make
sure the show ran smooth and I was the
audience they're like how did it differ
from like I'll hear they're so different
how so and out here in America like
people will cheer they'll clap they'll
give you a standing ovation to laugh out
there it's like it's just crickets what
don't they'll clap and stuff too but you
like almost have to tell them down
probably a respecting like don't
interrupt the performers you know yeah
you think so even even when I saw like a
movie out there it was so crazy just
because their culture is so different um
so at a movie theater yeah I went to a
movie theater and basically i sat
dead center of the theater and I had a
couple on my right-hand side and they
had their cell phones out with their
screen all the way up just like the
brightness yeah just their whole movie
during the whole movie then the cup on
my left was just having a normal
conversation I mean about the movie just
talking that's annoying
yeah and that was like that's just like
the culture out there and like I end up
eventually getting in on my scene
picking a new one thinking it was gonna
be better but it was like the same thing
happening on it so you think that's just
a cultural thing in China or in Macau
it's just a little different it's just a
little different I mean like even like
personal bubble space was different oh I
know that you know why do they get in
your face real close not on purpose
that's just I mean yeah but yeah that's
a culture mm-hmm like if there's room in
an elevator like you can easily go to
the corner but they'll just be like in
your face
so the stereotype I mean I don't know if
I should say this or not go for it you
know stereotype when people you see all
all those videos I'm sure not adults I'm
not saying every single person but yeah
the stereotype is there's you know
Chinese tourists from China mm-hmm or
tend to be known as like kind of well in
our culture rude but all they're
actually it's not even considered rude
it's just part of the culture yeah like
talking during a movie having your
screen brightness like it's like they
give us opposite of what you're saying
it's not like they're trying to be
respectful and not clap for you guys cuz
they don't care about interrupting the
show maybe they're not watching it
completely they had some you know we had
some good nights where like you know
tons of people will clap and laugh but
we also had some bad nights too or it
was just dead quiet and I think
sometimes you got to go
you gotta experience the bad to
appreciate the good right but uh but
yeah it's just different like when
people when foreigners come out here and
they do things that are culturally
different for us we think that they're
rude or yeah you know but they probably
think the same thing about us when we go
over there that's true I mean like when
we went to Japan I felt like I became a
more polite person but I know for a fact
that I was offending probably a lot of
people cuz I don't we don't act the way
they act they're extremely polite
everything they do is super polite and
like down to like I got Yoda at when I
first went out there for like a business
trip because I didn't accept somebody's
business card with two hands why if you
if someone hands you a business card
with two hands and
don't get used to hands to grab it from
them that's really disrespectful in
Japan I don't know if that's like
anywhere else but I got yelled at about
you when you receive it well yeah and
when you meet them you kind of bow like
when you say hello and stuff but yeah
like those little things and even like
just like slurping when you're eating
ramen and is considered polite yeah or I
don't know if it's polite but it's like
a compliment to the chef yeah right so
like it's not like I can see both sides
yeah like for you know people who
complain about Chinese tourists and you
know they do certain things that we can
are considered to be rude I guess they
probably see Americans go to Japan yeah
you were just there I was just there
yeah you're one of the rudest people
here but you are out there especially
for an American yeah I'm definitely out
there but I have a I'm self aware of
myself a lot more now than I have been
before
right well I'm I'm aware like Oh to that
a little bit if I'm being rude yeah like
to you guys or whatever it's a joke
right it's acceptable do you think is
not acceptable no I think it's fine
because we know you exactly but most
people I think we see it from a
third-person perspective when you're
like at a restaurant or something and
you do something you think is funny i
order for example what i don't know just
like yelling and joking with the waiter
that who might not be having a good day
and you're just assuming that you're
making their day I'm making you could be
a waiter that's why and so like you go
through repetition all the time and so
to have someone like like cuz usually
when I joke with him it's like a
compliment type of thing - uh-huh
let me ask you this right and when you
introduce people to Paco do you have
like a disclaimer to a certain degree
yeah depending what I mean I'm not like
a very like oh he's different
mm-hmm um a lot of people say oh I met
Paco epic oh and then when they see
their reaction to how they felt about
you because of everything oh he's funny
and it's like okay yeah I'm he's stupid
he does dumb things but if it's like
yeah I met Paco and they don't and they
stop there it's like yeah I'm sorry it's
like the three dots
we don't know lady did he get naked in
front of you we don't know like who
knows what he's doing I'm predictable
yeah I do a lot of dumb things but
usually it the situation is right I'd
say within was it within the past year
I'm a lot better but in the past you
have a lot better better when we first
met you you were very wild no I was I
was I was actually very conservative in
the very beginning he was it was like
that brief like when you're shy
yeah with entering the group funniest
funny story about entering that when you
were and entered the group
Derek we found out like only this past
year when Paco first came here three
years ago we didn't know this but Derek
didn't like him for a year I didn't know
that it was like two years yeah Derek so
quiet and polite he won't say anything
no the thing was Derek was like even
when he didn't like me he came up he's
like hey you want to do the show with me
it's called wild card and I was like oh
cool so I was like yeah Derek likes me
he wants to do it show it me he must
have liked him by then what to do wild
card yeah I mean I guess what didn't you
like what didn't you like about him
mm-hmm it's not so much that I I don't
know man it's just hard question yeah it
is kind of a difficult question because
I'm awesome you think to me more you
just think you hate me but I'm just all
he said we nobody said they hated you
Derek I just didn't know who you were
I didn't know like what your intentions
were with the group I guess I was kind
of being like the protective guy of the
of the group you know like kinda like
the guard dog you know I mean we've seen
tons of people come in the group and
leave the group for different reasons
maybe they've asked for stuff and maybe
they wanted something like personally
but with Paco I just I had no idea with
him no idea what his intentions were
mm-hmm but I mean like over time he
became a cool guy but you know I did I
did have to make a disclaimer for him -
who did you talk to everyone so you're
about to be my friend but just just he's
different like your disclosure mine's
more like mine's more like crazy
Paco he's a cool guy but he does some
shocking stuff so the thing is if people
know you it's not a big deal
because they know like most of time
you're doing it as a joke yeah
for whatever reason even if it's not
necessarily you know their style of
comedy you'll still do it yeah but but
also I'll do it you do things in front
of people sometimes that you might make
us laugh but they might be like well
that's rude yeah
they don't know you're joking yeah yeah
but that's fine but I say my I say my
disclaimer not not to hate on you or
anything like I say it's for your sake
yeah yeah I know you guys looking out
for me he's like oh he's just joking I
want them to experience like the good
side of you too you know I think I think
okay I'm the one that does like all this
crazy stuff maybe in public where it
could be a little bit more dangerous but
all of us do something crazy to an
extent I mean within our group within
our most viewed groups do that though
yeah a lot of friend groups say things
and do things in front of each other
that they would never do with you know
out in public I'm not the only one who
gets naked in the group yeah well you're
not yeah say who it is but you
definitely get naked for no reason the
most for sure I would say and we don't
ask you to but it makes you guys laugh
it's more like a shocking kind of thing
yeah yeah but it's like if like during
set you know and it's like oh man
everyone's like a little bit down I
noticed we'll make people laugh you know
give them a little bit that's not what I
am a little bit of energy I mean maybe
it helps some of the guys hey you laugh
do though sometimes brightens your day
most the time I see him do this laugh
you know no but he laughs after his
forehead a little bit rub his eyes kind
of like looks around in the corner I'm
like is this really happening yeah this
is gonna be over Derek no see so bad
it's not that bad I mean yes we want to
be unlike Derek was literally almost I
think your opposite I think so dude
quiet guy who's like always like not
gonna say what he's thinking necessarily
gonna be polite and respectful yeah I
think it's an interesting dynamic that
kind of really relationship usually
works if you have two of you in a group
oh you know end up fighting yeah that's
annoying and they end up trying to top
each other and it becomes competitive
yeah I don't know if there's other
friend groups out there that have that
usually friend groups have like one guy
like that mmm but also my experience is
idea of two people who are like that
they have to have like a good
understanding of each other in a
relationship where that it isn't too
much of a competition you know when to
stop cuz there are there are very few
people who can do that that is true yeah
you know what though on based on
entertainment you're the character
people like though cuz you're like the
not at first
well you're like the Naruto basically
sorry not at all I say right I didn't
understand recent I wrote oh dude he's
like the crazy guy who's like that does
things that people might shake their
head at mmm but that's like funny to
people you're like the Ralph from
Simpsons there you go yeah I don't know
who that is but it's a guy that picks
his nose okay all right you also should
give disclaimer for Derek Derek is a
he's a troll he is a troll
yeah let's miss Derek now no he's not
it's not really a dislike Derek time
he'll pretend to be more confused and
confusing than he really is mm-hmm I
think and it's not for see I do things
usually to make you guys laugh Derek
does things to make himself laugh oh I'm
gonna turn on the AC okay I got it
laughs man did what why why do you do
that though is it is it purely just for
your own entertainment sometimes and
you're just like dude this is I'm gonna
make me laugh mmm
sure yeah for sure I mean you know I
don't even do it on purpose I just
naturally do it you know what I mean
do you think he doesn't I think it's
what I think it's your upbringing it
right you said your dad does that to you
yeah my dad and my dad likes to joke a
lot too maybe that's where I get it from
but I don't know I mean I just I just
talk man I just do mean do you this that
great nothing crazy man that is true
Derek just does Derek regardless of
who's around so and how about you Ryan
what mmm what whoever disclaimers oh you
have a disclaimer for Ryan I have a
disclaimer for Ryan
and it's I'm gonna is basically adding
on to what David and Arden said mmm-hmm
so whenever people are like hey man do
you think Brian would want to come out
to this event or to this party or
something like we're trying to push this
thing and be real cool
I don't know Ryan's in Vegas it'd be
real dope my thing is is if you get him
out of that house that's amazing so
that's that's shit-talking that's I'm
doing my disclaim we're doing our
disclaimer to help so that when they
meet you they're not like oh I should be
offended yeah for saying this guy does
not like people he stays home and he
does not want to meet you oh you want to
take it in that they're saying no
there's been a lot of times where we've
had Paco say like something crazy
outlandish about Ryan that Ryan's never
said before to other people like what
there's a lot of times hmm where I I
mean it's it's just happened so often
I'm just like what did I say that or
what did I do that
and I'm just like and then you wouldn't
go would you okay yeah but I wouldn't
tell it to them I'm being honest man
that's not necessarily being honest
sometimes shooting yourself down this
became a therapy session hey you know
what every episode I mean is a therapy
session I know but it's fun they're a
piece of Gator we could all have therapy
I mean there's there's no um you should
be a stigma on that Oh is there a flare
up piece eNOS of the week not bad come
on don't owe me thinking it was a penis
thing actually like therapy's actually I
think is really helpful because I I had
a heart-to-heart talk with you yesterday
and it's actually like really good to
just air out everything rather than like
we did that in private yeah but now you
can tell the podcast in the world like
why you bring that up are you gonna tell
us I mean we you know like I've just
been going through some rough times and
off-camera like I may I may look like
pretty sad and stuff on camera but off
camera I really got to talk to Ryan
about some personal stuff that's
happening in my life and yeah it was it
was really good to air it out and you
gave me some like helpful information
and direction and just advice that I
feel as I
I need to hear so and that's good I
don't want to pry if it's too private
you know but I guess for viewers that it
could be going through something similar
you you know maybe you can give them
like some general advice that would you
guys spoke about you know if you don't
feel comfortable talking just bring up
to the point that you want to talk about
it I mean to summon up I'm basically
going through a breakup and you know
it's real tough you know coming out from
a long relationship and I just you know
I felt lost I felt confused felt like
inadequate and this guy over here just
like really like instilled some some
good words back into me and I think if
anyone is having like some similar
trouble like that it's probably best
that's turned your friends and talked to
each other rather than just holding it
in because those thoughts can go deeper
and deeper and deeper and that stuff can
manifest into something like real
negative well I think the reason why I
even said anything is because I mean we
could I mean I could see it that there
was like something bothering you and
then I'm like you and that I like to
hold in my own feeling like I'm like I'm
not gonna bother someone else yes and
like it's not gonna help me you know
even though it does it does help even if
you're like me or Derek where you just
don't like to talk about your feelings
and I don't know that's a bringing thing
or just personality thing but it's
literally the opposite of some like Paco
it when you have issues you literally
hey can we talk yeah like I would never
say that Derek would never say that you
know but unless I unless I go to him or
you know vice versa and I feel that I
feel that like like of course I'm going
through some stuff and like in my head
what's the point in calling someone else
too everyone's got their own problems
you know like why would I want to bring
my problems on to someone else or yeah
but it was actually really helpful to
just kind of like talk it through right
so I would recommend that yeah yeah and
I think from my perspective because
we're very different like you guys said
the reason why I bring up my problems
because I know other people have
different perspectives and that they
have a view that you know maybe could
show me oh I didn't consider this you
know maybe you know and sometimes we get
too caught up in our own thoughts and we
overthink situations and we start going
down a 10
that's like not even logical or possible
but it's because we're so consumed in
this that having someone else from an
outside view speaking to our lives
especially someone who cares about us
and will be real with us and not
sugarcoat it like that that's always
helpful and that's what I think and
that's why I like I appreciate you guys
well I think the number one thing that
we came to as a conclusion yesterday and
I don't I don't mean without having to
say too much you can talk about it if
you want but I think the number one
thing that I think I learned not
yesterday would I was telling you and I
think I told you too in the in the past
but it was that it's okay to feel shitty
like you should feel shitty because we
were I mean we were talking over like a
couple of drinks and I was just worried
like I've seen people when they go
through that kind of stuff they you know
whether they smoke or they drink or they
do whatever they can to kind of escape
it but it's not you're not really
escaping anything like you're just
putting it off and it's gonna let it
build yeah like it's just gonna get
worse and worse and worse and the worse
it gets the more you drink your smoke to
cover it up and it just keeps building
it's not going anywhere
you might feel fine because you're high
or you're drunk but it's it's just
building so at some point you got to
face it and you're if you let it build
more it's just gonna be worse later down
the road yeah that's the way I see it at
least and I think it's okay to just like
like you should be feeling like [ __ ]
like don't try and like avoid it because
you got a face at some point yeah yeah
one thing I learned over in China was
actually like something that I the whole
China trip felt like fate to me with the
conversations I had with people and the
things that I learned and one of the
things I learned over there was that
like you know I was taught like a 10 a
10 rule 10 rule a week kind of thing
which is uh if you have like a lot of
stresses in your life you have like a
lot of depression or issues that you're
going through like you know try to
maximize that to ten and what do you
think is really worth that effort to
stress over so for example if you're
stress about money you're stressed about
like you know your situation your living
situation that's already two things you
know and you only have eight left and if
you give that a week you know you could
pile on a lot of things in in a list of
ten you know so what really deserves
your time
what really deserves like your energy to
really feel negative about something
so you're saying like the you only have
the capacity to care about ten things is
that what you're saying yeah and those
10 things should be very valuable like
it should really be something that makes
that list rather than like you know
there's tons of little things that
people are always stressed about you
know yeah finance
I don't know social media the right
shoes I don't know you know like
everyone's got their own problems but is
it really worth like to make artists
smart where did you hear that from like
it sounds like a therapist John it was
actually from a girl that I met out
there and she told me like you know
that's how she copes with stuff she also
told me like you know she has like this
five year rule or something like that
where if something is not gonna affect
you in five years and you shouldn't put
that much effort into it I was like
that's pretty interesting either
something's not gonna I've never really
thought of it like that so it was it was
kind of cool to hear your different
perspectives kind of like how you said
you know yeah yeah and I I think just
where the sake of it that for the
disclaimer and everything like just
because you're going through a breakup
and everything doesn't mean you have any
ill-will towards Eric alright like oh no
yeah I think that's something we should
bring up yeah I would never like wish
anything bad upon her we've had you know
we've had a good relationship and I
don't want nobody to tweet negative
things to her right bad comments we you
know we had a clean break up is just
tough yeah yeah yeah such a long time
too
yeah and if you like respect like Derek
and and Erica or even just Derek or
whatever or Ryan guys like you would not
go after you know someone like that
especially if you still like care about
them she's a friendship yeah for sure
we're definitely friends I mean we still
talk sometimes we have lunch you know
it's just it's just a different page now
which is okay yeah yeah yeah I went we
went deep therapy session we did I mean
early into the podcast how was it for
you when you made that video you know
you made a video on your YouTube channel
about a breakup did that help
it uh it helped me a lot and I'm very
lucky that you know I didn't come out
with my relationship and see like who it
was and stuff and show but it was very
therapeutic to me because like you guys
said I'm somebody who like really I'm
very I wear my heart on my sleeve I'm
very
you know I'm not soft though but uh like
you're pretty soft I mean you're like a
definitely more emotional than both of
us I think you're like the most common
toilet paper yeah the most emotional
person in the group
sure one person who's spoken to my life
a lot every Instagram picture I post
since that podcast he puts toilet paper
emojis soft who this guy collide that's
funny yeah that's um but it helped me a
lot because it got me to I guess be
transparent with who I am and say like
this is the mistakes I made this is how
I was viewing a life and her and clearly
I was I had a lot of clouded judgment I
was infatuated and it was kind of just
like because it's something that
everybody goes through everybody goes
through that like that first
relationship or you know one of the
first ones and it just does not go well
and everyone has to go through that but
a lot of times people will be like all
this first relationship was suppose to
be everything they over romanticize it
is all my fault and for me I felt that
way too but I also learned things from
it and I was like this is like not just
the advice that I have to give but it's
kind of advice that you all like pour it
into me and like spoken to me you know
so in a way I was just like
regurgitating a lot of things that you
guys have told me she basically stole my
video then and like our videos and yeah
oh okay good and I made money off of it
so that's nice nice student someone is
almost at a million so thanks man no I
did well yeah it's a good script it's
not scripted all right what is it is
that video it has no cuts no edits
because I wanted to be very like
transparent and show like I didn't write
down any of this mm-hmm you know right
well moving on to a non a less serious
topic and something since Derek's here
yeah I know he's really into Avengers
comes out soon and game nap
Derek is one of those hardcore Marvel
errs what do you call yourselves Marvel
errs
yeah marvelous oh really he's all those
people who watches like every single one
when it comes right in theaters when it
comes out and whether even he he'll go
by himself
and watch it
and you know I've seen some I mean I
would say about 50%
Paco's seen one movie one just Iron Man
Iron Man and it's funny because we're
all coming at you from perspective I'm
kind of excited I know you're you could
care less yeah absolutely careless and
then Derek you're just hyped because
it's the last one right oh I mean it's
not gonna be the last Avengers ever game
cuz they're like that that letter that
was on Twitter and everything did you
guys see that letter yeah no yeah so
basically are the directors right you
talk about it since you're the fan I
mean it was more so than actors you know
their contracts are coming to an end
they've done the character for like 10
plus years you know they're also uh you
know who knows where they're gonna take
the storyline I don't I don't know since
we haven't seen the movie yet but who
knows like Iron Man could be finished
captain Moore uh Captain America could
be finished who knows you know maybe the
originals are done but I know that
Avengers will still live on through like
spider-man and like the other characters
like Bucky or whoever you know right
like Panther basically also the Twitter
letter was saying like that their
journey has come to an end and like you
know every all the hard work that
everybody's put in like don't spoil it
like don't be one of those douchebags
that spoil things
I suck yeah yeah I mean just just like
the game of thrones just premiered yeah
and that's like I took a meme in itself
like oh if you spoil like I've seen more
on those in actual spoilers mm-hmm like
of people putting like well if you spoil
this you're and then it's like a picture
of someone dead or you know yeah
something something like that yeah
people really eight spoilers I mean I
can relate to it there's a reason why I
didn't watch the what was it there's a
big thing oh oh the UM the firt the
Avengers that uh the most recent one
that came up oh yeah with Thanos so I
saw that only when it came on Netflix so
we're gonna watch it in in theaters but
I knew the ending I was like okay well
something happens and there's a meme and
people disintegrate or something like
that's no boilers dude I don't get to
see it if okay here's my thing if you
haven't seen it by the time it's out of
theaters that is your problem like for
real like if people do that about Naruto
and when that was like coming out live
and like people would get mad because I
would talk about stuff they came out
like maybe about like a month or two
I'm like well if you're not gonna like
if you're not gonna keep up then you
don't really care that much and that's
how I felt - I didn't care that I knew
the ending but I didn't go watch it no
it was on Netflix yeah manatee war was
dope they packed like tons of different
storylines and characters into one movie
that was just like just blew your mind
you know like they've been doing this
what for a long time like over a decade
you know just planting seeds and letting
it letting it grow watering in and
getting everyone together it's just it's
a dope movie Marvel knows what's up see
so I have always been like excited that
it I was excited because I thought I was
coming to an end not because I don't
like those movies but because it's like
oh all these talented actors and
talented like screenwriters and all
these people putting all this I feel
like every movie that comes out these
days are like a recreation of something
there's nothing really original anymore
that does box office like records other
than stuff that like Jordan Peele is
doing with Gale you know yeah what does
the recent one us yes yeah he's only
part like I mean there's there's some
others too that are doing original stuff
but everything else like oh they're
making a live-action Disney movie yeah
they're doing Omar because they know it
makes money yeah but like I just miss
the days when like you miss them every
yeah there was like something original
oh that's a unique idea or it's like
kind of like this but it's kind of
unique it's not just a recreation of
something that's already been told so
who do you blame you blame the studio's
you blame like audience retention it's
both pretend it's it's the audience it's
our fault for buying into it like it of
course the studio's gonna make what they
want to make right yeah but it is also I
think the studios because they decide
who they're gonna fund there's tons of
talented writers and scripts constantly
being you know I'm sure pitch to these
studios but why would they make those
movies and take the risk of putting in
all this money for something that they
don't know how it's gonna do verse make
something that's already has a proven
fan base and for sure milk the benefits
you know it's have to say it's a studio
it's just money billions yeah but it's
like money kills creation like
creativity for sure I think for the most
part it's anything for it with YouTube
like that's what happened to you too
because people like a formula like they
like knowing what's gonna happen when
money gets involved yes yeah I mean
that's
yeah you know yeah so yeah I was excited
that it was coming to me for that reason
but I guess it's not I mean I'm excited
yeah I want to know what happens yeah -
thank you I already got my movie tickets
for days yeah - yeah seriously yeah I
got my movie ticket for the premiere and
then I bought another movie ticket so
for IMAX are you going to the one here
is there one here in Vegas yeah yeah
it's premiering everywhere oh so I mean
like every city has their own premiere
well I mean like I just bought a movie
ticket to regular tea and your skies
when you say premiere I was thinking
like red carpet and oh heck no oh sorry
my bed oh no no I was just I'm not I'm
not cool like that
all right well um on that note I didn't
know we were already at that point but
we have to take a shishi break so uh
we'll be right back we'll be right back
why did I snap thanos half of us can go
shoo birdy
and we're back that was louder than
usual was it yeah usually and you're
still eating Oh
make it loud slurping noise I guess we
didn't give you enough time or hmm okay
so do we should we just wait for you or
like are you good now we can start okay
I guess and and now we're back so what
else we got on the agenda today um that
Derek can't bring it up still on the
Avengers nay I can't believe he did that
to the world do you like yeah okay so
the one thing I did like about Avengers
that infinity war it's very similar and
I tweeted something like just as a joke
that it's so similar to like a lot of
the villains in Naruto Naruto just for
the people who get mad at me for seeing
it wrong right I'll fight you I'm from
America okay that's how I speak actually
you're from now retail I'm from Hawaii
gets America yeah a lot of people don't
think so but the thing I like about that
thanos and the villains that they have
um you know in like art or other a lot
of enemies actually they actually
believe that they're doing good for the
world
mm-hmm like it's actually like thallus
is like as much as he did like horrible
things like he destroyed half the world
right population wise it was out of in
his mind mercy right and he actually I
mean it's kind of like a not an analogy
but it's kind of like the whole it's
very much so related to the thought
behind like the conspiracy theory or on
the Illuminati in the New World Order
but like this world is being too
overpopulated we're all gonna suffer at
some point because you're gonna run out
of resources so if you were to reduce
the population right scientific I mean
this is not saying that I agree with
this or that we should do this but what
they're saying is if you reduce a
population it's actually mercy on the
people like the human race will still
survive cuz at the rate that we're
growing everyone's gonna die mm-hmm huh
what are your thoughts on that I think I
think you should happen you think half
the world should be but no not
necessarily half the world but I don't
think start to be we should die I think
people who type that's a hot take I
think people type first on YouTube
videos and dislike videos even before
they watch the whole thing should die um
I think so we were trying to make a
serious conversation when you're just
naming people that annoy you
I think people annoying me should die I
think people who I don't know I'm not
someone to be like you know oh these
people should die just think like there
are ways that we can go about making
sure everybody's okay cuz you guys heard
about the whole like uh no no turd on
the yeah the fire yeah right and it did
like I think couple millions it's not
billion dollars of damage to it and
people are donating money to get it
fixed already but a lot of a lot of
Catholic people feel like why are we
donating money to a building when we all
that money that we're spending could be
used like feeding homeless people or
helping people who have been through
naturally so I mean like that yeah and
how rich the church actually is ready
like they could easily afford to build
it back but if you think about it it's
it's cuz it was covered in the news
right uh-huh
like
and so people feel so distraught by it
because it's like a monument is a symbol
yeah it's a symbol but so it's like if
they were covering like this huge event
that happened to kids you know starving
recently if it was just a news thing
like something that was just on the news
mainstream media everywhere like in the
same way that that fire was covered
something kids are always starving but
if there was some big event where all of
a sudden tons of kids were being covered
on the news for starving I guarantee you
that same thing would happen yeah it's
just a matter of people get take action
when they're emotional ah majora not
everyone some people actually help
because of you know they they really
care about what's happening yeah but
some people are just going based off
emotion like oh my god this is awful I
need to do something which is a good
thing like it's a good thing to feel
that way but that brings me to my point
like they're only caring about that
cause because it's covered in the news
so much I mean that's why I think but I
mean you're I was just talking about the
aspect they're like we could not have to
kill and necessarily a bunch of people
we could just figure out how to solve
that issue in a different way because we
do have like a lot of resources that
could help that out well tell that to
Thanos maybe maybe people can like stop
eating meat like they could stop eating
me and like start eating like more
greens I mean that is that that I know
what you're talking about yeah but it's
not are you are you gonna actually stop
eating meat Derek they should call
themselves vegans
there's vegetarians yeah I mean well I
mean what he's talking about
I think is another solution but what
we're talking about is an alternative
like for coming from what you're saying
from the Thanos perspective right I'm
giving an analogy why did he if he would
that gauntlet thing I don't know what
does it have you can do anything with it
right pretty much she's got some stones
so instead of killing half the world why
didn't he just create a second world or
the population yeah or if here you live
here everyone lives or he snaps and just
doubles the food he doesn't what end the
land yeah we need right why could I do
that he doesn't work like that man why
why it so he is evil the net that
defeats my first point like he's not
doing it for PR see ant-man should go in
his butthole and explode him Nina
mmm Danish theory yeah I mean in his
storyline like he's doing that for years
like going to galaxies and just like
wiping out half of it already to help
him it's C but it's not really he'll
like if you have that kind of power you
don't need to kill half the world right
you could just if you can have if you're
like a guy why not just create like you
said more resource or maybe when he
snaps he's sending them to another world
and that world has enough resources for
everybody
man maybe we misjudge stano's I mean
yeah I would see it actually that one if
it's the last one I'll see it yeah but
it's three hours long holy
I know it's types like Titanic though I
know I don't think I could sit through
that now but Titanic had some nipples
and that was I remember that I was a
little kid my nipples in Avengers
there's tons of nipples and Avengers
girl nipples though mmm yeah now you're
talking Game of Thrones you don't watch
that I have seen I watched a little bit
of Game of Thrones acts pretty much
anything that's mainstream and people
like you don't really know not
necessarily is I I just like video games
a lot I know but enough time for that
stuff I watch James I watched Game of
Thrones man it's not so bad but I watch
Game of Thrones with his girl who I
liked I know you're already laughing
look at that what but and then when we
kind of like stop talking I'm somebody
who associate stuff that I do with
people with them you know so I can't
watch Game of Thrones without thinking
about her I mean we're cool now and
everything but back then I was like well
I can't watch this anymore because then
I just feel sad it's so emotional yeah
poor guy hmm you what you want to watch
Game of Thrones with me you gonna break
my heart
probably then oh yeah I got asked to
watch the Game of Thrones that season
premiere one huh and and then and then I
got an ass
what do you mean uninvited yeah I got
asked to go watch it and then we went on
me my friend we went to Trader Joe's and
bought hello snacks cookies and freakin
some water and some like ice creams to
bring to the party yeah and then and
then it
didn't work out and they told you not to
come she was just like is this is my
friend he's cool and she's like well I
don't really like the homegirl it was I
don't really want like a random guy to
come to my house she was just inviting
you
yeah you think he was about to have his
own game of Thrones love story
damn okay cock-blocked yourself no no I
didn't she the friend just didn't want
me to come over cuz we never never met
oh so it's a her thing
I'm probably just like a random guy no
not tinder but there's some kind of
acquaintances yeah yeah friend all right
did you have any Game of Thrones love
stories in China well I never seen Game
of Thrones so what does that mo did I
have she make love with your sibling
yeah see you know you know what do you
say
I didn't hear which is yep insist oh
yeah you know what that was about no I
mean the thing about Game of Thrones and
always made me wonder too cuz you know
back in the day wasn't the whole idea of
like being royal and you know keeping it
within the bloodline yeah aren't they
all product of incest yeah technically
aren't we all
it's in some way I guess it depends on
your religion yeah but but yeah I mean
it's like in the whole like the
Christian thing or whatever right cuz
then it's like it starts up at the top
of the tree there's Adam and Eve and
they are they related then no they're
not related but still like you know
where do they make how do they make how
do their babies make babies yeah there's
no there cuz no they're siblings right
yeah yeah well now we know let's talk
about the season the hell up bad about
Christianity okay I should not even as a
joke sorry to my Christians out there
that's we we're digging ourselves a hole
right now and man's gonna jump in and
explode us there you go
and that's kind of funny though that we
can even like not that I said the joke
but we can even like talk about it
because if this was another religion
specifically like something in the news
yeah I was talking about like Muslims
uh-huh we were seeing someone about that
we'd be in way more hot water
oh yeah Christianity is like so popular
here that we can make fun of because
it's always like punching up as
you're bunching up it's okay sure that's
why like you know black people like when
they do comedies that they can make fun
of white people true sure what a white
person can't make fun of of Yashin or
even an Asian really yeah yeah yeah that
makes me think where do we fall on the
chart we're kind of like below white
above or below black do you think so
yeah I think so
because I feel like a Asian couldn't
make fun of a black person for being
black no we can that person could make
fun of an Asian for being I think I
think it's kind of like similar levels
yeah it's pretty close I think it's
close yeah no I was just thinking about
that sorry random tangent it's tough to
say you look like you were trying gonna
say something Derrick I mean it's just
my opinion
Asians don't really get casted that much
to be lead role son true though true I
don't know where they stand on the on
the food chart but the food is
definitely on the lower and I would
think yeah yeah that's true but I mean
like like I said in a previous video
like Steve Harvey making fun of Asians
and it cost him his career mm-hmm but if
you've seen like an Asian guy make you
know fun of black people for being black
and singing by people are undateable
then that guy's career is probably done
what did you think an Asian guy's saying
that I don't actually see more Asian
people do this self-deprecating thing
where they make fun of how like Asian
guys yeah but I'm saying I know they're
made I know I think we're I think we're
still punching up though but they don't
but Asian guy can't make fun of a black
person yeah for being black but I think
also it's because like black people have
kind of taken like though we get to make
the race jokes it's everything because
they've been so proficient in it they're
very good at it they're very good at
their jokes that is true yeah I'm just
trying to figure out the totem pole
they're just very observant and they
know how to make it fun right but then
where does that leave everybody else
struggling we got to talk about politics
and stuff okay well I somehow we we went
from Avengers to like penis of the week
the week see we got back that we didn't
do that in a while we haven't yeah yeah
but now we're back I started
so anyways in China yeah what about Game
of Thrones any any good love stories you
had uh yeah I met some people out there
it was definitely some fun interesting
experiences and did you know some people
just listening Derek just smiling the
whole time
[Music]
I love living through Derek man cuz
there's way hotter and like sexier than
me and stuff and he's just like he
always does cool stuff with like very
pretty girls some house like hey Derek
what happened but they're all down plays
everything you know cuz he's very humble
and stuff so he's like you know he's
hung out and kick it as like just hung
out and kick it and it takes like 15 to
40 minutes to get him to say like he's
cuz you're asking him like that maybe
yeah I'm kind of creepy
yeah I wouldn't want to tell you
anything either if you're asking me like
that it's alright you kiss already like
ignoring you yeah you know what is a I
guess for you was the most fun thing you
did in China though probably just meet
people just meet different people around
the world experience different
situations and stuff out there compared
to here performing again was was amazing
that felt really good but you guys went
to China together before and that sounds
like a completely different situation
yeah I was yeah we went to Beijing yeah
we met and it was I'm not gonna lie it
was not a fun experience I was one of my
least favorite trips and it was uh not
no it's not not because of Derek it was
um
we none of what I mean Derek's Chinese
right yeah but it's just the trip was
rough for one every place we went
because we couldn't speak Chinese we
didn't have somebody like normally when
we go out for events people accompanying
us thick tape set us up with like a
local or somebody we had no one so we're
on our own for one just getting a taxi
to go somewhere that we needed to be was
a struggle because if we don't have
somebody telling us this they're
constantly we didn't know this at the
time but they constitute our to rip you
off like it's not like hey this is the
set rate yeah they try and negotiate
with you and we're like what it only
costs us like I don't know what the
currency was like 40 bucks to get there
why are you saying it's gonna and we're
in the middle of nowhere right because
we don't know where we are
why are you gonna charge us like a
hundred bucks to go back like how was it
gonna cost that much more and then we
found out like oh you have to negotiate
or you can negotiate and I think they
knew that we couldn't speak Chinese so
like yeah he texted her we were talking
to you because there's a line of them
just kept telling people to skip us oh
yeah so we were like stranded there with
this one guy and note we couldn't go to
any other taxi driver so we ended up
having to walk like hella far to get
home taxi yeah and even that taxi was
like where's your hotel we would say the
name and he wouldn't know like yeah
where that was and we didn't know if
we're being scammed again so we end up
getting dropped off in the middle of
this like downtown area yeah and we had
to just walk and look for it like on
Google Matt we are phones don't really
work ray can't call anyone yeah we we
saw like a map on the street no Wi-Fi
yeah and we just kind of like this looks
like something familiar yeah kind of
like that friends episode you put the
map down you stand and yes I didn't have
a good experience but apparently Macao
is like the opposite of that
well yeah where I was at it was
definitely like the Las Vegas Strip or
it was a Las Vegas strip some of they
had some of the same hotels from here
out there and you said it's like there
because whatever what I've heard is that
bad place is like stacked with cash like
oh yeah hell of money they told me that
um Macau is richer than Dubai and they
told me that the ratio from Las Vegas to
Macau is one to seven so any time an
American spends a hundred bucks out here
someone in Macau is spending seven
hundred equal vient to that damn yeah
it's pretty crazy yeah
do they bet on fights and stuff like
even watch that stuff I didn't see too
much sports betting I saw just a lot of
table games mmm a lot of table games
yeah that is true and just crazy too
rich Asians like it's like a whole
nother level of wealth yeah in China it
is yeah you know yeah there's weather
that's why they're taking over that is
did you know that yeah I know I know
that we owe them like hella money we
need to learn which one is in Mandarin
or manners man yeah I think it's which
one's Cantonese then is that in Taiwan
no Cantonese
in Hong Kong Hong Kong yeah I know I'm
being careful cuz I know that people get
really offended yeah I like I'm going to
Hong Kong
okay what was it when we when I went out
there I met up with this I'm in it with
a couple people out there I meant this
like super rich poker player that I does
just play poker and that's like his life
out there
we and again like a table and a couple
bottles and stuff and just partying all
night I met this other guy who was super
rich and he picked me up in his Porsche
and he took me to some really dope local
spots where I ate some really good food
took Mia's really dope desert spot some
like touristy kind of local attraction
spots and then the end the night when he
was dropping me off we parked in this
parking lot and I smashed his Porsche
door into another car door and I felt so
bad he looked at me and I don't even
know why I reacted this way but once I
open the door went Bing
he looked at me and I immediately closed
my door like I didn't even do it
I don't know why I did it that way I
yeah I don't know why but I just like
what do you say he just kind of like
chuckled and I'm just like I'm sorry do
like it was a complete accident like if
you want me to fix your chip or your
pain I'll I'll go get a Sharpie from the
concierge phikul you answer I'll get a
sharpie and color it in or something
damn but now he didn't mind I mean he
was he one of those crazy rich people
are just pretty rich crazy rich Asian
yeah dang that level of that level of
money it's just like such a like there's
rich people yeah then there is that you
know that's what that movie is about
it's like a whole nother level of
richness it's like everybody a bunch of
like Bill Gates out there like rich and
then your wealth yeah yeah yeah but I
felt bad I felt really bad because he
gave me such like a cool day like you
know like kicking it with the local and
stuff and showed me around town just
getting out of the hotel or off the
stage and then I freaking ding his door
it was it was a bad feeling I mean I
know most people like they think that's
the dream right to have that level of
wealth yeah but like I would never I
don't think I would ever want to live a
life where I'm that rich like
in the billions I really don't think
that would be you you're not you're not
the same part in the same way like I
would never want to be like Justin
Bieber famous yeah or like at that level
mmm because at that point you can't live
a regular like some people might enjoy
it some people do fine with it but
there's a reason why a lot of those
people who have everything still kill
themselves they're still like depressed
yeah because you can't live it's a whole
nother way of living you got to change
your whole mindset everything and you're
almost it's almost like you're couldn't
find to certain areas in a way because
you lose your freedom yes you're too
famous right and and just being that
rich to everybody you meet is gonna
treat you differently yeah for one you
can't trust almost anyone that's true
not even family at that point right on
time yeah yeah for the most part usually
it is that way um unless you're just
born into it and everyone around you is
rich I think a lot of times it's you
can't trust anyone because there's such
a big it's such a powerful thing and I
don't I don't think I would ever wanna
live that life I think you for like a
day I like a week yeah I think I saw um
I could be wrong but somebody who
recently like won the lotto like had a
mask on right so nobody would like their
family wouldn't know that they're rich
you know cuz like what you know it's
hard to turn down family and it will
change everything it would change
everything if you have the nicest family
members they know they know like oh you
didn't even we got dinner and you're not
gonna pick up the bill yeah like it's
just a hundred two hundred bucks like
what is that to you like it just because
it changes the dynamic between people
and I know that I mean like even I've
met like hundreds of millionaires
billionaires and I feel different around
them like oh I know they feel different
like I'm already thinking like how do I
act because this is like a different
level and it's hard to even treat them
like a human being sometimes yeah even
though you know I know I should I know
what they're thinking like they have
like a trust issue thing and yeah I
don't know like I think that's an
interesting dynamic uh and I think a lot
of fans like think like we're rich but
we're not especially Ryan Ryan Ryan is
hella broke because he's wearing our
didn't shirt right now that's not even
your shirt okay this Arden was wearing
that shirt when you and me did that
video with her remember which was the
one where we ate at uh Roxy how do you
know this is her shirt okay this could
be she wears my stuff you know does she
I think this is my shirt I've never seen
you wear that shirt ever I like wearing
my shirt seven times okay well you know
why I got shirt I feel like I know
adidas sends her stuff but I I send me
stuff as well and I'm pretty sure this
is my size shirt nice and thanks Derek
looks good on any little hair thanks
dude I mean I've been trying to well I'm
not trying I haven't been I just thought
about growing it out okay and then I'd
also thought about shaving it because
Paco made fun of me before you came
really what do you say hey Mimi low self
conscious but he's like not like he was
with his friend and they came over
earlier before you got here and he was
like oh can you take a picture of my
friends like oh oh yeah I guess I
couldn't say oh you're not gonna shave
it was even before that you said oh
you're gonna really grow it out like why
who are you trying to appeal to like
what dumb are you trying to appeal to
cuz you can't even with all those
patches oh like I was like yeah I get a
roasted first thing in the morning when
I see to it there's context to it
Oh shaver picture no because so whenever
I ask him to be in my videos yeah if I
don't let him know in advance and I ask
him day of and he did his shave he's
like aw do you shoulda let me know
before so I could have shaved
okay so every time I ask him he's always
like I should have shaved so when he did
it she only do that's why yeah I was
like oh you're not gonna shave dude and
then mmm that was he's trying to make
himself some no making fun of me like I
think I'd maybe I should shave that's
right at first was like you're not gonna
shave he's like I'm thinking about
growing out and then I went to get host
and then he was like oh yeah but you got
all those patches like you know cuz I've
talked about it like I can't grow full
beer no sir
yeah but maybe if I grow it long enough
at all like cover up the spaces yeah but
he just really didn't want me to do it
dude saying things like well what damn
waiter can't you like your fans are
gonna like that and I was like you're
right no but that's our friendship man
it's always like roast each other's
stuff I mean the patches look cool bro
thanks to you yeah it makes you unique
yeah it gives me like some error over
here why you so mad dude I thought that
you know if you shave it more I think
this is a myth when people say they
shave it supposed to grow back thicker
it doesn't work I shaved this I let grow
and shave all the time hoping I'm gonna
fill these patches one day and it just
doesn't work dude I know how Sean did it
and you're egging on well Gregan will
have always hey that's true actually but
you can't grow a beard huh that's a girl
any hair anywhere the three of us can't
the three of them can their real hair
it's just patchy yeah it doesn't look
good you guys can't grow hair and I
think that's like almost a blessing
that's you don't have to shave as much
or I'll have to shave cuz then mine will
come out real quick and then chill there
for like a little bit what like like
mustache hair would like come out like
the next day oh yeah well then just stay
that length for like five days right
like this people who are listening they
can't see it's like stubble that is not
in every spot so it looks stupid but if
it was filled out it would look you know
it look doh but to start it off you have
to start from somewhere I know I know
Sochi it's a life lesson for people emo
is like even like when you're growing
out your hair there's that phase where
you look like an idiot and you will look
like an idiot but if you commit to
something you you might still look like
an idiot but at leaders a chance you
might not yeah people respect you a
little bit anyways you have chess here
though yeah I I do but it's like even
that it's not like a like how you see on
like a movie yeah like that like an
actor who has like nice like I don't
know it's just like still it's like my
face is sporadic yeah and it's just like
I could easily just wax it and it'd be
gone and like a you know it wouldn't be
like a Steve Carell situation I got
three hairs like I look like a cheek
like a cat's cheek you know like just
whiskers that whiskers coming out that's
all I got nothing else there mmm
you know you know it's like a long
desert real flat a little bit concave
cuz I have no muscles and then like
three hot and pine trees sticking out of
the ground
what are those pine trees doing there in
the middle the desert what people tell
you that no that's me girls what I'm
just wondering no I actually had a girl
tell me the other day she's like wow you
don't have any hair on your
back or your chest lucky and I'll just
like Oh what am I supposed to and then
she's like well my last boyfriend was
Russian known to be Harry I don't know
they're a little bit I don't know what
that mean they're like a human loofah
but he's Russian he's not Asian so damn
dude are you trying to you know that's
the one kind of people you don't want to
upset dude
Russians are dope though they're freakin
tough there hello let's uh yeah it's a
different breed out there dude no but
Derek I gotta ask you this then if you
want to know how to say kiss in Russian
or no I'm sorry Ukrainian you say the
song you say what to some just saw is
that the name of a watch just song is om
but the one watch I do have is to slant
it in church
anyways I still wanna know saw this so
that might be French I think there's 20
Parker's sponsored oh it's light um
sorry what were you saying
Derek what's that I was a girl seeing
your shirtless back and chest oh it's
just like wrong with that there's
nothing wrong I'm getting a massage did
you have to pay her something about the
bass that I have to turn on my
headphones it's like it makes me like
earwax wiggle something I don't like
about when you do that I think your
voice is so deep it II dude it's
bothering me I think is just the basin
might hit my headphones in Japan though
yeah like people said like I had a
really nice low voice you do cuz I would
do like out speaking like Japanese to
them but they'll be like Walkley Cucuy
which means cool yeah voices your voice
is naturally very low thank you doesn't
mean you need to force it or thank you
all you talk about the weird things you
were gonna do in Japan but dude I was in
doubt I did chicken out man I was gonna
do new do new do massages I was gonna go
so plan explain is they even illegal
like what is that what is that is legal
you can explain I think it's okay to
talk about it cuz you didn't do it yeah
essentially it's like it's a massage
parlor but
the oil brothel they all you themselves
up I think and then they just rub their
bodies on you it's like an erotic
massage so they're massaging you with
their whole body yeah that sounds like
porn that's not really am assault like
do they actually massage you I don't
know I was hoping for a massage board
that's my favorite thing that's cool
yeah but then there I I didn't do that
well yeah yeah why mostly because I was
streaming the whole time and you can't
like do that kind of stuff that's
against TOS what's to us Terms of
Service oh yeah you can't do that yeah
cuz it's not like family go there though
no mmm
to an extent to an egg's what does it
mean like they can rub themselves on you
but as soon as like they touch like
genitals and things and you're paying
them for that that's like supposed to be
not allowed that is silly to me like
it's you're already rubbing a naked
person's body on you and you're naked
I'm assuming uh I don't I don't know I
didn't really do performances that's so
interesting
yeah how do you guys feel about the
legalization of we're not prostitution
but I guess that is prostitution like
sex there's a lot of people recently
coming out like I saw in like even like
Joe Rogan's podcast or like this has
been around for ages since like early
times prostitution yeah paid service
yeah and it should be legalized in text
mmm guessing the same with like like
weed yeah
but weed is becoming that yeah right and
then like it's not even legal here
prostitution but people think it is
actually in different parts of Las Vegas
there are really running brothels yeah I
thought that was illegal yeah I've heard
that before
yeah there's certain ones in Vegas and
really Nevada sorry none of that oh yeah
yeah hey Gaston yeah people think it's
are you I think Clark County is not
legal but there are other counties that
are right why I know this it's not
because I've been to one it's just doing
a research oh yeah jokes yeah what was
it like no I didn't go in I said do mine
he learned a lot of like sexual related
stuff because of Paco and he always says
research quote-unquote like the how
about the fact and the weird is almost
like hey remember one time oh actually
guys the age of consent
sixteen and like why do you know like
why as a 27 year old or 28 year old man
why do you need to know that like it's
just like so so for me like I was a
virgin until the age of 26 okay yeah
just maybe we'll put that out there in
your 28 and I'm 28 now that's cool and
uh so like a lot of times because people
make stupid jokes you know sure but I
want and they're like um Paco is like
you know he's so desperate whatever like
he like probably knows and like they
said like he knows that the legal age of
consent is 16 in Las Vegas and I was
like what like I thought it was 18 you
know throughout the entire country but
apparently it isn't like different
states have different ages consent
supposedly like in Japan like a
Prefecture has like the legal age of
consent is 13 what yeah
damn 13 where I don't know exactly where
now this is all word of mouth of course
I could be wrong so simple google search
a simple Google search good work all
right go on um but yeah and then there's
like uh like if they're under the legal
age of consent but you're within five
years of their age in certain states
like that's okay you know because if
you're 18 and your boyfriend or
girlfriend is 17 and you guys make love
or whatever ah and that person like it
would be weird if that person went to
jail for that it's 13 in Japan 14 in
China yes the age of consent is 12 in
the Philippines oh my gosh
Wow that's crazy yeah they I don't think
they had drinking ages out there any
they're you could drink it like any age
out there I heard something about that
though like was it like France or
something where they don't have a
drinking age or just like really young
and because that's allowed there there's
like significantly like less alcoholism
and do you I really like alcohol-related
incidents I don't know if that's true it
was really good they know I did
something like maybe I'm a younger age
or you just don't crave it or maybe it's
just less reported because there's less
underage drinking since there's nothing
maybe they get
their system earlier true so you don't
know they don't have to be with it later
whereas here in America you know you
can't drink 321 so people who want a
drink once it hit 21 and they wanted to
wise yourself yeah that's that was kind
of me I really went crazy 20 even like
clubbing and stuff like that although
I've been to clubs cause of like events
and stuff but at 21 I had like a six
month spree of just like doing little to
no work and just like going straight
clubbing and stuff yes and I've always I
learned how much I hated it like that's
and now and now I got it out of my
system I don't have any craving ever to
go again we should go again okay yeah
you love going out did you look I like
my eople I like going out I don't like
clubs do your weird bro you'll be at a
party just a Wallflower
how you doing just researching man dude
that is me at parties I just like I
people watch a lot really yeah
it's situational for me it's a very
situational for me yeah I feel like
normally you like to be the center of
attention if I know everyone there and I
you know or most people there then I'll
be really goofy but if I don't really
know anyone I know like 1 to 3 people I
kind of just observe dude David had a
cracking party hella people there tons
of games good for the toy yeah Oh David
birthday right right this guy's just
sleeping on the couch in there you
brought a date to a party a birthday
party and you you slept and she's just
sitting next to you where you slept at a
party yeah man
can't blame me can't blame me I mean I'm
not I'm not blaming you I'm just saying
that it happened
good I just remember I was on the couch
and then she was there and I was just
like watching King batch play Mario Kart
and yelling at people while playing
Mario Kart
now it's not additive yeah I thought it
was so funny and I just fell asleep okay
that doesn't okay
that's so funny I fell asleep yeah
wasn't that funny though it was funny
sinking bats yellow people now he's a
funny guy yeah they've been playing his
uh on do commercial yeah spite on do
commercial like so much it's crazy
the one where he blows out his character
and they play basketball
yeah yeah that guy's doing really well
yeah he's the guy it was fun filming
with them for sure was anything tons of
funny content hopefully we see him in
the next couple weeks
let's go save is there something coming
soon what soon because I don't know if I
don't because it's a private event but
it's exclusive it's an it's a private
event that I'm announcing something that
will be available next podcast I'll talk
about it let's just say I think people
already know let's just say I won't be
needing this cup very much longer
it could change the game good never know
it also not me anyway yeah well well
cross that bridge when we cross it what
crime is that the same well cross the
bridge when we cross it across the
bridge when we get old
well cross that road when you get there
I don't you know what just we'll cross
those in an hour okay I feel like I
didn't really let Derek talk that much
but that is for people who don't know
that is just Derek is no you did
actually just more more this is like 10
times you this is my sixth podcast it's
not your sixth podcast oh my god also it
Derek we know when a Marvel movie is
coming out cuz that's when he talks the
most it is true so you guys see that
movie yet or the jailor
yeah the trailer I gotta talk to
somebody about yeah it would be like the
shoot day and the trailer just came out
like two hours it was eggs I see the
trailer yet like what we had a new
trailer I was like you know and then we
look it's like Oh came out like an hour
and like he's been at the house since
like he's like looking at like red and
stuff like seeing fan theories and
everything ready yeah that's me for sure
that's me for sure yeah
all right well I guess that's it Thank
You Derek for being here today
paka Leto and I predict alkalete oh and
early leaky hose I guess that's it for
today huh yeah it's been a pleasure man
thank you for inviting me
well you're always around so whenever
you want to feel like talking I guess
we'll wait to the next movie next time
yeah we'll talk fan theories or maybe
when it's over after we see it we can
talk talk some holes in the plot that's
what I like to do
[ __ ] anyway it does bother me though
well um just like the little things like
you know they say like you have to have
the glove the gauntlet closed right I
don't want to get back into this but
just real quick the gauntlet
thanassis gauntlet he has to have his
fist closed right to use it but how can
he snap and get rid of half the people
with his fists
you can't snap with a closed fist like
you can't snap with a closed fist can
you this is not a closed fist
well after you snap oh it's closed but
you can't do you don't have the power of
this that's not a closed fist that is a
little crooked fist that is that I in
scary movies my germs will cross that
bridge when we cross the bridge that's
I'm gonna end this thank you guys so
much for tuning into off the pill
podcast we'll talk to you next oh don't
forget you don't follow us there you go
go ahead don't forget you guys can
follow us at off the bill on Twitter at
off the pill podcast on Instagram also
don't forget that uh we talk about a lot
of the podcast stuff on the reddit page
reddit com slash are slash nigahiga and
anything else you want to plug nope
that's about it so um I guess we'll end
it now in three two one Derek blowing
the mic you didn't do it oh my god yeah
so I was wind I'm going to kill him
let's cross that bridge when we cross
the bridge what is the real saying I
don't know I don't care hmm let's cut
this out but I'd really I'm gonna look
it up actually what do I sing yeah the
bridge yeah this is a better podcast
though we'll cross that bridge when one
comes to it
that sounds so lame I forget