oh yeah hey guys I actually have to hit
all right now I'll see you guys later
yeah I like man I love you let me guess
I love you what are you doing what why
are you showing so much affection for
each other it's weird
no we're we're friends I mean we're best
friends you know that's like um what is
that word was that one word I saw that
one video
[Music]
man
it's like Eminem and dr. Dre if I loved
you more I might be gay I wearing a
feeling down you know just what to say
to my homie yeah you know me ever need a
wingman any girl blow me off but you're
more important than the rest I confess
I'm a mess if I'm the hey you know it's
true you my male boo man I've seen the
chorus with me you feel the same way too
[Music]
nothing really gay about
anything wrong with in-game
[Music]
shouldn't be blamed or hi
in the most heterosexual
hold me to a promise that I'll be the
kind of friend that in the end will
always keep you company cos when the
world gets trucked and times get hard I
will always love you
I'll be your bodyguard cuz you're my
bestie
I started
not the really gay about
anything go within
you should be bender
[Music]
and
[Applause]
the same way
[Music]
[Applause]
if you
ah
the game
[Music]
you should be
oh I get it now up you brought me two
men holding that was my lower back would
you touch your lower back you've changed
to change
[Music]