hey guys ah he'll start this over real
quick hey guys so by now I'm sure all of
you have already heard about all the
drama and controversy around you know
Steve Harvey making the jokes called
Asian man basically he made some jokes
on this show about Asian men and how
they're not attractive and this is what
it looked like you know thank you
obviously there was a lot of drama that
fall there was two different sides of
people either you know attacking Steve
Harvey saying he's racist for making
those jokes or people actually defending
him and saying you know he's a comedian
and Asians need to learn to just take a
joke and even though I'm Asian and I
should be biased when I really thought
about it I wasn't personally offended by
what he said I'm not saying what he said
was right I'm just saying for me
personally I don't get offended by
things like that I've been hearing it my
whole life
obviously I can see why agents were
offended and are upset about this and I
have to admit I was upset too but
probably for a completely different
reason I wasn't upset by the fact that
he was saying Asian men are unattractive
I was upset for just two reasons first
of all the double standard that exists
when it comes to making racist jokes
it's like in our society's almost okay
to make jokes about Asians like this I
mean could you imagine if we switch the
rows and we have an Asian man playing
Steve Harvey and said the things that he
said but about black people on national
television excuse me do you like black
men no thank you yeah I'm pretty sure
that Asian guy's career would be over
any probably getting death threats he'd
probably not be able to book another job
there would be significantly more
outrage than there was about this Steve
Harvey thing but since the joke was
about Asians it's not as big of a deal
because you know it's just a joke I mean
Asians are like the punch bags of
society I can understand if this was
like the first time that this ever
happened in mainstream media let's be
real these kinds of things happen to
Asians all the time I mean remember
during linsanity and ESPN wrote about
Jeremy Lin and they titled the article a
[ __ ] in the armor obviously making
reference to the fact that Jeremy is
Asian and yes there was a lot of outrage
for that I'm not denying that though
again there was no people with defending
the fact that it was a joke but my point
is the fact that anybody would actually
think it's okay to title an article a
[ __ ] in the armor when you know it's a
non comedic sports related article it's
kind of ridiculous I mean the word [ __ ]
is basically like the n-word for Asian
do you think anybody would dare to
publish the article if they switch out
the word [ __ ] with the n-word of course
not because society and mainstream media
has taught us that it's not okay to make
black jokes but it is okay to make Asian
joke Steve Harvey is a comedian it's his
job in fact if I had to list my favorite
black comedians you know from greatest
to worse Steve Harvey wouldn't be the
last one no I'd probably start the top
of the list with like Dave Chappelle
Eddie Murphy Wayne Brady
Hill in harness rock Chris Tucker Ronald
Glover Bernie Mac Martin Lauren Tracy
Morgan Wanda Sykes the entire Wayans
family makes seven up yours guy Orlando
Jones animate the godom buying Bill
Cosby Steve Harvey and then Bill Cosby
after the rape allegation so see Steve
is still not at the bottom cap god I
mean let's be real the guy's funny thing
when you got jokes that are straight
fire like this one
[Applause]
[Music]
this Chinese food is often in another
language see so sometimes they pronounce
things differently and what seems what
steeps in
[Applause]
it's good job the funniest part to me is
that you know as a comedian he didn't
just laugh at his own joke he was dying
from his home job and look like it was
the funniest joke he's ever told or her
then again maybe he wasn't even making a
joke I mean Chinese food is hard to
pronounce it actually made me kind of
curious and I started thinking like what
would it be like to have someone like
Steve Harvey you know at a Chinese
restaurant for lunch just says spring
rolls look at this one look at this one
swing some bum let the sweet in a sour
pork it's literally for English dumpling
speaking roasted duck I might have
actually said Cohen correctly for know
you're on the drink menu that says Pepsi
any one thing in this entire country if
you can't even pronounce those there's
nothing you can eat in this entire world
by a world look like the entire
runner-up what yeah I can't eat anything
from this planet let alone any other
planet in this entire runner-up are you
trying to say universe oh yeah my bad I
always mix universe and runner-up so I
guess we just won eat lunch then huh how
about we just go to cook um right yeah
come [ __ ] it's easy to pronounce so we
can go eat it could [ __ ] if you want are
you swearing at me right now with the
restaurant you know go [ __ ] they have
like those the gravy mashed potatoes
corn you the big old bucket of a chick
fried chicken with the white and red
stripes and the picture of that old guy
calling now Bernie Sanders on it mean
KFC Wow
I cannot believe you just said that what
you're the ones because I'm black you
assume I like KFC racist that was a
horrible Steve Harvey impression I know
I apologize I know that wasn't a good
joke to end on either so I apologize for
that to say but at least I admit when I
have bad jokes
[Music]
well I should also say that Steve
actually did apologize already goes a
typical PR apology that no every
celebrity does when they mess up and you
know he doesn't really mean it because
you know when the backlash first started
coming he literally said this she kind
of beat me up on him in there right now
for no reason but but anyway overall
either Steve Harvey was making a lame
tasteless overused joke that Asians have
been hearing all their lives or he
actually meant what he said and he
really does believe that you know women
aren't attracted to Asian males it's one
or the other and we all can agree that
it was just a bad tasteless joke because
we know he's not a racist I mean he just
had a meeting with the President of the
United States so how can he be racist
but all jokes aside I decided to
actually do my own research and see if
you know maybe Steve was onto something
maybe women don't like agent man so what
I did is what any logical person on the
internet would do taking it to the
streets excuse me miss could ask you a
few questions it all in tech fine that's
gonna ask you a few simple questions my
first question if you had to pick
between these two individuals who would
you consider to be more attractive here
be probably be err be I'm gonna have to
go with B I would go would be what no
gave me in terms of attractiveness like
who would you I like the walking dead so
B be yeah if you had to pick one of
these two individuals who would you go
on a date with a or P B I'm gonna have
to go with B again of course B I love
John Cho I mean guess B which one would
you consider to be sexier be alright B
no bro B I guess you were to come across
one of these next to people randomly on
the street right now who are you most
likely to kiss hey hey for sure I'm
gonna have to go with a are you sure
yeah that's a definite a
so yeah the findings were inconclusive
probably have to just try again another
time stupid girls