so you're probably wondering why is he
sitting down I recently heard my ankle
in a pickup game in basketball you pick
it up no but really I did hurt my ankle
actually I could probably do this
standing I'm just being a little bit
he's sworn oh I was talking about my dog
who is a boy oh my god hey guys so today
I'm gonna be talking about something
that may give me a lot of angry letters
from parents obviously not that kind of
letters that's better
I'm gonna be talking about something
that has been bothering me since I was a
little kid censorship is so stupid
and I censor myself all time it's not
because I think cursing is bad or it's
gonna hurt someone it's because my
parents and society told me that it's a
bad thing to say and don't get me wrong
I'm not one to swear a lot in real life
maybe we were like almost everyone else
sometimes I can't help you looking at
think about it o is a word which in
reality is just a sound hurting anyone
if it's the meaning then why is it
socially acceptable to say the word hate
when you can't say the word see I hate
that I can't even see that lot of
context you know when you were a little
kid and you went home crying it's not
because somebody said a bad word you
cried because they said I don't want to
play with you anymore you're ugly what
that didn't happen to you guys and then
when you were your parents and tell them
what happened they tell you oh you know
son sticks and stones may break your
bones but words may never hurt you if
our parents taught us so why are we
allowed as kids to play with sticks and
stones but if we tell our dads you dad
and you know what happens next right dad
grabs the sticks and stones and beats
the side of you that didn't happen to
you guys either if I ever become a
parent I'm not gonna censor much if my
child questions me dad where do babies
come from
vagina oh I'm
be honest is he hurt from that no if
anything he's now smarter than the kid
that got lied to dad where do babies
come from well son when a man loves a
woman the stork delivers a baby to you
that means I'm adopted apart stork
which means I can fly it's not what you
want since you should kill his kids ha
just kidding but serious insertion makes
no sense I'm not just talking about
cursing and swearing all sensors like
why is the movie rated R when it has sex
and cursing in it and the pg-13 when
there's killing and explosions and wise
looking for women to take pictures and
bathing suits but when it comes to
underwear it's in a poke why is it okay
for us to see man boobs but when it
comes to women we have to censor then
what's the difference because one
produces no and the other one doesn't in
that case shouldn't we censor all the
cows they're basically like four legged
boobs walking around eating the grass
huh
sorry house they're just my tipping get
it tipping point cows tell Jimmy
anyway I'm not asking for there to be
changes because I don't mind living by
these rules that was just curious to see
if anyone else felt the same way because
this is something that's been bothering
me for a long time and it just feels
good to get off my chest I don't need a
censor I don't have boobs
Oh