dear Ryan what came first the chicken or
the egg hey guys so I don't know why
this has always been such a popular dear
Ryan I mean it always has been I get
this one all the time I mean look how
many likes this one comment has I'm
finally just gonna put this ridiculous
question to an end once and for all I'm
gonna scientifically prove what came
first the chicken or the egg using the
power of math I'm not gonna lie you're
probably gonna need to know at least
basic algebra to follow along it's not
algebra it's like my version of Ryan's
algebra algebra you have to learn how to
Brian to understand this so in order to
answer the most famous question of all
time what came first the chicken or the
egg we're gonna need to start with the
most famous equation of all time e
equals mc-squared
in school they teach you that einstein
meant that e equals mc-squared is energy
equals mass times the speed of light
square that's completely wrong in
algebra what it really means is egg
equals matter times chicken little
floating number two and in order to find
out what came first we have to figure
out the matter at hand which is M we
have to figure out what M equals
basically we have to find out what M
equals by getting M by itself this is
where basic algebra comes if you take
the square root of both sides of the
equation the square root gets rid of the
little phone number two leaving you with
the square root of e equals M times C
and now to get rid of C you divide the
chicken on both sides leaving you with
square root of B over C equals M now
this may look even more confusing but
bear with me a little floating number
two and the C that we got rid of earlier
will help you to understand C if we were
to write this out we're left with
chicken little floating number two
notice anything familiar exactly Chicken
Little and the nursery rhyme Nursery
Rhymes were trying to tell us the whole
time Chicken Little as the one who said
the sky is falling and falling is the
opposite of floating so if we take the
opposite of Chicken little floating we
get egg big falling big egg falling what
big egg is most famous for falling yet
another Nursery Rhyme Humpty Dumpty the
same one Dee dummy that was on a wall
and had a great fall get it on a wall
great fall he was on the Great War the
Great Wall of China which means Humpty
Dumpty was tiny in fact his name wasn't
even Humpty Dumpty it was just who but
they added the Humpty Dumpty to make it
more pleasant for kids I guess but who
was indeed a Chinese egg which means he
came from a Chinese chicken explains why
chickens go Bock Bock Bock
they're trying to say Bock is in bok
choy like a Chinese cabbage and since
eggs are the opposite of a chicken in
this equation if the eggs name was who
the opposite of that is on that was the
name of the Chinese chicken ah ah the
Chinese chicken gave us who the Chinese
egg but as you know as much as chickens
do lay eggs
do hats chicken so uh doesn't just give
us who who gives up because chickens and
eggs are one but don't forget we still
have the number two one to twelve
you see if we go back to our original
equation square root of e over C is just
twelve because the square root of an egg
where eggs come from is a chicken and if
you're left with the chicken over a
chicken that's two chickens that become
one one to twelve
we all know that in egg terms that
twelve eggs is it does a dozen equals
matter so if you really want to know the
truth and put an end to the most famous
question of all time
all you need is basic algebra and the
answer is simple it doesn't matter who
gives us so thank you guys so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the left if you
want to see the last year Ryan video
click the one on the right and remember
to leave a comment below if you want to
see a deer ride on your own