Christmas songs he's real like why non
gender-specific christmas or hanukkah
deny no raining oh hello there Rudolph
what can I do for you Oh Rudolph your
nose is what makes you special
oh that's just silly Rudolph Oh
everyone gets pimple so Mommy Kissing
Santa flash see I knew it
y'all just got caught I knew it I knew
it yeah I'm gonna tell I'm feelin all of
this no I'm filming I'm telling wait
till I tell Dad wait till I tell get
ready to get famous
worldstar Mantar drama boy
the what the drop that's not for us now
hold him ah
hey guys um I don't really know how to
spook this one I mean I don't even know
what chestnuts are I'm never even heard
of them actually I never had a meeting
had another think about it
I'll even think I've ever seen you know
nuts are funny because they're like
balls yeah they're not just nuts
I called chestnuts I mean I guess the
closest thing to having nuts and their
chests would have to be roasting on an
open fire
Feliz Navidad my confused American child
who didn't know Horse song was in
Spanish
Oh
I live crabs matches yeah
Oh what do you want for christmas I mean
um all I really want for Christmas is
you know those hoverboards that Justin
Bieber has I mean I don't want you to
buy it for me I mean you can you can
speaking of hovering boys I would also
you know and u-tube subscribers lots of
YouTube subscribers man that'd be so and
you youth I want to be young forever
and you know you grab a guy right over I
are a really big step you know I left my
purse back there stay right here I'll be
right back okay
god I hate this song so racist
grandma grandma you should save your
energy don't talk oh you're not thinking
straight he's gone grandma no problem in
the case of reindeer manslaughter over
grandma we the jury find the defendant
not guilty I don't know who they are or
what they want all I know is there's
more to it than this and I will hunt
down every single last one of them one
by one until I figure it out
look I'm upset too but revenge isn't
worth it it's not about revenge it's
about the truth my father still alive
these meetings last nobody
and the lamb that you help dare you
but look who's all grown up that's you
it's been a long time
hello son from the people who've made
underdone Benia what have you done with
my father I am you're a dear yes and so
are you
haven't you ever noticed your love for
grassy areas your preference of salads
over soaps are HP's theme present it's
time for you to become who you really
are well yeah who the hell is that day
so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you wanna see bloopers and
behind the scenes click on the left if
you want to see the previous video click
on the right and if not your hymns
they're here and watch the rest of this
yeah
telegram oh okay oh nice