got that cop makes me yeah oh excuse me
sir would you be able to spare some
change
why so you can buy more drugs god bless
hey what can I get you I just get my
grande frozen mocha sure
[Music]
every Grande frozen mocha thank you
Oh become my you got that leg right
been in love but I think I might be
for you
at first sight knock me off my feet
type taller skin me yeah you stood me up
but it's bittersweet cuz I got one but
you're all I see us
and I never thought that ever
my heart's been frozen time to let it go
and let you know
miss I needed to feel
[Music]
please don't make me beg oh there's
nothing wrong with sharing
Oh
I'll sip just a little it's the best of
the best like Starbucks the Big O gonna
do anything that I have to
with you study with you listen to Chris
Brown with you
I'm all ears when you need to meditate
way right there are we on
and I never thought I'd ever want to
leave the code even though my heart's
been frozen time to let it go and let
you know then you were the missing piece
I needed to feel
[Music]
baby after all this time I was stuck it
in the wrong place it's never about the
drink
it's about go
[Music]
there you got the money there you go
these are coffee beans well done
why
[Music]
so thank you guys so much for watching
if you want to see bloopers and behind
the scenes click the one on the left if
you want to get the song stick someone
in the bottom and make sure you guys go
check out Josh golden channel on the
right and see the acoustic version on
the right on the channel on his channel
on the right is what I meant to say also
the songs on iTunes in the bottom
blooper - my hands down the left