so we get dumped by someone you cannot
feel like not very confident so you want
to gain confidence back by cheating
something and the reason why a lot of
people think stock markets gambling
because they don't have a specific
strategies and we have about two
schooling that is over two million
already welcome back to another episode
of off the peel podcast
[Music]
all right today we got David in the
moderator seat we got I don't know why I
started dancing this right next to me
I'm Ryan and we have a very special
guest and also for the first time ever
all a sponsor of today's podcast mr.
Steven Ducks he's young 25 25 years old
like just very recently who basically
turned $27,000 correct me if I'm wrong
yeah into four million before the age of
24 and you're 25 right now 25 right so
five million dollars yeah so five-minute
dollars in well when did you start start
when I was 19 officially that is
critical in five years basically five
six years million bucks a year for
something like that summer it a good
yeah and that's why I'm intrigued but
but just just because I've kind of
butchered your whole story and what you
actually do I'll let you explain it okay
so it's gonna be a little bit different
and compared to other stock brokerage
not a lot of structure here is Apple
[Music]
Tesla Amazon's all those stocks or
options that guys here pretty much all
the time not a TV but what I specialized
I trade is the stocks are have a lot
lower market caps which it means the
stock worth a lot less compared to
Amazon's and smaller ones smaller
companies right and I'm just just as a
disclaimer for everyone out there and
and for you Stephen we're gonna have to
have you dumb this down a lot for us
because we're not experienced in this
world so even just what you just said
yeah I'm like kind of following well
we'll ask you though okay so you do you
deal with more like smaller stocks and
not like the big company the big
companies exactly that so what does that
mean exactly when you're saying you're
you trade ok so there's about three
sections of what I typically categorize
all the market caps so three sections
one is billion dollar cap which you
includes Amazon's and Tesla's or all the
bigger companies then after that we
follow with under 1 billion so will be
anywhere around 500 million to one bit
in this category is called mid cap so
that
little companies and kind of big are not
roofs with an example of one of those um
that's a kind of big company they most
of them are biotechs so they're making
medicines okay
testing their drugs and getting through
free one first two and then finally get
their FDA approval so majority the
stocks are sometime there's all types of
right types of stocks you can't be valid
tax it can be technology companies and
stuff like that and after that we follow
with anywhere between twenty million to
100 million so that's where I trade
that's considered small that's
considered small yeah is there anything
smaller than that like yes there is some
of company only worth about two million
to 10 million and they're in the stock
market yes buy and trade you can buy and
trade they're typically Nasdaq and the
bigger companies are there in your
exchange then if there's a lot of
smaller companies there will be in Pink
Sheets so just three have you heard
about pink sheets from the wolf of Wall
Street yes pink sheets are very sketchy
[Laughter]
they made the movie yeah okay so
generally when you hear about pink
sheets are pretty much garbage companies
and there's that back in twenty sixteen
twenty fifteen or a little bit early or
twenty twelve there's a lot of people
are pumping dump the stock so they're
sending out all types of emails saying
all this that's gonna go up and very
similar to awful Wall Street and except
they're doing the emails instead of
phone calls and now that people just buy
the stock and the instead ofwell dump
the stock and all the investors lose
money so the pumping means that a lot of
they get a lot of different people to
buy the stock and then the stock price
goes up up up up up yeah and then they
all sell it because other people are
like oh it's doing really well let me
put some money into it the average
people right and then and then it they
dump it because and then they all sell
it and then it drops the price right
they don't really sell it so let's say
as an average person I don't know
nothing about stocks and somebody sent
me an email this thing's gonna go up to
a couple thousand percent well of course
I'm interested so at first I'm gonna be
a little bit skeptical I'm gonna buy it
at one
and stuccos to files oh I missed a lot
of prophets so I'm gonna add more
putting more money into it and when star
goes to 20 and that's where the people
inside the stock they're holding a large
amount of shares and they sell the
stocks so when they sell I'm stuck
because I can't sell anymore if your
stock is already down 50 percent 70
percent it's not gonna go back up so
it's a scam it's a scam
yes is that illegal yes I remember in
that movie I thought they were doing
like illegal things
okay so pump and dumps it is illegal a
lot of people get caught basis and yeah
it's very sketchy so house opens sorry
yeah no no I'm just wondering I'm trying
to because I'm that's based off like the
movie and it has it like a negative
connotation around there right yeah I'm
trying to figure out what got to tie you
into that okay what do you describe what
you do and dumb down as much as you can
okay so what I do is I I study their
methods of I used to trade Pink Sheets
almost 50 times out of mana trades and I
will study the market makers so people
are inside the stock and I will study
their methods well they see and what
time would they dump so I will go into
the stock they pumped up before and I
will see there's gonna be a specific
pattern now when they see yeah they were
dumped the stock and so I basically want
to short the stock
I will go against us the stock going up
and the more the stock goes down the
more money I make so when a decides to
dump the stock one day and I'm shorting
I will make money instead of losing
money by buying stock so when you say
they are these people that you like do
you know like where they they are or who
they are no I have so yours but there's
a group of random people who have like a
certain pattern in the way they trade
sell and buy yeah it was shorting me
shorting is basically the opposite of
buying so when you buy Oh at one
daughter you sell at two daughter you
make money but we are shorting you
shorting out what two daughter buy it
back at one dollar okay so you actually
go against you don't go for
don't go ever ever no no interest about
10% of the time do you think it's safe
is that is there a reason for that is it
safer okay so a lot of people ask me
that question so shorting we are going
against a stock let's say when the stock
goes goes from two to five we are
showing that - you're actually losing
over a hundred percent of your
investment because you're shorting I -
it goes to four or you losing one person
goes to file more than that now if
you're buying in stock if stock goes to
one to zero
you only lose about 100 percent and
that's it you can't lose more negative I
see that's the risk of shorten now
Shirley requires a lot of methods risk
management how do you manage your risk
that's a whole different area for me to
cover but if you have a really good risk
management shorting does have much more
as compared to going mom especially on
these small cap stocks right because
generally the reason why they're small
caps because their fundamentals are
really bad so they're basically when so
when stock goes in when the company goes
public and the reason why they go into
public because they need money they need
people that you buy the stock days and
can do offering to raise money for their
projects when you have a really small
company you need money to grow your to
grow your company that's why yeah well
before we get more into like exactly how
you do things I kind of want to know
like just the origin like so I mean I
have a fact here that like and I said it
earlier you took $27,000 and turned it
into 4 million before the age of 24 yeah
how well for one how did you get the
27,000 to start okay because a lot of
people be like well that's easy to do
when you have so much money just a lot
for a lot of people right yeah how did
you get it to start and then also what
got you into this okay so when I was 19
I think I was uh I was one year later
and compared to other people because I
took one year off to narang where were
you I was 13 so change students and camp
here took a one-year of just learning
the language then go to high school
in Cincinnati then going to the college
Cincinnati
yeah how did you learn the language
though like we just taking classes or
were you watching light no I had I had
an American girlfriend and I had
American host been me so Wow that's what
were they he just kind of picked it up
yeah but why Cincinnati like it's old
yeah folks I supposed to go to bigger
cities and there is a bunch of at that
time because there's not a very good
relationship between the worlds China
and American it's just starting to
establish more exchanges going back and
forth so that program was just initiated
and not very long ago then that time now
nobody is very very familiar and that's
where a bunch of skinny people comes in
and it can take because it because the
Chinese parish doesn't really know
English you know take advantage trigger
Vantage of it that's why that's how I
end up being Cincinnati yeah Wow okay so
again you so you started with the
$27,000 yeah
is that just family might like how did
you get how did you start off with that
amount that's not an easy amount to
acquire for the average person yes and
at that time I think I was working at a
dorm in in the school so I was taking
night shifts because all the morning she
forgot to take other people so I was
basically working around 12 p.m. like a
literally just working a regular night
one more than a nine-to-five but working
a job and saving yeah they pay me a lot
more so that's why it took me about a
year to save them save that amount and
plus some of that like I would say 70%
come from the job 30% come from the
parents okay and they spotted you a
little bit not spy me a little bit it's
it's part of the tuition oh is it yeah
okay yeah okay so that's so you saved up
you had this
$27,000 and what just what made you be
like hey I think I can do this stock
thing like what did you get into it okay
so I was in this engineering project and
I had the idea of building a generator
and that time I were studying
nanotechnologies so well the professor
comes and say well well we don't have
enough to but we don't have enough funds
to fund the project and that's where I
think about whoa we need some fun so I
better just go and make some money and
also uh that's how I also got dumped by
my girlfriends I was a little bit
motivated to to make money to make
changes well can i I mean if it's too
personally enough to answer but is it
money related or is it just like I'm
gonna show her it sounds like the
Facebook movie like story doesn't it
what's the reasoning I mean are you
bringing that up so so we get dumped by
someone you cannot feel like and not
very confident so you only gain
confidence back by cheating something
and that's why I want to achieve
something insignificant and that's
that's why I just decided to get me the
stock market because at that time as
exchange students you can't really work
and you can't really invest because you
don't have a correct identities so
anything can do is to trade the
exchanges you can't do that oh wow did
you just
I mean you understood stocks before no I
have no I just looked into it so I just
started on youtube and watch people
expanding what the stock market is buy
some books stock for dummies yeah so I
was trading so a node ETF which is it's
not a specific company so it's basically
it's every day has volatility going up
and down so it's basically trading that
but every day is only moving about one
to two percent so I wasn't making that
much money but I see the potential let's
say if I invest $500 I can make twenty
five and thirty dollars per a day
it makes me feel good right because you
came up a little bit yeah so that time I
wasn't making $15 $13 an hour but you
can make $30 in a couple of minutes
that's not considered really good so
after that I was looking for more
aggressive income and I took a look of
add to the smoke cap market and I saw
there's one stock went from I think was
one
120-some home ridiculous like that and
basically every often they will have one
star going from one to sixty one to 50
that's a couple thousand percent gang in
only two days right so I was trying to
think how they can capture that and
that's where I started to get into the
market I'm trading right now mm-hmm
but when you say that I mean I'm sure it
always looks very like oh man I just
missed on something so big like that's
also trap in itself don't you think yeah
yes it is
that's called fear of missing out it's
conformal yeah okay hat I mean it
happens there's a reason why it's almost
like gambling right there's a reason why
people keep putting in money and and
going hoping they just get lucky but
you're a process isn't based around that
my process is not based on that at all
it looks like gambling it's not gambling
at all and the reason why a lot of
people think stock markets gambling
because they don't have a specific
strategies and you can if you think
about a lot of hedge funds like for like
Goldman Sachs and bigger hedge funds
they're winning a hundred million dollar
a day and they're winning 90% at the
time so they're opening 228 trading 220
I think was 200 trading days or
something ridiculous and their gains are
significant more than their losses right
they have a system yeah a system they
have a our algo system or computer
trading or some type of high our
long-term high winning percentage
pattern or high strategy they're using
for a while so well there's gotta be
something like that
and it's very similar to industry right
now on pretty much every single industry
either is youtubers or really stay
people or people do in South America
there's only 10% people can be extremely
right as full right so pretty much the
same laws and a lot of people are
thinking of stock market it's now for
them but it really depends on how much
work you put into but I mean like in the
stock market it's a little different in
that I feel like if you and all these
other companies are winning so often
yeah that means there's a ton of people
who are constantly losing yes so those
people
I mean there's the there has its like
energy right there's it doesn't money
just doesn't appear yeah has to come
from somewhere so these people that are
losing in a way I mean like if everyone
starts winning and if you're giving away
I mean your whole thing is you want to
help educate people right yeah wouldn't
that affect your own business no there
are so many people right I mean I don't
but in theory right in theory if all
these companies if everyone starts
catching on basically what you're saying
is there's always gonna be dummies oh
there's always a be done yeah and that
the you what like what is your goal
essentially right now okay so my goal
from the very beginning is I started
when I was a newbie I was a newbie and I
didn't get that many help from people it
took me about one year looking at the
market consistently eight hours every
single day without non-stop even the
holidays
well holidays I was studying for
statistics but and it took me a while to
really figure out what's working what's
not working so if I can give this to
people and that can help all younger
people that when I want to have their
dreams it will take much less time for
them to achieve their goals okay so I
have a question though the way that you
came about it it's just like your
ability to recognize patterns that you
feel like give you a lot of success or
is it something that almost any person
can see it's pretty much everybody can
see if you're a nerd what to do so the
the way I come out all those patterns is
I will track about a thousand samples
and up one specific pattern and I will
calculate how many times doing how many
times do I lose now will show me what
say if you trade this pattern for three
years ninety five percent can wink I
presume can news and well I would take
that trade all day and you favor peers
your peers and also attract a frequency
a frequency of the patterns so how many
times they haven't per year so I can use
that frequency times how much reward I
can make on each trade I can simulate
again of how much money can make for a
year mmm and this pattern that you saw
and you're studying is it something that
was already
I just figured out and previously talked
about is it something that you kind of
pioneered some of the strategy a career
day that by myself some of you are
already there from the books and stuff
you read yeah okay there's there's so
many different patterns and techniques
you know there's a lot of different
companies that have you know different
strategies and they sell their their
sale they sell their strategies yes kind
of like what you got you guys are doing
as well what's what's a differentiator
between your strategy and all the other
thousand strategies that are out there
okay so when you are search on internet
says how to trade that will penny stocks
how to trade micro cap stocks wait when
you when you searching there's gonna be
a thousand people come up and you don't
know where to start and so I think the
very fundamental thing you need to look
at is people's track record
do you have account statements laying
out does this person show you see is he
consistent profitable for the last five
years and if he is not then it's not
somebody wanna learn from and other
people just showing their cars no people
on YouTube showing their cars houses to
lure people in to buy their program but
they don't really have any official
track record mm-hmm that's called
lifestyle marketing and I hate that
button right but you have some stuff
that you kind of brought with us right
that like explain to me what we're
looking at because that this looks crazy
it looks like you're making a beat or
something okay okay so the green number
right here they realize so this is how
much I made today sorry real quick if
you could just because we have some
audio listeners so maybe this is a
program people can oh yeah okay so you
want me to talk about the program like
what's it about what you're talking
about okay so this is my brokerage
account this is a trade 0 it's the
brokerage out there that specialize in
small cap stocks and this is the
platform which I look the stock for and
well generally you don't really need a
path on your own all you need just the
platform to trade then it's just a
program people can download there's a
program for free uh no dad how 3 how
much the program's cost $7,000 so
this one cost about $200 per month
this one cost about $90 per month no
there's a trade zero this trizzie oh
yeah okay you don't really need this one
all you need just this one you just need
the trades are you okay ninety thousand
per month yeah so right here you can see
by sale Shore and cover so by the battle
style sale you sell style he's sure to
controller stock when once you finish
shorting you want to cover all your
positions so we're going to take a
position in shorting your position goes
in negative
we're buying your position goes positive
so it's literally the opposite and right
here that's my account number so you can
see it's XD use of ducks and and they
realize 33,000 today that's what you
made today that's what I made in profit
not in tours that in total that's in
profit so you made 33 grand today yeah
is that normal
pretty normal yeah on average you make
about 30 grand a day not averaging 30
grand a day but it really comes and goes
you know can't really tell
I think 30 grand every every three days
hmm so some some biggest lost days
biggest last days for me will be seventy
thousand well I think it's mean that I
only take that loss is pretty much about
two three times a year and the biggest
gain that made is two hundred thousand
three hundred dollars today and so I
guess with a this is an automated
program or do you have to put in
specific numbers in what you want to do
according to the patterns yes this is
what do you want to do specifically
let's say we want to short stock at this
time then you click short mm-hmm and
it's not 40 holloman air can't recognize
patterns and god yeah and why do you use
this program versus cuz I have some
stocks as well I mean I'm not a date
trader but I use like a trade
what's it what's the biggest difference
between a trade and a software that's
more looks a little more complicated
okay so I'm gonna give a very
the painting about Brokerage out there
yeah and you guys hear about probably
Interactive Brokers e-trade Robinhood
probably most popular and Robin Hood I
don't like that the way you see
everything is free but when you're
buying a stock especially for beginners
they're taking your entries so basically
they say you bought at one and they will
execute you add 1.05 what I mean
executing at 1.05 so when you want to
buy at one daughter but you actually
bought at 1.05 mm-hmm so all that zero
point buy for them belongs to Robin Hood
but I thought Robin Hood is free yes
free
yeah it's company to three trades right
when you buy it they were taking money
from tax yes I could tax
yeah so they actually charge you behind
the scenes on your profits yes if you
get yeah now when you get profit no it
doesn't really matter we can get profit
when you lose it will still take partial
when you sale hmm yeah also we again
take fire showing use mmm in or so they
win all the time that's why I don't
really like Robin Hood but it's I mean
yes the reason don't really like a Robin
Hood now follow three trade Interactive
Brokers the one I like the best they do
charge a very small amount when you are
buying certain amount of shares but if
you have a really small town they say
you only have a couple thousand dollars
or five hundred dollars I think to
produce the best for you follow on that
and brokerage take dollars per trade you
said they would take about ten dollars
on our trade and when you place the
order in the total amount it should take
ten dollars no matter how many shares
your trading mmm some of the broker you
take 0.0004 and per share so so the
reason right now that you're kind of
doing like this podcast and you've made
other appearances in other youtubers
videos and stuff like that is because
you're trying to get yourself out there
so that you can kind of I guess promote
the fact that you're kind of being you
want to be a teacher
those aren't degree like you gotyou
offer courses yeah to teach people like
us we know nothing from the very
beginning how you can get started in
doing something like this correct yeah
and you really believe that you're not
special
that in terms of like you need you
averaged um person like me or Paco you
could learn something like this if we
took your courses yes okay yeah I know
and just because I quit I quit you know
you know I didn't bring in David I'm its
mark yeah but so people like I mean
obviously this sounds like just seeing
that number oh you made 33 grand of
course I'm interested of course
everybody who hears is interested but
naturally the skeptic in me the skeptic
and everyone is like yes so this sounds
too good to be true this guy seems Shady
not that I think you're Shady
but you know why should people take you
as legitimate like why explain does what
makes you different from your average
shark or the things they see on the big
short or the things they see on Wall
Street you know okay so the thing is a
lot of people out there as I said the
very fundamental thing is they don't
have their track record and I have about
I think I have my verification on
2018-2019 and because a lot of people
did have a very very skepticism so like
they they doubted me that I actually
turned twenty seven thousand into nine
hundred thousand within a year and so I
replicate that performances in 2018 by
auditing my calcium and say every single
month to a CPA firm and I did it so if
you guys are a lot of people are skip
ilysm they can look at my account
statements and you put that out there
public yeah yeah and that cost you money
to do as well it cost
yeah they cost a lot cause like 50k
sometimes even every time you do an
audit every year yeah oh wow
it's expensive to audit that's just
that's six days of works okay and also I
also review the one of my count
statements that for the maximum
performances I turned forty one thousand
into three hundred thousand you know
Martha so now I guess um also with your
cuz how do people learn your stuff is it
a online courses or book it's an online
course online course and about how long
does it take or is it like you
at your own pace so typically will take
about a year year and half to pretty
much no other strategies and getting
settled in your head so it's almost like
a trade school in a way yeah when you
say a year and a half is it doing this
everyday for a year and a half doing
this pretty much study about at least
two to four hours a day okay you've got
something that we're like what you did
is work pretty much holiday to save up
and then study for like a couple few
hours so going to school and then also
yeah it's pretty much the same pretty
much very everything that you going to
school or going getting good at sports
they take you right how long have you
been giving out these courses I've been
giving out for a year almost two years
now and have you had people yes succeed
and have you had people fail good angry
customers yes we did so we have at least
20 students not it's already over at
least 200,000 and we have about two
students that is over two million
already in a year or a year yeah and we
did have customers that they won't speak
Spanish so like they can't understand
the course that's yeah but is there
anyone who took it and they just didn't
see results and maybe it's because they
weren't studying or maybe they weren't
doing it right but like there has to be
people who like it there's no way you
have a hundred percent track record it
not 100 percent tracker as I said a lot
of people they don't really put the work
in right failed and they have very angry
a lot of the 20 people how many roughly
do you think so 20 percent I would say
20 year of 120 out of 100 yeah kind of
like didn't so it's a pretty good
percentage 20 out of 100 are doing well
or not doing well 20 out of hundred are
doing very well
mmm do you well then probably 50 out of
hundred okay yeah yeah that makes sense
because I mean so so this track record
right I mean some would say that oh why
isn't it 90 percent right but what
you're saying is that even though
somebody can purchase your class it
doesn't mean that they're studying it
the right way is that is that how it is
or is it that they're not starting off
with enough money
or is it I mean I'm sure it's a variety
of reasons yeah there's a lot of people
that they just had kids and the bottle
cords and having get into a burner
because I do live trading webinars to
people I've trade in front of them
and they don't even come to the webinars
yeah and that's how they failed quick
they wanted they bought it because they
wanted to make money quickly as opposed
to just wanting to study actually really
apply it yeah well a lot of people that
just come in well Stephen Hubbell just
give me your alerts and the William bio
just buy the same thing with you you
can't do that because what happens and
when I just go off I just want to trip
I'm at home I don't want to teach
anymore you're not self-sufficient and
it's not gonna help you it's the whole
like teacher man or give a man a fish he
eats for a day yeah
teach a man to fish he eats for his life
yeah and also I feel like they're lazy
the the fundamental of the program is I
won't teach them to be self-sufficient
not being and to put in the work because
you did yeah you have to earn it you
can't just copy notes yeah yeah so
essentially and then going back to kind
of I guess skeptics you I mean you
clearly make a ton of money daily yeah
why charge for these courses if the
whole goal is to get these people to do
obviously I get it it's a business in
itself yeah is the goal to because this
business you think could be way bigger
and it also helps people or is it like
you know I mean it's kind of it's kind
of strange to the average person like
you're making this much money why you
need to charge why not just upload
YouTube videos yeah add you upload a lot
of YouTube videos for teaching people
and everything is free out there and
also the reason why I charge people is
that they want to feel something is
important when you buy something that's
super expensive you think is important
so that's why we just give stuff for
free they don't really care yeah yeah
yeah and they don't take it necessarily
as seriously yeah true okay well we're
at our half time right now so we're
gonna take our quick shishi break and
we'll be right back all right or do you
have a special talent oh yeah we do that
now can you tell us a funny joke or can
you sing is there something do that
halftime show performance anything you
want to do I'm really good at gaming but
yeah I guess we'll just cut to an hour
games
a live stream will come back we have
some personal questions for you as well
so I think it'll be a little interesting
yeah we'll be right back and we're back
so what do you have here okay so this is
my brokerage account statements you can
see starting day it's December 20 on
December 1st 2018 ending period is
December 31st also this is what you were
talking about earlier about having proof
of your track record that most people
who give advice to basically do this
don't have yeah okay so this is a
website and you can call it your
verified if it's real or not and this
listeners it's trade 0.30 Kol
yeah so this is a mag well I don't want
to show my account number but this is my
account number and now the only thing
you need to pay attention to is you can
see right here
net profit right net P and else and
that's net profit and you can see on
this day made one hundred twenty one
hundred seventeen thousand this day lost
six thousand this day lost thirty five
thousand the study made twenty nine
thousand and overall forum for a month
and made about two hundred fifty five
thousand that's one month it's one month
yeah Wow
so the days you lose like 30-something
thousand you don't even that's not even
a drop in the bucket
yeah and it's its base as part of it
it's part of it so it's not like it's
like you made a good bet and get a bad
name if you ask any legitimate traders
you can't really win every single trade
right now possible so so that's why you
had to start off with twenty seven
thousand because without enough capital
well I mean I guess you could bet really
low right you can't ya because so I mean
in general what what let's say someone
only has a thousand dollars okay it's a
five hundred cuz he said number but you
are making and losing between what like
five and twenty dollars a day yes pretty
much like that and then you'd and that
was enough to get you like how did you
at what point did you take that was it
gradual gradual growth because that
seems like
- big leap in such a short amount of
time okay so when I was treating with
the $500 I was losing there and there
and once I got into the small cap market
and that was tracking statistics so
because I was an engineer everything is
based on statistics so that's why I use
the engineering method into the stock
market and they want to track this one
specific patterns
well how much well when I trade how much
money can I make
what's the percentage of reward so after
I check that was 20% and that attract
the winning percentage was 85% so each
trade I have a eighty eighty-five
percent win chance and the twenty
percent of the world that can make
thousands of the same trade again again
and again then that's how I Verdi's put
more money so when you were just getting
started I mean assuming these people
that are taking your courses and they're
trying it for themselves
yeah they're not gonna be as good as you
in the beginning yes right so you have
to I mean I'm sure you've had a lot of
losses more so than now in the beginning
yes how were you able to convince
yourself like this is I'm doing the
right thing you know
okay when those losses were happening so
when the losses are happening a lot of
people so well as a human nature and
when people take a loss the instant
reaction they will feel is I won't make
this money back so yeah so I want to
make the money back they will make
emotional mistakes that's how casino
people lose money exactly yeah and now
the reason why you trade in stock market
because there's a wall there's a edge
for high only percentages 70 percent 80
percent even the sixty percent can still
make money in your honor wrong wrong and
when you are taking a loss in the single
into my mindset is so I track this
pattern and I do have 15 percent of
losing percentages and when I lose
also your mind I will know how much
money I can make per year because I know
the frequency of the pattern or
risk/reward of the pattern how many
times it happened per year and and I can
use that to simulate again it can make
about five million dollars a year and in
my mind I know I can make five million
dollars a year if I take a one loss it
doesn't really matter
is walk away and come back again so it's
more like a long-term it's more like a
long-term investment instead of like
looking at right right right
Wow how many different so like for
example yesterday how many different
companies are you trading are you
focusing on like one company or are you
inputting like a bunch of money into it
or are you kind of spreading out amongst
like a thousand companies and putting
like a tiny bit in each one okay so this
is where you want to pick one stuff so
you want to trade and now typically when
I look at the market I want to look for
everything that has volume that means
people are other people are looking at
it as well so typically market opens at
9:30 I wake up around 9:00 and just
generally take a look at the overall
market and what stock is hot so one
stock is up about or 50% already so a
lot of people will have eyes on it and
that's very generous volume that's the
stock that will pick the volume is the
amount of activity going on between
buyers and sellers yes mm-hmm
see so the higher the volume it means
that most people like a lot of people
are tricked there's a lot of activity
which means there's more potential for
ups and downs
well it's and downs and that means
volatilities yeah so up and downs and
when you there's more people trading
there's more newbies Kim right because I
mean in general like and in a way you
can't really feel bad because those are
the people who weren't willing to put in
the time to study yeah and and really
there's those are the casual gamblers
like going to Vegas with money yeah
they're not gonna play the odds they're
playing emotion yes yeah I guess I
understand that it's easier to because
you don't have to see their faces yeah
it's not like at the poker table yeah
you know he has the money I was waiting
you know
okay I understand that so you don't
trade like stable stable stocks yeah I
don't really trade staple stock I want
to trade something that can move 70
percent 100 percent thousand percent on
the day so the stable ones are the ones
that are more for long-term would you
say the stable ones are yes for non term
for swing trades or something index
family what's a swing trade it's being
traded is you are holding four positions
for a couple month a year so even a
couple months you consider a long
from trade yeah instead consider no
because you do it what by the day I did
a yeah yeah so take us to your everyday
like you told us something early I don't
know if it was on the podcast or right
before but you work like two hours a day
yeah obviously in the beginning it was
all day yeah and for now at your level
and your success rate you wake up at
9:00 you can start at 9:30 you're done
by 11:30 yeah most actually and most of
the time just by 10:00 I want to stay
about 30 to 45 minutes and then what do
you do go to LA you know get a haircut
so get into your personal stuff
apparently we just heard before we
started this that you're you made it to
a competition in StarCraft you're huge
gamer Starcraft 2 David and I both used
to play that not nearly as good you made
it to the top 64 in the world yeah at
one point I was in the WCS champion the
championship he was at WCS so we're
serious war series championship oh you
were in it how far did you make it I
think it was made in road of 64 and I
lost in the road of 64 oh my gosh that's
still crazy I guess you know what when
you have that kind of money and then
you're just like I'm gonna get good at
Starcraft so you buddy star crap every
day yeah is this before or after you
started this is before actually when I
trying to develop the stock market
strategies I used the sorceress
strategies because it's more almost like
same message same psychology counter
strategies you want to counter people
with that doing mistakes
yeah making me say if you were going the
meta which is like buying stock yes then
you're going counter meta yeah so people
are buying battlecruisers you're getting
anti-air yeah your minds okay so okay so
it's to you it was almost like common
sense yeah okay interesting and you see
something you can basically we never see
a certain action
you will know why they're building you
can do you need to against it it's just
very much a psychologist right right
right
you're interesting gaming doesn't just
create gun violence
it creates money so I have a question
here so I you know a lot of people say
they look up to you know the advice of
Warren Buffett right yeah as a very
successful trader mom you know something
that I did read somewhere that Warren
Buffett said is that if you you know
take your paycheck and you take a
percentage of it and you invest it into
a fund or the sp500 it has a history of
you know it's an uphill slope yes with
some dips in between but from the very
beginning of the stock market it's
always been an upward trend yes so he
was saying that you know if you put your
money in there eventually you will make
money and it'll compound and it'll make
even more yeah and and so that's like a
long-term kind of mindset right yeah do
you do you believe in I do believe it
yes when you invest into us being from
500 or going to in this index pounds you
do make money on long-term thank you
five years ten years but you don't
really make aggressive income and what
percentage do does that generate you
would you say oh I don't really know 20
percent 50 percent maybe it'll be more
than that she's pretty good over a long
period of time period of time but when
you look at anything I trade twenty
seven thousand into 1 million by already
account statements that's that's that
presumably over 20 percent
it's thousands of percent yeah right so
I mean ever since so it's been about
five years five six years of success
yeah right how has it changed your
confidence I mean like you said you kind
of started this because of your ex like
I mean there's no I'm sure a part of you
is kind of like you know yeah how do you
take us back to where you are now like
to that scenario that first collect you
start like how do you feel are you like
over that are you like do you keep in
touch with her like what's this one say
I'm pretty much over it
okay well that's good but as she hit you
up hey Steven hi rise up you have higher
standards meeting you up though that's
true I mean I'm sure you've seen it
people know you have money and you're
making money and naturally just in
anything anything you become famous you
make money you're naturally gonna get
people coming after you there's gonna be
people who want something from you
including girls yeah and she hasn't hit
you up since she did once but oh yeah
but that doesn't mean it was just for
money could be but I mean how has it
changed your life I mean obviously I
don't know I actually don't know how was
your everyday life now that you work
those two hours that's not trying to get
at what else other than gaming how does
it change your life really change
anything my life I love cars and they're
just bought cars and nicer car once you
try six-month and get tired of a generic
honor I don't think your personality
changes and they're losing you fly to LA
30 times a year yes private jet
sometimes no nope every day okay because
Cincinnati doesn't have a private jet
yeah okay well I mean like a like I said
that might change cuz you're only at the
four million more or five million mark
right who says in five years you won't
be what six exponent no what are you
projecting in five years I don't know
because there's a synonym you can make
on micro cap stocks
you can't exceed 20 millions a year yeah
so thinking about you think that at the
rate that you've been you know I don't
know maybe it's consistent you hit a
plateau where you get a million a year
or has it been like twenty dollars then
making a hundred dollars and then a
thousand then then thirty thousand like
yeah what's your projection the
projection is I don't really you don't
really want to do this forever
you always want to like spray your
folios really stay which I just a couple
properties don't want to go and once you
have all the proposals they all generate
any money and so on and and these
courses - it's a business in itself get
enough people then you don't even need
to do this and the reason why I start
courses is
you guys all know packing like a year
ago through a year ago lot of people are
starting lifestyle marketing I don't
know if you guys notice courses yeah are
showing you houses but there's like that
one guy on YouTube Tai Lopez yeah yeah
yeah it's all my stuff marking where is
the track record and why do dad show us
the track record well I mean I think a
lot of those I never I was just annoyed
by those ads I just be like this guy is
such a douchebag anyway I would look at
that I don't feel like it would get
people's attention you're right but then
but then are they legitimate they might
be don't know yeah you don't know but
but you're going the route of like
here's transparency yeah and I'm sure
there's gonna be people who the people
who are mad at you who are gonna speak
out against you yeah but if you have the
proof you have the receipts then I mean
there's nothing you can really say and I
think that's important to be transparent
I think it's very important yeah okay I
think it's one of the most important
yeah before you start teaching people
because if you don't know what you're
teaching then you're teaching that run
the wrong thing and a lot of people
that's not right yeah right okay I mean
do you so you do you enjoy the teaching
process would you say you're a better
teacher or a better try see my cuz when
I teach people because I attract a lot
of more younger generations so a lot of
people are gamers and funny people and
we have our own common languages so it's
actually yeah it's a do you enjoy
teaching yeah and then you feel
obviously so how exactly just to give
you a rough estimate how much are these
courses some of the courses or if
they're super beginners to start yeah to
start like $90 come on okay so it's a
good subscription service yeah like
anything else like almost like going to
I mean I guess a really cheap college
yeah not considering not calling what
you do a college but that's kind of what
it is is you're taking a school right it
depends on how what I well how deep you
want to go of course is I mean but do
you think I mean how many courses are
there like do you think you have to
finish it to get to where you're at
yeah I would say
there's about well it's not how many
courses is about how many live webinars
and I do and you watch me trade I can
pretty much do the same thing I'm not
there looking up in the morning and make
sure execution goes good and doing your
own statistics it's the method I see
it's like learning how to do it yeah and
you have a lot of videos online you said
right yeah so what differentiates that
from the classes like what makes
somebody go you know I think I should
take the classes because these videos
can only offer so much or is it is like
a way more intense dense because I so
YouTube videos are more general
beginners for people that just want to
get in the market and they don't know
what even stock market is and you can
listen some general opinions and what
should you or should not do
find your voice on beginning mistakes
there and there but if you really want
to get into pattern statistics and real
convince courses that just teach you the
patterns then yeah I'm saying that's
where the paid courses come again yeah I
really wish we had you here at 9:30 so
we got a watch to just do it yeah howdy
here right before after yeah I wish I
would have just seen it just to be like
oh okay
it's like that not that I would
understand how to do it just as like
visually just see you do it yeah and
then be like okay let's do the podcast I
just made 30 grand so cool would you say
that a majority of your income comes
from trading versus like your your other
business with the teaching trading
accountant of trading makes more money
and compared what percentage probably 70
percent 80 percent yeah mm-hmm it's not
the service is not started to I want to
make money from people
yeah yeah it's not dedicated in that
yeah but I mean eventually I mean if
you're putting in the time to build it
out and and run it yeah you have to
there has to be some read it's not a
charity
yeah right so I mean it makes sense it's
a business at the same time earlier he
said he wants like when you pay for
something now give it worth so that's
what it's true yeah true that's mainly
what it's for yeah yeah yeah well I mean
that's interesting we have some
questions from fans okay you mind
answering here we have one from Ji Young
here when do you believe the next
financial downturn will happen and
should we wait to begin investing until
that happens kind of like what I guess
Warren Buffett does right yes but when
it was really cheap and then yeah
so there's because when I trade while
micro cap stocks they don't have any
correlations being on well compared to
the entire market so when the market
goes down we rub it doesn't really
affect this affect the stock what I'm
trading so that's something that you can
be really safe to learn to trade and
also you can learn how to really trade
in on terms so financial process happens
every 10 years so we're at that mark
consistently consistently yeah okay so
it's coming soon soon yeah so I mean but
in your it's almost the opposite for you
right all right correct me if I'm wrong
but you're waiting to people over invest
and then you short right you don't go
against that yeah so you're not waiting
till it's well I guess it would be at
the same time right when the market is
bad then more people invest is that how
it works okay let me give you examples
it's very easy to understand okay and
okay let's start from the beginning so
when it stopped when this stock is going
up the first time and a lot of people
are telling your friends okay well
invest in stock the stock went from it's
the new Tesla and stock went from 1 to
10 and you tracked a lot of people to
invest the stock now well the company
didn't do that gun stock went from 10 to
1 and all of your stuck at 10 so the
next time with stock bounces to 10 go
spectacles to 10 again after 2 years you
guys are tired of holding and the stock
goes back to 10 I was short a because
you guys will sell you guys don't want
to hold out that's one more pattern that
you've recognized but when I'm shorting
it there's still people buying at 10
because they think always gonna be
potentially break through 10 and that
time we trap will trap new people into
at 10 right
and when stock goes against the time
again will cause a certain chain
reactions will
keep coughing are you like coughing is
it very rare that you're wrong about
that like let's say something it is the
next Tesla lately it yeah like how often
does that happen to you one not a 50
very rare yeah so we're betting the
percentages so this kind of happened
with Bitcoin right wait what's your idea
like we remember when there was such a
big I mean I'm sure you know it was such
a big thing we crypto right yes it was
at I think our friends were like oh it
was at well I don't remember them didn't
20 he was really yeah but it was like a
10 when I was super popular and then it
went up to 20 yeah and people were still
buying along the way even our friends
were buying her on like 10 went up to 20
and they were still holding on to it and
people were saying it's gonna come back
down it kind of did it did I was
shooting it but okay
yeah so you you I was being part of it
yeah yeah it's same thing and so what if
though and people still believe we have
friends who still say bitcoins gonna be
the future what if it just keeps I guess
a it's just a pattern thing like you're
assuming it's never gonna come I'm not
assuming it's never gonna become big but
I think about like this so at that time
back in 20 I think it was 2017 yeah so
the big one when there's a huge hype
about it and understand the industry of
pretty much everything 90% people do
this morning so when 90 people for some
people trying to buy something you're
trying to be cool against it so that's
how you make money I see now since since
it was a huge hype and there's more
people are trapped in it so a lot of
people holding 15,000 16,000 17,000 even
though 20,000 when that goes back to
20,000 again other people will sell it's
the same psychology right so first to
recover from that many back holders
which people are holding the bag we
don't looking to sell I will take years
and years so for the next couple of
years the investor will be fighting the
pack holders for a while so you right
before this you mentioned breaking ten
so are you saying breaking 10 because 10
is a whole like a good number like a 1 0
and then like 2015 or yeah so the first
time when stock arel I'm not gonna short
it because I want to know where the bag
holder is I want to know where to start
drops once they trap enough back holders
everyone know or at this price before
looking to sell and we go stop rise and
short sell it
and people when they're people well when
people are trying to buy it at ten there
will be new people traveling again so
will cause a chain reaction next time
when people trying to buy again I was
still short selling and then mm-hmm do
it again and again again no always make
money mm-hmm until the day I'm
theoretically on to the day that it just
keeps but blows up until the day that we
were saying even then it should come
back down well until the day breaks ten
yeah then now we'll cut at ten fifty
then we just lose fifty cents out of ten
dollars talk I see right oh I see okay
there is me so I'm just trying to follow
everything in my head yeah it's like
yeah it's such a new concept right I saw
you nothing about stocks I think if I
can under I kind of understand but I
think if I can kind of understand I
think a lot of people listening will
know a lot more know people say that a
lot you know he did like the one with
Andrea I was like what does he not know
anything on this show yes we I need
things dumbed down but I did a great job
I think I understand this a lot more and
I think I appreciate the fact that
you're being very transparent even
though as a skeptic person myself I
would personally be like well how do I
know what I'm looking at because this is
confusing and we're taking it from your
words so if I had somebody verify that
doesn't know you been like oh yeah this
is legit I would probably believe it
more but I'm not I'm not questioning it
I'm yeah and I've met you now and you
seem like a very straight up dude and
you play Starcraft 2 so that helps
there's like a certain connection there
and I I don't know I think it's it's
definitely interesting and it seems like
you genuinely want to help yeah and yeah
I mean if you're gonna I wouldn't
personally I don't know enough to
encourage anyone but I think if you're
interested we can find Steven where can
they steven duck sitcom so d Steven Dux
i com QX I okay yeah Steven ducks EECOM
okay cool um did we miss anything well I
mean we do have a couple more oh yeah
questions
yeah so Eric Wynn has a question and
it's like if you gotta be combined with
a lot of other things too but it's just
like I have a 9 to 5 job that requires
me to have my full 8-hour attention but
I really want to trade and make a profit
yeah do I have to trade hourly / daily
in order to be successful okay so
there's two strategies I'm teaching why
you can be a full-time day trader one
thing can be a part-time day trader but
right now I'm leaving on part-time
because I only stay about 45 minutes so
as long as you can all take your time
and wake up at 9:00 try it until 10:00
then you're good just what is it every
day it's pretty much every day is there
a way you could do like does it or does
it just not work this way that you do
follow your stress is your strategy
based on you have to be there every day
a strategy is based on you have to be at
least 30 minutes every day every day
what if you did like a week straight and
then you skipped a couple days and then
you win another you can still skip yeah
so you can you can't skip Camus a day
that doesn't ruin your strategy oh no
okay well what about whatever at like
the beginning though you know when
they're just starting to learn because
some people aren't gonna be able to just
you know do what you did and or aren't
brave enough to necessarily just give up
what they're doing and commit to this
full-time right yes so if you're not
really committed to this beginning I
don't really recommend people to
recommit time for to learn these
strategies to learn the industries you
need a year of learning repetition yeah
for actually trading just 30 minutes to
45 yeah what about people who aren't I
mean a lot of this seems like pattern
recognition is pattern recognition
something you can learn or is there
something like it's it's like math where
you can learn the formula you can learn
the formula okay so it is like a math
it's like it's not like writing we're
like you have some people are creative
and some people just there's an answer
it's 80% math 20% I'll say sick ha
judgment judgments okay yeah in the
psychology part refers more so to
whether that day you want to like you
feels more selfish
yeah sometimes you feel more greedy
sometimes you want to make more money in
sometimes well if you
take a loss you want to make you back
here so it's it's more about discipline
right so that's what you were saying
about like people make emotional
decisions and your whole thing is don't
do that don't do your robot that's
that's definitely um interesting do you
wanna go through the list of us we got
one last one from Adi Chon do what
advice do you have for high schoolers
that want to start investing okay so for
high schoolers I don't think you can
open up a brokerage account before you
turn 21 but when I was 19 I I think I
yeah when you turn 18 you can open it up
approach broker check account but you
can't really have a margin account
what's a brokerage account a brokerage
account just have an account you need
trade and okay it's just like to get in
like the program your unit is due to
open up you have to be 21 to 18 18 and
you need to when you turn 21 can have a
margin account which means you have a
leverage you can borrow money in from
the brokerage I don't know which allows
you to short which allows you to short
okay so okay but you're not borrowing
from nothing you're borrowing from the
money that you've already put in the
yeah yeah so you can't short until your
until you have that margin account
account
yes uni that's your strategy restaurants
but you can use your parents do count
but yeah that's how yeah yeah okay well
again I know I kind of followed but
people were really interested I'm sure
if you actually are interested there I'm
sure there's a lot more they can see on
YouTube first if you like what you see
go to Stephen ducks I Dux
Icom Yeah right and check check his
stuff out any other handles or anything
you want to plug Twitter Instagram stuff
like that
oh yeah there's yeah yeah yeah just take
the description I mean also spar audio
listeners like description well you can
just say it like what's your Twitter
handle and Instagram what do you use
actually Twitter Instagram and YouTube
that's it okay sweet you choose me
Steven dogs and just look up Steven no
Pablo you pop up yeah if you want to
find him you'll find it also just don't
give skin but I think accounts there's a
live fake and some of you of me yeah Wow
okay whether you have a verified cheque
mark no no no you should probably ask
yeah if cuz if not that could be a big
deal if we were falling it wrong yeah
that's like open wrong this is like
really sensitive with money make sure to
check the description to find the
accurate that's the main thing cool with
that being said I guess thank you again
for being here man this is very very
educational you can follow us at off the
pill on twitter at off the pill podcast
on instagram and basically how we end
this is we just breathe into the mic so
in three two one
stocks now the stocks