hey Brian welcome back to another
cooking we're sure Papa Sue's yeah yeah
they're right remember this show I did
this with Shawn about two three years
ago actually last time we did was with
you we did it for Shawn yeah it wasn't
as good what part of you watch the show
you might be wondering why it's on this
chap there wasn't any vlog type of stuff
on this channel before but I figured
it's time I'm gonna have more personal
stuff on this channel things that are
shows that are around what I do I don't
cook I know I said that I'm lying but
not really and you know what I've
actually learned a lot and the
difference is we don't have Shawn this
time that's my little worried because
last time we had Paco it was so hard
because you don't know I mean I don't
know how to cook I'll admit that I don't
know how to cook that's why I made this
show I know how to cook you do not he
doesn't know how to more than you okay
so well here's a scenario all the guys
who we normally cook for the rest of our
hpc they're not in town right now so
basically have to make something that
will last two days because that's when
everyone gets best so what are you gonna
do today what are we making one last two
days and then we can meet I guess we
need ideas huh a little bit aside oh we
should make our own why we just make
Papa but like our own versions dessert a
dessert a hot pot we can do a dessert
one yeah we should do a dessert one but
we need like a meal or do we just be
like cheeseburgers so you have patties
and then put cheese like some onions or
like any kind of burger we want you make
it negative and we make fries but the
prize itself are hot pockets we hollow
out the fries and we put cheese and
stuff inside the fries sender like fry
hot pockets I don't know how that's
possible you've ever had cheese and
fries they're really cheesy fries yeah
yeah
but to be a hot pocket but things got to
be on the inside not the outside that's
different it's kind of like what's
realistic right
second you know what we're doing it this
is our show best pen ingredients what do
we need for the hot pocket mm-hmm we are
gonna need dull so good ol burger cheese
diced onions same cut fries doctor
cheese for dessert
cream cheese strawberries and some kind
of we don't because I don't have it so
I'm kind of syringe or Smith it inject
the food with to fill up the dessert
yeah this is why you don't throw stuff
into your cards I didn't know I
literally have never made anything like
this before so how do you open these
just just bring it open right just like
that it's pop it like this yeah oh oh
dude how much do you think like how big
does this get when you heat it up
how many pockets is it come across the
key take it out part what take this much
no stretch it you know maybe don't do
that maybe what do we do with it then I
think usually take it apart what do you
mean take it apart a bowl there oh it's
not like you just like like play-doh all
right so we've got our frozen burgers
because me and coke for you I'll make
some real burgers so wait what maybe
uses a knife no warning the following
video contains stupid and dangerous
activities do not attempt to reenact
less dangerous yeah I've separated it oh
it seems so sketch turn up me already
separated I want you to grab it like
that I'm not strong really I think you
just cut it open wait if I'm get you can
you step in it yeah this yeah see just
like that that didn't do anything
should we just put it on there or should
we no you know what this is so much this
is too much this is not cooked
no it's not what are you gonna put in
the oven okay if you say so
actually we should cut the onion we need
a diced onion um okay I'll do the onions
then yeah do I cut I don't know onion I
know you're supposed to cry that's not
working
daddy's no cuz you oh you're so scary
why what let me try I know how see see
kids you want to cut the nipple off cut
the nipple up now we dice pieces like
this see it's like an apple I've seen TV
shows and when they're dicing and you
just just listen they do the longer
shows they're hella fast you ever watch
those videos you're like
[Applause]
[Laughter]
hey what happens if you win the Nicene
championship you know it surprises some
terrible pun that you're gonna make an
onion ring and that was pretty good come
on come on I'm done I'm not soaked you
hurt you every angle I just wanna make
sure it's not just hey this is pretty
ketchup in this one you know go give it
now really all right so now we wrap this
bad boy
yeah yeah just tuck it in whoops big big
whoops that was a big whoops I just made
pockets aren't square watch it we'll
watch
well I got it I got the burger is that
still is ha ha ha it's too wide it has
to be like this we don't know how long
it takes to cook the meat the burgers
what's on it are you sure yes okay then
10 20 I'm on record saying we should
cook the burger first now I'm on record
saying this will work all right we'll
see right you will eat a big you need
this much onion that's okay this much
all right so what happens if it is good
oh you're gonna eat that
yep oh man that bread doesn't look kind
of good this is the test 20 minutes s
quarter of an onion is the meat the
bread seems good I'll give you that but
is thumper that's a good it's pretty
Chris any good Chris oh that cheese
cheese is gonna this is look at the
burger though that don't look like a
very cook the burger to me
[Music]
eat that again that's not cooked at them
all right here it is right all right so
we have our dough it's a little bit more
rectangular I guess I'll baggage cheap
but this time we cut the burger and we
cook the burger more in the shape that
we want
oh yeah that's pretty good Jody but you
know what that's just how our pockets
are this is our test if this works we're
gonna make a bunch of these in two days
for the guys and see how it turns out
let's fill it out but you know what who
hasn't made a hot pocket this goes out a
little bit from that it's right so the
shape is a little wider and higher than
it should be for our pocket button looks
pretty solid to me so let's try this bad
boy there we go oh yeah that looks good
that is hot still don't burn on the
bottom but it looks good dude this looks
like something this looks like real food
I blew it for us we're good
not bad Shawn would be proud of this
sometimes you make these things and they
look cool but they're not the best
tasting this one's up there the fries
are clearly not known workers are too
skinny yeah we have tear tots as our
backup and we're gonna try and make the
Tater Tot fill pocket yeah and we're
gonna shoot it is gonna cook it make a
Holden Tater Tot fill it with cheese
which we need to melt down and I don't
know if this is gonna work follow my
fingers I'm gonna burn all right let's
try it
we're we gonna cook them first I wanna
see if it works
isn't working oh oh okay sorry we cook
it I think it'll work right
these are test tots and we're gonna see
well that she's stayed in it didn't spit
out anything he's more cheese
look good all right we know that the hot
pocket thing works the burger cheese
burger Haut pocket works the tear tots
are they work for the most part yeah I'm
sitting on it for dessert how do you
have a thing I got a thing I'll put down
four things I need Gracie got sugar
cream cheese excuse and where's the
strawberries I'm gonna smash the cream
cheese kind of into like a square like
thing slices of strawberries and we're
gonna put brown sugar on it why Brown
graces tis I like brown sugar what you
don't know what the difference between I
don't either so why it was so why brown
sugar if you don't like brown rice it's
healthier so I figured brown sugars over
here alright well put that bad boy in
the oven and let's try it
hey that's a nice golden brown and it
held its shape interesting strawberries
nice you could be sweeter more I need
something is not sweet yeah marker
[Music]
preparing or surprise all the guys are
here how do we describe lunch I'm done
it turned out lighter than its didn't
work it so at least we got the treasure
all right you're gonna come try this
hello I'm not even enthusiastic cousin
Paul it looks today we made for you guys
something that was good two three days
but today we have for you three day old
[Applause]
we have cheeseburger hot pocket oh this
is our idea was to have fries with the
cheeseburger but putting cheese inside
the fries when it didn't work with fries
so we used tater tots oh that was even
hard to do for the kids bursting apart
so they're just care puffs are barely
any cheese in them all right hot is the
pocket and this is Papa's vacation and
this is the dessert this Punk was crazy
this is our apologies how come in this
way it actually looked a lot better
before see it's a complete knockout
cheers boys 5/5 star rating presentation
whoo I might be able to actually eat
this whole thing
Wow a solid for unsure running faces out
of 5 these Ryan phases like just wait
dude just keep burning himself that's
how good it is you got you can't come
you know so it's a burn y'all
poor Bert comes out of I'm a well
done guy in this meat right here is
definitely well done so I say 5 out of 5
[Applause]
[Laughter]
it's the fruit I think that's where it
makes out the sweeteners three
strawberries rotten strawberries what
it's not even that graphic it's just
overall we can we still can't cook it
that was cooked
[Music]
[Applause]