hey guys as a lot of you know my two
most popular videos how to be gangster
and how to be emo were removed from
youtube
and guess when they were removed that's
right christmas eve
but it's okay because it was youtube's
gift to me to help open my eyes and
realize
that there are kids starving in
yugoslavia so as i was saying a lot of
videos
including mine are getting removed from
youtube because they have copyrighted
material in them
it is silly to remove videos that that
cause no harm
you know they're not doing anything
wrong so what if it has some music in it
that doesn't belong to us
it's like free promotion so you're
welcome but anyway
i wrote a beautiful poem to express my
feelings youtube will not last life long
if all the videos are gone from a little
stupid rule all of this happening just
ain't cool i thought it was a place for
fun
entertainment for everyone now these
companies are barging in tearing up the
site like it belongs to them threatening
youtube for having their songs
help we all just get along remove every
video left and right almost everything
on their site if there's just one thing
i hate is all those mother beeping
copyrights
that's copyrighted not really anyways to
all those companies out there who helped
remove my videos i just wanted to
apologize and say i'm really
really sorry