oh hi didn't see you there oh wait yes I
did you didn't see me cuz I'm a ninja
every day I wake up the first thing I do
is work out a new strength speed and
cardio for strength I start off with
one-handed push-ups good for speed well
have you ever seen I need to move this
fast see and one of the hardest
exercises of my day would have to be
working on my cardio yeah how much you
want 2500 deal
are you a true ninja always seems the
harder run from point A to point B that
is though this parkour or as I like to
say Park hour because that's how I like
to pronounce things I see in the college
spell I don't care if it sounds dumb
[Music]
being a ninja I've been known to break
things I can break anything I can break
wood I can break price break branches
break wind take a break break dance
break cars break cars break fast and of
course the most extreme of all breakups
We Need to Talk we are talking I'm so
sorry no yes is it another girl another
guy no why
it's because because you're bleeding all
over my carpet
mr. quiz everybody knows that a ninja
has to be stealthy and use camouflage
can you find me here no I'm not under
the couch not the lab not the table that
where am I
boom wrong I was the left in order to be
a ninja if the hose and the artist
surprised with you last but not least
every single day I buy at least one
mission for my ninja ow
thank you head of a bull let's do this
[Music]
for the name of the broomstick gods I
summon thee
what are you doing here oh I think you
know I really don't okay when you're a
lot of options and ninja stars you know
what to do that's right remember
[Music]
the last thing you'd expect from a ninja
is ninja good star surprise why are you
doing this to me I was ordered to but
you're tough they want to kill me
no just didn't buy my cookies well in
that case let me get those thin mints I
really really like those the way they
just touched my mouth and by the name of
the broomstick gods give me a sharper
broom