do you Ryan can you dance without moving
hey guys so have you been watching this
channel long enough or if you happen to
know me personally in real life you
would probably know by now that one of
my biggest weaknesses in life is that
well I can't dance
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yesi most of those dance moves were for
jokes but that's actually me trying
especially the top Raving remember that
thing but dancing without moving now
that that kind of sounds like the dance
that I would be good at but I might need
a little help
[Music]
[Applause]
so leave your questions in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video
[Music]