hey guys so late is Mother's Day today
or it was Mother's Day depending on when
you watch this video and I normally
don't ever do serious videos like this
especially videos that are related to
mother's day just because of the fact
that I know there's a lot of you out
there that don't have mothers and I
never wanted to make you guys feel bad
but then the more I thought about it you
know Mother's Day is all about
appreciation for mothers and even if you
don't currently have a mother you can
still show appreciation for and for the
rest of us that fortunately still do
have mothers it's a great reminder to
keep appreciating what you have but
anyway for those of you that don't know
why I made this video even though I just
posted like two days ago
I made a video in the TV app earlier
this week asking you guys to send me no
video messages for your mothers for
Mother's Day and I was honestly shocked
with how many videos we got and how
touching the or and let me apologize in
advance if your video wasn't chosen it
wasn't because your video wasn't good
there was just that many videos this
video would have been like an hour long
if I put them all in plus I had to make
room for some very special guests who
sent messages to their mothers as well
at the end of the video but you'll see
but before I show you all your messages
to your mothers I want to first and I
think for the first time ever publicly I
want to talk to you about mine unlike a
lot of other youtubers my mom is you
know not really known to the public
she's hardly ever in any of my videos
it's one of the only time she was
actually in a video skit was like back
in 2008 and I think that was around the
time when I was leaving Hawaii for the
first time you know it's moving away
from home
to come here and you know my mom had
some very nice beautiful going away
words for me I think she said my house I
did but not as serious no my mom is
nothing like that she would never say
that that's a big and force her to do
that line you could even see at the end
like she couldn't even keep a straight
face my mom is and I know everybody says
this but she's literally the best person
I can honestly say that I wish and I
strive to be as hard-working and nice
and genuinely kind as she is I mean
don't get me wrong just like any other
mother she can irritate the hell out of
me I mean she called me every single day
and I know that sounds super bad that
you know I'm saying that's a bad thing
but she called me every single day like
multiple times a day and it's always for
some reason when I'm filming like I'm
surprised that I was like 90% sure that
there was gonna be a call or something
right there
and mom I know you're gonna be watching
this video because you watch every
single one of my videos and because I
know I don't say this nearly enough I
just want to let you know that I I love
you and you know I I know I don't say
that a lot and it's probably your fault
as your upbringing you didn't teach me
you didn't teach I'm just I don't know
why I keep making jokes mom on a serious
note I love you so much you do so much
for me you have no idea you have no idea
how much well I never thought I'd be
that guy on a youtube video what is
wrong with me huh oh okay
[Music]
saved by the call this is not even a
joke thank you she saved me she saved
herself from making this too emotional
it's already too emotional I honestly
never thought I'd be that youtuber that
cries on his own video and I'm probably
gonna put this in the Edit because
that's never happened to me anyway now
that I'm a complete we'll see to the
entire world x direct oh your attention
away from this mess and to go and watch
all the other videos here is all of your
messages to your mothers in three two
one
dear mom your mom dear mom dear mom dear
mom dear mom I love you so much you've
loved me unconditionally for years and
years I love you thanks so much for
helping me through every rough time that
I've had and the reason I love you is
I know you don't have much money and you
still get me everything I want you
always help if if of course thank you so
much for everything I wanted to say
thank you so much for everything that
you do thank you perfectly food and not
yelling at me for laughing to load up my
videos I just wanted to thank my mom for
being a great person putting up with me
now that I'm actually a mom myself I
can't thank you enough for everything
that you do just learned said a quick
happy Mother's Day to the best of all
the worlds I just wanted to tell you how
much I'm proud of you I can only hope to
one day have all your patience in trying
you're the biggest inspiration in my
life from my ups and downs thank you for
being you raised me alone you know
what's funny because I'm not the best
kid but you did something right hey mom
happy Mother's Day you raised three
bratty boy that's tough to do and when
everyone was telling you not to let me
play basketball you encouraged me to
pursue my dreams I love you have a great
day
I want to say thank you so much for
teaching me how to be a superwoman and
showing me how to be strong because
there's no way I would have an S on my
chest if I didn't see one on yours first
I love you so much happy Mother's Day
thank you for being it's the most
amazing supportive generous creative
silly cute tiniest little brother in the
whole world I'm so grateful to have you
I would be so much everything I had and
that I've accomplished is because of you
and one day I hope I can return the
favor I hope one day I can be just as
good of a mother as you were to me to my
own children
[Music]
hi mom happy Mother's Day I love you so
much right peachy yeah love you hey mom
I just want to say thank you for being
in all of our videos even though I know
you don't want to be in them thank you
so much for saying all the curse words
that we write and all the rules where we
say that you're like a murderer all that
stuff so thank you mom mom thank you so
so much for being an amazing mother
happy Mother's Day and most importantly
thank you for pushing me out of your
vagina and I just want to say happy
Mother's Day to mama I wouldn't even be
making YouTube videos for living if my
mom didn't tell me that I could be
whatever I wanted to be as long as I put
in the hard work thank you I love you
happy birthday hey mom it's me I want to
wish you a happy Mother's Day happy
Mother's Day mom happy Mother's Day love
you mom Mother's Day mama I just got the
key yeah and I'm using your account
don't get mad
sorry but I love you bye so once again I
just want to thank every single person
who sent in a video again I'm so sorry
if your video didn't make the cut but I
will say that I probably will be making
more of these videos so all you gotta do
is stay tuned in the TV app if you don't
have it go and download it that being
said I just want to wish all you mothers
out there to have a very wonderful mud