dear Ryan can you have a staring contest
with your Lamson fans I know what you
guys are trying to do you're trying to
shine the light in my eyes so I blink
and you're gonna blow wind in my eyes so
I blink well guess what today
oh yeah really again we're never gonna
be can we just win one tear Ryan can you
be a fruit ninja
oh dear Ryan can you do inception sign
normo
I think I'm in limbo dear Ryan can you
be invisible
oh I guess not
dear Ryan can you have an army of lamps
the wind makers cometh to our kingdom
and try to take it all up freedom nut we
shout not laying in like a bunch of
boulders and a creak on with us day we
shot never say name like some things a
lot would say we shan't need to be free
now just stand beside thee one who ought
died of thee what thou accept at the
scene so hold with me um excuse me could
you repeat that because nobody can
really understand what you're saying oh
it means we're gonna go fight the fans
[Applause]
I'm done for right you talking that
little laugh you're gonna pull through
this everything's getting dark probably
because it's late none of you are
plugged in right now we're gonna go home
you're gonna light up all my rooms I'm
gonna keep turning you on everything
good no what a weird dream
lamps fighting fans that's not even
realistic see we used inception - like
you did earlier in the video so we could
distract you is that what you really
think it's time to wake up we good
morning dammit
so leave your questions in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video we shot not laying here
like pebbles on a cricket or something
on a border we should not lay here like
pebbles on a creek what are you see
pebbles and boulders we shut lay here
like a bunch of pebbles
[Music]
me