- you're right can you make a parody out
of other famous youtubers guys guys
watching the show of The Amazing Race
pretty much just as amazing so my dad is
that we're watching it we're like we can
totally do we can do this
dear Ryan can you be a weather girl
thanks Chet so today we have lots of
rain and sunshine for tomorrow but don't
forget to wear your umbrellas you're
gonna have lots of clouds and not to
mention a lot of wind coming from the
for ease and that's all we have for
weather so lots of how to tell which
sports I like Bob here right can you be
an awesome basketball player dear right
can you be on them such a great day to
be a lamp oh hey big lamp
hey little lamp one day I want to be big
like you hey guys I'm a lamp - no you're
not silly you're an iron no no no I'm
enough all right guys that yo what's up
dudes hey douche laughs dude my bulbs
are so hot right now totally linked up
with this outlet last night but big lab
said you're supposed to use a surge
protector big lamp what did you just say
heard me bro wait Calvillo just get a
laugh yeah yeah I agree let's all just
get along you'd be laughs you guys know
I'm adopted right so leave your
questions in the comments below and you
could be responsible for the next video
Dennett our guys gonna be awesome so
that's all we offer and then I went to
this park
[Music]