here right I challenge you to mind with
us so you want me to mind then all you
have to do is say this word the right
way you don't have to say it out loud
just read it in your head if you said it
the way that I said earlier mind then
you're wrong let me point out why first
of all you should already know that I
don't curse to my videos I mean I just
don't see the point in it secondly in
order to trick someone's mind you have
to be fast so fast that their mind can't
keep up I call them fast tricks Astrix
point your mind in another direction
whether you think the direction is right
or wrong you're right because the
direction is right or it's wrong so if
you think that the direction I'm
pointing you in this right know that you
are because you know more about this
equation than you think it may sound
confusing now but the point is I need
you to see let me explain in order to
pull a fast trick on a mind you have to
first know what a mind is a mind is made
of five different things
consciousness perception thought
judgment and memory so in order to pull
faster gonna mind you have to target all
of these points and how do you do that
you've been looking at it the whole time
the first thing you may have missed is
as simple as an Astrid because an Astra
is nothing more than a star and a star
has five points point one consciousness
to be aware were you aware that I gave
you every single point starting with
wine as you said it the way that I said
earlier mind then you're wrong let me
point out wine let me point out why
point to perception or the way you see
something did you really see the point
in it when I said it first of all you
should already know that I don't curse
in my videos I mean I just don't see the
point in it see the point in it to the
poor me the point is I point three
thought I literally told you to think
about which direction I'm leading you in
so if you think that the direction I'm
pointing you in is right know that you
are know that you are all these new or
point for judgment based on evidence you
decide something now did you decide to
see everything the way I wanted you to
or did you see around it so the point is
I need you to see
[Music]
point-five memory oh wait that was the
end of what I said right well do you
remember the very first point in this
video so you want me to mind you no
longer born the point was that you
because like I said at the end I need
you to see you are why I see the fash
trick and because the letters you are
why I see are the five points that make
up an aster you now know that this
entire video is not a mine because it's
just another simple mine fast trick