hey guys so yesterday was Thanksgiving
and the day before that I went to the
market to go buy a turkey because I like
market turkeys better than homemade
anyway and partially also because I was
too lazy to cook I know so I don't know
how to cook but anyway as I was at the
checkout counter checking out my turkey
well really no one this time all right
doctor she said really she said it so
you know anyway as I was checking out
minding my own business this old lady
comes up behind me and feel the need to
preach to me and your total is 21 figure
Oh having a Thanksgiving dinner
oh yeah it's for tomorrow about you I'm
vegan so yeah I just don't really
believe in the whole slaughtering
animals thing I mean really you should
think about it there are a lot of
documentaries online that you can watch
and it is just disgusting I mean what
gives a person the right to decide
whether it and then that exact moment
right then right there that's when I
realized this cashier did not even have
my back he didn't say one word giving is
just sick immoral and wrong yeah no I
yeah I'm probably still gonna get this
Turkey so okay so maybe I didn't say
that last part term but I think vegans
are awesome they don't eat anything that
has to do with Adam which actually saves
a lot of animals for the rest of us even
though I can't stand with you or try to
force their beliefs unto other people
that old vegan lady kind of had a point
and it's kind of messed up to say out
loud but when I think about it I
actually don't value an animal's life as
much as a human I mean I love my dog but
if there was a ring that will stop not
anymore I mean I love my dog so much but
if there was a car that's about to hit a
person and a dog I probably pushed the
person on the way instead but if I did
that I probably get hit by the car too
and that would suck I mean I probably
just do the logical thing and as the car
drives by I jump into the moving cars
window force the drivers foot down on
the brake till it comes to a complete
stop grab the cell phone he's texting on
halsted outside shifted into reverse run
the phone over pull up my arsenic inject
him in the neck shove the body outside
of the car put it back into Drive and
steer it away from the man and just hit
the dog so that I could save his life
and then I'd probably have to run him
over as well because he just witnessed
me kill a guy and run over a dog just to
save his life but the point is I would
save the man's life over the dog and
then enough to kill him as I was saying
I always saw myself as like an animal
but I guess I never realized how little
society actually values their lives
compared to ours think about if a human
kills another human he ends up in Jim
and Adam a were to even harm a human it
wouldn't go to jail we probably kill in
fact most of our pets that we love the
most are pretty much already in jail
take dogs for example we lock them up so
they don't run away they only eat when
we tell them to and if you have two dogs
I mean they might not be in a shower but
there's always that one dog that likes
to hump the other one even people who
love animals most like zookeepers think
about in an animal's perspective they're
pretty much just a warning of a Big Joe
that profits off of their prisoners so
overall I guess what I'm really trying
to say is I get it now into the video ad
standing behind me in the market thank
you thank you for helping me open my
eyes and realize that animals really are
a lot less important than I thought they