I don't think they have the 50-piece
anymore really yeah it was just there I
feel like we just got to you know the 50
feet of the party in the mouth I was at
her I'm looking to try when last time
I'm pretty sure you said excellent Oh
fine okay rock paper scissors then fine
already
rock paper scissors you when you're
ready you went ugly again I want you
always go early
dumb war then all right okay ready one
two three four I declare a thumb war one
of your Alyssa's ever met dread
no I'm calming away I did not come fast
yes you always regular speed count good
mrs. Kapinos badass oh yes like you
helped me like that
top left top right back my fight chomp
turn rave to a bird shot down to the
ground I'll bring it around time get
pretty deep and lay wake up its day now
it's time to say don't I replay top left
top right back haha you remember about
you that was the fight you Eddie not you
I get you a you were late you know
whatever right right let's go
Oh
you
I have to hand it to you Goku you really
nailed me back there you making hand
puns Frieza so you finally figured it
out if you of course I did what do I
look dumb do you know but take you
looking at a beautiful right now that
was so bad on facepalm oh you think
you're so cool don't you go cool I think
you're not cool it's time I put an end
to this and send you and this entire
planet straight down to heal you that's
a good one
it seems that I at the upper hand now go
so what are you going to do about huh
what are you laughing at you're not the
only one that can perform hands
formations Frieza huh let's see how well
you handle me when I go super say hey
seriously this is why you guys gonna
come out me okay
we were just practicing for our plane I
can't believe you guys would play
without me tune in next time on an
all-new episode of Dragon Ball Z meets
Naruto's so once again thank you guys so
much for watching if you want to see
bloopers and behind the scenes click on
the left if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the right and
thank you so much to hawk and pac-man
for being our hand doubles for the day
it was a really weird request and thank
you guys thank you I'll get back man for
Max's and make sure you guys go check
out the channel they do some of the
craziest things I've ever seen my mind
always gets blown by them my hands bloat
their hands blow my that sounds wrong
check them up