on the last episode of Dragon Ball Z
Goku discovers his toughest enemy yet
the Prince of all Saiyans Vegeta so
Vegeta I'm a-saying right
mmm and you're saying - yes the Prince
of all Saiyans you on the other hand our
commoner saying who doesn't even deserve
the right to fight a prince like me so
I'm like Aladdin then what yeah I'm like
Aladdin and that would make you Jasmine
Jeff what are you talking about
Wow Aladdin was the commoner and jasmine
is the princess and Shenron the dragon
that grants wishes when you get all
seven dragonballs together he's like the
genie and I even have a flying Nimbus
that's like the flying magic on me oh
but I forgot about Aladdin's monkey a
Bowie can't have a ladder without a book
go on Gohan even has a tail he's just
like a boo he could be Maya move he's my
boo you think that Aladdin would kind of
like sue us or something sure this is
nothing like a damn movie I don't watch
movies on the Prince of all Saiyans not
a princess and you're not there's a
Latin character you're a saying and
he'll eat more your racial does nothing
but fight and go stronger after every
battle so shut the hell up about this
bad Disney movie
wait a second Vegeta what now move what
about it you just said Disney so what I
never said anything about who made that
movie which means you did watch
we're evenly matched gia I'm not even
getting started yet
you're a lot stronger than I thought
Vegeta those last couple of blasts
really hurt me
hashtag ouch mmm let's see how well you
can fight when you're blind from my new
technique solar flare what but how did
you know why would you tell me the
attack you're going to do before you do
it well maybe you can stop that Vegeta
but I learned this one from a pig come
on you idiot you Goku ah I missed
drats this is starting to get boring
Kakarot
I knew this planet would be a
disappointment oh really Vegeta I guess
I'll just have to do it it's a good
thing he's just standing there letting
me do this one because this one takes a
while the rivers the trees the wind and
all living things in nature that are
good at innocent
please settle your positive energies I
ask you
Vegeta from all the good people of the
earth let's see how well you handle the
spirit bomb uh what has to be more good
energy in the world of this well well
maybe it's just really small and dense
yeah that's gotta be here take this
alright that's enough of this nonsense
I'm ending this right now
wait Vegeta one more destructor this may
look weak and explore enough for us to
have this conversation but don't worry
you can cut through anything no matter
how strong their oh I have boobs no you
idiot you just cut my skip into two
pieces I didn't mean to lose aiming for
you but you dodged it oh you ain't for
it oh I didn't I was aiming for you like
this watch
mistake another mistake oh no I'll never
be able to fix it it's a million pieces
mean to be fair you're kind of over
exaggerating it's not like in a million
pieces house it's a b-cell yeah but like
a low thousand like two or three
thousand thousand little more than that
I thought was still more than that eight
thousand was there I doesn't mean
Destructo deep and humble now it's
overnight Dada
look I patted with you say goodbye to
this entire planet wait what to do
something fight Donuts in a global
entire planet no just set them No
you can't beat me
I'm the prettiest
ah go ahead Kakarot finish me off
deserve to live I can't be a simple
commoner like you know I'll give you the
choice Vegeta either you choose to stop
your evil ways and learn how to live
among us learn how to live a normal life
without killing make new friends learn
how to trust people maybe even marry a
[ __ ] named boma I don't know
or I could blast you right now another
one would ever see you at home the
choice is yours Vegeta so what's it
going to be
dummy
hey Bo cheetah did I ever tell you I can
teleport really far big deal Kakarot we
can all do that no but I can teleport
really far like into a whole nother
universe it's called Instant
Transmission your what whatever Kakarot
and can you stop calling me Kakarot my
name is Goku no it's Kara no it's Goku
no its Kakarot Goku it's gotta rock
Goku Goku Goku what are you doing here
you know I'm not quite sure but you guys
can't fly what hey everybody it's me
piccolo you want to see the behind the
scenes and bloopers well then click the
one that says or you could watch this
entire video again but with no effects
which i think is even funnier that way
or if you don't want to watch either of
those at least stay to the end so you
can see the bouncing ball that's green
green like my skin and that is my balls