so I was never gonna do a draw my life
video because to be honest I personally
don't think my life is nearly as
dramatic or interesting as some of the
other draw my life's that I've seen but
because a couple of you keep asking well
maybe more than a couple of you I am
going to draw my life or at least what I
call drawings you'll see it all started
off on June 6 1990 I was born in Hilo
Hawaii a small town where I grew up I
was lucky enough to have two loving
parents that I look up to even till
today I also have an older brother who
I've always felt competitive with my
whole life
he was always better than me and
everything he would beat me and
challenges competitions video games and
of course he was naturally gifted in
judo sea judo played a big part in my
family being that both my brother and I
pretty much did it our whole lives well
at age 5 when I first started I hated
you too because I was terrible at my
brother on the other hand was like a
judo club star pupil all of our senses
or teachers for those of you that don't
speak French loved him I was probably on
the exact opposite side of the spectrum
anyway my brother would almost always
win at every tournament we entered while
I on the other hand would be lucky to
place third out of three people that is
I remember specifically hearing at a
tournament a man say oh this is the
younger Higa not the good one but I
couldn't even get mad because it was
true anyway in elementary school from
kindergarten to fifth grade I really
don't remember much all they can
remember is that I hated judo and I had
the hugest crush on a girl not gonna say
her real name but let's call her Nichole
I was pretty much in love with Nicole or
at least what a seven-year-old thinks
love is but I was too shy and scared to
say anything to her until years later
but we'll come across that later after
fifth grade I moved schools for middle
school sixth grade was specifically a
terrible year for me not only did I lose
all my friends because it was a new
school but because it was a charter
school we all had to take tests to see
where we would be placed I guess and for
some reason I got placed with the older
kids at the time I thought this was a
good thing because I thought older kids
would think I'm cool because I skipped a
grade however it was pretty much the
opposite so this is the part of story
that most of you don't know about
because I've never really addressed it
publicly but I know a lot of you
watching this can relate so I got
bullied a lot you know nothing really
crazy just your typical getting pushed
down to the ground being made fun of for
no reason and yes I remember every
single one of them including the worst
of them again not going to use a real
name but we'll call him Richard because
as you know another
richard is dick see dick was such a
Richard to me that I'd actually make
excuses to my mom why I couldn't go to
school or why I needed to change schools
so I was heating life at the time and
wondering why someone so mean could be
so popular by picking on me even got to
the point where I had some darker
thoughts at the time that I think most
if not all teenagers go through at some
point in their lives or perhaps it was
just puberty messing with my head I
don't know however I was able to stick
it out and I actually found a way to end
the bullying on my own terms I noticed
that the reason dick was bullying me was
to make people laugh so I figured that
if I could make them laugh and become
the funny guy they would stop treating
me like I was less than them and
surprisingly it worked every time they
made fun of me I ran within and I made
fun of myself even more than they could
kind of like that last rap battle that
Eminem did an eight-mile except that
movie didn't exist at the time so he
pretty much stole my idea it's all good
though me and I'm never like best
friends forever now I still didn't have
many friends but at least I wasn't
getting bullied anymore but from that
point on I wanted to be funny I started
picking up my mom's VHS camcorder and
recording little skits and videos for my
family to watch they loved it of course
some of my cousin's would be like you
need to get a life Ryan but it became a
traditional thing every Sunday I'd have
a new video for them to watch and laugh
at in eighth grade I finally reconnected
with Nicole you know the girl I had a
crush on since elementary school she was
still at the other middle school where
all my friends were but I somehow became
in contact with her again through MSN
Messenger a lot of you might not know
what that is now but it was like the
Facebook of that time but when I finally
had the courage to ask her out I got
completely rejected no explanation no
excuse just a straight-up no nothing
more and I'm not gonna lie that bothered
me for a long time you didn't just make
me sad it made me very unconfident it
was devastating to me at the time then
in high school came around up until that
point I considered myself a complete
loser I always saw myself as less than
everyone Nicole got a boyfriend I was
less than him my old elementary school
friends had found new friends and they
became close with I was less than them
my brother who had just left for college
not only left high school with honors
but he ended up placing second in the
state for high school judo which as you
know and my family is a big deal so yeah
I was less than him too
that was back at square one I had a few
acquaintances but little to no close
friends even the kids I considered nerds
had friends they had each other in my
mind I wasn't anybody I was less than
everyone I looked forward to class more
than recess and lunch because at least
that way I could sit somewhere and not
complete loner and then it happened one
of the most momentous occasions of my
life I joined the wrestling team and I
know what you're thinking wrestling is
just a sport well to me it wasn't it
literally changed my life and well
almost ended at the same time I remember
this one time I had to lose roughly 16
pounds in a week to make my weight class
this was by far the most I've ever had
to lose in such a short amount of time
so I discipline myself to survive I'm
half a can of tuna and roughly 32 ounces
of water a day pretty sure I would have
died had my teammate landing that
finally collapsed on a run sorry mom
just finding out about this now was
probably one of the hardest things I've
ever had to do in my life but it was by
my own choice just to prove to myself
that anything can be done with enough
effort sure enough I made it to 102
pounds a whole pond under my weight
class from that point on I felt like a
completely new person I didn't feel like
a loser anymore I felt like I could get
anything I want to do in life as long as
I put the work by the time high school
was over I was lucky enough to earn a
state championship wrestling title and
just like my brother second in the state
for judo even with a dislocated elbow I
had lots of friends most of which were
fellow wrestlers you might recognize
some of them for my videos I even had a
girlfriend no not Nicole someone that I
thought was even more beautiful perfect
oh and those videos I made for my family
every Sunday I decided to start putting
them on this website called YouTube so I
wouldn't have to physically bring them a
copy and little did I know a few other
people found them and started sharing
them as well before I knew it I was
consistently getting thousands of views
every day and comments kept telling me
to do it so again however my parents
really wanted me to get a college degree
so for the first time in my life I left
Hawaii to attend UNLV for a degree in
nuclear medicine I hated it I was
spending most of my days and nights
learning about something I had no
interest in the workload between college
and posting YouTube videos just became
too much and my girlfriend remained in
Hawaii so the long-distance thing wasn't
helping either I realized that once
again I was completely stressed out and
I'm happy so after about two years into
college my girlfriend and I broke up and
I finally ended up telling my parents
that I'm dropping out to pursue this
YouTube thing it took a little while but
to my surprise they became completely
supportive and because of that thanks to
my parents thanks to wrestling thanks to
my bullies thanks to not only the good
but the bad experiences in my life and
of course thanks to all of you watching
right now I am Who I am today because of
all of you like everyone I still go
through highs and lows but ultimately
completely happy this is my real life
story no I'm not telling you this
because I want to brag about my life or
because I want you to feel sorry for me
because I was bullied when I was younger
or whatever I'm telling you this story
because I know for a fact that there are
a lot of you watching this right now
that are going through the same things I
went through when I was younger and I
wanted to let you know that life will
get better if you choose to make it
better it's okay to be sad and angry now
and then there are some things that may
be out of your control like employee
that picks on you or a boy or girl that
rejects you or even a sibling that
outshines you but the one thing that you
and only you control is your perspective
and your actions being depressed and
feeling sorry for yourself it's easy I
challenge you to change that today
happiness is a choice choose to be happy
choose to better your life because only
you can make that decision you are not
less than anyone there are only two
things that can stop you your own mind
and your own body some might argue that
there's a third and say your heart as
well but if you've been on my channel
long enough you already know that even
with heart it's still less than three
[Music]