right now we're in the desert this is no
place for fun and games you do not want
to get lost out here but every year
stupid tourists get lost out here every
week got a little rough on the dismount
but we're good let's go it's been nearly
three minutes and I'm completely
starving I need to eat fast or my
tummy's gonna hurt have to be really
careful he's one of the most dangerous
creatures of the desert the hippopotamus
I don't think he saw me yet so we're
still good but I was wrong all right
sneak up from his rear grab them that's
why I'll take them right this is
incredibly dangerous so don't ever try
this at home do it somewhere else
it was a bit risky but it's gonna be
worth it you can pretty much find these
uh these canned vegetables pretty much
anywhere you go especially in the
deserts I just gotta know where look and
that it's just that it's just awful this
is just awful
it was awful luckily uh
there's a technique that I heard about
from my mother's father's grandson where
you just take a big whiff that is much
much better
the ancient natives use this technique
to absorb half the vitamins and minerals
because half the taste is in the smell
all right we really need to get moving
we have a lot of ground to cover
I have to get moving now before the Sun
goes down because I'm afraid of ghosts
and that's about enough for today
I need to find some shelter please well
time to find some shelter because I
don't know what time it's gonna get dark
here but I luckily uh I usually I
usually have a watch but uh let me have
my cell phone so I can use it like a
sundial
and it's about it's about 10:30 p.m.
right now so I we really need to get
started
the ancient natives use this technique
with their cell phones but it's not
always completely accurate I was off by
about 6 hours I have to work hastily
because the Sun is going down and I need
something to protect me from all the
Predators and aliens so I've been
working about five hours now and I think
I think I got enough shelter to last me
the night here
but it's no time for rest I have to get
moving this terrain is incredibly
disorientating but luckily I can
navigate using the Stars so if you can
find the star all you have to do is
follow it and it will always always lead
you home 50% of the time unfortunately
for me this was not one of those times
I'm completely lost