this is Ryan Higa logging in day three
this is less than a week until the world
ends and there is a global panic
happening right now
cars are pressing people are running in
the streets things exploding no one is
safe and I'm here recording every single
event happening it's in case someone in
the future finds this and knows not to
make the same mistakes we made
what are you doing my closet oh you know
yep yep you're right sorry sorry about
that sorry I knew I should have okay so
maybe I exaggerated a little bit on the
whole global panic this is how it really
looks wait Jeff the stove yes
stop that the end of the world is less
than a week away for some reason no one
seems to care last year everyone was
being such a big deal about but now that
it's less than a week away it seems like
nobody even gives a [ __ ] I give a [ __ ]
now clean it up I said [ __ ] Oh what
happened to all you people who say
December 21st 2012 that's when the world
is in Dubai it said the world is ending
an earthquake that means the world that
our voice is also the same so where are
all those people now they're hiding from
us because it about a week they're about
to look really stupid I mean either that
or they're actually hiding in a bomb
shelter which is when they props you for
sticking to your gut even though your
guts stupid I'm just kidding but
seriously I mean I'm not gonna lie there
are some signs that show that glimpses
of the world ending hey what are you
listen to the best women of all time one
direction oh come on they're not the
best boyband what a ball didn't seem in
sync there like wanna be one Direction's
that's exactly where they belong in the
sink okay Backstreet Boys wanna dumbass
boys Wow okay um okay what about the
Beatles thing lots of Beatles I mean
don't you listen to anything else uh
what about the only guy that's bad that
Michael Jackson the real King of Pop
Justin people Never Say Never
but didn't say never oh well I mean
don't say that either so see these are
minor signs but it's nothing to be
frantic over frantic frantic such a
smart person work and you stop being so
friend because people have English
accents sound smarter so sorry ADHD
anyway for all those people watching out
there who are still saying alright you
can't tell the future either you don't
know that the world's not gonna end
your boys's do like he's if you really
believe the world's gonna end let me
make a bet with you if the world doesn't
end you have to subscribe to my channel
even if you're a hater and if the world
doesn't I mean I mean I guess you can
have everything you get at my house my
car my YouTube account I mean if the
roads anything I don't really I don't
really give a [ __ ] [ __ ] god damn it
Barney