dear Ryan can you pretend to be a mime
[Music]
Wow mime let me see what you got
okay it's a box
Wow that's that's actually pretty good
what else you got
okay okay sit down
driving pretty cool in the oats okay
sitting and going to the bathroom is
kind of similar a little more gross is
that it another box oh right
visible box challenge it's kind of like
two years old I guess that's the reason
why there's not so many mimes anymore is
this part of the act or home soon music
playing
[Music]
you just know each other
I'm kind of confused
[Music]
I'm scared
Oh stars
paper airplane
[Music]
Oh
oh my gosh that was amazing here please
take this soup here you guys deserve it
[Music]
Thanks met mimes don't talk so leave
your questions in the comments below and
you could be responsible for the next
video Oh green screen
[Music]
no no