hey guys so I know I don't ever say this
cuz I don't like to brag or anything but
I'm probably the most romantic person
I've ever met
in the entire world ever if anything I
always say in my videos that I'm
actually the opposite that I'm not
romantic but I really am I'm a womanizer
which means I'm a I'm a Britney Spears
song apparently that's crazy
oops did it again as I was saying a very
romantic person
I literally do all the things that grows
want for example I open doors oh you
want me to drive of course not I'm a
gentleman
get in okay I bring her flowers hey I
got something Oh
and are there curtain fire but I
remember this time I remembered I got
your real ones as well Oh
see how they're like realistic I pulled
her chair oh thank you
how was he and I know nobody even does
this anymore but I'm such an old-school
romantic that I even take her jacket oh
that is cold here let me get this Oh
actually I'm kind of cool no it's okay
okay that's way better should I get your
jacket since you took mine no I'm good
moms go should you see shivering is not
dead or something like that anyway isn't
already incredibly obvious that I am
clearly joking I'm horrible when it
comes to romance and I honestly believe
it's because of romantic movies they set
the bar too high for the rest of us
Holly what does the same thing every
year they take this best-selling
romantic novel turn it into a movie all
the girls in real life go and see this
movie fall in love with the main guy
who's impossibly perfect and makes it
impossible for the rest of us to compete
and when I thought about it actually
gave me the idea that well I should do
that so I did here's a little trailer
representing pretty much every single
romantic movie ever made except for the
fact that it's not based off of a novel
and of course again it's not a real
movie it's just a trailer and also the
main guy is me which is well obviously
that would never happen because you know
bring my eyes
Hollywood would never cast somebody with
eyes like this but you know I have bad
eyesight and if you had eyes like this
you wouldn't be able to read the script
and also I mean let's just be honest
Hollywood would never cast somebody with
my type of race you know with my kind of
genes because I mean if there was like a
running scene or some
you know I would never believe these
things these jeans are way too big to
race in and of course the most obvious
reason that Hollywood would never cast
someone like me is because well I'm
white with mapping centers pretty much
every single romantic movie ever made
take a look when an obviously older than
20 year old high-school boy moves to a
new town you're gonna love it here
sweetie
friendships will be made I also broke
SAS gun I'll bring one printing
birthrates up Brian hey do you guys know
what that girl is in there yeah actually
the hottest girl in school tall blonde
you don't want to mess with that what do
you mean she's kind of weird man she
doesn't talk to him she just plays with
Cola
until fate and venial II brought them
together welcome to chemistry 101
I am mr. fate today you'll be pairing up
for the rest of the semester what why
don't you hook up with Kady what hook up
with Kady be a partner really get to
know each other so that you two can
create some chemistry together
um just don't start frenching in my
class okay you too but no I wasn't
planning that says here you do also have
French class
together with mr. wingman oh right oh
yeah
you two should probably keep secrets
will be discovered Hey so I know you
don't talk that much but I was just
wondering if maybe we should meet up
after school to work on our magnet
mother was a coal miner but she died in
a coal mine after caved in and I'm
emotionally distraught and the only
thing that makes me happiest carving
figurines out of coal because it reminds
me of her
okay um I wasn't really asking you about
that but you save you're never going to
opposites will attract so since my
magnet is positive and your negative
should be able to attract thank you what
I like you like like you oh you were
talking you're talking about the magnet
sorry
doors will open
this is where I may call myself how
they're actually amazing you could sell
these that's it's now I make them with a
cute montage to show how perfect they
are together
with beautiful moving shots of inanimate
objects corny lines for teenage girls to
quote on Facebook love it's like a fart
it's warm
predictable sometimes it stinks but it
can also be the best feeling in the
world that's why I'm so happy I passed
through that day I know now I fart you
it's an insignificant act that will
probably make sense at the end of the
movie hey can I ask you something kind
of random sure do you believe in
miracles no I don't think so or not I
guess I've just never seen one happened
before but just when everything seemed
perfect Ryan I hate to tell you
something what's up why are you being
all serious all of a sudden anything
yeah you're the sickest no I mean an L
like I said you're the coolest girl I
know you don't understand I'm terminal
terminal we're not even at an airport
friendships will be tested we need to
stop hanging out with people starting to
talk about you then I don't care buddy
right you don't
why do you think you care about was her
client fair one lies will unfold what do
you mean I'm adopted ray will fall
from the people who brought you walk to
remember the notebook and paranormal
activity are HPC presents
you sculpted something yeah it's sort of
cool why mirrors that every time you
look into it you see that you you are my
miracle
Doug miracle hurt you hurt you too
I'll see you in another life wait what
directed by Michael Bay so thank you
guys so much for watching if you want to
see bloopers and behind the scenes
flicked on the left if you want to see
the previous video click the one on the
right and thank you so much to Arden for
being in this video if you want check
out her channel click the one in the
bottom that being said I'm going to bed
peace that's run video I don't know if
it's from I don't know