hey guys so Valentine's they just had
and once again for the third straight
year I spent it by myself
thank you thank you thank you don't stop
stop I know I know it's I'm just kidding
guys like I tell you guys every single
year there's nothing wrong with being
sing every single year around that day I
always see the same pose on Twitter
Facebook MySpace is about MySpace about
people complaining about being single
I've been single for a long time I'm not
gonna lie sometimes I miss being in a
relationship actually around Valentine's
Day or when one of my friends starts
dating someone new or if I watch like a
really good movie action movie because
I'm a man I don't know who Nicholas
Sparks is I mean romance and movies
always makes it seem so much better than
it really especially in movies like The
Notebook I'm gonna be reading these
stories about our love and hopes that
you remember them I walk to remember
we're gonna get everything on your list
done before you die Dear John here John
hi okay so maybe I didn't watch to your
job but I'm assuming it's somewhat
similar this is how those movies were
look in the real world
and I know those are just move the
example but that's what a lot of people
think romance is really like like you
know move so if you're single and you're
sad about it I'm here to tell you that
you're not missing out on much because
this is what romance looks like in
reality oh my god I I'm so sorry you
like cactuses it's crazy I love cactuses
like cactuses whatever loser I went back
to the very spot that we'd run into each
other and waited there hoping our paths
would cross again but she never came
until one day hey it took me four whole
minutes to find her on Facebook at the
same time 1 2 you didn't either okay
okay bye
[Music]
so um everyone gets their girl flowers
but I remember the first time we met oh
you remember that I'm gonna put this
cactus right here so that every time you
go to sleep you remember the first time
we met remembered what
when we first met I was spitting cacti
practices cacti but it's still sweet
that you remember I'm gonna put this
cactus right here so you know what it
feels like to see nice to somebody with
prickly legs shave them
[Applause]
look I made a huge mistake I'll do
anything to get you back if you get this
message just meet me at the spot where
we first met look I'm really sorry I
mean everything that we did I just
[Music]
no no how long should I wait to start
dating other people at least oh I love
you YouTube but I'm still gonna date
other people
Taylor tea tea okay so that last one was
obviously a joke I would never say
teehee in real life that's so lame look
in all fairness to all those couples out
there this is coming from a single
person's perspective and in all honesty
I'm probably only saying these things
because I haven't met the right person
yet I truly believe that once you find
the one and you really do fall in love
every single expectation you ever had
will become a reality so to everyone out
there that is looking for real romance
don't give up just yet just give up