there it is
can't beat the classics can we just
start it already
he said he'd be right back yeah when I
was like 20 minutes ago you know he
always does this could it play one by
now just kick him alright do a quick one
Tilden Towers no no no wait guys I'm
back I'm back finally what took you so
long
oh yeah I'm sorry about that it's okay
just ready up I totally will just just
give me like one more minute wait are
you kidding me no just start it real
good I swear I'm just warmin I just got
to finish something real quick anything
to do one one more second I swear
seriously if we're gonna wait for more
on the time I might as well just get off
and call it a nine wish what's up so
it's play class oh my god everything
we've done all the sacrifices the lives
lost the materials it all comes down to
this I know that I may have let you all
down in the past
well not this time
feels like it's been years since the war
began there to remember our days and
shifty chefs
you see grow all that time was rude it's
been 7 minutes we just started yeah what
are you talking about didn't go too
greasy grow yeah why do you always get
so weird when we play this that's what
separates me from the average player
what are you doing it down this is the
kind of mindset you need if you want to
make it to the top the ROI seriously
there's a team out there crouch see this
might seem like some kind of game to you
through whatever your videos knock down
I get a scar to me pistol you don't the
best players get the best gun for
tonight way of laughing yeah no you
can't catch bulczynski I know is someone
gonna revive me or while we starting
over looks like you don't got a gun
neither do you
I guess we both dropped in the wrong
house I guess we did you guys see me why
would you put that on down camouflage
or instead of a house
see
[Music]
damn you got all of them yep are you so
good at fortnight but so bad at public
restroom cleaning
yeah I'm really bad at cleaning those so
what no I'm talking about why are you so
bad at publishing books yeah I'm not a
good writer either so it makes sense
what no I'm talking about just stop what
I'm trying to get a sponsorship all
right can you please stop shouting out
the other one the VBox don't grow on
trees sorry I just find it weird that
you can't even say the name pub Jesus
man
[Music]
oh shoot yeah we're gonna take some
damage yeah say we keep going well
obviously we have to keep going yeah I'm
just trying to give you some tips you
know no I don't need ya boy you don't
play the skin that often what happens
game more than you hold sir yeah
finally I'm super low you got any heels
left uh no I don't have anything we're
too busy outrunning this polar penny
it looks like it to left in there
fighting we should go now we got our
materials we're not gonna make it that
far
what was it I didn't waste a dime okay
we gotta do something all right well I
got one rocket left
maybe we just shoot the guy behind the
tree in the blue field normally unless
unless what
still got that rocky of course I still
got that racket what you thought I shot
it while proposing my master plan he's
still got it
all right you ready so we're gonna made
it in by now you want to try this don't
bring it yeah pretty much
[Music]
okay you have to shoot it then that's
what separates me from the average
player what are you doing here
it's the kind of minds that you need
to top
[Music]
see this might see
did it come on look little four years oh
he's not gonna shoot over there and
definitely into the circle yeah there's
no way he's gonna make daddy's farm I
don't wanna know the raw end open you
mean like this you mean like like this
live you know I'm just gonna grab some
bullets and I'm gonna just watch just
gonna shoot all right itself you're
still super low remember yeah maybe yeah
let me hide just a little bit you know
for a bunch of dead guys you sure have a
lot of opinions on how to stay alive
I see it all right look just because I'm
not that good at the games you guys play
does not mean that I am not good at this
game because I really wait there's only
one dorm here how do you leave so thank
you guys again so much for watching if
you want to see bloopers and behind the
scenes click on the left if you want to
see me actually try to play for time for
the first time on PC cuz the one on the
right and once again thank you so much
to Epic Games for allowing us to make
this video if you want to download their
game for free I'll put the link in the
description the way we already did that