hey guys so first of all I don't even
know because I'm filming this video in
advance but if there's been a delay in
my videos lately I sincerely apologize
I'm sorry to everyone who continues to
watch and support me I truly do
appreciate it and don't think I'm
neglecting my youtube at all I know I
don't post every single day like some
other youtubers do now but I'm not
neglecting YouTube and I'll believe it
or not that's my number one priority I'm
either writing or editing every single
day not even on the weekend I guess I'm
just not as fast of a writer or film or
editor as some other people but anyway
thank you guys again so much for bearing
with me through this struggle the
struggle is real yeah that's just a
preview to how crappy this video it's
gonna be no one will blame you if you
click away now not even me thank you
guys dear Ryan where do babies come from
the vagina dear Ryan this video is three
months old so you're probably not even
reading this Never Say Never
it's a deep joke cuz it sounds like a
basketball shot clock buzzer it's not
video some of you might get it anyway
dear Ryan are you from Hawaii tear Craig
yes I am from Hilo Hawaii on the Big
Island where we like to speak a lot of
pidgin okay so for other people they can
understand what I'm saying right now
this is a shuttle for you guys cuz
nobody else can understand if you're
never more you know you don't can speak
pidgin not gonna understand what I'm
trying to say I know some of the people
from Hawaii to speak pidgin I still know
can understand what I'm saying cuz I'm
talking too fast I just wanted to give
you guys one shout out because I really
miss you guys in Hawaii I'd be a long
time since I've been home so I just want
to say make sure you guys take care
Malamud I now make sure you guys take
care I said that twice not over that's
okay but just one of us say Mahalo Aloha
mauka okay I make up or agree to Michael
all over luckily Kona get a shoe scare
right can you draw a picture of me I
mean I'm not the best artist but I guess
I can I mean I may have to zoom-in a lot
cuz that's an awfully small picture but
I mean I guess
[Music]
she touch is done ladies and gentlemen I
present to you
Royston Bob I may have something too
much
you're right can you do my drunk kitchen
you
do you write please show a day in the
life of all am Bridget preach tear my
can you tell great to cut his mustache
hey Greg cut your mustache okay do you
Ryan get two slices of bread put them
down the back of your underwear while
sticking one to each butt cheek and sit
on it for ten minutes I mean I guess ten
minutes late and that's where Nutella
comes from here right can you moonwalk
while wearing high heels dear Ryan if
you made your own toilet paper what
would it be like and what would you call
it tired of having to buy more and more
paper aren't you sick of having to wipe
multiple times yours really be relieved
you dry an unexploited well look no
further thanks to the newest mention
employing new technology we now present
to you the Sam Cooper never go another
day without when you went sad looper no
more wasting your money buying role that
the role the Sam Cooper all you need is
one just wet wash me and you never have
to wipe multiple times again because
with the sad baby river the Sam Boober
and everything it was not to mention
every time you use a sample where you're
also exfoliating at the same time dear
Ryan if you have to choose a Naruto
character which one would you be in wine
if I had to pick him once all the
characters I would pick gada because not
only can he control sad he has an
unlimited supply of sad and he lives in
the sand village which is like the
exactly is where I would want to start
my company for it dear Ryan can you fall
in love with a tree
[Music]
Hey look I know I may be barking up the
wrong tree I just want to talk things
out just get to the root of our problems
I know it's too late for breakfast and a
little early for lunch but maybe we
could go grab some branch or something
okay fine I know those last tree plans
weren't that great and if you had hands
you'd probably facepalm three times by
now but but just please say something
anything like if you want me to grow
I'll grow just don't ignore me okay it's
either me or the drugs so what's it
gonna be that's fine fine
see no it is just gonna little little
drugs just soil everything we had
everything we grew together and just
throw it all away well I hope it was
worth it because I'm leaving you I'm
leaving you for good
goodbye Katrina have fun with your weeds
ah that was so tight but you really
rooted down and stood tall I'm proud of
you Katrina thanks Bush you're always
there for me I'm always here for you to
Katrina shut up a rock you ain't even
shut up just shut up for once jeez I'm
taking the pot I need to go for a drive
Jesus what's her problem yeah why she
gotta be so Moody she's probably just on
her pee right now yeah she's definitely
photosynthesizing what did you say
nothing nothing so thank you guys so
much for watching if you want to see
bloopers and behind the scenes click the
one on the left if you want to see the
previous dear Ryan video click the one
on the right and if you want to leave
your own dear Ryan leave it in the
comments below or tweet it to me or
Facebook or do something you could just
shout it out probably here no no no