hey guys so throughout my life I've been
called a lot of different things you are
amazed you're like the coolest dude man
you're the greatest friend anyone could
ever ask for both man you're great and
what he goes talking about golf loser no
not me the one thing I can't stand is
when people call me lazy I am NOT lazy
if anything I'm the opposite of that I'm
not late I'm on this lazy I'll figure it
out another time yeah okay sure at 6:00
p.m. and I still have my pajamas on but
it doesn't mean I'm not a hard worker oh
you're broke you think you could do the
dishes um yeah I would but I just I I
don't want to so Iran didn't give me
here with this no hello hey bro
nightclub sorry bro I I would but my dog
just uh turned into a lamp wow if you do
wanna go you said so sure well looks
like it's just you and me buddy okay so
maybe I can be a little lazy sometimes
but I don't really think that being lazy
is a bad thing yes maybe I didn't learn
that much in high school because I was
too lazy to study and I cheated to get a
good grade but I wasn't too lazy to
cheat right and I know most parents and
teachers that see this would be like if
you're cheating you're just cheating
yourself you won't learn anything being
lazy that's not true at all if you're
cheating you're learning on a problem so
for example the problem is that you have
to pass a test to get a good grade sure
you can spend hours and hours studying
and actually learning things you sure
you could be lazy and find a faster and
more efficient way to pass the problem
I'm not trying to encourage you to cheat
on the test I'm just saying that if
you're able to cheat and get away with
it and get a good grade then you kind of
deserve an A because you helped smarter
than teacher but also goes the other way
as well the teacher does can't do
cheating on the test you deserve an F
you deserve an F because you're not
smart enough not smart enough to cheat
the right way I'm just gonna go ahead
and say I believe that lazy people are
the smartest people lazy people are the
reason why we get to live life so much
more comfortably today I mean I'm sure
back in the day people called the guy
who invented the dishwasher lazy as well
wow they're so
you can't even wash dishes or what about
the guy who invented the washing machine
wow you're so lazy you can't even wash
your own clothes or what about the guy
who came up with the idea of the car
wash wow you're so lazy that you can't
even wash your own wait what is that
it's a car I got tired of walking so I
invented the car those are all people
that follow lazier way of completing a
simple task and I don't know about you
guys I think they're absolutely
brilliant so for all of you lazy people
that are tired of being belittled and
criticized for your brilliance I'm
standing up for all of you sitting down
sit just I think it's tiring you know so
the next time somebody calls you lazy
whether it's your friends your teacher
your mom your dad don't get mad don't
get sad
be glad be proud say it out loud from
the brightest cloud and even you one day
that's that's all I got I didn't feel
like writing anything else I just
watched the video too lazy to light a
simple candle he found a way around it
they were too lazy to drive so they came
up with a new way to get places faster
[Music]
cut from his high school basketball team
he locked himself in his room and cried
because he was too lazy to go back to
playing basketball his girlfriend broke
up with him but instead of chasing after
her he stayed in his dorm and created
something that would make her come back
to him he was studying to become a
doctor but didn't finish and yet still
became one of the most successful
doctors of all time when their movie
series were coming to an end instead of
not being lazy and starting a new series
they spit their last movie into two
parts and made way more money that way
they didn't know how to end their movie
so they let you do it for them you
wanted to make sure Thomas Edison was
the one who invented lightbulb and not
Benjamin Franklin because he was too
lazy to pay attention in history class
if you've never been lazy and done
things the easier way you're probably
not that smart