hey guys I'm sure by now a lot of you
have already seen or at least heard
about these this new trend this poi
called a fidget spinner yes once again
the Internet has blessed us with another
wonderful trend that everyone can't stop
talking about so much so that I can't
even ignore this one because it's so
heavily requested by you guys in my
comments dear Ryan can you make a video
about fidget spinner dear Ryan can you
do fidget spinner trick shot here Ryan
right your hair still look gay me what
pitcher spinners are one of the biggest
trends in the world right now
so of course had to go pick one up to
see what all the fuss was about and here
it is yeah this thing right here that's
all it does it spins okay it is like
three sir well it's still going because
it's kind of fat kind of fast okay yeah
like most people in my age if you're in
your twenties you probably took one look
at this trend and says is so stupid why
would anybody waste their money on this
well it does is spin and to be
completely honest this video was
originally gonna be me making fun and
bashing these things and people that
play with them you know kind of like
what everybody else is doing right now
but after seeing all the hate for this
little harmless somewhat useless toy I
just had like this epiphany
it wasn't like this it I don't know what
I'm doing we are a society that just
hates the generation below we hate
everything that they do all the trends
they start because we think that our
generation is the best and the smartest
and upcoming generations are only
getting worse and worse I'm not just
singling out our generation this is an
ongoing pattern that has been happening
forever I mean think about it when we
are growing up the generation above us
complained about us in the same way when
we were kids Sam you kid the rap music
game boys and polka man back in my day
we used to play stickball outside and
listen to the classics like dirty if
you're around my age I'm pretty positive
that somebody older than you has said
the exact same thing to you before and
yes it was annoying because they just
didn't understand because they're old
they were just being haters well take a
look in the mirror
that's us now we're the old haters our
generation is literally doing the same
thing now damn you kids in your
hoverboards and babes and lil yachty is
back in my day we used to ride bicycles
it had beyblade and we listened to real
music like Eminem Britney Spears and the
Backstreet Boys yeah I don't know why
our generation sounds sold we're still
in our 20s but you get the point you see
it's an ongoing cycle of hate and it all
stems from our arrogant we think that
growing up we had the best childhood
because of how proud we are of ourselves
you believe that the younger generation
has to have a childhood like ours if
they want to be as successful and
knowledgeable and hardworking as we are
that's why when older generations see
kids doing trends like this you always
see them say things like oh our future
is doomed or I'm losing faith in
humanity or something else negative and
no I'm not making a video just to defend
these things I agree that these toys are
you know kind of useless and not really
worth the money but that's exactly the
point their toys
just because we're older now and way too
mature to play with these things doesn't
mean we gotta hate it I mean you think
this is stupid think about the toys we
grew up with we had pogs okay we
collected and play with little circular
pieces of cardboard that with pictures
on them that we would slam on the ground
to try and flip over other little
circular pieces of cardboard with
pictures on them and that was fun well
what about trading cards our generation
loved trading cards some of us still do
from Pokemon cars to ukyo to Magic the
Gathering and like reading card for a
huge and we were growing up and they
were expensive that's right we paid a
bunch of money for a bunch of pieces of
paper with
is on there wasn't even cardboard and
yes I understand these were games you
could play them and these these you
can't play games with these they just
spin right well then maybe who can
explain chattering remember those that's
right kids we had chattering for a short
amount of time chatter means were just
as popular as these in the world when we
were growing up and literally all it was
was a bunch of little rings that you
would spin onto a bigger ring and keep
spinning the bigger ring so that
littering keeps spinning and make a
bunch of noise with them yeah that
didn't sound stupid back then I do
remember some adults saying that was
stupid back then and I laughed at that
they laughed at me that's how it went
they did I didn't laugh at them still
not enough you also play with yo-yos
which is a wheel and that's attached to
a string that you wind up and then
unravel really fast so that the wheel
spin it's a little younger than my
generation but we also had beyblades
there were little toy tops that you
would spin to hit other tops I was like
taking two of these spinning them and
then hitting each other with them oh
great
look at that came off whoops we had gak
it was literally just goo that you could
touch I don't know we had slinkys a
spring-like toy that you would place at
the top of the stairs and then watch it
go down those stairs this is starting to
sound even worse con depressed we even
had whatever how this thing is I don't
think anyone even knew what these things
were even supposed to be but a lot of us
had them like this soft slippery sausage
licking thing but it had like an inside
so you could like put your finger in it
or hold it and like kind of move it
around and wait a second you see
what I mean I'm not saying that these
things aren't stupid okay because they
are why are we eating in the younger
generation when we are just as stupid as
they or maybe even stupider okay we had
this thing it doesn't make sense we're
hypocrites oh I'm sorry if you thought
this video was gonna be what most people
are doing which is hating on fidget
spinners fact I am gonna do the opposite
and show you how awesome and useful
these things are okay I can name like
hundreds of uses off the top of my hand
like you can spin them forwards you can
spin them spin the backwards kind of you
can use it like a ninja star in case
it's a burglar in your house it could be
the propeller of a mini helicopter maybe
even a blender if you're blending like
really soft easy to blend things you can
use it to draw the perfect circle the
perfect flower brush your teeth faster
get some spinners on your rims you don't
look like a baller or like a ceiling
and for really tiny people a lazy susan
for really lazy people test your
eyesight one or two pretty much the same
could use it as a magnet you could use a
strobe light you could even use it to
explain to your mom what your gauge
years are gonna look lysee
there are hundreds and hundreds of
different use okay yeah there's not a
lot you can do with come on it cost like
ten dollars
what can you even do with ten dollars
and what would you rather have a ten
dollar bill or one of these see that you
can't spin a ten dollar bill yeah we
also had a game like this growing up
kids it was kind of frowned upon over
all I'm trying to say is all this hate
that we show to other generations
especially the younger generations are
so unnecessary and kinda hypocritical or
so quick to judge others especially
younger people because we think we know
better and we expect them to grow up the
way we grew up but the thing is Humanity
is constantly evolving and just because
things are different whether it's music
or toys or trends it doesn't mean that
they're wrong we didn't grow up the way
our parents grew up our parents didn't
grow up the way their parents grew up
and kids today aren't gonna grow up the
way that we did let's just keep doing us
and let them do them some of us will
also keep doing them that doesn't sound
right so once again thank you guys so
much for watching and for all you
younger generational kids watching when
you're our age and you guys want to
start hating on the younger generation
below you for starting some stupid trend
just remember this right here at one
point this was the most popular and most
talked about thing in the world because
of you guys playing with them and
enjoying this for fun okay it's your
fault
kind of mine too I guess
it's kind of fun damn you kids and your
no smoking laws and flying skateboards
and beat Bob rock music back in my day
we had hoverboards that didn't have Apes
that gave everybody a new form of cancer
and more than anything we had real music
like we had like okay well you guys got
us on the music