every year of every day each one of the
week thousands millions even hundreds of
people continue to fall victim to FW PS
I'm so sick I have no place to sleep
tonight so hungry is nothing to eat also
known as first world problems I'm so
sick of these routine doctor checkups
there's never anything wrong with me I
have no place to sleep tonight my
friends took the bed and a couch so
hungry is nothing to eat I mean on this
little carb diet sure I can have all the
steak I want but a steak without
potatoes
hi I'm Ryan Higa
you may remember me from the first fwp
campaign when not only our fwp is still
around but they're getting much much
worse phone always dies in my friend's
house and all he has the old iPhone
charger too much clothes drawers won't
close it's like having a mountain in my
way and every time I get over it it's
always another why did God even have to
make speed bumps ignoring the problem
does not make it go away my hands are so
big never reached to the bottom half of
the Pringles can these people are
continuing to suffer every single day I
just bought this dress yesterday and now
it's on sale sauce these fw PS
firstworldproblems whatever you want to
call them aren't going anywhere unless
you do something about them my boyfriend
didn't text me back but he just tweeted
it's like everything I built came
crashing down all at once the pool
already began phone not in hand I'm so
hungry I already brushed my teeth the
pool was too cold the jacuzzis too high
I ordered the salad now never taste the
soup my owner got me bacon treats but
they're not even barbecue flavored
but now there's a way you can help by
calling the number 1-800 WWF WP at gmail
org slash colon and parentheses / colon
begin parentheses / dancing lady in red
dress / / will send you the FWP helper
kit which includes an open book here's
an open book now shut it a miniature
batch of wine here's a mini batch of
wine now you can stop being such a
little whiny batch and a complete poker
set including a case chips cards and not
to mention poker sunglasses I don't mean
to be heartless but welcome to the club
in case you didn't notice there's no one
here gives a chip so if you could just
cut it out grow a forking pair and deal
with it that would just be amazing with
your help we can put an end to fw peace
for good and focus on the real problems
like violence or drugs or people who
still don't know which you're to use the
Biebs Crocs yellow starbursts the real
issues at hand so please join me help a
soul and help us all the heck is that Oh
my Internet's so slow it always has to
buffer first so thank you guys so much
for watching if you want to see bloopers
and behind-the-scenes click go on the
left if you want to see the previous fwp
video click the one on the right and if
you don't wanna click any of them at all
then that's kind of a problem and
that'll be really sad for me