every year of every day thousands of
people fall victim to fwp so cool story
nobody cares about me
also known as firstworldproblems
[Music]
somebody set the AC to 72 I needed it 73
oh yes Doris nobody cares about me I
commented they're like my status hi I'm
right here
and for just five hours of attention a
day you could help somebody with fwp
keeps putting so much pressure on me I
don't know what I want for my birthday I
have too much chips for my dip if I open
any dip too much dip for my chips
why does Apple keep making new iPhones
now I have to get another one
they've been through so much struggle
remotes over there but I'm all the way
over here so much hardship my iPhone 5
is too big for my skinny jeans so much
attention attention attention my port
was surreal I thought I'd check in to
see if we had milk
[Music]
so please show your support and send in
this video and show them how much we
care about their have W piece I could
lots of any groceries now I'll have to
make two trips all you have to do is
call the URL 1-800 org and we'll send
you the fwp healthy kit which includes a
bridge a straw and a full cup with the
cover there's a bridge now get over
here's a straw I'll suck it up here's a
full cup now shut the full cup with your
help we can put an end to FW peace and
focus on the real problems like starving
children are homeless people because if
you're complaining about something as
silly as the iPhone 5 just wait till you
see the iPhone 6 all this this is the
iPhone 5s this is the iPhone 6