life isn't about what happens to you
it's about how you react to what happens
to you you know give me like ten minutes
of conversation by the punch bowl and
the chips and she's like I might suck
this tit
any plans on having kids well here's the
thing
special announce clap claps oh for mine
welcome back to another episode of BOTS
appeal podcast hey you remembered this
time I always remember oh you know what
will was will was doing it last time and
he forgot anyway I'm Ryan Pok was in the
moderator seat and we got a very special
oh gee youtuber and mainstream
celebrities now Ryan methey delageteau
hi what's up guys it's okay you can feel
but you don't put that out anyway I
don't really put it out there but it's
out there you know I'm not like hiding
it either whoever silicon my real name
yeah my real government name is tim
chantarangsu that's my tie last name and
here's something a little tidbit of
information that not too many people
know my real like first name is not
Timothy it's just Tim oh really yeah
like on my birth certificate your your
youtube name is Timothy delegate yeah
yeah I just thought Timothy like rolls
better with the delaghetto
you know yeah Timothy like I know and I
mean speaking of which because you I
said og youtuber you were around when
did you start probably my current
channel to this day my current main
channel is oh six right
I had one channel before that in oh five
that got like just someone gets my
password and delete all my videos you
know that is so what you know you know
what's crazy though YouTube has all
those backed up do they yeah I don't
know if sure say this I could probably
say this I deleted a ton of videos when
like copyright strike started to happen
yeah right when we got YouTube
partnership I think that was like oh
seven you didn't private him you just
deleted him I didn't know I didn't know
better
I was like I don't want to get sued yes
I just had started making money mm-hmm
and they flagged like I guess all of my
videos had music so I started deleting
like like all of them mm-hmm and then I
went back I think it was a couple years
later and they I don't know what
happened they updated YouTube or
something and they were all in my head
my inventory and like in my my videos so
like I have like lip syncs and stuff
that I'm like 5,000 views desk raised
may have everything and I deleted I know
for a fact I deleted them I every they
keep it oh [ __ ] it's probably all in
some like crazy database mail dude yes
there's videos you didn't want up it's
there oh I mean anything that got
deleted with that first channel it was
so stupid too cuz I was like I remember
I was really just excited I had like 500
subscribers on my first channel and it
was um there's a lot back then that was
a lot no well it was oh it was no okay
actually I had a couple it was one
called funky fresh
that was my first channel ever ever ever
and um and my channel my password was
funky cuz I was just dumb and lazy and I
was like and I always forget my password
and I think one day somebody had just
like was [ __ ] around and um I can say
that right yeah oh yeah somebody was a
[ __ ] alright and guess my password
and like it was literally I have maybe
10 videos that were there of just me
freestyling or doing whatever and they
all got deleted and and someone had just
uploaded like choreography videos you
know and then and that's when I started
the Timothy DeLaGhetto
account and um and then I lost that one
because I don't know if you remember but
way back then when YouTube first started
out there was no like moderation you
know no one really paying attention that
how everything worked but if somebody
just flagged your video enough it would
just get taken up
I do remember right so there was no you
know limited access or 18 or older it
was just automatically taken down yeah
and then they also had a three-strike
rule so if you had three videos taken
down your channel was just deleted you
know and then I think there was a time
on my original Timothy DeLaGhetto
channel where I think just like a
handful of like haters we're just
constantly flagging my videos
and within like a week and a half it was
like video taken out video takedown
video taken down channel suspended young
and then I had to start all over and I
think it's because I mean like you you
kind of I mean your content especially
back then you really like push the limit
right yeah and yeah well you know what
and and also back then I mean I remember
specifically a couple of videos that
that got deleted that week it was just
tell us about it
it was silly stuff bra like I wasn't
even taking it seriously yet it was
literally like a video of me and a
friend of mine like making out that's
one of them and then stuff from like my
cell phone you know like me maybe like
playing with like a butt or something
you know this is way back it's like
single working at California Pizza
Kitchen Tim like just having fun with my
friends on my phone I was like oh let me
upload this video me like playing with
my friends but you know and so you
didn't start off wrapping then it was it
was a combination of stuff it was um me
freestyling and then whatever just
random that we've got you to start
YouTube kind of what got me to start
YouTube specifically was you know my boy
PD flow yeah
so me and PD flow we went to high school
together and PD flow and my boy
super-ego and Rick we all went to high
school together and me people and Eric
specifically we used to make these like
short films in high school and we had
one that we did call Jason versus Gumby
that like PD flow put on his website and
and it started to get some traction
online like it was getting spread around
a lot not even when there weren't a lot
of you know there weren't websites to
share videos back right so his website
was like running out of bandwidth you
know I'm saying it would shut down
because we couldn't afford to keep the
website up with all the hits were
getting so one day I was on MySpace and
someone posted a bullet in my space is a
website where people used and someone
posted a bullet in it was like look at
these white girls dancing to Laffy Taffy
lol so I'm like okay what is this about
it clicked on it I watched the video i
LOL but i was like wow this is a website
where anybody can put any video and
it'll give you like an embed code for
your myspace this is crazy
so I told Peter I was a young man we can
just put our videos on this website and
we don't have to worry about bandwidth
and
that stuff so we put our little sortes
on there and then I was like maybe this
is a good way to get my face out there
so I just started uploading just like
silly stuff like me freestyling or like
you know lip-syncing and then I would
tag all my freestyle videos as Jin 106
and park freestyle Friday Asian
freestyle don't know that's another
completely different person Asian rapper
that's smart though that's what you had
to do back yes I think you know so I
would get the occasional comments of
like lol to st. Jean you are right
though the biggest compliment yeah
exactly I don't like ten people that
were like like what the hell was this it
was a handful of people okay you know I
think I like this well speaking since
we're talking about like rap and stuff
like that for those that don't know you
are on a TV show for how long six
seasons eight season six years Wow dunno
why I was on MTV right Stan TV oh it's
open you're not doing it oh yeah I am
NOT on the Sony maja
what happened were there um you know
what it was just um we I was feeling
like it was getting a little repetitive
for me and I had been telling the guys
in our little while in our group chat
for a couple years a couple seasons like
I JA think is my last one I think I'm I
think I'm cool I'm ready to move on
there's my last one but I will keep
doing it you know and then um one day we
just we kind of had a mutual well one of
the producers like hey man I don't think
we're gonna have you anymore they broke
up with me basically oh they told you
that
well yeah cuz I mean I already had it in
my head that yeah maybe I'll do one more
season and then I'll move on and tell
you why I've heard a few different
things so so one of the producers called
me up and he's like hey man do you have
time to talk and I was like ah [ __ ] he's
breaking up with me I'll say I was like
this is the break-up talk you know yeah
and because he text me is you got time
to talk I was like yeah bro I got time
to talk but if this is if this is what I
think it is you owe me steak dinner and
I'm I'm going somewhere expensive yeah
and I'm ordering everything and he's
just lol there's like okay it's going
down yeah so he called me and he was
like yeah you know what um he was just
like you know I think you know we're
gonna go in a different direction and I
was like sorry man cool cool works for
me and
because is did they replace with another
Asian dude the only Asian they've been
trying they've been trying without many
people like you man
I agree you know and they've been trying
to fill that void a little bit um so
they so they kind of you know retired me
as I like to call it or fired me if you
want to say that but um and then they
brought in a rice gum try they tried it
out oh man they tried it out I don't
think that really works for anybody you
know saying you guys are opposites I
feel like yeah and you know while
announced is a different beast you know
yeah and like I can be quick and I don't
know maybe he is for all I know I
haven't heard him rap it feels more
though that Tim is like an authentic
genuine character who can like yeah
really you really fit that you know like
you it didn't seem like oh they're
trying to fit diversity here honey that
Asian audience is just like not Tim
matches yeah what else I think about it
when I used to watch Wilin out cuz it
was it was on way back and then I was
basically brought on I was brought on
for like the reboot you know um and so
when it was on back in the day I was
like yo I would be perfect on this show
but I remember I think I was like in
high school or you know and I was like I
would be dope on the show cuz I was I
was rapping and I was funny you know and
this show is like rapping and being
funny here I'm saying so when I heard
they brought it back I was like ah yes
let me get in there
did was actually they have a say about
how I got on no so would you like to
know I would love to know okay well let
me tell you some I heard Nick Cannon was
bringing Wilin out back so I followed
him on Twitter and then one day he
tweeted who's the funniest person online
whoever gets the most retweets of
hashtag Wilin out needs me I'll audition
personally so at that point you know I
had a decent YouTube following this pop
like 2012-2013 and so I got a bunch of
retweets and then someone deemed me and
they were like if you would really like
to audition contact this person come to
this address I was like sweet and and
also during that whole process a friend
of the producer who was a guy I knew was
like hey man I know the producer if you
really want to get in there I'll get you
in there and I went in for the audition
and Nick already knew who I was from he
knew me as a rapper
not necessarily comedian yeah cuz on
some super random random stuff he used
to manage this artist name collect car
and that year or the year before that
billboard came out with this chart
called the Uncharted chart and it was
basically people who were kind of doing
their thing online and and I was number
one on when they premiered the the chart
because you know I was doing like I was
doing music and stuff too yeah and so I
guess Nick just saw me on that list so I
auditioned and they had me like
freestyle and we played some improv
games and and it was stuff like they'd
say Kevin Hart is in front of you right
now dissing with a rap you know stuff
like that yeah and we do that and they
called me back for the group audition to
see how you are with the other would-be
cast members what we'd like makeup games
and stuff and yeah and then they call me
next week so I was on the show and yeah
yeah and I was like you know like seven
years ago but did like six seasons and
so and then they about eight seasons
eight seasons six years and they kick me
off and brought on Rice go and tried
that out I don't think he had fun either
though yeah yeah I think he was like
knowing just knowing him personally I
can't see him really doing do you wanna
do want to name-drop who you're
competing against to get on the show as
an Asian yeah well oh do you know this
story yeah you do no I don't know this
story so so you know they kind of were
looking to fulfill that kind of token
Asian spot you know cuz a majority black
cast and it came down to me and
dumbfounded oh and um and if you ask the
producer or if you even asked dumb like
what went wrong on his audition he'll be
like I messed up my freestyle I don't
know what happened I like I'm his dope
too dumb is amazing he's like a
freestyle guy
I know his freestyle is crazy and I
guess he just got nervous yeah yes I was
like oh good for me
but he doesn't really like you do like
funny yeah um is more like a serious no
he's got jokes oh really
yeah he's like I mean he's dope so I
figured he takes it so serious you know
I think we both agree that um that ended
up the best though like for the best yes
and like I think I was the perfect
for you yeah that's like your comedy you
were actually I mean like I didn't watch
the show I watched on like Facebook
video and stuff yeah yeah yeah all your
stuff was always like really good like
really smart well thought out thanks me
and sometimes it would just be so like
when they would go at you yeah I mean
maybe I have a bias because I'm Asian
but all the jokes are the same like
every single time I don't know maybe I
mean I'm sure you saw a lot oh you're
right well that's the thing too is like
scene with the Nick Cannon jokes I know
that was really annoying to see well the
thing is when people complain about you
know they only came out you with the
same jokes I mean they did but at the
same time everybody kind of played their
part like I got it you know everyone has
their role in the show where they would
get made fun of for the same stuff like
the fat dude would get the fat jokes and
you know the white girl Justina she gets
all the you're a [ __ ] joke centers but
even if it's the same kind of joke it's
the way you tell it right totally
so like the little to me you and the
short black guy was really conceited yes
really he's so clever with it he's
clever and that's the thing and there's
another white guy on there named sharone
from Canada who's also yeah he's he's
good at switching up old jokes and
putting a new spin on him you know and I
was tell people I'm like the thing about
those the reason why those jokes were so
easy for me to rebuttal was cuz I've
been hearing those jokes in the whole
life yeah yeah so I mean not of the
whole cast oh actually you know you you
roasted a lot of like celebrities - out
of everybody who like you met during
doing the show you met a bunch of
celebrities right yeah who was the worse
on the show like as a like just as a
talk about your personal experimental
areas pretty much every week well you
know what was annoying his first time on
and then the second time on he was super
nice yes so I don't know what changed
but like the first time Rick Ross came
on he came on with like 15 different
people that they insisted would all be
on the stage you know I'm saying and it
was very like the whole atmosphere was
very tense you know because I feel like
he didn't wanna look dumb and even even
like there was kind of like a little
they were like hey guys you know no no
fat jokes for Rick Ross and that was
yeah there's no veg sometimes sometimes
what kind of coming with certain
restrictions like and and don't touch
areas and he they were like no fat jokes
but the hidden but then Nick made a fat
joke so it's not like you know him as
the boss man I guess he was allowed but
then the next time Rick Ross came on
super nice didn't have his whole
entourage and it was down to make jokes
I mean especially since I guess he had
lost a lot of weight but that was
probably one of the most like I don't
know just like the the vibe felt a
little yeah you know I mean it might be
also like he was hesitant you know yeah
not sure how this goes and then after
that show aired you know maybe he saw
like a jump in sales jump the extremes
he's like oh this is good for me I think
everybody's a little weary to go on
while a now because they don't wanna you
know they don't wanna feel like you know
they're gonna get made fun of and it's
gonna go viral or anything like that but
especially that first season was kind of
hard to get guests but I think now that
it's been on for like a few years now
and people realize it's all just fun and
games like movin yeah exactly it's cool
so you're cool with Nick Cannon then
next cool yeah no we're we're good we're
good
I mean it's not like we're homies I mean
it's always like you see people make
jokes about the boss you know yeah there
was a made it seem like I don't know
there's a lot of things you people would
say your cast would say yeah and I was
always like do you guys actually like
him like that was all you know it's all
just fun and games Nick makes a good
dude Nick if anything Nick is a very
supportive guy you know if he like FS
with you as a person he will put you in
other things he'll let you know if he
has like a part in a movie he wants you
for and he's just a supportive dude
actually what I heard through the
grapevine I don't even know how true
this is but what I heard about the
reason why they decided not to bring me
back another season is I heard that Nick
was going through like the list of
people of the cast and he and he said
this is what I heard I heard he was like
he got to my name and was like I feel
like Tim could be doing more and then
that's why it's sad to let me go so I
don't know if that was just like I'm
gonna say that and make myself feel
better about like letting him go or if
that was um that's how he genuinely
feels by the way it's all up yeah yeah
but you said you were trying to not like
you're trying to get off the show for a
while anyway
yeah I mean I I didn't really voice that
to too many people maybe like a producer
that I was really close to shout out to
Rachel
and a few cast members that you know
just in the group chat I'm like you know
what guys I mean maybe this is it for me
but I was but it was so hard to say no
when it's like because we shoot the
whole season in two and a half three
weeks so it's like why wouldn't I go on
a free trip for three weeks and live in
a hotel for free have fun you know get
drunk on stage like play stupid games
with celebrities and get a check you
know but you know it just got a little
got a little old for me you know so it
was cool
well I guess continuing with a wild and
out stuff there's a brief moment in time
I don't know if you're still doing this
I haven't seen you tweet about it but
you were doing improv shows oh you know
what that I was doing shows at The
Improv theaters but I wasn't doing ask
what improv shows what that was was hold
on this is your area some are second
what that was was a me and I would bring
on special guests and I was doing a live
game show called follow me and and well
basically they had they had approached
me with the opportunity to host his game
show and it was like we would get
volunteers from the audience and just
see what how much they would embarrass
themselves for money you know so it
would be like let us go through your
pictures in your phone or let us go
through your text messages what's your
what's a crazy talent you can do and and
it was awful like a thousand bucks it
was a good time it was it was a nice
little fun little check you know just
get people up there embarrass them I
wouldn't have to really even like do
anything really and that's what that was
okay I mean I have that improv in the
past like I took improv classes in
college and stuff and you know yeah I
met Wayne Brady on a plane and you guys
did videos with him yeah super nice guy
Wayne's a super nice guy super random
when I met him at JFK like I saw him in
front of me insecure know who you were
oh he watches you too so what's crazy
here's what happened as I saw him I saw
man it's Wayne Brady
and I was like such a who's lying fan
you know
yep I was like you know what I'm not
gonna like blow up a spot I'm just gonna
chill he's going it's early whatever so
he goes to security in front of me I'm
behind him and then he was like hey man
I just want to say that uh hey you're
funny and I was like oh wait thank you
and I appreciate it bro
and then so I just upgraded my seat that
morning to it's a first class and I sat
down in my seat and I was like I think
Wayne Brady's gonna see this I felt it
in my soul like he's gonna sit next to
me and sure enough he came in and he sat
next to me Wow and we like chopped it up
on the plane for a little bit and
exchanged numbers talk [ __ ] about you
for a good hour and then but yeah he was
supposed to be the guy he was supposed
to what's the word at the wedding the
person that marries the purse officiate
he was supposed to officiate my wedding
but but he had like a last minute but it
wasn't last minute he claims that his
assistant messed some scheduling stuff
up so he had a shoot that day for a
commercial that he she told him was the
next week after my wedding but was
actually that day sorry man I can't get
out of it I was fine so I had to use
stupid David so instead you have a show
with him I do I do
and you guys sold it to a I did I do
right yeah okay so I was um I do a show
David so comedy if you're not familiar
he's a funny portly korean comedian man
and um i started a show last year early
2018 called sin foots where me and him
go to different food festivals and we
just eat all the food and like and get
drunk and critique it and make jokes you
know and originally he wasn't even
supposed to be like the perma host it
was just I was gonna have a different
person on every episode and then um but
after the first one I was like hey uh
well who do you guys think should be on
the next one or should I just keep doing
with David and everyone's like oh my god
you don't know what dated so kept doing
it with David I was shooting it like out
of my own pocket like you know for a
good I want to take almost a year and
then um the people at Thrillist Tim you
up through this is like you know
lifestyle food channel website day we're
looking for content and so they hit me
up
the interest of like acquiring the show
and and so I was down cuz you know I
wasn't making any money doing it cuz
like you know I had to pay for like the
food and the basses and the crew and the
editing and all that [ __ ] so I sold the
Thrillist
and um and I've been doing it with him
now for like a year it's super cool now
I can like travel all over the country
because originally I could only afford
to do it in LA in San Diego so now that
they pay for it and actually pay us for
it we can take it all over the country
and it's super fun people like it yeah I
mean that was I mean we filmed something
not that show ah we have another show
coming out yeah yeah I have another show
on three list that's gonna be on their
Facebook watch it's called a quired
taste where I get a special guest and
and we try a interesting unique food
menu item and so we were gonna shoot in
Vegas and they were like hey do you have
any talent you might want to have be
your guest in Vegas and I was like
talented yeah so that was cool we did
some we did some I mean I don't want to
spoil it
when he comes out you'll see I had Ryan
try some some interesting is and I've
never had it before
yes I haven't either yeah and and let me
just say Ryan's face was really funny
what is that I tried to not make it look
like I hate like yeah it was it was a
good face dude it was I think the ideal
reaction that I have a very
I have bad was expressions no like just
like just being conscious of what my
face is doing yeah like you can't
connect oh yeah like I look like mad
more than I usually a.m. yeah nothing
[ __ ] face I do have that yes yeah like
I'm not mad I know I have the same well
that's because that's when I'm engaged
doing conscious of it when I like when
we're when I'm interacting am i I got a
happy ass face but when it's chilling
when I'm not talking buddy not doing
anything people like I've heard like
I've gotten multiple multiple comments
when people like man I was gonna say
what's up to you but you look pissed
like you're in a rush I was like no
that's just my face yeah I wish I had
those like you know some people just
have a like a natural like kind of up on
the sides of their mouth you wish you
had an approach
well my god like you know there's some
people that just walk around they're
just kinda like oh yeah I know that's
not me yeah me too
if anything my my jaws droop a little
bit yeah like I don't like I try to be
more conscious of that yeah I have to I
learned I should probably think about
that a little bit more be more conscious
of your face people have been telling me
that's hard it's hard to always be
conscious of your face if anything I'm
just Jonah my posture is terrible my
face is droopy
you're pretty self-aware though I mean
like to be a battle rapper you have to
really know yourself right cuz I mean if
anything now I'm always just kind of uh
especially when the cameras are
following us around like when we're
shooting send foods I wear more that
there are people potentially like taking
cell phone footage so I try to like just
like stand up straight my chin gets kind
of squishy when I'm just looking down
that stuff really bother you then when
you would see the playback or is it
because yeah sometime think it'll affect
your what your viewership or no just for
me in general I like to look cute you
know I have a little makeup on right now
I'm grateful for this light you have
here and I'm also grateful that you're
shooting me from the right side because
on some locus is exactly what your shoot
we were swish I have a good like not
good but this is like I rather get John
this side yeah you rather get shot on
that side yeah for your shoot we both
had our bad sides oh I didn't know that
that was your bad side too yeah like if
you would have said that we could have
made not an argument I don't want to be
the only one like this is my bad side
get so let's switch seats
I didn't really care I'd prefer decide
and it sounds silly for people that like
don't really consider that a thing but
if you've seen yourself on camera enough
like girls get it girls get it they
always look at a girl's Instagram it's
always the same angle oh dude me too
secretly I'm gonna put it put together
its bags though well and people that
know me like Rick like one bit whatever
people will laugh about me having a good
side like my boy Rick he'll be like oh
no no his left side is way wonky erisa
it's just not as um you know what's the
word symmetrical yeah I'm just like
beside cute besides ill you know it
doesn't look bad dude no but you know
your face it's not bad it's a tiny thing
huh yeah so I guess talking about
insecurities for both of you guys you
know a little bit do you want to like
touch up on that like cuz one thing that
you've always talked about and almost is
like like that big dick energy you know
where people are like oh my gosh like
how are you how are you with your now
wife right right right you would
constantly preach like these people
clearly don't understand more than just
the physical right I mean and you know
what no but you know what no no no even
like [ __ ] what you just said because
physically I'm cute whenever people
would like just like defend me like okay
so if some would say damn housed him
with his like tim is out of her league
or whatever even with like my ex or my
or my wife and then and people would try
to defend me like maybe she doesn't only
care about looks I'm like oh hold on I
feel like yeah like confidence is
important confidence is key you know and
even when I was like a little kid and
you know I was thinking about this the
other day cuz someone's like dude how
are you so confident and and I would
always give the the answer of like and
and this is true to not that this isn't
true but I would say you know I always
felt like it life is so short why waste
time worrying about what other people
think about you you know cuz I feel like
people are people are gonna find you
ugly and people are gonna find you hot
and like people are gonna love you and
people gonna hate you but at the end of
the day um worrying on that and dwelling
on that is really gonna keep you from
enjoying life to its full potential you
know cause like if you're if you're
self-conscious about like oh my god how
do I look if I'm doing this and like
this person's gonna hate me and this
girl's gonna reject me you're there's so
many things that you're not gonna try
and attempt and you just never know do
you do you feel like part of that too
though is because you kind of prep for
that like you've kind of like like for
example like sitting on that side
like showing your good side do you feel
like I know that I prepped for this like
I put a little bit makeup on but I feel
like I look good so I'm confident enough
to put that energy out there if you
hadn't done all that stuff do you feel
like you would feel the same way okay
see in this and that's and that's funny
that you brought that up because I was
thinking like okay why why am I really
confident because you know how I said
life is too short to care about it and
then I started thinking why don't I care
why didn't I ever care even as a little
kid and I realized this is the reason
dude I loved girls so much that's like a
little kid I was never like worried that
oh this girl thinks I'm ugly I was like
I'm gonna try and kiss this girl pretty
I'm gonna hold her hand you know I think
not gonna lie I feel like that was my
main motivator for just like not giving
a F growing up you know it's like you
know what did I think this was cute um I
know I'm hilarious I always tell people
like I know I'm not like the guy that
walks into a room and a girl's like man
I'm gonna suck this dudes penis you know
but I say give me like ten minutes of
conversation by the punch bowl and the
chips and she's like you know I might
suck this dude's penis because at some
point there must have been a time where
you realize oh I'm good at conversation
right so I mean to get to that point to
even talk to girls most people your
average person I would say even most
people in general you don't naturally as
a kid you know that oh you know what I'm
good at this
until you make a realization it must
have been a moment in your life when you
realize like you know I can do this
maybe I mean I just um were you always
just naturally gifted that way I
wouldn't even say it I was gifted I just
I just feel like I liked making people
laugh uh-huh um and I was always doing
that ever since I was a little kid um I
think my mom always told me I was cute
to help build my self-confidence you
know and I was always like I liked being
um I like making people laugh and I I
guess I liked like a sexy tension yeah
well thanks I I'll tell you I'm not that
funny I just work really hard you know
and and I'm likable you know I hope like
I malls like I'm not the funniest person
in the world like I'm really not but I
think I think people enjoy working with
me and and and going back to just the
confidence I don't know man maybe just
was always as in me you know like
because I remember just being a little
kid you know and the janitor at my
school being like you you walk you walk
like a big man okay so you had it for
you it wasn't that kind of a natural
thing your upbringing and that's just
you I think maybe man I think my parents
just loved me you know made me feel good
about myself
laughed at my jokes told me I was cute
and we know it's thanks that's how you
raised a successful kid you know their
confidence for sure cool well real quick
we're about to take a quick she she
break and we'll be right back you have a
podcast yourself I do a podcast myself
it's called the No Chaser podcast uh-huh
and it started off being like sex and
relationships but you know and got and
that got a little old well you know you
can get old so you know I'm just gonna
talk about everything
yeah but get a very clear voice for us
we're we're just everywhere yeah I mean
you know it I try to keep a clear voice
in some type of tone yeah you know I
think it helps but sometimes it's like
you know we definitely had an episode a
couple weeks ago we're just talking
about the emos random [ __ ] and I love
that episode but you know the thing
about is I love talking about random
stuff yeah but you know for sure like
for titles and getting people to click
on it it helps that you know sexual
things that always helps that always
helps and people will be in the comments
complaining that you know do you only
talk about one thing all the time
but then it's like those are the
episodes to get to most of you I know
you know I'm saying and also like if you
watch the actual video the whole episode
we're not just talking about that yeah
you know that might be the title right
but like shut up and watch it a lot of
times it's like it's the thing that's
most impressionable and it sticks with
them which is why they feel like oh
there's the only thing you're talking
exactly but it just means like you guys
covered that topic so well and like
there's no real holes in it so that's a
compliment in a way hey thanks man you
know you know I also feel like the whole
like sexual conversations specifically
for like like in like the young
asian-americans growing up you know I
don't remember anybody that was like
Asian and talking about stuff like that
and that was a big reason why I made my
content so kind of like dirty in the
beginning because I was like I want to
be like from just the from the first
like clique I want to I want people to
be like oh this is not they this is not
a stereotype you know and I was like and
and and I first of all you know I I like
talking about dirty stuff you know I
enjoy butts and talking about butts and
stuff like that huh and but then I
remember you know when I was making my
youtube content I was like people were
already kind of shocked when they would
click on my rap videos you know cuz
growing up in in LA and I feel like when
you're in more diverse cities it's not
weird to see somebody that is Asian and
and and raps and like maybe like walks
and and talks in a certain way but then
when I was getting clicks from people
who were like you know I wouldn't even
be saying anything like on some gangster
[ __ ] I would just have like a backwards
hat on and they're like this dude wants
to be a gangster so bad and I remember
those comments for you what do you mean
I'm literally just I'm chilling I'm just
wearing a backwards hat I'm just I'm you
know I'm rapping a little bit I'm not
saying Oh nor do I claim to ever be a
gangster but for people that aren't used
to that they are so just taken aback by
it they don't know what to do so I was
like okay well let me do this - like I
like talking about dirty stuff I'm gonna
talk about dirty stuff I've never seen
an Asian dude talk about dirty stuff and
I felt like for a whole generation of
young Asian Americans who
maybe necessarily didn't have anyone
older to talk to about that I kind of
became like um an older brother / uncle
when they had questions like that you
know so when I was doing my dude
delegate Oh stuff where they would send
me their relationship and sex questions
that was one of the first things to
really kind of blow my channel up you
know cause like some of these kids that
used to watch me are now like dude you
know what I was watching you and I was
13 years old I'm in college now you help
me get through high school like because
you know they had they really had no one
that they could talk to about that yeah
yeah I've gotten that comment or for
sure yeah crazy
well it's speaking of that it's pretty
funny cuz I was told I told my dad I was
like hey this weekend cuz he watches the
podcast all the time yeah I told him oh
we have Tim on and he's like oh he's
kind of crazy huh I was like no no and
by that he means he's seen your stuff
yeah I was like no he's actually like
he's a really cool guy like he's not
every everything when we talk is not
just like yeah like I did take sexuals
yeah cuz you know he goes by like oh he
sees your podcast title right oh they
know no he's very is very normal person
- it's like when people judge you by
like a couple YouTube videos yes you
know especially you know especially
early YouTube was so like hey guys
what's up blah you know I'm saying jump
cuts and [ __ ] it's like you want again
you want to keep everything so
fast-paced and it's the tone is
completely changed now yeah but I
remember back then putting up content
like that and people meeting me that I
was just like having food with or
chilling with and they be like wow
you're really calm I thought you were
gonna be annoying and I'm like no and
I'm like that's me but I mean it's me
times 10 you know like real me isn't
always just yeah which is why I like the
whole podcast era right cuz it gives you
a chance to actually chill and have a
conversation that's that's why I wanted
to do it in the first place well when
people when I first started it everybody
was like was Ryan so depressed I was
just like no this is just how I am but
like when when I have to do a vlog I
just gotta turn it up a little bit you
know chug and extra energy at the time I
didn't have a ninja milk chug an extra -
Red Bulls you know ninja milk engine
thanks to him but yeah like people
thought and I don't blame them because
that's all they've seen right unless
they watch our second channel which is
behind the scenes button that's besides
the point
and they see you chilling and talking
and exactly that we he's mad it's the
same thing and being conscious of your
face and stuff he's he's mad you know
he's like he's not happy he's when I
used to watch back the vlogs when I used
to edit them I would make sure that
every single clip every since split
second was if I looked a little bit mad
he would comment on it so hmm
I was calm this is me not being
conscious of my face right yeah and
that's why people think I'm mad or sad I
don't know well you know the thing is
and also you know I feel like your
audience is uh you know was really young
at first they were yeah you need to
cater to that yeah I kind of stopped
well I mean Shea we're old I know I know
we are you guys audience is grown up you
know but also like you know YouTube's
constantly the audiences are changing
people are growing out of it new people
are coming in yeah um how have you guys
adjusted to that because you guys are
getting older you have new interests you
guys own the places which is something
that you know kids are like I don't
understand anything about this you know
I didn't understanding about it until
like a year ago when I bought the house
that buying house is one of most
confusing things I've ever done it's a
lot of work yeah more than you think oh
that's crazy
you should the kids out there that we
eventually want to buy a house if you're
in high school look into it a little bit
beforehand just you understand stuff you
have a realtor I did I did thank God or
else I would've been completely lost
yeah they don't teach you that [ __ ] in
school don't that's the stuff they
should be teaching kids exactly in high
school dude when I was going through it
I was like why was there not one class
on buying a house or something or like
uh or a chapter in like you could have
got screwed over at any moment yeah in
your ear tour was a bad person I was
signing things I was just like okay yeah
I know my rotor so it was like fortunate
for me but I couldn't even I knew
nothing
yeah same boat as my parents for
everything I was literally just like oh
just tell me just tell me what's a sign
you know you don't even own the place
but yeah in terms of getting older yeah
it's been a long time we've been on
YouTube just about same amount of time
yeah yeah like 13 I started little after
so six okay okay yeah oh six
yeah same so it's like in 13 years
almost 14 years yep and I'm always kind
of I feel fortunate that my audience
grew with me you know because I feel
like you know we've we've seen people
and channels that were really popping
and maybe they were doing one specific
type of thing for a long time and maybe
they were catering to a specific
audience and then you know that only
worked for so long before people are
like you know I've outgrown this you
know so the fact that people you know
still tuned in as much as they do I'm
like huh oh thank god that's crazy
of course it's not the same like it used
to be yeah how about you you how's your
audience you feel like they've been with
you it's I I would say for sure
cuz I've seen it like the age ranges
obviously it's hard to say in the
beginning because it's 13 to 17 but
really that means 13 in under mmm
because you weren't allowed to make
accounts back then right and for the
longest time it was slowly starting to
go up and I was trying to force myself
to get back down there because that's
where the biggest group is so I would
say and I just talked about in one of my
videos but like I used to try so hard to
cater to that group and getting the
young ones coming in that I would have
to dumb down the content hmm and take
jokes that I thought was funny and kill
them for myself
make it good for other people yeah and I
used to hurt like it literally hurt me
and I would see it that's so funny
because it I had the same thing happen
to me but in a completely different way
because of course I never catered to a
younger audience I was always just kind
of out there yes stuff right but where
where that happened to me was you know
of course you know a lot like a lot of
my skits were kind of dirty kind of like
slapstick II in the beginning and um but
personally like the type of stuff I like
to watch is like way drier like weird
almost you know and so when I'm like I
really want to make some content that I
would watch I'm like audience isn't
gonna get this they're not gonna like
this I think we're very similar one of
the funniest videos I think I've seen of
yours was just you and that dude dance
and just rain yeah
that's my favorite video but I never
done I can see if like like that stuff's
funny to me but if I were to post
something that I would get it would not
work
yeah but that did okay for you that did
great for me and but that was one of the
ones I was nervous about yes I was like
but that was also a video that I was so
proud of to be a part of the house I
don't care if they like this or not
yeah and luckily they loved it you know
but you know that that's definitely out
of you know in my mind like kind of
range of content it's like it's one of
the special ones oh yeah what's that
dude same just rain just rain just ran
yeah
should I just learned that you're not
supposed to call people Indian what
ethnicity is he he's Indian oh no okay
well I just learned why people are
called Indians Native American people
are quiet Indians but there's a I used
to mix up the two
I think that guys actually end you know
I know yeah but what I mean is like I
didn't want to say either because I
didn't want to mess up just in case yeah
and I used to get mixed up the two and I
just I just learned about the whole
history I'm very ignorant but like I
mean I want to learn so I watch things
in that that's what I learned I'm I have
to be very careful when I speak that so
I don't tweet a lot because I'm always
scared to get cancelled right um let's
talk about that you guys are from an
older generation of social media where
you know there's a lot of things said
that you know potentially be like whoa
whoa whoa these before you know yeah I'm
surprised you're nothing you've said has
gotten you into trouble really not you
know what it's like look for sure there
is content that I put out in the past
that wouldn't put out now right like
stuff I wasn't a lean guy and I might
have private a couple videos just with
the change of the times you know and and
and I also understood
like I of course cancel culture as a
comedian is like it's annoying right but
I also understand that the like the just
society is maturing and growing you feel
me it's like things are different
and that is okay and I'm not mad at that
so there are definite like and I feel
like back on Twitter especially there
was kind of a thing where you were
trying like people are people are trying
to be edgy like you would say just crazy
[ __ ] just to like get real yeah get
retweets and get laughs because you know
like it was like who cares it's Twitter
you know and I've definitely gone into
my past
tweets done a little search I mean like
you know I wanna just delete a whole
bunch of these because I don't in ones
that weren't even bad but it was just
like words that were kind of like um
like like anything that came up that was
like even like specific you know if it
was like oh um I met this cool black
woman today
I'm like let me just delete black woman
just in case anyone wants to go you know
find some issue with this they don't see
eye to eye I don't agree with that I
feel like that I I am mad at cancer
culture because I think I think that's
ridiculous like yeah even it's
especially if it's a long time ago and
let's say there's stuff you wouldn't say
now right if you found a video that you
deleted and someone reuploaded and they
decided to cancer you for that I'd be
pissed I'll be like this isn't right
even if unless you were like I stand by
it right you know I get it but like I
don't think I think there's this mob
mentality that happens and that's that's
the difference if someone can say
something offensive and the people
offended should be offended but it
doesn't mean everyone needs to be
offended and agree with the offended
people no I totally agree I totally
agree and I think everyone has the right
to be offended yep I think I I people
shouldn't feel obligated to agree with
you if you're offended and I totally
agree with that
but at the same time I'm like I'm still
gonna delete these tweets oh yeah I mean
like don't why take the risk right right
yeah because I mean that's the stupid
part look like I said I'm not mad at the
fact that things that we said back then
maybe aren't as acceptable now yeah but
I am mad at mob mentality and the fact
that people are mad at you for something
you said 10 years ago because or that
they want to cancel you for that because
it's like what like look you had to have
been asleep before you can be woke you
don't say and so how you gonna be like
mad at me when I was sleep like I was
sleep yes
how are you gonna be mad at me for that
I didn't know what's going on I was
sleep yeah and I'm and all I'm saying is
right now all the people who are
currently quote unquote woke how do they
know that everything they're doing right
now 10 years from now isn't asleep yeah
you know so uh it's it's one thing to be
upset by something in the time like okay
I get it I wouldn't say certain things I
would say I would have said like ten
years ago right but how do you know that
what you're saying right now isn't gonna
be a friends of ten years from now
I mean exactly and the thing about it is
like men even five years ago it's like I
feel like you your mind and everything
can grow so much you can become a
completely different person you know so
I it's it's silly to hold that over
someone's head forever
yeah I agree yeah and a lot of times I
think it's especially with social media
um you feel so isolated and not like
real connections but you want to feel
like a part of something bigger mm-hmm
so a lot of times a lot of people in
these mom mentalities are this walk
mentality they don't even really truly
believe it they're just like I'm just
saying what I think I'm supposed to
because everybody else is doing it
mm-hmm you know any gets likes yeah like
that and it's which is the ironic then
you feel a part of it yeah so that's the
new culture and I think people are
trying to fit in for one and it's the
majority so it's easier you're right to
jump on that bandwagon I think it's
gonna switch eventually because people
are getting tired of that I think it's
already starting to happen you see
comments like the people are kind of
getting sick of it they're over it yeah
but I think another part of that mob
mentality is the fact that there's just
a internet culture there's I don't know
what it is there's like people who just
like to make people feel worse and I
think part of it is because they're not
happy so they want other people to feel
that pain mm-hmm because they maybe they
got called out for something so now
they're like okay you know what you're
coming yeah I'm gonna call out other
people to make them worse I might just
maybe be in my head I don't know that's
a theory I have I mean you know it's
it's so it's it's crazy that it's gotten
to a point like that I just you know I
just I just want I want to be a better
person
yeah and it's like if I want to be a
better person
then then let me make my mistakes you
know and and I'm sure like eventually
you know there's gonna be something that
like happen in the past that like people
are gonna be upset about you know it's
and that's I mean I mean we all like
Sade and do dumb things when we're young
and growing yeah you know figuring it
out well like the Indian thing like I
just like I said I used to call Native
American b-boy and I didn't know the
difference I didn't know why that
happened
apparently it's because when people
first came here they thought they were
in India I know this is true yeah and
then they just stopped just kept calling
them Indians so I didn't know how
offensive that was but when you when you
watch cartoons and stuff I know you
associate that's like I grew up learning
from cartoons and stuff right in history
class I mean I guess I didn't pay
attention to well and then you know I
mean and in cartoons they're playing
cowboys and Indians yeah exactly
actually you would let's it that because
that just happened right Columbus Day
it just happened did it recently I
believe that I don't know yeah but a lot
of people are talking about you know
Columbus Day and or should it be called
indigenous indigenous peoples day yeah
changing it up cuz everyone likes there
everyone's like yo Christopher Columbus
shouldn't be celebrated anymore he did
he didn't even really find America and
he just really just kind of what he did
to the people actually because uh you
know he was like I'll trade like certain
objects for land and the Native
Americans were like you can't own land
sure like this is a good idea for us and
so when they got this up and then you
know he started to enact oh we own this
or we we do this and then Indian people
or sorry Native American people see your
cancelled bro a Native American people
they they they taught him certain things
how to do certain stuff and then what he
did was enslave them you know and so a
lot of people are like wait a minute
this isn't right we've been celebrating
somebody who has persecuted people who
previously owned this land right so
that's the whole contract I didn't know
its own digitus people's day no way see
that's another thing too what you back
to Noah lumbus lover bullet clip from
this exact exactly they could and I was
just I didn't know yeah they say like oh
he's so ignorant but like that's how you
learn yeah exactly you have to learn at
some point and there should be some not
like you don't need credit for it but
like I just show like I'm not closed off
right to say like oh no I know
Christopher Columbus and that's why
Columbus Christopher Colombo that and
that's why I don't like the whole like
if someone's ignorant like you get angry
at them for not knowing
I mean if someone's ignorant and and
they have questions let's help each
other out you know you know some people
though you know there are they're like
if the kid touches the stove and burns
themselves they should know you know and
some people are like oh no you know what
let's teach him but you don't know the
temperature of a Native American person
I don't know how hot until the the white
people brought over the flu then they
probably had a fever yeah see whities
man messed it all up that's another
thing I don't even bring that up
ooh now I want to know but we can
transition out yeah we can transition
out we have 10 minutes left let's go to
a couple of the bigger questions
questions yeah I have like one or two
sure mister um but actually one that I
wanted to talk about is because you are
one of the first prominent youtubers to
be in a long-distance relationship oh
that has actually panned out yeah yeah
so I don't know if you want to talk
about it a little bit about this cuz you
know especially again with social media
because a lot of you were like oh I can
find love anywhere right right but
there's a whole like subtle Asian dating
thing where people finding love across
the country across the world yeah
there's apps all over
what advice cuz we've already asked Ryan
about this but you know you have a
completely different story so let's just
hear about that a little yeah I mean um
you know what I when I was younger I
would have never said I would get into a
long-distance relationship you know I
used to be like you know what I couldn't
do it I need like just to touch somebody
you're horny we've got my one boy I was
a horny boy yeah still am but when I met
gia my my wife my current wife my only
wife I remember thinking like if I don't
at least try to make this work then I'm
just
regret it forever you know and and
long-distance you know it's possible
it's just it's not it's not easy and I
think it takes very specific kinds of
people for me like let's say I was with
a long-distance relationship with my ex
okay who at the time like needed to talk
on the phone all the time needed to know
where I was and and if I was trying to
do that with her long-distance with her
that would have never worked but with
Chea not only is she a super secure
person like isn't jealous isn't like
where you add who you with she also was
really busy you know I'm saying she ran
her own business in Canada so it was
like we both had our own stuff going on
so it wasn't somebody or - yeah it's
really important because if one person
is busy all the time and they can't text
back and they can't call back the other
person is like what's happening you know
their life kind of gets revolved around
the other person and like and and that's
not good for even a regular relationship
you know and so what worked for us is
like she could worry about her own thing
I could worry about my own thing we were
both super secure people no one was like
tripping about like why aren't you
hitting me back you know and and and
also and this is a big thing in longest
relationships ooh is that like um we
both had money yeah we could both afford
to fly back and forth to Canada when we
needed to and she also she ran her own
business so she could leave whenever she
wanted to that is huge yeah dude so it
wasn't like you know cuz some people are
in long dissipation ships they can't
take the time off of work for like six
months right but we were we had a system
where we would work work work for three
weeks I would shoot I'll go on meetings
she would do all like her appointments
for three weeks she was an aesthetician
pedicures manicures waxing vaginas we do
that for three weeks straight we'd set
one week where I wouldn't take any
business and she wouldn't take any
clients we'd fly to each other and hang
out for a week and then be like alright
see you next month you know and um it
was hard at first first couple months it
was like you know crying at the airport
and [ __ ] like that but after after a few
months I was like alright well uh see
you next month
you know have have a good trip and um
just coming out used to it how long ago
did you get married a year ago
oh so it's oh that that's way more
recent than I thought
is uh so that's that's during a time
where immigration is a big thing is she
is US citizen now dude that whole
process was a [ __ ] it's booked for ever
I would assume right now in like the
past four years three years she
literally just got her green card like
two weeks ago oh really and it was over
a year no dude not only that yeah I'm
talking about from the beginning process
of trying to get her k1 visa which was
the proper visa to get to get married
it's the fiance visa where she enters
the country and has 90 days to marry me
legally this is all we're doing
everything the super proper way from the
day we applied for that visa to the day
we got it it got married and since she
got married like we've done a couple we
she did an interview I did an interview
the whole approval process took like two
years yeah that is crazy yeah and and
and here's what happened to while she
was married while after we got married
she wasn't allowed to leave the country
or work she couldn't even go back to
Canada for like a straight year yeah she
could even visit her family it was crazy
yeah that seems I mean that I guess in a
way that shows true love because if you
guys really didn't love each other you
wouldn't go through that [ __ ] you
know it was like and he was 22 his is um
you know when we kind of got into our
long-distance routine at one point I was
like hey babe is this weird but do you
almost think it's better that we're
long-distance and she was like babe I
was thinking the exact same thing
because she loves her alone time I love
my alone time she was working so hard
and it was like dude who I don't even
think we would have had time for a
relationship if we were together like
that so how was it different now then
well now we've taken all those skills
and apply them to living together you
know because like now that we've gone
through all that nobody's mad when
someone's like just in the other room
for like the whole thing like we can be
yeah we can be chillin not even talking
to each other and
it's not an issue you know no one's like
needy yeah you know and being to people
that really value they're kind of like
space and a lone time I think the
distance helped us get into a space
where it's like okay I understand that
this is you need to be here I need to be
here sometimes if I'm snoring too much I
will move to the next bed because she's
like pushing me my face cuz she can't
sleep that's something she had to get
used to like me snoring apparently I
snore and but yeah it worked we got
married yeah that's not good
thanks not bad and I guess we can
continue into another question from
Caesar that ass what do you believe to
be the key to happiness cuz you're
somebody who always promotes that type
of stuff I know there's a lot of Keys
you have you have more keys than a
janitor more keys than I have two keys I
have two key or that I try to apply to
my life all the time one being like I
said before the more you care about what
other people think I think the more you
/ the more you like cut yourself off
from like potential happiness you know
cuz you're you're leaving your life
according to other people's opinions
like you give them the power instead of
having own power exactly like once you
stop caring then it's like you're free
you know it's like who cares the second
thing I always try to apply in my life
is something I learned in like a Taoism
class in college which but but then
people like so many people have said
this in so many different ways and it's
that um life isn't about what happens to
you it's about how you react to what
happens to you you know it's like once
you realize that you don't control
anything and you stop worrying about it
and you're just kind of like okay I'm
just gonna make the most out of whatever
situations I'm dealt then it's like okay
cool I'm just gonna take this and roll
with it and and and try to do my best
and then you know you just you're okay
with it I think nice yeah very clear
concise stuff
this table is of Will Smith he thinks to
not let things happen to you but you
control the universe is that he says
something like that like you can make
force to universe to Ben there's a lot
of people yeah who believe like
manifesting disks it's a similar thing
no I mean I'm here's the thing I mean I
totally believe in the universe too
like okay like it exists oh yeah it's
all exist but when people used to ask me
what I wanted to be when I grow up
whenever they asked me what did you
think
did you ever think you would end up here
now I'm like yeah this is what I wanted
to do like I didn't know in what
capacity but one night when they asked
me I was little I'd say oh yeah I'm
gonna be famous cuz I knew what I wanted
to do and I knew that if I kept working
towards that goal I would make it happen
you know and whenever people asked me
like how does it feel to like live your
dream I always tell them like well
here's the thing I never looked at it
okay here's here's another here's I've
said this a million times in my videos
but but this is Ryan Higa the audience
so I always say hey what do I say don't
look at your goals as dreams look at
them as destinations okay because for me
when you think of dreams you think of
like like unicorns something that's like
that's not tangible you know but if you
look at your goal as something that that
is there as a destination and all you
have to do is keep moving towards it
then you'll get there eventually you
know and and I feel like I looked at
like being famous the same way somebody
would look at getting like a college
degree or getting like a becoming a
doctor you know like you know what the
end goal is so you go okay I'm gonna go
take biology class and go be pre-med I'm
gonna be a nurse I'm gonna take all
these steps that eventually make me a
doctor so for me I was like I know where
I want to be in my career I'm gonna take
the necessary steps and you know get an
agent and go take acting classes and and
even though I haven't done that but but
put myself in the right positions and
take the right steps so I feel like if I
just keep going I'll only keep
progressing you know and and then and
that's what I did well universe there
you go
last go ahead last question from Sarah
any plans on having kids soon well
here's the thing um special announcement
no just kidding oh my god Breaking
exclusive yeah yeah sooner than later
soon later my parents have been bugging
me for grandkids since before I even
you know we even got engaged you know
one of the main things that we that kept
us from having kids right now is that
like she didn't have a green card yet so
we want a few years of just like
traveling or maybe like maybe a year of
traveling where we don't to worry about
a baby you know I worry about reading
pregnant we haven't been gone honeymoon
yet so yeah so now that we can actually
go on the honeymoon you know she can
take her cute bikini pictures without
having a little baby bump and then huh
we'll come back and I'll start you know
not pulling out do you have anything
that you want to plug you know you have
your podcasts all your shows I'm sure
check out my podcast no chaser podcast
it's just on my youtube channel and make
sure you check out sin foods on
Thrillist and when did this come out
probably Sunday
oh cool and check out no whining which
is my Facebook watch show where I
interview little kids oh that's cute hey
oh it's so it's my favorite thing I've
ever done and then uh another Food Show
on MTV's YouTube called basics abou G
that I do and and that's it and I might
start working on new album soon thank
you again so much for being here dude I
know you're very busy thanks for having
me oh you're busy thanks for having me
let me know next time you're in LA we'll
have you my podcast I will be there in a
couple weeks actually
I mean I'll text you well figures on
yeah so that's number seven you have to
do now yeah I know I'm doing a little
mini podcast tour in LA oh man all right
well let's just hang out dude forget it
let's just grab a drink
forget the bike take a break call your
podcast let's just grab a drink with
your I like [ __ ] guys are easy I mean
it's fun it's just like being yourself
so yeah cool well the way we end these
is we just breathe into the mic so in
three two one
[Laughter]