you may have seen or heard about the
experimental product in his Google glass
spot up to the future and virtually does
everything your home can do in your
glasses here at Google we finally teamed
up with the makers of the iPod human
hand line navigator to bring you the
brand-new highly advanced cutting edge
of the blind glass with a completely
original design the Google glass human
is not just better it's bigger you know
people ask me all the time why don't you
guys have to make it so big every time I
keep it in the same simple response
that's what she said
the Google glass you make up to multiple
styles and colors such as product
placement white recyclable green
bandwagon blue mustache where you can
stereotypically traces Asian is what it
seems I get first but is in black I'll
take two and just because the Google
glass human is easy to use it doesn't
mean it has any less capabilities you
maybe do everything your best smartphone
can do and much more such as voice
activation and voice response who will
bless human find me the nearest coffee
shop no picture taken with zoom Google
glass human take a picture okay zoom in
a little bit all right
no damn it you blinked again navigation
continue on for 2.5 steps are you sure
we're in my room it feels like we're
outside calls answer call hello
Christine says wait really
yes tell me yes I don't know what made
her change her mind no but you are a fat
girl
wait what thanks to our top-of-the-line
scientist here at our Google Maps we're
proud to announce one of our newest
features never before seen or done on
any place in the past the automatic
fragrance feature also known as an
fragrance oh really on my neck you know
one of those people that uses a lock and
your phones people don't steal it when
you sleep well with the Google ask you
bananas triangle lock feature not idea
to not worry about sleeping it is so
secure that it'll actually
helping to sleep not completely
convinced yet here some of our satisfied
customers I cannot live without it
to be honest I don't leave home without
it it's stupid it's too heavy and it's
really inconvenient okay well how do you
feel about your iPhone oh well obviously
that's one of the best products of our
generation the Google glass human is not
something you just use it's not
something you just do it's something you
bought and for the simple price of six
hundred ninety nine ninety nine you can
get one hoped end of a Google glass
human but wait if you order now we'll
also throw the Google shoes human as
well but wait order now get the Google
watch you can do but wait if you want to
now we'll throw the Google Bell human
also well lay a beat in our order when
we taught you to order now the first
three time it's a good thing you wait is
if you order now you'll get everything
we mentioned so far plus an additional
lifetime supply of Google glass units
wait what somebody please help me
hello Sean do you require assistance yes
get all of these Google things off of me
I'm sorry did you say call two googly
coffee me what no that's not even a name
in my contact I'm sorry did you say yes
what no calling two googly coffee meet
cancel cold call cancel good now call
for help calling for h-e-l-l-o number
just call 9-1-1 calling one one one one
no not when I live in one one just now
the number not dialing 900 one one
dialing one no not a singular one you
know what I meant dial two one
sighing one one great now that's too
many delete one which one would you like
to lead it does it matter
No delete a wire leading all one no damn
it just add a one and another while
adding one plus one - oh my god you know
what Google glass human I'm done I'm
sorry did you say 9-1-1
I mean yes yes call me I'm sorry did you
say College Oh call it comet
no call it Cottage whole wallet call
number hauling finally two googly coffee
me wait you're an actual person no I'm
one of your Google glass humans but I'm
at the top so I'm more updated and you
what's up thank God okay please listen
to me I just need one thing purify
please call for help call for an
ambulance
I'm sorry did you say I want more am
fragrance no no initiate am free
not like this yes