oh really I never realized how expensive
weddings are for me I always see life as
like something that you can look back on
and remember and those you're only gonna
remember certain things when I got
punched like a chunk of my jaw line got
taken out alright clapping claps welcome
back to another episode of off the bill
podcast today we don't have a guest well
technically we do cuz Greg's not always
here but you know what's going on great
just be honest and say we have to intro
this three times because we keep end up
laughing and talking about nothing this
episode I can't wait till we start doing
this live what's up I'm Paco by the way
oh you're not
we got Paco in the moderator seat Greg's
across from me and we are going back to
our roots and we don't have a guest
really and we're just gonna be talking
about the things that we want to be
talking about let's talk there's no real
topics but also we have nobody helping
us pay the bills no sponsors today so
sponsors into that walmart.com slash
ninja milk thanks to go there right now
people ask you know people ask it's been
artists talk in a lot of places
I know it's doing very well well not in
those like those places that are they're
out of stock is where I have the most
feds so like it really sucks anyway if
it's not there just go to our site ninja
muqaam but uh yeah it sucks that they
were out of stock because Walmart bought
a whole bunch for me so we're like
running a little anyway we made a second
batch so that's our sponsor for today's
podcast because we don't have a sponsor
yeah but you can be the next one yep
what were you saying we're just talking
about like what's going on with our
lives and stuff well you just did
something with JK news for people who
don't know Bart and Joe originally yes
right yet they were just kidding films
just them too and then they transitioned
and they made like multiple channels
just getting party everything a podcast
yeah it's it's kind of like a podcast in
a way it's like twelve minutes of news
but it's not necessarily focused around
the news it's just like then just
discussing it and then sometimes stories
will pop out it was a really fun
experience with them
it's basically us except they have their
like prepared yeah and their more vulgar
their little more they're a lot more uh
they're not afraid to say things whereas
sometimes Ryan will be like probably
shouldn't dip my toes into that water
yeah I need to work on that I feel like
Jo and Bart are people that should be on
the podcast soon they want you oh yeah
oh you mean on ours yeah yeah on ours
but they also want you on theirs but
you're not gonna be as good as me that's
how I was out I mean I don't think I am
good at that that's why I brought you on
this in the first place
because you're just a talker you know I
mean like I had one of the reason I
started doing this podcast is because I
wanted to get better at doing this well
you've improved over these bascomb
yeah I thought so too yeah well you know
because one of my biggest fears if you
go back and watch like back from like
2000 actually has early 2000 when I
started doing this and then like not not
the podcast like YouTube in general
every single interview I do I'm hella
awkward and I just hate doing I mean I
hate public speaking and I hate just
doing things
um that's live I guess and being
recorded that I don't have control over
because I I just my biggest thing is I
lose track of my train of thought
mm-hmm I even like when I take adderall
I like I don't have any
I still get those moments of just like
my mind wanders if someone's talking and
I'm not like super excited about it I
don't try to like I really try to pay
attention but I can't anyway that's
that's one of the reasons why I want to
do this because we are just uh you know
trying to get better at our week you
guys have been getting better it's
definitely something that I've been
trying to the same way then listen to as
much as I can for you guys like you know
all the podcasts I don't listen to it
that much but every time I do did you
listen to us yeah I do I know when he
does I mean it's like it's like a lot of
people it's like select yeah this is a
oh I guess you care about or the the
good window I really like the one that
you guys it with though with the Chang
qu yang Oh
Oh change yo whoops yeah the window with
yang was up you clearly paid attention
during that one yeah that was a good one
like I learned a lot from them and I
think for me the reason why I mean I
liked it is because I literally was like
those are my real questions that I
always asked it you don't get to
normally have those things answered from
someone you know right you don't have
the opportunity to have that person
there yeah he definitely dropped a lot
of information on us that was kind of
like I mean it is gonna be a little
biased because it is coming from you
know his campaign his perspective stuff
like that but nonetheless I mean what
you see also in the news is kind of
reflecting what he talks about I don't
know if you guys saw though but they
were talking about in terms of who's
raising the most money he actually
raised like a decent amount but even
then news networks are not putting his
like he's raising more than some people
on those news networks and they're not
showing him like that so that's
interesting there's I mean that's been
like the narrative from like months ago
right like he's coming out of nowhere
and they keep there's all these like
there's like it's not really a
conspiracy cuz it's actually happening
like there's so many things
coincidentally that that goes against
the mainstream media is doing against
Andrew yang so for whatever reason he's
being targeted I think to a certain
degree and I guess if you just look it
up you can you can see like people have
made videos of him like proof race it's
happening and I'm not sure why and maybe
it could be because he's the only one
that's not a politician could be that
crazy
yeah same way of that I guess in the
same way he's kind of like Donald Trump
should I say that like but the way like
he's not a politician it just came in
here and took people by storm maybe
they're afraid that he'll he'll actually
what if that's the route though for like
the next presidency is like someone who
isn't a politician who isn't playing by
those rules I think was formed I think
that's true like I think that's why
they're trying to not show him because
they want they want somebody who's that
they're used to in there that will be
conformed will conform to lobbyists and
stuff like that mm-hmm
or it's just because he's Asian could be
ya know I mean you know they're making
big jumps but he's
that's a big too big of a jump yes maybe
maybe the reason to not stir away too
far but still talking about you know
presidential politics and opinions on
things something that recently popped up
that Ryan and I both picked as a good
topic was the Obama vs. woke culture
exchange I was shocked
yes all that video you want to explain
why Amin well I'll take that back I
wasn't shocked I was just shocked that
they that he said that publicly so
basically Obama there's a video of him
was he at a Q&A or something it was
Chicago yeah doing he was doing a speech
I think it was for something for him let
me look it up as you talk uh-huh so he
was giving some speech or whatever I
would just watch the video I didn't see
the full whatever thing he was doing any
kind of like went out against like
cancer culture sorry woke Obama dude
yeah not really not really against it he
just showed he gave a different opinion
um from what you're used to seeing from
one side like from the Left Party which
is like they're usually very Pro being
woke and and being you know canceling
people who have done the wrong things in
the past and he was basically not saying
he wasn't going against it completely
but he kind of gave his opinion and he
said we can't everybody makes mistakes
the exact argument that a lot of people
make when they mess up it was coming
from him though so it was like very
strange because he's cancelled for
something that's what I'm there
something like what's coming up that
someone has dirt on him for or like
nothing that I've seen so far on the
news but basically he was speaking at an
Obama Foundation summit in Chicago on
Tuesday where he spoke out and asked for
Americans to like abandon ideologically
pure ideal ideological purity test set
his quote in politics no it's a this is
an article that's quoting him but his
quote was that this idea of purity and
you're never compromised and you're
always politically woke and all that
stuff you should get over that quickly
he said the world is messy there are
ambiguities people who do really good
stuff have flaws yeah and that's so true
like
but now coming from Obama that's and
he's again it's always been like you
know I mean you hear people on the right
and they're also saying things contrary
to that but it's almost like they go so
far and above it's like it became this
like extreme vers extreme yeah that's
someone who's finally like kind of in
the middle yeah you know it's like and I
feel like a lot of times - a lot of
people who do speak out are the
extremists where most of America
probably sits somewhere in central you
know like they'll lean to a side but
because it's so extremists on both sides
you're afraid of like oh if I speak out
and be like well the other side does
have good points like what about this
then your own side will be like oh
you're betraying this you know you don't
truly believe us you should just be with
them and right it's so polarizing you
know I thought it was just great cuz
like we got even like we talked about it
a little bit too much I think here and
we're talking about it again about like
cancer culture and how much I hate it
even with the last August with Tim I was
talking about like he was like I can
understand it like he was trying but I
was like I don't I'm pissed and I don't
like it but just even having saying that
there's negativity towards me and saying
why why that it's necessary to that that
happens you know that people do get
counsel for doing these things because
it's a necessary sacrifice for the good
of humanity and I think the initial
cortical cancellations were important
you know like Harvey Weinstein like
people who have been doing terrible
stuff for a long time and then it got to
the point where this monster just grew
and was like fetus more fetus more and
no matter what they did they just wanted
sacrifices and it became its own
religion and cult in a way if you think
about it yeah well canceling people you
mean yeah yeah and I think that kind of
bread the whole and again the divide
happened right it kind of bread the
whole anti-cancer Asian culture so
canceling cancellation culture
we're like people were so annoyed
including myself not that I would do
that speak out I get like people who
deserve to be canceled should be
cancelled yeah but I think somewhere
along the lines we lost that you know
where do we draw that line and then
people were so annoyed by you know
the whole Kevin Hart situation or Dave
Chappelle's you know thing people are so
annoyed by it that they went to the
extreme like almost troll level off just
like canceling every but like going
against council culture in every single
way and I think that's yeah I mean I
don't I don't know I hate talking about
this cuz like it's just gonna draw more
of those same people we're gonna anyway
whatever what are you excited about
right now Greg what's going on right now
they tricks it we can talk about
whatever we want whoa ninja milk
stop-motion is done yato now my focus is
on my wedding okay
and this is something that a lot of
people have kind of like I don't think
there was any like real announcement
announcement at least on this John
additional yeah yeah I mean that Dana
had a ring but Greg and Dana
go ahead I mean you can say like you
guys are engaged you just said it so
like yeah Greg and Dana are engaged so
what happened was I was supposed to make
like this crazy video because I had this
thing all planned out it was super cool
in my mind but yeah my proposed oh let's
just say it was it was cute but the
execution was audio you said he had
issues right well the video was horrible
yeah the video is horrible but the way I
did it was like you know I was supposed
to propose to her with like like Legos
me and her are both in trillions of
Legos and I made this cool little Lego
thing and it broke when I gave it to her
I was trying to put it together Wow
stuttering and mumbling all sweating
anyway I'll make a video of it I can I
think and make a good video of it just
wait for that but that's honestly more
like that's like everyone sees those
videos where everything is like super
planned and romantic and like that's
like s'more you you know like that's you
guys that's like I mean I know it's
always been fun industry but like that's
like it's the epitome of your
relationship I feel like I mean from my
perspective I feel like that that's
almost even better that it ended up that
way
I think so instead the footage though
it's it's of you like breaking in and
then panicking and yeah yeah yep I think
that's better I don't know it's pretty
funny it's really cute but yeah me and
Dana are getting married
yep next year sometime in October you
guys are invited
what Oh realize how expensive weddings
are yep Wow I my brother just got
married too so just when they were
talking about they did it in a different
way only went destination and then there
was actually you were there you're
filming it there was only like ten of us
right give or take
and that way they could just have fun
right but you're doing a little bit
different the tradition oi yeah my
family is give us some own family in a
way in Filipino so it's being yeah but
it's just my family never really had a
big wedding
in or at least in my immediate family we
recently had something smaller but we
never had like the grand scale of like
actual wedding yeah and I thought it
would just be fun to see what some of my
my auntie's and uncles dressed up I mean
they never wear anything close to like
suits and that's easy yeah something
different something different yeah that
you know it's always about for me I
always see life as like something that
you can look back on and remember and
those are your only gonna remember
certain things mm-hmm and I just want
like you know for my family that would
be a cool thing to remember when
everyone was dressed up and had like
this actual ball or whatever kind of
like something that was from like a
fairy tale or something but it's not
gonna be that it's gonna be our version
it's gonna be a Greg and Dana wedding
like always and Dana's family is her
family is big
her family is huge she has some like I
think she herself has 100 something
people and oh my god what well of course
it's gonna be expensive then I mean
don't you think big does well even if it
was like cheap like yeah I mean not
cheap even if it was affordable
like if you got McDonald's for everyone
mm-hmm inviting that many people is just
but even like the venue like just
because I don't know and I'm sure Paco
doesn't know and a lot of people who
haven't gotten married don't know what
is like give me an average breakdown of
like when you're looking for venues and
like say you have what 200 people coming
right what is like what is the price
they're giving so the venue itself it
depends on like what you are going for
if you're going for like a wake up like
a big venue yeah usually they'll have
everything included like the food and
all that and that can get up to about
100 to 200 dollar sway a person okay so
what is like so if you were to go with
those bigger venues right 200 people
like it's like a bigger wedding I think
right but in general like what was like
the mid-range price they were quoting
you probably about mid range with drinks
and food and the venue everything
included I would say a clean hundred
dollars per person in Nevada the average
cost for weddings is 296 dollars per
person that per person okay so that's
already way more than what you're seeing
that's crazy that's freaking crazy
and you saw $100 per person is
affordable yeah that's like she's always
a 200 people that's 20 grand
right yeah and that's not even including
the videographer photographer I'm just
gonna have you guys just shaking a
little bit and think about like how much
is the average wedding dress you know
Dana's wedding dress price like all
those things add up it's like you got to
be rich to get married exactly or we're
not rich but you got it like to have
like one of those like a pretty wedding
that you've seen in like movies and
stuff you have to be pretty wealthy and
and it's kind of crazy to me how many
how expected that is I'm not even I'm
not even including the ring like the
cost of a ring yeah and I've always
thought this and I know that a lot of
people will disagree including my own
probably my parents cuz they're married
I think weddings are like a scam I
didn't agree with that too but I thought
I thought woked oh okay explain to me
explain to me why what you what you were
told I wasn't told anything I was
okay when I was when guests come yeah
they usually give money as gifts
so I guess get back the guests are
paying for the experience with you
mm-hmm
so if you know as long as you're not
like just going ridiculous like you're
not spending a million dollars in your
wedding it's not gonna be that much of a
financial it's like an investment of a
good time right something that you can
like experience with your family and
your loved ones right they're gonna at
some point give you something in return
and it should be kind of like a balance
right but in the grand scheme so you're
kind of essentially like so the way I
see it is you're basically I mean the
way you have to see is you're just
throwing a party for other people right
but I think like okay so you're saying
that you put in all this money in this
venue to that whatever you get a lot of
it back because the people coming right
not all of it but you've got a bunch of
money or gifts or whatever it is you get
value right
the only people like I get that and when
they have weddings the same thing
happens to them the only the only people
who are really coming up is the business
itself like wedding the wedding industry
people who sell the Rings who set who
are that you pay for the the venue and
right and so on and no those those are
the that's what I'm saying it's like
it's not I'm not the scam was a wrong
way to say it I think it's just a very
smart business that we've in society
taught people that is this is the route
you go it's something that you're always
like everyone like this is the dream I
always face is that like that's
everything know like any event you're
gonna want to celebrate it's gonna be
that type of model where it's gonna be
someone's gonna be making money off of
it even as small as like a Super Bowl
party right you know like some any type
of event where you're gathering people
and you're just celebrating having fun
mm-hmm I mean anytime you think about it
you are spending you're willing to spend
money what just outfit a difference is
is like there's things in weddings that
is not your average party a getting a
dress that cost that much that you'll
wear once to meet like logically if you
tell someone who doesn't who's an alien
from outer space and they're like oh you
so you guys can get
right you're gonna be together risk your
lies cool why do you need to pay this
amount of money for this thing that mmm
that you're gonna wear once and same
with the ring like it's like oh there's
diamonds in general again we're taught
that has so much value but I don't know
if this is true but I've heard so many
times that diamonds aren't actually that
rare and compared to other gems I don't
know it's diamonds are not rare yeah but
we've given it so much value right I
actually just looked at up cuz I I've
heard this before about I wanted to look
a little bit more you know how it it
basically talks about how it was a
marketing campaign in the nineteen for
what's-his-name Ryan no all right
I didn't see it but I know what you're
talking about that's exactly what the
myth of like diamonds you're saying yeah
weddings in general right all weddings
in general we're just back then rich
people used to get married and now it's
like you know lower-class people wanna
do the same things that the rich people
were doing right and is also used it was
a ways of exchanging land um back in
like Europe and stuff really or it would
be like we have a treaty things like
that it was basically used as a in
agreement between two richer larger
families uh-huh that's what it was for
or there was like you know dowry whereas
it's like I think dowry is worth the
woman's family right has to give an
offering as well to the man and that's
just how it was before and then we
normalized it by saying hey this is like
what love is you know marriage right and
all these things and I mean that's kind
of just like what capitalism is you know
you're selling people an idea yeah and
if you can make them believe it you can
make money off yeah but what I'm saying
and I'm I think what is happening is a
lot of people are going non-traditional
yeah as I think like with anything right
we're not gonna do everything
necessarily our parents right right over
time you get your own you know point of
view but anyway I don't have any issue
with with it because it's still that
normal right and I in our society and I
have no issue following that because it
does bring happiness to people but when
people don't do it a specific way and
they're being judged for it yeah I think
that's where it's an issue I think it's
definitely an issue when you know it
doesn't become fun for the people right
and doing it yeah two main people that
are supposed to be having fun I feel
once it gets to doing traditions that
they don't even understand or you know
they're they're just doing it just
because that's when it becomes kind of
you know why are you even doing it
they're right yeah it's just like you're
just following these traditions but
that's so many people who do things to
please others yeah but I mean like
that's that's where I think it's
changing because in the past you just do
it right like our parents days like yeah
yeah get a nice dress get a nice place
make sure everyone eats well right you
don't worry about eating you like deta
and my parents don't even remember
eating what their meal but everyone else
did right and most times you hear this
only reasoning because we're at that age
where a lot of our friends are getting
married and stuff like that you hear so
many stories of like oh I'm so stressed
I gotta plan the wedding like for a
whole year the girl or whoever's
planning it and and it's a financial
burden and you know they don't have
necessarily the same money that a thirty
year old when our parents were growing
up might have and it's kind of like why
are you getting married then like I get
you go to the courthouse I get you don't
have the dream you're not everything we
grew up watching and movies and stuff
like that but like if you're so
miserable from this you know it's gonna
put a strain on your actual relationship
then you should just you don't need to
do that and also you could technically
do this you could just go to the
courthouse get married and then do the
like official wedding later cuz your
friends aren't ever gonna be like hey
this is your actual anniversary
hey do you remember when your
anniversary was yeah you don't remember
your friend's anniversaries or anything
like that so why does it matter it
doesn't matter it oh yeah that stuff is
just it's if you actually love each
other and you can't really you're not
into throwing parties and you're not
into you know getting your family and
friends together and that that's just
not your thing then yeah yeah weddings
it's not something you have to do and
also like going back I mean like one of
the main reasons I guess arguments for
marriage is because it's religious as
well which I mean like I get that it is
right it's a religious thing yeah
if other if not for that reason like
let's say you're not the most religious
person in the world or you don't go to
church every Sunday or whatever like you
know you're just
average person that sounds bad
not that the average person doesn't go
to church anyway I'm covering up my
council culture right now so I you know
giving myself insurance mom if for
somebody who isn't necessarily getting
married because of religion what really
change like for you yourself like you
guys aren't I don't think it was a
church what's really gonna change other
than like you know being able to claim
for me you guys are a couple like
legally what changes for you how was
your life gonna change once you're
married versus not because you're
already living together yeah as far as
lay together I mean the we're always
gonna love each other we've been
together for so long that the main
reason we're getting married is just to
have some fun yeah like that's why I'm
really excited like I'm actually really
excited because I know that we're gonna
have this big party
don't the main thing that's gonna change
for us is basically just taxes Yeah
right that's like one of the biggest
benefits too right but I mean like that
that that's the thing too if you'd
really think about it other than the
incentive of you know having taxes it
doesn't it's there's not a big jump
anymore because people are already
living together they're already sleeping
together it's too expensive in the past
it was a little different right yeah
because it was like you don't well for
one you don't have sex until you're
married right like I'm one I'm sure
people didn't always follow that but it
was more of a thing yeah
also I the fact that you don't really
you're not supposed to live with someone
before you're married mmm I don't know
is that a religious thing was just like
temptations I don't think that's so much
a religious thing it's just like that
you're allowing yourself to be living
with temptation there any but yeah but
anyway that times were different right
way I mean marriage was it was so much
of a bigger deal it's like now it's like
people move in after being together for
a couple months right you know what that
would be that would be a complete you
wouldn't that's unheard of right now
parents time and I think that's it's
just where we are right now that's why
it's it's kind of changing yeah it's
definitely changing but I think it's
changing for the better for sure yeah
it's like you know people are realizing
that yeah like weddings aren't essential
like you don't have
to have a big wedding and you can do
these just kind of non-traditional
smaller weddings but you know what to
play the devil's advocate then cuz it
seems like we're all on the same side
mm-hmm since you mentioned that weddings
aren't essential and it's something that
you can choose to do to display your
love what did it mean more than if you
are doing that to spend more you mean
yet to spend more grand gesture I'm
doing this is how much I love this
person and sometimes a lot of people
because they're there's different love
languages you know but who are you doing
that for because if you're both on the
same page right the girl and the guy and
they both don't care about that no but
see what do they do that maybe that's
that's what that's why if they do then
do it like of course like that's if you
want to make her happy and she wants
that or vice versa right then you do it
right if you can afford you do it
because you want to make your partner
happy if you both don't care about it
who are you doing it for mm your family
members you could do it for them but
like really then should you be really
making them happy with your wedding just
throw a party but I mean I understand
what you're saying but what I'm saying
is like that's good our perspective yeah
if we're trying to understand somebody
who is actively trying to do a wedding
right right you know what I mean I mean
great they're doing it right now and I
think like you said you guys don't
really care about it that much but it's
something you've grew up wanting right
I'm sure you did too and I'm sure Dana
of course did yeah Dana grew up wanting
one I just never it wasn't like wasn't
even a thing it was just like like
people got married courthouse is like
that's like my family tradition so
having like a big wedding it's kind of a
surprise
and so she didn't want to respect your
tradition I'm just kidding Wow yeah like
I think it's just yeah I could see it
just people wanting to ball out I said
when people are the clubs and they just
buy a thousand dollar bottles for right
you know even though it's like 30 bucks
at the store yeah exactly
it's just like a cool something you
don't get to do suggest your sub ah yeah
it's a good reason to do something kind
of crazy
we've talked a lot about weddings and it
disgusts me I've been single for so long
but that's besides the point but are we
still going to be seeing crazy
Gregg cuz you kind of toned down a lot
over these past couple of years yeah and
uh this what is crazy Gregg well I just
want to ask about a story that happened
in Singapore if you want to share that
that's a lot of course I'll share that
your sheriff urilla oh you've never
talked about this what ever talked about
yeah all right but before we get into
this let's take a shishi break because
this is a long one this is a good one
yeah this is a crazy one this is gonna
make people look at you different yeah
even they may not marry and we're back
rhythm yeah we um that was a long break
what were we talk we we were a good
story
yeah in Singapore not nobody knows it
really publicly some people know if they
live in Singapore it's or they're at the
event yeah it's very well kept yes a
very sensitive sensitive story yeah
let's let's start this off with a little
so we hop what year was this when we
went to Singapore before I was in yeah
so what years that either 14 or 15 okay
so it was me Greg will and David David
was there
Arden was there as well there was just a
few of us yeah yeah we were doing like a
little mini like shows like we just do
more shows and stuff back then and then
we were in Singapore and I believe this
is before we actually did the show like
people take us out and stuff like that
we went to this club and it's at the top
of Marina Bay Sands which is like for
those of you that know ones like that
that ship looking thing and crazy rich
Asians you know the three towers yeah
has like a boat ending scene in crazy
rich Asians that their Jemma meets Harry
Shum Jr and then you're like do you
remember that
remember that I just do my work was a
dog I get what okay
anyway it's a very famous pitch at the
top of there it's called c'est la vie
I think the club we're at this club I
guess a day before performance and then
it goes down like so mind-blowing we had
a performance the next day mm-hmm he
didn't have a performance ready
two days two days from there right
that's true two days yep so we had a lot
of work to do still
mm-hmm and we wanted to get to sleep
early that night just how we can wake up
and you know get to get to making our
performance yes so we're trying to get
out of this club early and our hosts you
know brings out some about although for
drinks free drinks right and we're like
oh man this is gonna take forever
yep none of us wanted a drink and we
just kind of wanted to get out of there
quick but you know we didn't want to be
disrespectful disrespectful and the fact
that like you saw the prices of these
you know a bottle at a club is expensive
lot about a club there and Singapore is
so you like oh dude we came up on free
alcohol anyway we tried to finish it
really quickly which results in so I
took the bottle and I just like down the
whole thing basically like the whole
thing like a lot of it a lot of Daniel
and was a lot the night was it was a
slow night when we first got there at
least and so me and will we're dancers
where we you know we like to dance so we
were you know just dancing on the dance
floor after I drank the drink and we
were just dancing the night away and now
were you were you dancing being goofy or
no like we're actually dancing having
fun okay keep in mind this place was
kind of empty right it's kind of empty
because we got there kind of weird there
kind of early and then you know Oh as
we're trying to finish this bottle you
know Greg everyone's game or intoxicated
yeah right and they're just dancing like
in the open floor
like not that many people so people on
the side stuff like that and I mean I
don't know if it was like the Singapore
culture or whatever but it was kind of
like more wallflowers than we're used to
people were kind of not really enhancing
mood yeah so we were like me were like
oh come on dance you know let's have fun
and so we were we're getting the the
dance for kind of cracking you know
people were with random people
we're random people we were like dancing
with a bunch of people like we got we
got the place poppin I mean I'm sure the
club appreciated then he's like the guy
who went and got the party started
anyway like you could have gotten a job
that night basically man the party's
maybe yeah and they're not things got
kinda out of hand because I was trying
to get the whole place dancing the whole
place I literally I mean like everyone
dancing I wanted everyone to be off the
off the chairs off the walls and moving
and grooving and I I just pulled the
wrong person up these two gigantic dudes
who are like we had our table there was
like at some random other table not even
at 8:00 like we were like sitting down
they were like standing up next to this
table two big-ass dudes like I'm talking
like bodybuilders like think think you a
mountain you know from from what's a
game of Thrones but like shorter so that
same with almost like Brock Lesnar's
kind of thing with not as big as Brock
Lesnar but like think similar build got
it same build as Brock Lesnar but
smaller okay anyway these two I guess
they're a different weight lifts a who
knows what their their weight lifters it
looked like just two dudes who look like
they could be freaking
bodybuilders anyway Greg goes up to
these guys like he has to everybody else
and I don't know what happened from
there cuz I wasn't there either
yeah well you don't remember according
to other people who did see it you're
just doing the same thing like trying to
get them to dance or something and then
I don't know what happened what were you
taught yeah like I I had no idea what
happened from there because I don't know
what happened well the big dude punched
you in the face that's what happened
like so we got filled
over time what happened and supposedly I
was really adamant about getting these
two guys to come up and dance with us
uh-huh and supposedly one of them was
look Polynesian and I mean I'm neither
from New Zealand right yeah I think one
of them was uh yeah and I was like hey
are you Samoan or whatever I guess I was
just trying to you know connect with him
right here somali yeah and they were
just not having it I mean from what I
what we heard was that they probably
thought that we were you know like they
were just kind of homophobic maybe and
maybe they thought that we're getting
them to dance I was like trying to hit
on them or something and they just
weren't having it and I guess one of
them just knocked me out yeah straight
in the face and the crazy thing is again
I didn't see it firsthand but I'm being
told from people who did see it cuz it
was right next to us I just wasn't look
in that direction is that there was no
like like pushing like you know you know
when fights start shake happens people
gather and then you separate but there
was no like pushing away moment it was
just great was in this face I guess I'm
not like gonna degress it when they come
the school party whatever and then it's
just turn around punch straight in the
face there was like it was instantaneous
and then it was just like panic so what
happened was it was a just instant punch
right to my face only thing I remember
was I was I was on the ground wills side
of the story was that he punched me and
then instantly he was like in regret
mode because all of the Singapore not
Singapore what club security like
surrounded him and I was on the ground
and out you guys thought I was dead
pretty much hmm I will they picked me up
and I guess there was just blood
everywhere not to be too graphic but it
was literally pouring out of my face
blood everywhere and I just got my
braces on maybe about
maybe two or three months before that
and my teeth were loose because of the
braces well that's what the doctor told
me it's loose when they're moving you
know you guys lifted me up and I guess
two of my teeth were missing yep
the front not the front two but one of
the front tooth and then like the one
next to it yeah if you're watching these
two teeth
we're not gone gone gone did you ever
find them we spent like a long time
looking for them because we thought
maybe I could get it back in him you
know like we spent a long time looking
all over nobody could find it we thought
maybe he swallowed it but we it's not
funny it is traumatic for him I think in
the moment Greg is Luke I don't once
he's lucky but he does not realize the
scare we had to deal with we're in
another country yep right we don't I
didn't know at first what happened we
thought he wasn't responsive because he
was knocked out like cold um and we
thought he was dead
will was freaking know it was like
crying because he thought he was you
were legit dead David - he was so mad
he's like I'm gonna kill he was like I'm
gonna kill those guys and he was serious
I was he's like the funniest picture
first of all David is what like four
feet listen to this and those guys you
guys were saying or like oh he was big
he was like ready like he was gonna he
didn't he was in a rage I've never seen
that mad before anyway yes yeah you know
you have good friends when someone well
we talked about the size I was willing
to just rage out on someone double your
size my whole thing was trying to stay
calm because they came to me like ooh
did you see what like will was like in
tears I was like what what and then I
didn't know I didn't know what was going
on it was so loud I couldn't see
anything anyway
this is like a couple minutes after it
already or a minute after it already
happened when the commotion was going on
they told me what happened and David was
like I'm gonna kill it like he's gonna
kill these people and the whole thing
the whole time was this like just trying
to calm them too and and I don't know
where you were that
but you were with somebody was in heaven
yeah and then you came back down and
then the next thing I remember we were
um they were dead like security their
version of police who are which is so
funny because these huge guys are police
are small dude like like those guys
wanted to they no one could stop them
they're like huge and they're police
people were very tiny like our size
anyway they took statements I guess like
that dude did all that thing I'm sure
they took them in you went to the
hospital I was rushed to the hospital
I'm not in an ambulance and hmm I
believe you came with me I was with you
uh me and already went with you but yeah
first before we even got to the hospital
she woke up and I had you on my lap and
they had the club yeah at the club we
were like we're waiting because it was
like they were gonna they're taking
statements and stuff like that oh yeah
your lap like I was like you were like
like laying on my like like I don't know
how to just be laying on my lap you're
just like bleeding all over me like a
baby
kinda like you're just like knocked out
like you couldn't sit up straight and
you kept trying to you just kept falling
over anyway I don't think I even told
you this but no you just kept
apologizing and I was like dude it's
okay and you know I don't think he even
knew that your teeth were missing at
that point so my jobs I'm trying to not
say that to you because you're already
freaking out and then you were worried
about Dana's like no I'll talk to Dana
don't worry like I'll text you that
you're fine like you were so worried
about everything it was like how am I
gonna drink it to him that he had no
teeth though like if he's freaking out
about this how am I gonna tell him he
got no teeth it was crazy
and anyway yeah so we went to hospital
we just followed you okay I don't know
he didn't come with me in that no they
didn't didn't let so we went met
separately okay the hospital waited
hella long you're in the room and
they're just they just saw us in that's
when I woke up for ambulance no I woke
up at the hospital and that's when like
I consciously remember from there mm-hmm
he has remember that first episode of
Walking Dead when he wakes up in the
hospital and like he doesn't know where
he's at
and like everything is just foreign to
him that's kind of like what I woke up
that's terrifying
it was legit her she know you were still
in Singapore so I knew that I was in
Singapore but I didn't know like I felt
like I time-traveled mm-hmm and
something happened because the lady came
in and she she was talking to me in this
thick accent the thick Singaporean
accent and I mean I I could barely
understand her and the only thing I
could worry about was my hat because I
had hair back then and my hair was you
know was a mess you know like I was
balding and was a fool here did you know
and then that's when I realized I was
like man the hell's wrong with my tongue
like I feel like a metal bar in my mouth
uh-huh and like I was feeling around in
that metal bar that I was feeling was my
braces because my tongue was poking
through the whole of my mic gap or your
teeth or you know I was feeling them the
braces and I was feeling like the
bracket and or the bar the brace with
the brackets and they were loose mm-hmm
you know like that the toys at the
dentist's office were you know he can
spin the thing on the thing yeah yeah I
could do that with my braces brackets
and I was like wow that's weird and then
I think I had my phone and that's when I
popped open the the camera and I looked
at myself and that's when I that's when
it finally put it missing my tea did you
put it together though like what have
you know so I was like crap what
happened like I was like my memory was
so bad that I didn't even remember that
we were at the club the only thing I
could remember was you know well you
know us getting ready for the club yep
and then you know maybe us dancing but I
slowly like the doctors are coming in
checking up on me it really started to
hit me that it was serious when a
Singaporean police guy came in he was
like hello mr. Sonny time like how you
feeling
need to go over some you know some
question I have some questions for you
and you know that's why I'm like I was
freaking out because they were he was
asking me if I had any gang affiliation
wasn't like you know yeah if there was
if I had any like firearms or anything
on me I was like what are you talking
about
and then he told me the whole back sort
of what happened and then I was I was
caught up from there right but I checked
out my um you know my tent my doctor
stuff was all good I the the doctor said
that they couldn't find my teeth
supposedly I swallowed them and they
were you know they were saying if I made
bowel movements recently and if they saw
if I saw teeth in it that is like you
know to check there or whatever and then
I was like the after that I was released
and that's when you guys sent someone to
pick me up right we were there
ardan went in there that's right that's
right cuz they wouldn't let me in but
she somehow convinced them to let her in
that's right I think she lied honestly
to get in to see she was like family or
something she said that she was yeah one
of my family members she came in to talk
to me and and tell me you know all the
septa to tell them to the tell the
police to you know like be the author
what to update the police what happened
yeah and I don't remember any of that
I must have blacked out again I think so
but basically what happens was I got a
strike in Singapore how many strikes do
you get there I don't know but I know
here you get three strikes baseball
strike we work with cricket or all I
know is I have this Singaporean police
thing this is one strike
it's basically says you have a warning
blow of love but the police chief guy he
said that I have a strike don't mess
around here ever again yeah I don't
think like
like even though even if you were gay
like you were getting people to dance
like you don't that shouldn't give you a
string like that guy should have like
3/4 that if you get one he should have
at least 3 yeah you know what it was
like a 17 strike so don't worry dude 1
strikes not even that bad yeah you're 60
more I have no idea what happened to him
supposedly he got a way worse punishing
punishment than I did but I have no idea
so well you could have if you wanted to
take like in a lawsuit against him right
right there was a bunch yeah became not
worth it right cuz you have to go back
to Singapore something it was like if I
wanted to pursue it I would have had to
stay there and what it's out months and
months and I was just trying to you know
[Music]
talk about the because what yeah because
that's what funny part that's really
yeah that's right so that was the
beginning of the trip yeah that was like
the second day we were there and we had
a lot of stuff to do is one that next
day you were still separated from us we
didn't in you dread to make her perform
I was all right sorry I kept you again
but yeah you guys picked me up and I
came back to you guys yeah I was still
kind of dazed and confused I was still
kind of that walking dead
you know like mindset like that time or
whatever drunk and knocked out I I go to
the hotel to put you guys and you guys
are practicing you guys are practicing
the the routine
yeah and I'm like hey guys and you guys
are like oh hey Greg's here we can we
can put them back in now you guys didn't
address any of the crap that we we did
it's just without you knowing we did
yeah but like I was just like okay and
we just got to practice in you talk
nothing about what just happened we did
after we'd finished practice after we
did with Dean because you're making
jokes yeah and then you guys like I was
crazy night huh yeah you just kept
trying to whenever we were like look at
you you just smile and show us your no
teeth like are we going to start
laughing and like it was a weird eerie
feeling just like nothing was really
that bad to like that's what it felt
like to me except that I was missing
teeth so after after we got the routine
down we had to do these like we had to
do the performance obviously so we did
the performance and after that we have
like meet and greets yep where we had to
go to you know take pictures with fans
and all that so every fan that was take
pictures with me I'm known to smile
usually whenever I'm pretty happy yeah
I'm usually smiling
there's not one picture of me smiling in
that trick this tight-lipped yeah and I
mean I feel bad but at the same time it
that's where you know like I I came up
with this thing you know that the thumbs
up picture I always do that's because of
that Singapore now we know so that
awkward thing that I always do on my
Instagram that's because you don't have
teeth that's why I didn't have teeth and
then you got perfect teeth almost even
better than your original ones yeah they
did they did a really good job with
their clothes and ears no so I got
implants so they went when I got back
the dentist said yeah your jaw line is
jacked so they had to put in bone graft
was it Jack because of a punch
yeah I think when oh damn when they when
I when I got punched like a chunk of my
my jaw line got you know taken out with
it and yeah they had to put in some new
new bone to be able to support some
metal implants so that way they can
connect new teeth too so I have to fake
teeth and they look like the best - in
your mouth lesson one kids if you lose
your teeth you can worst-case scenario
if you can afford it
yeah back there's all
was a chance there's always a chance to
get your teeth back always a chance and
then you'll have a great story with
friends that you can share and then also
the lesson is don't worry about
finishing your free alcohol yeah yes and
also if you do finish your free alcohol
don't dance with big people yeah so he's
basically lucky that only two teeth left
his mouth and his soul didn't because
shocking that you didn't get some kind
of brain damage maybe you did who knows
it was pretty it was pretty um it was
pretty intense he was over abit i watch
you if i watch MMA yeah and like nah
clothes don't normally last that long
when they're knocked out mmm but then he
also had alcohol in his system really
drunk yeah and you didn't remember
anything this is a good commercial for
like PSA for like not getting wasted
well if you think about it you're lucky
you drank a lot cuz then you already had
anesthesiology like going through your
body sure that's my guess so yeah i
always think about half cup half full
positive they're optimistic there it is
oh the real optimistic thing is like
crime in singapore is like punished by
like lashings like the real bad crimes
yeah it's not it's not like crime here
like you honestly like i died
you're lucky you just got a strike even
though it wasn't your fault yeah but
like crime there is and i'm speaking
just from Singaporeans telling me like
you get you can get lashings first I
don't know what has lashings are there
like whips like you're getting wit they
have is that capital punishment I
believe so
they have acts like I think they still
do hangings like yeah I could be wrong
but Singaporeans you guys can let me
know like that's not in the comments the
worst thing you've heard about no but
you can get like a legit like wit and
like people this is another story that's
that I was told from my Singaporean is
like this guy did something and they
whipped him I think like once or twice
and it's so painful because they put
something on the on the whip yeah
it slices your back open and so painful
that he passed out rather than
continuing they waited till he woke back
Wow to continue the rest of his lashings
oh so it's like that's like but if you
think about and and Singapore is one of
the safest places in the world
that's why with that kind of power I
know why I know so if like I know it
sounds inhumane right that's the
argument even for what people are you
hear right for the death penalty but
don't you think if our punishments were
things like that you you would think
twice about a lot of things oh for sure
but like how do you argue that because
you know people will say like that's so
inhumane you know I'm saying it would
definitely kill comedy yes yes well the
thing is we wouldn't change our laws
right if we kept the laws of thing just
the punishments mmm
don't you think that would work well
this the argument is right for the death
penalty is like what if you find out
later that guy was actually innocent
then you murdered someone who was
innocent Yeah right but then like we
still have the death penalty so like it
could still happen so a Singapore we're
coming out next year
I actually would love to go back to
Singapore
I have a great time there yeah I know I
do don't know that Singapore has been
great safe for us great yeah I love it
there it's just that got was even from
Singapore so I don't think he was oh he
wasn't like from a New Zealanders to
just rowdy Americans causing trouble you
like their country he must have had what
makes sense that he would have a roid
rage because who turned around and just
hit someone without like pushing them
away for like you would have if that
happened there would have been a crowd
you wouldn't have gotten punished you
probably would have fell to the ground
very far away escorted out yeah you
would have got escorted out probably and
him yeah and then we would have been
fine but like well let's just say this
Greg doesn't even know that he might
have pushed him in like you know I do
everybody else that was there said the
same thing yeah but a lot of times you
know like in in in panic and stuff no we
were trying to figure out why would he
do that that and then and then we were
like okay well let's think about like
this if some random dude small dude was
coming up to you like all drunk and
dancing he you would think he's trying
to hit on you or you were thinking like
he's you know whatever we were trying to
give reasons cuz it didn't make sense
why he would have that reaction I don't
know I would have punch me maybe you
said something racist
anyway that was the UH that was a long
story that's a funny story
it's out there now yeah it is out there
but I'm gonna be looking at me
differently I don't think so your teeth
are very nice now actually it was a show
you show you I bet you the comments are
gonna be like Greg hope your teeth get
soon buddy
well now said it was a good one yeah man
we sold your story man hey it was worth
it
plus it's barely your story that's
morning like cancel culture thing I
don't have to worry about anymore I
think you think of it as a bad thing
because you got that strike but really
you didn't do anything other than drink
too much that's true you didn't commit a
crime though any crime you committed was
you didn't commit a crime victim blaming
that's a thing yeah I don't know anyway
um I think that's been like an hour got
really into that story I was fine it's a
good story that's why anyway this is fun
I know we'd have a guess but hopefully
you guys were still entertained thanks
Greg for being here and I guess you can
follow us at off the pill on Twitter at
off the pill podcast on Instagram leave
us your questions what you want to see
next go ahead and bother people to get
them on our show get us sponsors because
we could use it yeah um because we
haven't had one we haven't done one in a
while huh we have not she probably lost
like two that less than ten but still
more than five anyway thank you guys for
watching end it like how we usually end
it by breathing into the mic in three
two one
it would have been great if Greg blew
into the mic it was just whistling like
cut dinners two three