we're probably the most viewed youtubers
that no one's ever heard of right now
last 30 days we got 250 million views
it's crazy I always thought that the
whole flatter thing was just people like
trolling I thought I thought that too
until I left you know but yeah people
actually believe that you're lucky you
missed the idea age now we had to we
used to I mean have you seen her I dare
use that we've done podcasts no no just
uh did we do a show where we take fan
comments and we do just stares with
people with guests you know
well it was and then we did main channel
stuff but it was just like uh it got
crazy so we had to like we found that we
had to chill out a little because it was
like the only way to top yourself is do
something crazy right it's like pranking
right I have to go above yes that's not
people have seen it so I started getting
crazy the things we were doing and then
we get we got Community Guidelines oh
you got flagged for a lot of I was just
sayin before you know you're in Japan in
a forest and yeah well I wasn't that bad
it was like so like we had one where
it's like was the Meryl twins they were
that there was - what was it there drink
lemon juice out of a condom yeah they
were down for that huh they'd be their
dad yeah and there that was there so
yeah so we were checking in with that
and we're like okay so you know
everybody's cool with this like you guys
are you actually can do it you don't
have to you have to do it and yeah but
they want to win so they did it like oh
but at the time when we made it they
weren't as like anal about that kind of
stuff
okay just said anal deal now we're all
well we didn't collapse and none of this
is going in no week it's a it's a late
clap it was interesting well regardless
I'm gonna do the intro again anyway
welcome back to another episode of off
the pill podcast today we have a very
special guest mr. Chad wild clay thanks
for having me
and we got pakka little moderate owing
and the bigger applause you always give
yourself a bigger applause he tries to
know I feel like you know I'm just I'm
that good it's so loud I can't it's
deafening little I can hear my worst
mistakes was saying hey I think you
should be the one to control that
instead of me just taking advantage of
it and you know actually caring about
the levels the thing is too if you took
advantage of it yeah nor ADHD you'd be
like that is true all the time
it is tribulus you're saying nothing the
whole time we're just talking about this
right before you got here how like he
needs to be watching the levels and
stuff and like when he starts getting
excited he'll start shouting with you
know I mean if our guest is shouting -
I'm just like oh I need to get over
there rather than contribute to the
conversation I'm like trying to figure
out how I'm gonna make this song your
sound guy I know I don't know I think
that would be fun I'll see if I can
bring out that the energy in you get you
real well you actually are energetic
person Thanks it's very true yeah okay
well I'm just for people who don't know
why don't you tell people what you do
wait I'll say that you are a youtuber
definitely yes I consider myself a
youtuber um didn't you two prefer a long
time 2010 not as long as you I'll stay a
long time fun fact I started my youtube
channel four months before you did
did you really heard some 2006 oh like
you all like you signed up yeah yeah
yeah got it
so you are actually on YouTube longer
I'm old same thing yeah thank you and V
told me that you had told your mom like
oh yeah these kids are coming over and
then your mom said like I don't know if
I said kids okay but I didn't know you
were we were like oh sweet yeah I mean
you guys both look young and you're both
on the channel you envy yeah oh she's
your wife yes she is yeah and you guys
do kind of like a I mean I donno if
that's the only thing but I know you do
a lot of like a well you have a series
with a bunch of hackers you have a
hacker issue yeah we got a major hacker
if you hackers are trying to take over
YouTube right now they all I
sure it's not it's a constant threat
it's bad we need we need some more
ninjas who drink ninja milk now you help
us we did not pay him he's just we're
just very fortunate excited about ninja
milk guys this is my first time having
it I'm fully wired right now well you
are kinda always worried but I
appreciate the plug
shameless plug maybe we should take it
away from him yeah just watch the levels
well I mean so that's on your you have
multiple channels right yeah yeah and in
the main channel you just ache more to
kind of that you know I don't I don't
know how in detail people actually get
to know you the person I'm pretty pretty
decent i guess you know like a more
energized version of me right right of
course you know just like any youtube
channel yeah I mean just like most
people don't realize but that's the
thing too like I was I was just saying
like when I first arted doing these
people were like thought I was mad yeah
why I said yeah but it's just like I've
nobody nobody's really like that all of
yeah you can I know unless you're on
drugs
you could really like that on drugs or
on ninja milk yeah Locke was pretty god
I'm gonna bring him every week every
week gonna be here but uh do you I mean
how in-depth do you go I don't know
talking about like I don't know I don't
want to give anything away but you think
people know you're here yeah okay so you
live in wait do they know that oh yeah
they know I live in Las Vegas yeah okay
okay yeah Las Vegas that's right yeah no
you moved here when I used to live in
Minnesota that's where I grew up right
and then we moved to LA for three years
and then we moved here nine months ago
okay
okay at the advice of Ryan Higa right
here well I I don't you asked me and I
did I did my pitch yeah a little bit it
was a good pitch I don't remember
exactly what I said but I was I remember
saying something along the lines of so
so Chad DM me and he was like you were
what was the thought process you were
thinking about moving out here yeah we
were looking in Los Angeles for a long
time for a house right and man the real
estate market there like it's ridiculous
the house like right next to where we
lived it was like kind of run-down
2-bedroom I was 2-bedroom 1-bath
$800,000
crazy oh my gosh you know what you get
for that here yeah three-story house
gigantic three-story house with a pool
and an elevator house house be liking it
out here she I think she really likes it
really yeah we're you know we're we're
not the type people who need to like go
out and party all the time and I go to
all these events and stuff which is you
know if you're that type person la is
good for you and we're very much like
now let's stay home watch a movie or
whatever or just let's just work all day
well to be fair you can do that in Vegas
as well yes you can you can that's true
you might you do this trip so if you
want to do fun stuff yeah I mean people
don't realize all the times but like
Vegas is here Vegas you picture the
strip but where we are where you guys
are
yeah you know but the majority of Vegas
is not the strip right very chill yeah I
people have been like wait people live
in Las Vegas I know it's like yeah yeah
and I'm trying to I'm still trying to
sell them what is your page what is your
page to try and bring I should just put
the DM know just alright I'll recap the
deal okay what I remember is there you
go
real number one real estate prices
incredibly good you get a great house
for a good price number two taxes state
has zero percent income tax compared to
California top end is 13.3% so you're
saving a lot of money see when you say
numbers like that it's not so much but I
wouldn't have said that there's a point
something percent I know I didn't put
that in the details ero is better than
anything else and and no traffic yep
no well well except for on the strip and
when we get the readers Sunday's might
be okay but we are getting the Raiders
Oh getting our own NFL team we have a
hockey team that was in the Stanley Cup
yeah we and that's big in Minnesota
yes hockey I think also uh now we have a
WNBA team really do okay and then I
think we also have a baseball team I
don't I don't think they're in the
majors though it's uh I know what fields
being built yeah where's it being Bill I
think I think it might be done okay
I could be wrong I've been hearing about
this this Las Vegas getting a basketball
team for years though and I think that's
gonna be huge when that happens if it
happens but we were supposed to get the
Kings Sacramento Kings but we never did
but hopefully we get an expansion team
like the go tonight
and that might be quite you into any
other sports or you know I
yeah I did play basketball in like early
high school but now you know Ryan has
invited me to basketball once or twice
yeah cuz you're like seven foot eight
yeah you true like I'm pretty rusty I'm
kind of nervous to play good so I look
you're being like if you played in high
school like I did we didn't play in high
school
okay and we play in that league yeah so
just based on fundamentals and your
height yeah you would probably be MVP
all right all the stuff that you do in
your videos like it's a lot of like no
anyway let's talk more about cuz let's
get back into you you know we wanna know
more about you yeah so you live in Vegas
tell us about Vegas I'm just go ahead go
ahead but uh like with your content it's
a little bit more like kids content and
you have to gear it towards a younger
audience but with the guidelines that
YouTube has and because your stuff is a
lot of like fighting hackers and there's
a lot of like not weapons but gadgets
gadgets you can't say weapon don't say
weapon you've had to adjust accordingly
so maybe you want to discuss the
transition you know since the YouTube
algorithm is changed over these years
yeah good question yeah it just keeps
changing and if you don't keep up you're
in trouble yeah we've definitely like
when we first started on YouTube back in
2010 we were doing a lot of parodies
growing up I thought I was gonna be a
famous musician and that was my plan
that's my goal
played guitar and piano and all that
stuff and was in bands all through high
school and all that and YouTube was kind
of my creative outlet for doing music so
I was doing parodies I loved Weird Al
Yankovic yeah man so we used to do a lot
of parodies it was they were very like
kind of adult ish a little bit no
swearing or anything but very like
Saturday Night Live humour and just we
did that for many years never really
went crazy actually well the videos
would get like you know a million views
sometimes two million views but never
really built a huge fan base because I
think that style of content it's very
like you're in the mirror yet you're
there for the video not for the
personality essentially yeah and so we
moved we eventually moved to Los Angeles
once we hit like a hundred thousand
subscribers let's just give this a shot
we're not we're not really making any
money but if we did this full-time let's
let's just see what
Bin's at the time v was running she
owned her own curves fitness center for
women she sold it I co-owned a software
company still do so but I retired from
the day to day work on that and my
partner's took over the kind of
operations of that I came out here he
came out here and we just kind of
started experimenting with different
types of content we did some roasts of
youtubers i roasted ryan that's one of
the first ones I seen yeah I liked it
and I was annoyed too right yes yeah Bob
juice yeah for sure
those were fun did that for a while I
just kept experimenting
it was very influenced and inspired by
Mathias in fact I think I think you you
remember Mathias he was on it yeah yeah
I always said from the when the moment I
saw him was like I was telling him to
cuz he was on the same season oh cool
and I was like this guy's gonna be yeah
this guy well he one saw that this guy's
gonna be huge and it did yeah yeah so
yeah when we first moved to LA he was
the first person I had up at the time
yet we were at like a hundred thousand
subscribers he was at three hundred
thousand and I was like hey man you
wanna can I take you out to dinner and
just pick your brain talk YouTube
he was like yeah let's do it I thought
that was really cool of him to do that
and just became really good friends with
him and his wife and he always
encouraged me to experiment try
different things and he did - he used to
do parodies and songs in kept
experimenting till he found his niche so
it was very inspired by that tried a lot
of different things and then I think
once we decided you know let's try I was
like let's do something that I would
love when I was like 10 years old right
and from that thought process came you
know when I was 10 I loved the Teenage
Mutant Ninja Turtles so I'm gonna buy
all the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
ninja gadgets and test them out on fruit
chop them up and so doesn't all that me
and that video did really well like well
let's do some more of this and so we did
like 5 video game weapons and we would
choose different video games in
different movies test them out that
series did really real great so that's
kind of really what started to blow us
up on YouTube and kind of evolved from
there and I've probably got off topic of
your question yeah like Ryan could have
gone into that but the first time he
tried using weapons uh well I mean I
and they've advanced too well yeah I
tried to cut through fruit as well oh
okay um but it was more for it was
actually a skit I wasn't actually trying
to cut through it and it was recreating
fruit ninja in real life yeah yeah and
yeah I I tried to cut through a
watermelon and the watermelon hit the
sword the sword hit my nose and that's
why this scar here yeah and that was on
Mythbusters cuz they were like talking
about like was it fruit ninja I don't
know I didn't watch it wasn't yeah
and what were they saying on Mythbusters
I don't even remember the episode but
they were making fun of me
probably is like the 88 who like got cut
by a sword because of a Waterman trying
to cut a watermelon and they're
especially like this guy's in Asian and
he doesn't even know how to use a weapon
even worse Asian American definitely a
myth but he gotta be math I never I
would never
I got a C but yeah so I mean continue
talking about you know you had to adapt
to it
yeah these things so yeah I just kind of
kept adapting and we still do you know
we still like pay very close attention
to our analytics we're very yeah very
analytical we have a team of five people
who do our YouTube videos with and I
guess I like to say we're probably the
most viewed youtubers that no one's ever
heard of we right now last 30 days we
got 250 million views that's crazy
and yeah did your videos I mean I don't
always see them but when I see them and
I go check out your channel it's like oh
one day ago three minutes like cutie-pie
numbers in his prime yeah
not that he's not trying but it was like
you know cuz you guys post often how
often I've right now five days a week
yeah like five days a week and then like
every videos like Oh
million five million two million you
know it's pretty crazy yeah it's really
crazy and I'm surprised that like I mean
like you said like it's weird that you
get you're getting all this attention
but it's like in the realm I guess of
like talking about bigger youtubers that
are blowing up right it's all about like
who's making the news like with the
drama news drama yeah so if you guys had
drama then then really holy crap these
guys have a lot of views right yeah for
sure yeah right so all you gotta do is
attack a famous youtuber with you ninja
gadgets you're in there someone who's
been on YouTube for a really
long time what do you think now you got
to go for somebody who's in the new yeah
not somebody here elephant's irrelevant
yeah you gotta go for somebody who's
like like like fighting yeah
oh she do a boxing match and then Midway
do the boxing match bring out your
gadgets mm-hmm and then kill just get
disqualified
it'll be demonetised but people will be
talking about that's true like that
crazy youtuber yeah gadgets yeah yeah so
you know we're thinking like since you
are very analytical I mean I'm sure even
noticed the trends and those things
working obviously that's not your thing
that's not our thing either so yeah yeah
but what if we were to evolve it because
it's always about thinking ahead right
so what if we were to take that fighting
this whole drama scene to the next level
right and what if it is ninja battles
ninja battles yeah ninja battle royale
you tell me that would not be clickable
with a bunch of youtube I mean you'd
have to get them to do it but I mean
come on already kind of did that they
did yeah well we are mr. beast did that
whole battle royale with a bunch of yeah
but that would be even harder to film if
you're gonna do it in darkness and at
night and then you have loud people
going welcome over there and you're
gonna go and Dave Mack them in the face
it will do it Mortal Kombat style like
not necessarily in the night jury you
know you know arena
realm type things like little torches
all over the place exactly for our for
our dudes like yeah with spikes with
spikes see now we're thinking tell me
that would not be I mean granted we'd
have to I'm trying I'm really trying to
make a version of it but that's a lot of
paperwork that's a lot of paper well but
yeah that's the future though guys if
you want that give this video a thumbs
up yeah and then you know what if you
know how to say uh I've never done this
before but I saw recently Anthony did
like oh if it gets so many likes I would
do something yeah but his video reached
that crazy amount of things I don't know
what he has to do but it's something
ridiculous and I don't want to do that
oh okay it works so go to jail yeah yes
once like if he gets enough 40,000 like
yeah it was on a BTS video so it's just
we didn't think it's gonna get that many
it did I said puck was going to jail so
he's still has to go to jail I have to
run a tank through a house because of
thumbs up maybe we haven't done that yet
actual attain a real tank so what one of
my favorite videos we've ever done was
we went to Minnesota they have tanks you
can drive army tanks and we I actually
in Minnesota yeah I didn't know that I
mean it's Minnesota they don't have much
else to do yeah exactly we just have
open fields and army tanks that's all we
have my job likings
yeah basketball football and hockey
right yes a lot of they're just not
having the best but yeah I rode I've
drove an army tank over two bands two
cars and crushed them
that's really fun sounds like if this
video gets and it's just a number that
never hit if this video gets 192
thousand thumbs up I'll run this through
a house any case the because the tank
place was like we have a special package
it's only like eighty thousand dollars
you can buy a trailer house type thing
you could run the tank through it I was
like oh they offer it so maybe I'll I
didn't think whatever the return the
investment there is yeah I mean you're
getting into mr. B's territory now you
need to have a sponsor yeah that's
that's pretty crazy yeah but I mean you
gotta do it yeah good yeah we're still
planning it we will do it sometime you
know for sure gotta do it yeah I'm gonna
go to jail eventually too right yeah
it's either you are real reason for real
yeah it's just a matter of time a real
crime yeah so that's how we don't make
those bets anymore because we I don't
want to not do what we're supposed to be
doing yeah SH we're gonna be honest yeah
yeah so the trust of your audience is
everything when you're ready dude jail
but giving back to your I guess your
regular life in a life um I'm curious
because you post so much I mean I know a
lot of youtubers do this but a lot of
people also backup their content you you
I mean you moved to Vegas but you
haven't really gotten you were saying
you haven't gotten to do much Vegas
things cuz you're always working yeah
yeah so what's your schedule been like
we've pretty much we start every day
like 9:00 a.m. and we usually don't end
till 9:00 p.m.
like this past Tuesday we went from 8
a.m. to 10 p.m. I was a long filming day
that's exhausting so yeah it's true
we're trying to get more people right
now because I feel really bad for our
employees they're working their butts
off oh you guys are you guys here's our
hiring yeah yeah yeah yes you know
anybody good yeah got a little YouTube
experience yeah a little bit of you
trust me I don't know anyone I don't
know anyone good here 12-hour day the
last time I worked a twelve-hour month
I'm looking for someone real honest and
straightforward yeah so it's been it's
been pretty crazy for you guys and I
mean how many like obviously this this
whole schedule how long has this been
going on like this almost every day I
mean it's pretty much every day yeah
yeah every day you know we do kind of
take weekends off but you know V and I
still work a little bit though because
actually our employees do - they do
editing and stuff though the weekends
are kind of supposed to be off but like
Memorial Day we didn't even know it was
a vacation wait like last minute oh
shoot it's holiday we text messaged
everybody like hey if you want to take
the day off
you can everyone came in anyway and just
worked a normal day yeah they're like we
know nobody else here yeah you're our
only friends that's true that's true
we met one of them yeah one didn't you
guys Melvin he plays basketball we're
still trying to convince we're just
trying to get him but I just asked
because I think that is I mean it's it's
commendable but do you think it's a
long-term thing because I feel like
that's that sustained a burnt out for
sure that songs that sound mean it's
good because you're taking advantage of
the situation yeah just you should yeah
yeah but that is that sounds like I mean
most I mean I don't think anyone can do
that no I consistently that sounds
exhausting yeah it is for sure yeah
we're we're trying to figure out how to
how to get down to normal all right
we'll get there yeah bring it on and
bringing on more people helps yes I hope
so you know they'll be they'll be a
period where it probably has requires
more work because yeah I trained them in
but mm-hmm okay yeah cool unless you
unless you you know find someone who
already has some YouTube experience and
I would be horrible for your channel
yeah
yeah because I'm I like cuss a lot I'm
very not family-friendly yeah you would
hear the kids would not be people talk
trash in the comments about me I go at
them respond he's a responder iris first
responder he definitely responded
instead of giving first aid I just hurt
him more I make it worse so the parents
would be like you can't watch these
channels anymore yeah exactly yeah but
news all in terms of all your I guess
going back to talking about your content
and you know what you guys have been
producing it's a lot of it has to do
with being hacked right or be all
hackers hackers is that is that like any
true stories in terms of like have you
really been hacked in other I mean if
you think about my own issues that's
what also work you worked at a software
company right yeah I did yeah
I mean it's legit thing so are you I've
actually if you look at my social blade
you'll see a month where I had negative
99 million views because I had so many
videos taken down
really those were copyright strikes but
that's another story but yeah actually
you might get this to you like every day
I get like a Google Alert like did you
just request a password reset your
Google password this was always people
trying to get YouTube right it's crazy
yeah so actual hackers yeah actual
hackers you gotta watch out you guys
watch your back there's there in Las
Vegas well back in the I mean I've
already been hacked a few times this is
before I really knew because it wasn't
really an issue up until like a like
five years ago maybe
well my Instagram was one the first
thing to get house and I I didn't really
care too much at the time Instagram was
still big it was huge I just didn't I
don't normally like posting a lot but I
my Instagram got hacked twice actually
and they ran some kind of like I don't
know a script or something that
basically blocks all the people that
I've that that follow me I like that in
there's some kind of algorithm they did
that people who follow me that have
interacted with me like the most active
people basically and it was like
thousands and I only recently walked
them yeah they blocked they made my
account blocked them
mmm all the heart like the really
hardcore ones yeah and it was a thousand
I know a thousand thousands of people
and I finally finished unblocking
everybody but there's no I tried to
reach out to Instagram and everybody and
they there's no way I just wasn't
getting any help
there's no way to just do unblocked all
sounds familiar yeah well you've had
those issues I mean with not without
getting help from different yeah I
recently had a video that said please
contact your partner manager about this
and I was like they say why you don't
have a it's because there's there's a
manual review of process now yeah yeah
and they said that my video head blood
and gore in it which none of my videos
do so the manual reviewer was like this
video contains violence blood and gore
like no it doesn't assume it's a
violence and I said if you disagree with
this please contact your partner manager
is like I don't have a partner manager
so wait you don't have a partner man you
know that is incredible I don't think I
have one either
well that is predictable no but no but
let's bureau that's that's pretty
ridiculous I mean the mound that you've
been on for a while you've been posting
consistently I'm not saying Papa doesn't
deserve one you should have one too
you deserve one too yes but it is
ridiculous that you don't have one and
we should I mean that's a simple we
should get you a partner manager it just
it just said even someone just someone
there to be like hey this is not right
yeah the thing that people don't realize
is like yes you can anyone can attack a
video like copyright strike it whatever
it is yeah and even if it's not true you
can get it you can fight it you'll win
and they'll switch it but it takes time
and all that time that that's happening
somebody else is benefiting yeah and
that's the ridiculous part so I mean you
should it's kind of crazy to me that you
don't like there's not many other people
there's a lot of youtubers to get views
but not the same a trainer ship is you
you know like I think that's kind of its
kind of ridiculous yeah sure you know I
used to have one uh-huh but usually they
pass you on to somebody else yeah that's
what I heard but no yeah we didn't get
passed on that is very interesting to me
okay well you know what we will come
back after so I thought I saw hacker no
I'm just kidding we'll be we'll be back
we'll be back after this quick shishi
break to talk a little bit more and
we're gonna get you a partner manager
right now I'm your partner manager now
all right well that sucks to be you
I hate Taco Bell that's my thing are we
filming right now yeah still clap
anywhere I love talk about yeah I was
trying to like get sponsored by Taco
Bell for quite a while I remember your
saying that house like smoothing with
the bigwigs at a Taco Bell in fact but
they they do know who I am and they have
invited me to many things mm-hmm they
invited me to the Taco Bell Thanksgiving
dinner right where they invite like 30
youtubers and some other people it's
really cool cuz all all the like YouTube
chefs are there mm-hmm
that sounds kind of funny to say YouTube
chef yeah but like these are like like
legit chefs you know and they're like
goal is to make a Thanksgiving dinner
but each item each like the turkey and
the stuffing and all this has to use one
Taco Bell ingredient so like the for
example they had like the honey glazed
ham but instead of honey glazed it was
Baja blast glaze wow it was so good it
was really good Bob glasses dope it is
my picture with Turkey little ham ham
ham that changes everything difference a
big turkey it's two different things
no no but I go to Taco Bell so much that
so when I moved from Minnesota to
California the Taco Bell employee got me
a going-away present no I'm gonna miss
you so much
yeah yeah so I went there like every day
damn talk about yeah well I mean I I
tried to pitch a show up like I guess
it's like a documentary it was it was
like based off of supersize me but it
was it was like Taco Bell but my goal
was to prove that and this is like five
years ago my goal was to prove that you
could eat talked about every day three
times a day yeah and still lose weight
yeah and I still and I still think I
could do it I think it's very possible
I'm not trying to say and recently they
released an article that talked about
one of the healthiest food fast food
chains Wow um I feel really good about
what well I did they also put a
disclaimer and say it doesn't mean it's
healthy it's the healthiest yes fast
gene or one of the healthiest pearboys
yes but this is before that article this
is like years ago when I wanted to do
that but they didn't want to do it so
weird like hey I want to make your
product look really good right now just
help me out but nah we're gonna stick
with all the what myth it might have
been worth like he's gonna get really
fat like Oh what campaign are we trying
to push right now yeah you know yeah
timings everything
I actually did something when they first
release Baja blast but it never released
but they still paid me for it that's
nice but it was yeah I don't remember
why it didn't go through with the
campaign but it's cuz they saw Carl's
jr. and they're like I think that's why
they hit me up for it was wrong that
time oh really
yeah yeah a long time ago a bunch of us
got hit up for to do a cartoon or thing
like it was like me Smosh like a whole
bunch of us Dave days a bunch of people
yeah remember and we all did it and we
all made our own videos and people just
hated us for like a while guys they paid
me so much I don't care what you say no
but I was I was hurt at the time I was
like man I never got this much hate
before and I was like I'm not gonna do
this ever again and little did they know
this is brought to you by name thank you
guys so much for watching Ninja milcom
or yourself case and I talking about
nostalgic youtubers yeah another
nostalgic thing Pokemon actually just
made an announcement for a new game you
guys know about Pokemon go right yeah
they've announced a game called Pokemon
sleep this is let me get a joke on a
sleeping app to fall asleep - no it's uh
it's my idol games kind of yeah where it
wants you to sleep more and it's like
the more you sleep like you can catch
pokemon or get like better things and
it's it's kind of dreams dude it's
really nice that was
yeah you know how much sound effect for
a drum hit but don't surprise we GUI
there you go that's kind of quiet but
okay alright and this is so that's right
afterwards it'll be really cool
yeah be way funnier so they announced
that a Pokemon study will be turning
sleeping into entertainment much in the
same way that Pokemon go turned walking
into entertain could you try to make
everyone healthy that sounds like a
nightmare okay I mean that's really good
it was in the new I didn't hear anything
about that is that recent it was a
Tuesday it was on Tuesday did you play
any of those regular Pokemon I did
collaborate with the Pokemon go song kid
do you remember him Misha
speaking of retro youtubers although it
was like four years ago
Misha famous kid from Czechoslovakia
really okay well it was it was great but
you didn't play the game I did not know
well we kind of played it a little bit
but I got over it pretty quick cuz it
required walking in the house yeah no
but so many people I actually did it now
I'm wondering like this makes actually
surprisingly this makes more sense
because people actually play games for
that reason like there's Idol games
where you don't need to play yeah to
play the game true and that's huge right
now so if it's anything like that it
could work better than Pokemon go
actually yeah I mean it's like
interesting that you can but I want to
know how they're gonna turn
entertainment or sleep into
entertainment yeah I don't get that
either yeah they're gonna hook wires up
to your head while you're sleeping and
read your dreams it's just a it's a ruse
to gather information find out more
about you there how do you know how much
do you know about conspiracies do you
look into those I kind of like
conspiracies I don't believe in them I
think they're really fun same me - yeah
- cool sometimes when it's really
creative it's like man
that's such a stretch but you put in the
effort yeah like it takes talent to
piece together all these things right I
could fit together and what's the most
recent conspiracy that you've looked
into um gosh I kind of like gosh done
recently I never got into the Flat Earth
stuff I know it's kind of more recent I
saw that I watched the documentary on
Netflix I was actually pretty interest
off ladders thing was just people like
trolling I thought I thought that - I
loved it
yeah people actually believe that see
when you look it up though and you watch
like you know you it you when you say
flat-earthers you picture a certain kind
of person you're like okay that person
is ridiculous this is so out of the
realm of possibility
but then when you have these people who
like oh you actually sound like
articulate and you yeah it's just like I
can see why some like most people would
fall for that well I can see the
arguments are there like if you ever
really get into it okay not that I'm not
saying I believe that are this flat but
the arguments are really energy yeah if
you like it with the entertainment
factor yeah I think you'll like it's
like oh wow they put a lot of thought
into this they have a little dance yeah
they're studying like flight patterns
and like why certain planes fly a
certain way instead of like they eat the
quicker route yeah okay and then also
certain things like oh like the degrees
of Earth and how like oh I shouldn't be
able to see this far into the distance
but I do okay it's it's actually is like
oh you see like the alright earth I'm a
flat Chester okay
I can't develop muscles but good yeah
you're something else there I mean that
- but I should keep it family-friendly
yeah but uh yeah basically the whole
thing it it shows in the beginning of
the documentary like a lot of stuff that
makes you kind of like oh I can see like
how this possibly make sense and you
start to like slowly question all that
you believe yeah and and then I guess in
the latter part of it the scientists
come in and they're like explaining like
yeah but the thing too is like the
scientists they're surgeons the thing I
like about is the certain scientist and
it's not necessarily a flat or
documentary talks about more when you
are educated in
in a certain way of thinking and it's
been proven and stuff don't always be so
quick to look down on others yeah you
know these people who are flat earthers
what they said was view them as people
who could have been potential scientists
but we're just miss educated you know
because they're doing their own form of
learning and they're aspiring you know
right but so what you can do is you can
mentor them so don't be so quick to like
look down on them these people are
actually like like you said articulate
smart they're doing their own research
they're finding out things yeah it's not
easy to make up I mean to come up with
that stuff there believe it and even
have their findings are true even though
they can be disproved a lot of it to
even come up with that is like amazing -
yeah but in the same way and I guess the
argument is and again I'm not defending
it I'm just saying you know one of the
arguments are that obviously the weight
the reason why we are already feeling a
certain way the moment we say the earth
is flat and everybody's like okay dude
is because from the moment were born you
know and we're brought up in a world
they show us globes they show us on TV
everything you've ever seen and learned
in school everything you were taught was
you know a certain way of course you're
gonna think it's read Atrios the moment
like I mean if everybody told us the
earth was flat and we had pictures of
like in space of a flat earth right our
whole lives and all of a sudden someone
was like you know what I think it's a
globe I think it's round like this is
ridiculous people make any sense like it
we would be think about that like it
could be something not that I'm saying
that I believe that because I don't know
but there is a point something percent
chance that flat earthers are completely
right now but there's never a hundred
percent there's no 100% of anything yeah
science doesn't even believe in how
you're sitting in the matrix right now
it could be yep what is it flat or is it
a round matrix look at the source code
sure well then you'd have to hack into
the system yeah and that's why we bring
it back to hackers hackers you're a
hacker I'm not a hacker oh well when you
play basketball you might be Oh
hacking jack yeah a little deep
different big big just talking about
that but uh Oh for the flatter thing I
wasn't so much looking at it in terms of
like believing the flattered but what I
liked about it it's something that we
can uh create an analogy
to a lot of other things is when we have
a certain way of thinking sometimes
we're so quick to judge others because
they don't think how we think where it's
like oh you know you believe in Flat
Earth meant like you're dumb yeah you're
not you're not here trying to explain it
you're not here trying to like show a
new perspective you have this elitist
mentality where you wanna just like brag
over others yeah yeah and I want to
transition that into another thing where
the state of Missouri is now looking to
shut down their last abortion clinic oh
gosh
yeah there mm-hmm and following Alabama
I was gonna say is in this Alabama it's
no Georgie Alabama's voted on it all
right
and so but the state of Missouri is
looking to shut down there.last you guys
are like trying to get demonetized right
now what's the biggest things in news
just like what what is your thoughts how
can i how can I say gwei into this uh uh
Ryan's like you're not getting paid and
I'm like neither are you so I'm just
going into that because you know a lot
of people are like oh pro-life
pro-choice oh you don't get this you're
dumb and it's just like that whole opera
right not necessarily asking maybe what
your stance is on it maybe you if you
want to go into that but it's more just
like uh do you like what are your
thoughts more so on like the whole
elitist mentality cuz that'sthat's huge
everywhere yeah I mean with all that
stuff I love to have my mind changed I
always try to keep my mind open like I
do believe certain things but if someone
wants to try to convince me otherwise
I'm like totally down and I'm definitely
willing to like have my mind changed I
in fact I find it super enjoyable it's
like dang I never thought of that before
I would have known that maybe I think a
little differently so I think if that's
just a good mindset to have same for
everything I agree with that I think for
uh the thing for us though a lot of
youtubers who are low-level drama is
they're very open minded yeah yeah what
do you mean it's hard to get it'll drama
when you don't have like a super hard
opinion on yeah right right right
yeah because you're so fluid with things
cuz you're willing to be swayed you're
willing to have listened to the other
side right yeah maybe I'm wrong about
this yeah just to have that thought you
know yeah I mean I always have that
thought process for most things but I've
found that even that can be called out
on
because then you know giving people the
benefit of the doubt a lot of times like
even if you question the the the
majority a lot of times though they'll
find ways to mark you to as like on the
wrong side like they'll call you an
apologist right like people people were
shooting what's a good example like wait
like when the whole like when the
president wanted to talk to I think when
Obama said yeah I'd be willing to talk
to Iran or wherever how how could you
even listen to them right yeah exactly
and then people would just jump on you
and and if you have opinions about
something else too like for example like
the Logan Paul situation right and how
everybody was completely against him and
everybody gets how you know wrong it is
right I was there thinking like well I
don't think he's the devil
like I think he definitely didn't
realize it was gonna be you know he
wasn't he wasn't trying to I don't think
he was trying to offend any but I think
he was just think about himself and like
how can I make this interesting but
people were treating it like he's the
he's the devil
like he's literally like has no respect
for people who are you know but if I
were to come on say that it's like Oh
Ryan's being an apologist like yeah but
I'm not I'm just saying like I think
people are taking this a little far like
hoping he dies you know like right it's
a little ridiculous what's it's really
fun right now for people to like jump on
the bandwagon of anger I don't know it's
canceled culture because in a way it's
it's a you get to end someone without
directly doing it right and so you and
you can feel like superior like yeah and
again so you know back to the elite ease
alleviated mentality yeah yeah so I you
know and I think it's gonna get to the
point where like a lot of people want
others to be cancelled yeah
from my perspective I think is because
they feel like oh I've done bad things
you know but if I can make other people
who have done equally or worse things
right like get cancelled and stuff then
it makes me feel better yeah you know
because now I'm doing a good thing I'm
doing a holy thing so maybe it cancels
out my fault my sins or my past
yeah gonna make yourself feel better
right yeah also thing a lot of people
just genuinely believe they're right and
they just think this is the right thing
for like I mean not saying that they're
not but that they believe this is right
and the majority agrees with me so if
you think otherwise you're just wrong
all right I'm gonna pose a question now
okay so are you asking for a friend
how good to someone have to be to get
away with a crime well speaking from
experience in the YouTube world in the
YouTube world thank you I think you
answered it like you just have to be
popular like you just have to be
populating that it's not even Talent
really while some people might consider
it talent but if the more popular you
are the more you can get away with but
Logan was super popular you know yeah
but for what reasons people never saw
him as that way but I mean he's still
making videos like it might not be where
he was at but how about PewDiePie cuz
he's still like where he's exactly yeah
yep and it that's talent in itself to
get yourself out of those situations
like PewDiePie knew what he liked he
knew how to turn everything again you
know he was smart enough to be like hey
these articles said this let me prove
them wrong like he's he knew that's a
talent to do that Chloe didn't have that
skill yeah and that whole situation with
PDA I think he gained way more of a
loyal following from that and I think he
learned from it and I just saw I could
see what his mindset was it and he stuck
with that mentality he's like hey ie
it's me versus them miiverse this person
me versety series it's always like if I
can get other people on my side and make
it give myself an enemy it helps build
that because you give yourself a
competitor you know and that's it is
what it is and that's how the whole
drama scene works too that's why it
builds people when it's someone for
someone and that's just I mean that's
just how that's all it's always been
yeah right like the equal amount of subs
James Charles lost
Tatia games yeah exactly
yeah t-series just hit a hundred million
saw that channel ever crazy did you ever
think that it would get to those numbers
back in the day back in the day meaning
like 2008-2009 everybody was that like a
million yeah at the most I would say and
I know that when you were the number one
most subbed YouTube channel
there was a very for
Tom I was it was for like less than a
week oh okay because it was like I
passed I think it was Smosh or and then
Fred Fred asked me like a week I was
like well I was there for a little bit I
was like who's Fred yeah and then I
think it was like what
I passed Fred again or something and
then Ray came
oh great william johnson then he do you
want to just quit and then Smosh passed
him or something like that and then
PewDiePie the rise of PewDiePie and he's
just been killing it that's what the
algorithm changed for the first time
yeah it was based on my gaming long
content something like that and see but
like like and I've been in this mindset
of like hey I want to get back I would
be like man PewDiePie's content is it's
not real like I would've started
something so ever been my chambers his
team yeah but I just didn't want do that
and then in the back you boy drama hey
Felix do we got each other exactly and
we would have both grieve and faster but
he didn't need that I mean he was
already milk in the system and he killed
it you know the thing I respect about
him because at first I was like I didn't
like his content I was like this is not
entertaining to me to watch somebody it
wasn't normal to watch them play games
right at the time - yeah and the thing I
respect about him is that he he realized
like okay this is working but I'm gonna
evolve and he changed his content to
what he does not like he actually
evolved he didn't just stick with the
one thing and just keep doing it over
and over cuz it works and that's when I
realized okay he's actually smart he's
not just like doing something he gets
what he's doing very few youtubers can
do that yeah sure some people get lucky
they make it they realize oh this works
I'm gonna latch on to it but they don't
evolve right and then the algorithm
eventually changes and then they exactly
him yep so I look like PewDiePie if he
never slept why because his eyes are
smaller my eyes are smaller yeah no
really I mean I don't I think you're
just being racist
I think you're just a racist so you just
think all white people look the same
yeah nah not true there's definitely
there's definitely different doesn't
look anything like Felix because you
can't go yeah
actually can you grow like a full beard
no I can't
really know I've never been able to same
I just shaved today because I knew I was
gonna see Paco and he just makes fun of
me do the use and girl here for me and
just like patches whatever all right
well let's get into Twitter questions
okay because I actually kind of see
something that kind of wraps up a lot of
what we talked about you know you uh
someone says oh it's from Mickey five
Luke yeah yeah but they said you're the
master at always tweaking your content
to keep your channel fresh if the
YouTube algorithm wasn't a thing and you
were guaranteed to get millions of views
per video what type of content would you
produce and I think I want to see from
both of you guys yes I think for Ryan
what he would produce is just him
sleeping ah the past go ahead okay um I
mean if the algorithm wasn't a thing I
probably would have never been forced to
like venture away from making parodies
because news I really yeah really loved
doing it it's a really great creative
outlet I used to like recreate all the
music and like play all the instruments
and and just really enjoyed creating the
music and writing the lyrics and all
that was really fun about regionals I
didn't I did do originals like with my
band I used to have like a ska punk band
back I old-school but yeah I you know
wasn't a thing I probably would still be
doing that but because you love you love
making music I do love it but I think
the bigger thing is I won't have been
forced to try new things right I really
I really do love what I'm doing now and
in fact I think I'm having more fun now
then I would if I was still doing
parodies right now I just really love
this whole like series thing and just
kind of video 2 video kind of continues
and it just keeps going and builds it's
a really cool story so I love what I'm
doing now more than back then but yeah I
think it was the algorithm that kind of
forced me to like adapt and change and
try things and so you'll see what would
work on YouTube yeah how about you right
what would you be doing um I mean I
think I would be
going back to making the videos that I
was making but taking a longer because I
would do it I mean we would we would
rush a lot of stuff like even the videos
people think are like oh that was so
great that was so you know we put a lot
of time and take like three weeks a
month whatever it's all it always could
be better
yeah and I'm never there's only a few
times I was very satisfied with how it
turned out and it wasn't completely cuz
it wasn't completely what I thought it's
gonna be in my head but I mean it's
gotta be realistic and also to YouTube
so you got to post some time but if I
didn't have to worry about that then
yeah I would be on that alright I'm just
gonna make a dope you no matter how long
it takes exactly I'm just gonna make
something crazy hasn't been done
regardless of the time and the right
know viewership falling whatever it is I
would love to do that but I couldn't I
kind of forgot about that demand I mean
I'm doing it now doing five videos a
week but yeah when we did the parodies
we used to spend we actually used to
release like one video every two months
right right and just like put a lot of
effort to perfection get it really good
and yeah that was a thing so app kind of
after the parodies the next thing that I
have evolved into was I created a series
called crap and the goal with it was
like I'm gonna release a video every
week because what the parodies just
couldn't do it yeah just with just like
me and V it does it couldn't do it once
a week so yeah I'm gonna create a series
called crap because the videos are gonna
be crap compare it to so funny compared
to what they used to be and the crap was
an acronym for comments raps and
parodies so I would take like the
viewers comments and kind of weave it
into a parody song with like very low
production value right so yeah yep
filler yeah yeah yeah I think um had you
even stuck to doing those like parodies
though I think like you said you would
have got I think you would've got bored
eventually of it and you probably would
evolved it anyway like you probably
would have moved on to what you're doing
probably or something different yeah
yeah anything you no matter how much you
love doing it you you actually want to
try something different maybe your
current series will become a musical
musical that's why I don't want doing
musical at all a ninja musical I like
doing music stuff but um yeah that's not
that's not my gift
[Laughter]
what about you wanted what would you be
doing if it weren't the algorithm if it
were the algorithm Al's getting millions
of views man I wanna I just wanna do
videos with Ryan man you know cuz I'm
hanging out with him Wow yeah I mean
podcasts I like doing these because I
can just be myself put millions of views
yeah that's what I'm saying we could
still do this and get me if we got
millions of views that's like basically
Joe Rogan right yeah you just do a
podcast you just hang out with your
friends and you just get millions of
views and you know like do a three for
our podcast I know the thing is we could
do that is just a Joe so captivate like
he's quick on his feet yeah I think part
of it is cuz he's always hi
I mean he is he's super smart yeah and
the people he brings on are like okay
it's just like the smartest scientist in
the world like yet what's his name
Neil deGrasse Tyson on and that was such
an interesting one to me because it goes
back to what we were talking about
before about like people who are just I
mean he's a scientist so obvious he has
to say certain things and I found it
interesting
he said yeah this is a hundred percent
there's absolutely no way that we'd let
we didn't land on the moon ever stop
talking about something about when
landing and I was like what but I always
wondered it I don't know if it's true
but like as a scientist isn't it wrong
to say that anything is a hundred
percent yeah like Albert Einstein was
like really confident that this this
whole quantum mechanics thing wasn't a
thing right but he was wrong exactly so
confident he could have said 100 with
that like we were saying he's they're
just they're just cocky cocky Letus
elitists yeah there's still that point
something 1% chance you know you never
know you never know so flat or earthers
um which is gonna be our new viewership
yep we're getting them all to this video
these guys but we're getting near the
end of this episode so that's our other
ones you know what was your first job oh
okay
dying about I kind of like readjusted it
my first job I was 14 years old I got a
job at the local groceries
or back boy has a bag boy hey everybody
a bag boy like at a young age that's
where you start because that's the
lowest here right yeah it's like the
lowest I really like you like you just
put the groceries in the bag carrying
out to their cars - yeah you carried it
oh yeah we carried out to their cars
yeah I mean he's not our age he's a
little bit older a little bit you know
and then there used to be these 80 pound
bags of salt that people would buy for
their 80 pounds it's the salt for like
your water yeah yeah
and I'm like 14 years old no muscles
skinny still and I'm like still Sam just
like now man that was difficult and then
co-workers including my older brother
was there they would laugh at me and
make fun of me like you stick out like a
sore thumb
you look so and I did I was 14 years old
that 14 year old kid shouldn't be like
wearing a shirt and tie and an apron and
I don't know you're a fellow flat
Chester then like me yeah flat Chester
block but you said you're you're
brooklet your brother worked there to my
older brother worked there as well and
he was in he's not tall and skinny he's
he's tall and muscular and he always
looked older for his age so he found
pretty good no now you're winning cuz
you look younger yeah so you retain the
young the young look in the young
viewership and a last question from
Gloria which is what is your favorite TV
show you like and I guess something that
I wanted to add in is like is there a TV
show from like your younger years or
maybe now that kind of inspires you to
do what you do yeah well you said Ninja
Turtles yeah for inspiring now Ninja
Turtles for sure was probably the
biggest inspiration for what I'm doing
now and just take a lot of inspiration
from them and as far as little TV shows
I don't watch TV much lately I want to I
can't want to catch up like everyone's
like you got to watch Game of Thrones
I'm like oh man I don't want to get
sucked into that it's gonna be too
time-consuming I don't time for that but
a lot of time the last show I had
watched that really loved was Breaking
Bad I suppose who knows amazing yeah
when it was still releasing lie like
that's how long I think it was probably
right after they actually know it I
started watching me like during their
last season so I I kind of got to watch
them all binge style a little bit
without waiting too long
else one fun nice okay well I mean I
guess at some point I was always
wondering - for your for your series and
your channel do you plan to I mean I
guess it is very like based towards
children like younger people but do you
plan to like I mean your core fan base
eventually they're gonna grow up yeah
you want to keep it and keep bringing
the younger ones and you viewership and
replenish the other ones get up or do
you want to evolve the content and go
maybe a little bit edgier well I always
say they keep making new kids so do keep
making education so you don't need to
know where the with Alabama putting yeah
right you really want us to give you
monetize huh you want to keep going back
to that I know yo Mike that's a really
good question right yeah I think let's
go back then let's go back to Chad yeah
yeah I don't know proud I think
eventually it probably will slowly age
up a little bit kind of like superheroes
have kind of aged up recently yeah you
know like I was always a huge spider-man
fan let's the other thing let's maybe
inspirational to me used to watch
spider-man cartoons and you know used to
be like Oh spider-man's for
six-year-olds or eight-year-olds but now
it's like in your 20s 30s yeah you
should enjoy those movies great jokes
and it's still clean yeah
and that's that's a challenge but yeah
it's still like it still works
yep yeah okay so yeah well to be to be
seen I guess yeah we'll see what happens
I guess but it seems like that has been
our time and do you have any plugs that
you'd like to milk in the world make
sure to buy it where can they buy it
ninja milk calm jamilka also make sure
you check out Chad Chad wild clay Chad
wild clay but then you got the actual
name right yes Chad wild and oh yeah
that was another question too but I we
already asked you but yet that's his
real name
that's my real name I believe that
including us yeah I thought that I was
like maybe that up ya know I wasn't sure
Chad was your real name or clay was your
real why a lot of people mix those up
yeah or what all three all three it's
awesome noun like a cowboy like name
they get south
you know definitely not you sound like
you grow corn or fun yes I do check out
Chad wild clay that's it you're lucky
you got the actual that sounds made up
but he it's his real name and is that's
his channel yeah you can follow us at at
off the pill podcast on instagram at off
the pill on Twitter when are we gonna
fix learn like know what you it's
because it's always it's the same it's
they're taken and we reached out and
they won't give it to us so I wanted to
get it so it's the same one both but
yeah anyway thank you guys for watching
another off the pill podcast thanks for
being here yeah thanks for having me I
don't know if you know but this is how
we end it we usually just count to three
and then we breathe into the mic good
leverage all right and in three two one
[Music]
mmm smells great in here