hey guys so if you've been subscribed to
my channel for a while you know that i
make a lot of commercial
or infomercial spoons and the reason for
that is because i think so many of these
commercials are just so
irritating i mean they're already taking
you away from whatever it is you're
watching and most of the time they're
not even entertaining commercials are a
bunch of lies the only time they tell
the truth is at the very end of a
commercial when they're talking really
fast and you can't even understand them
anyway kind of like what i'm doing right
now i guess for example you know like at
the end of a toy commercial for kids
they're always like
you mentioned in this commercial
satisfaction not guaranteed batteries
not included or like medicine
commercials they always have those quick
disclaimers that have all the side
effects of the medicine at the very end
and sometimes it's even worse than what
the medicine is supposed to cure
you could bring this opportunity against
hiv stds or pimps if you experience
nausea heartburn and headaches vomiting
dizziness loss of sight diarrhea
gonorrhea sangria or even death contact
your doctor because he
may not be right for you and we are not
liable batteries not included but more
than anything that i hate about
commercials is probably the subliminal
messaging in it you know like in every
shampoo commercial they use these
beautiful
perfect girls with flawless hair using
their products because they want to put
in the back of your head that if you use
their product you'll end up looking like
that i mean come on would you buy a
shampoo if the commercial look like this
hairball essences batteries not included
probably i'd probably still get that one
but you get the point most commercials
are just not honest because this is what
commercials would really look like if
they were
laughs
what do you think he's on this time i
don't know shrooms
pepsis
he drinks beer not because it tastes
good but because all his friends do he's
quick to make decisions
that he would later regret he wakes up
like a new person
that has a headache and nausea all day
he is the most average man in the world
i don't always drink beer but when i do
i prefer not to
stay sober my friends
a delicious hot juicy 75 grams of fat
less than 875 calories fries dripping
with oil and probably some sweat from
the guy cooking them in a 32 ounce cup
of soda that could be enough for a
family in africa you'll feel so full
you won't even want to move thanks to
the all-new angus cheddar cheese
big whopper maca meal burger we know
he'll be back soon
because we forgot to give you half your
order
that's copyrighted
with nearly 10 miles per gallon a
whopping 145 different horsepowers
equipped with a neighborhood waking
exhaust system and a working engine
light that will come on for no reason
all backed by our one month warranty
that you're going to need the all-new
used 2004 three-wheel drive four-door
h-150 with a hemi roid
by getta just get a car
hello i'm the spokesperson for gecko
insurance or should i say spokes gecko
i have nothing to do with car insurance
a comedy for that matter in fact i think
the only reason why i'm here is because
the comedy name is similar to gekko
seems quite lazy if you ask me gekko in
15 minutes you could spend 15 percent
more time than we did writing this
commercial
do you need cash now are you running low
on funds well thanks to cash to gold
you can now send us your gold
do it cash to gold we're a real business
i'm sorry charlie i can't do this one
man just read the lines
i'm not going to do this one this is not
cool damn voiceover
don't you point it over charlie won't
you dare point at me don't come over
don't you point it
out that [ __ ] charlie oh
charlie
what's great about the iphone you can do
this and this
and this and the and
you can hold on
hey oh oh
introducing the new iphone it's okay if
you drop it because the next one's
probably coming out a month after you
get this one
with bouncy's new rip in half there's
now 100 more sheets per row because you
can now take a half sheet instead of a
full one
because when you're at your worst bouncy
is like a purse
you know because it you know because it
holds things and it picks stuff up and
charlie this one doesn't make sense
either man
all right so maybe i exaggerated some of
these anyway thank you guys so much for
watching i know i haven't done one of
these
type of rants or like off the pill type
of things you know where i get really
upset about something and talk about it
really fast i
i just hate to see people getting
tricked i hate when people are not
honest and commercials are just the
worst thing i could ever think of
bobbleheads new shirts
different colors that's not my merch
do it