ah hey guys so you probably already
heard all the hype from Pokemon buh-bye
now unless you've been living under a
Geodude it's literally everywhere
YouTube Facebook Twitter Instagram and
that's just online turn off your
computer they're talking about it on TV
if you go outside to a park or grocery
store or anything public there's
probably people playing there too I mean
there's been so much hype around pokemon
gold that I've been starting to see it
in places that it's not
[Music]
what don't act like you wouldn't catch
her - I mean she's still rares better
than catching another Taylor Swift again
so there is around here and no before
you Swift these jump to conclusions I'm
not saying Taylor Swift as a Rattata
because she looks like a wrath Rattata
ratata rock taka it's a vine meme she's
a Rattata because ratandas are
everywhere and even if you don't want to
see or hear another one you're still
going to and also because Rattata can
learn the ability Swift and just like
Taylor Swift it might not be the best
attack but it's still gonna be a hit
because Swift doesn't miss ok enough
Pokemon jargon jargon I don't know why I
use that word I've never used that word
before it sounds like a Pokemon door guy
again Jon Jon see this is exactly what
I'm talking about
it is the 90s again and it is all about
Pokemon it has taken over the world
again and this time around it's not
something to be ashamed of I mean when I
play Pokemon and collective Pokemon
cards as a kid I had to do it like
almost in secret because back then like
Pokemon with me make you a nerd it made
you uncoil and the chairs well we now
live in a day and age we're playing
Pokemon does not make you up well I mean
we're all still nerds but there's more
of us now Pokemon goal has once again
made Pokemon the biggest thing in the
world right now and no one should be
happier about it than me I've always
been a super Pokemon fan I mean I played
all the games from the beginning pokemon
red blue green yellow or pokemon snap
with one pin ball I watched every
episode of Pokemon that was on TV I even
had the Pokemon soundtrack so that I
could memorize all the songs not a part
of my life I'm particularly proud of but
you need to know how big of a Pokemon
fan I am in order to truly understand me
when I say this I'm not trying to be a
hater or a Down or anything
I can't be the only one who absolutely
loves Pokemon that doesn't love Pokemon
go you're just jumping oh I forgot to
pin the black bars and now the text
pretty accurate look I don't hit the
game but in my honest opinion I was a
little disappointed especially after all
the commercials they put on that - you
know to get all of everybody excited
about it and trust me I had normal
expectations I wasn't expecting the game
to look like the commercial just an
unrealistic expectation well maybe not I
mean there's virtual reality now but to
go from this to this it's a little
misleading I still think it's a great
idea and I know this game took like 10
or 20 years to get done but I think it
still wasn't ready to be released the
way I see it it's not even really a
Pokemon game it's like Google Maps
styled with a Pokemon it's pokemons
lease like Pokemon get what am i singing
that did not make sense how do I
describe this better in 2016
Oh Pokemon goal is basically Google Maps
mixed with Foursquare with a Pokemon
snapchat filter on it
BAM with no chill lint
savage FINA turnt up Oh
see I'm still hip but you know what it's
not even the look about Pokemon glow
that bothers me I can get past that it's
the fact that half the time you can't
even sign into the game because the
servers are down or they're experiencing
difficulties and maybe it's just me but
even when you can sign in when you're
playing the game it just freezes
randomly especially for some reason when
you finally catch something something
that you spent a lot of time looking for
and it kills your battery faster than
any game I've ever played before if I
could go on for a long time but I didn't
make this video to hate on pokemon gold
in fact I actually hope that the game
becomes more successful so that they can
put some money into it and then I can
finally play and who knows the game is
so popular and they're making so much
money that they're probably already
working on a second version that looks
like the commercials so for all of you
who haven't given a shot yet especially
if you're someone who loves Pokemon like
me don't have high expectations and it's
still a fun game I mean when you can
actually play it just don't expect it to
look like the commercials so one expect
it to be what we all wish for as kids
Pokemon in the real world because it's
not quite there yet in the
time that I was actually waiting for the
Pokemon goes servers to come back I
whipped something together that would
help you with that here's a more honest
commercial of what Pokemon dole is
really like in the form of the same show
that we all grew up with and loved
watching I mean except for the kids who
didn't even know that show existed fam
let savage know chill oh my god I'm not
gonna put that in yes I am
[Music]
[Applause]
on the last episode of Pokemon girl Ryan
finally spotted the rarest of pokémon
Mewtwo with only seconds to react Ryan
finally threw his pokeball net
I'm not even joking look what popped up
our servers are humbled by your
incredible response we are working to
resolve this issue please try again soon
I love this game