hi your child um like this Apple dumbass
well thanks to walk on funny we make
your dumb ass fun what you know but Eve
me well can want our satisfied customer
vegetable confining it's not longer not
know how to not read makes the hook on
Banach I can now read at a five grade
level before Hogan phonic I used to look
like this now I look like this
Oh God Bonnie taught me to read but then
I bought the expansion hooked on chronic
and then I forgot see how happy our
customer are that could be you but wait
if you also hook on phonic you also get
fresh order of dog number forty dollar
value but we're giving it to you for
just 13 easy payments of $14.99 and if
you call in the next two and a half
seconds you get all of this for free too
late you slope I okay