Tim anybody wanna play house
you
all right we need to get him to a
hospital
no yipping house written diagnose him
okay but he's actually really sick and
that's why we're gonna help you you're
not a doctor you can't diagnose him
Shawn hurry up he's sick you know Shawn
are you okay
he's so fat Marja heartburn indigestion
upset stomach diarrhea go yay
pepto-bismol yeah he didn't have any of
these symptoms well then what do you
have well
you have the seizures that's boring Sean
what did you have before the seizures
yes you're singing okay and how was he
singing badly okay we have an exit the
phone damn what else
well abnormalities of his nervous system
or an imbalance in metabolic system
could cause a seizure which means when
he has an imbalance he says to shake
uncontrollably go on which means when he
gets sick he starts to do this go on
Neverland
he's naughty okay although I may agree
with you that's probably something you
don't want to say out loud no ugly as in
uranium guy satanically nasty yeast
infection come on if he had ugly he
would also have done he isn't my house
what the hell are you guys talking about
he is ugly dumbass he has uranium guys
atomic and lasting East infection this
do you really am a stickler by acetone
cysts onyx syndrome there we think you
have your ring and recipe
yeah we think ya do it John
ha oh good you're up
we think you have your main invest on
the Gnostic East invention mr. Yuri
pneumatically my hesitancy itani
syndrome so that's right you're an ugly
tone deaf dumb ass just like Helga who's
Helga Helga
Helga patenella the other girl we make
videos with who the hell is that
I was Tim not not held after all these
years
Oh what does it mean means he doesn't
have a big dumb ass
well he does but you know it's not the
problem is that they're the same person
Shawn see that one more time that one
more time
no say that again that again no see what
you said before that one more time
nevermind ok it's likely the same person
because they are he has Miley Cyrus had
a man kind of syndrome my symptoms fit
they both wear wigs when they perform
the both bone death well you're missing
one little detail what he has seizures
today
well let's go play rock band I do I call
drums wait I'm still alive no you're not
Tiguan going on doctor you can't dive
into jean hurry up you're not a doctor
just like a [ __ ] [ __ ]
good you're all giving your uranium st
good you think i'm duranium good you're
up
we think you have uranium best Tomica
gnostic yeast infection history ringing
left if you by asking systemic syndrome
OB dumbass for sure oh yeah and your can
go