oh hello there and welcome to how to be
the perfect boyfriend where you'll learn
skills and techniques to be the best
boyfriend you can be now if you're a
girl watching this you'll probably just
be doing this the whole time
nodding along to the genius that are
these tips you're welcome
first tip be humble no girl wants a
cocky guy nor do they want to [ __ ] a guy
that's timid and afraid like a chicken
so be confident but stay humble like me
the humblest guy I know in humbles
Milltown be mature the perfect boyfriend
more like the perfect man's friend
because girls don't want a little boy
they want a man it's time to mature grow
up the next time you hear a fart joke
you hold that laughing he manages a
natural process of life not that funny
so because mature men don't laugh at far
they've matured way past that all the
way to shorts he's supported supporting
people is easy but the perfect boyfriend
supports everything she says and does to
the very fullest the new girl at work is
so irritating again I just want to kill
her sometimes yes do that murder her ass
late I'll start planning out the route I
already got the gun right here and the
men we can head together around 9 and
this actually wants murder exactly don't
murder anyone because that would be
crazy
crazy the most sane person I know he
stopped took the words right out of my
mouth stopping right now gosh sometimes
you can be such an idiot dumbest idiot
around I hate me ahh Oh clothes that's
how my mouth is gonna be from now oh my
god God Church prayer love it somebody
please shoot me already cute and
meaningful nickname when you're in a
relationship for a while you give each
other nicknames and the last thing you
want to do is the perfect boyfriend it's
give her a nickname that's generic and
has no meaning at all never call your
girlfriend baby because that would make
you a pedophile don't ever call her
angel because she
and please whatever you do never call
your girlfriend big not only is that
overused but she's not a small part of
the ocean where the land curves inward
this perfect boyfriend will come up with
the perfect nickname something cute
something unique something like hey Ryan
hello fat boy my favorite Ice Cream
Sandwich look at dirty honk excuse me I
don't know what that hole is doing
inside has all muddled over it hmm oh
wow I didn't even see you come in here
you little [ __ ] what did you just call
me cute female dog yes you wanna give me
mom didn't see you come in here there
pedophile baby exact opposites in order
to be the perfect boyfriend you have to
be attractive to your girl and they do
say that opposites attract both
scientists and people who say that say
that so although you want to be a
supportive boyfriend you also have to be
the exact opposite of her in every
single way I like about thick what do
you think I hate that outfit really
maybe I should change that well then I
think you shouldn't change then but you
just said you hated it didn't just say I
love doing you just saying the opposite
of everything I'm saying not saying the
same as nothing you said okay oh I like
the color white where's the color black
I love oranges apples are my favorite I
love to watch a big bang there hello
friend I love how I make your mother
you're not even a part of this and How I
Met Your Mother had the worst any other
you are a part of this and how I Met
Your Mother
yeah it had the worst ending ever mm-hmm
get along with her friends the famous
poets known only as the Spice Girls once
said if you want to be my lover you
gotta get with my friends I get with my
friend with my friend my friend so date
all her friends stay away from the
period when it comes to girls no cut cut
the music this was not even a joke when
it comes to a girl's time of the month
for your own safety just stay away from
the topic don't talk about it don't
mention it and especially did I make any
jokes that has anything to do with their
time of the month period and last but
not least comfort her when she's down no
matter how perfect of a boyfriend you
are there's gonna be times when your
girl is feeling down or sad or maybe
she's just on her periodic table of
elements I see that was a test good job
I passed
dazzle was it there's gonna be sad time
in order to be the perfect boyfriend yes
to be
comforter and know exactly what to say
even in the toughest situations Yugi
what's wrong my grandfather just passed
so sorry hey he's in a better place now
hey G what's wrong my dog ran away I
can't find him I'm so sorry
hey he's in a better place now hey G
what's wrong nothing I'm about to start
my period and Sarah used my last tampon
oh I'm so sorry
today it's in a better place don't you
say it what you can't keep saying the
same thing over and over again I'm just
trying to comfort you not comforting I
just don't understand why just for once
you can't be like any other normal
boyfriend and comfort me like Ryan
where'd you better place now Ryan what
where are you told you already I'm in a
better place less yelling over here what
the heck you can't just leave a note and
leave mid-conversation what no the note
right here
[Music]
[Applause]
are you freaking kidding me
[Music]
welcome gee the better place hey my dog
and Grandpa you're back - that must mean
where's my tampons I'm sorry what my
tampons it's that time of the month I
need it remember oh no if you don't have
those you have to leave right this
entire place is completely white you
have to leave are you making a period
joke oh oh no no I wasn't what thing you
never do look I was just yeah it's
perfectly fine he can stay we could use
a little more color in here and that is
grilled I mean that is not true
because it's a perfect period applying
for girl I mean time period I'm not
period commas so Joyce Marcellus when I
met PMS whole bloody hell just calm down
okay
it's just a natural process of life and
that's the story kids if all I should
have met your mother oh no that's not
funny when you do it that's just gross
you're gross thank God something for
wine cars are getting worse than worse