hey guys so I know right off the bat is
it off the bat or off the bat what does
it even mean who's back and what bat are
we talking like Batman Batman is back so
I know right off that men's back that a
lot of you guys are gonna be like it's
such an image of our topic how to hide
your fart well let's just be real for a
second this is a real issue that we've
all had to deal with before and if
you've never had to deal with hiding
your forest before you either never
leave the house or you've never had a
bad meal in your life or you just have
really strong Buttle muscles but almost
flat whole muscles but a lotta muscles
lot of muscles I'm not gonna act like
I'm the most mature person in the world
it's clearly I'm not if I were mature I
probably wouldn't have repeated the
phrase butter muscles like 20 times
off-camera just cuz it sounded funny lot
of muscles that's like a new word butter
muscles it's not even butter whole
months it's just bottle muscles so
nobody else would get that but you guys
won't know what I'm talking about bottle
muscles I actually think it's even more
immature that people judge other people
as being immature just we're doing
something that's completely natural
that's like being judged for sneezing
can't control if a sneeze comes or goes
it just happened and that should be the
same per part farts are basically butt
sneezes and they shouldn't be looked
down on they should be blessed bless you
thanks Oh
unfortunately this is just not the world
we live in today we live in a place
where farts are considered rude
inappropriate immature well I've
compiled tips and techniques for all of
you to help survive this cruel fart
hating world that will keep fighting for
the freedom of farts but until that day
comes yours how to hide your fart
dedicated to all you people out there
with weak buttom muscles it's it's a
good word okay I'm a little immature
fine so in order to hide a fart you must
first understand the signs of a forge
when you make a fart sound with your
mouth it's created because your lips are
pressed together and air is trying to
escape your mouth it goes the same for
your butt but if you were to open your
lips and do the same thing there's
almost no sound at all same thing
applies to your butt that's why this
first one is called the cheek spreader
this technique is perfect for when
you're in class or any place that you're
sitting down all you have to do while
you're sitting down is put all your
weight on one butt cheek slide to the
other side to create that opening and
before you know it silent farts the
gentleman now one of the most terrible
times to be gassy is when you're on a
date not that I go on a lot of dates I
it's actually been a really long time
probably because I make videos about
farts anyway the gentleman is the
perfect technique for when you're on a
date all you have to do is open the door
letter and close
and as you're walking to your side of
the car yes I was I was saying about my
mom a cheap sink so we all know what a
lip-synced it's when somebody sinks up
their lips to a song to pretend like
they're singing but in this scenario
instead of lips you have cheeks if
you're in a scenario where you have to
relieve some gas just listen for
something around that you can cheek sink
too sometimes there might not be that
many sounds but you just have to listen
carefully for example if you're in
elevators think of your farts to the
beat they're raising the volume so I
don't know if you guys remember but I
had a technique like this a long time
ago in a previous video and basically
this strategy is if there's no other
sounds around you to cheek sing to take
matters into your own hands and just
make something louder than your fart the
other night I went on the worst date
ever
hey did I ever tell you guys that I have
a really good impression of a racecar
I mean that was okay racecar the vacuum
name says it all just suck it up see you
later man and what's that man I forgot
my are you all right blue the delay
this one's common sense when the herds
ready to move you just delete a little
bit we should probably uh yeah pretty
soon so the biggest fan
oh my god I'm your biggest fan here can
I think this new around the corner that
it was really bad we you know yeah yeah
it's car broke down out there isn't I
was late that's crazy
the happy birthday man I got you beats
by dre happy birthday man I got you a
present here try it on right now flower
hey snow this bro
shoot I hey man your shoes are untied
the Airbender and last but not least the
oldest trick in the book the blame this
is for when all the previous methods
mentioned above fails all you have to do
blame it on someone else did you just
fart uh you know I thought I heard that
too it who was that who did that there's
no one else around but us you know it
probably just came from the TV or
something I mean I thought when we sat
down I felt the couch move when I sat
down like the leg of the chair and the
floor must have created like a vibration
they made a weird sound or couches
bolted to the floor that's weird
that your family would vote then you
know what I mean make sure it wasn't you
then I know it wasn't me then we know it
must have been your damn dog I was
farting and yeah that was you don't
blame that on me
I was blaming a dog I know it came from
it I could smell I got a good as us
sorry
and when all those pills and every
single one of those tips and techniques
doesn't we're the best tip I can give to
you is to just own up to if you're gonna
get caught you might as well make it
look like you did it on purpose and like
I said in the beginning there really
isn't anything wrong with partying in
the first place there's no reason to be
embarrassed its natural all those people
that judge you for them they're the
immature ones be proud of your parts let
them shout from the highest mountain
let them soar through the vents of the
AC let them be free and join me in the
freedom of farts movement because
together week in three parts forever one
little step at a time one little fart
step
what wasn't me who's that guy over there
look look over there's that guy over
there he's clearly the one that was what
lunch why why is the camera still on me
that wasn't okay that was me so thank
you guys again so much for watching if
you wanna see bloopers and behind the
scenes click the one the left if you
want to see the previous video click the
one on the right and because I know you
guys are already gonna ask if you wanna
download the full version of the far tip
song all you have to do is make it
yourself upload it to iTunes and then
download it because that's all we're
gonna make so you guys have to make it
yourself easy simple just like that