hey guys so as you can tell from the
title this video is gonna be about how
to know if you have ADHD or not and for
those of you that don't already know
ADHD is attention deficit hyperactive
disorder the reason I'm making this
video is because I feel like a lot of
people these days say or they think they
have ADHD but that's only because they
don't know what it's really like to have
as a little kid I was diagnosed with it
but I never took any meds for it so I
never knew what normal people thought
but I can't stand when people say that
ADHD is not a real thing and that it's
just an excuse for lazy people to blame
their laziness on what I can't stand
even more is that when people actually
do use it as an excuse even when they
don't have it just because they didn't
do well in school or they're bad at
studying or something but really there's
no excuse because I grew up with it and
I didn't take any medication for it I
still got all A's and B's and again I
also cheated a lot so after watching
this video if you can honestly say that
you relate to more of these things than
not then chances are I mean I'm not a
doctor but your brain is probably just
as messed up as mom I'm gonna be giving
you guys actual examples not those
typical ADHD joke you know which jokes
I'm talking about I'll be talking and
then all of a sudden pretend to be
distracted by something kind of like
what I'm about to do right oh look a
butterfly I mean even I made that joke
but only as a joke because that is such
a huge exaggeration it's really nothing
like that most of the time if they sound
unrealistic to you it's probably just
because you don't have it trust me
they're all real they actually do happen
I would know because sadly they're all
my personal experiences so without
further ado do and no more hesitation
here are some real examples to help you
guys know if you actually do or do not
I'm not even kidding there's an actual
butterfly right there I gotta see how
many of these you can relate to go you
meet someone new and then five seconds
after they've introduced themselves you
already forgot their name no matter how
hard you try to focus whenever you're
reading something like a book or a text
bloom read every single word on the page
you hear every single word in your head
you had five pages down the road you
have no idea what's going on or how you
got them you look at someone straight in
the eyes and rather than paying
attention to what they're saying you're
trying to decide which eye you normally
look at the left eye or the right eye
maybe it's the nose or the mouth or
maybe you're supposed to look at the
face as a whole but you already forgot
to do that because now all you see is a
bunch of face part to you there's no
such thing as sitting still you don't
realize it until someone tells you to
stop but you either been rapidly shaking
your legs hopping your hands or not in
your head to music that isn't there or
playing with whatever is currently in
your hands like a cell phone you're a
time traveler you go in take a five
minute Facebook break from work when you
come back it's an hour later sometimes
you have to remind yourself to smile
when you're with people or not because
you don't like them or because you're
upset it's because you have a bunch of
other thoughts going through your head
that aren't smile words no matter how
hard you try or how important the call
is when you're on the phone with someone
you have to be doing something else at
the same time you don't intentionally
procrastinate just most productive when
you have to get something done you work
best when you're under pressure again
you don't intentionally procrastinate
but you can never decide what you want
from a menu until you're under pressure
because the waiter just got to you you
have a bunch of incomplete things
because you're always jumping from one
thing to the next you leave your room to
go get your phone that you forgot in the
kitchen when you come back all you have
is a cup of water snacks and pretty much
everything that's not your phone a lot
of the times that you're on the phone
with people you freak out because you
can't find your phone you're not sure if
you just came downstairs or if you're
about to go home force yourself to burp
to remember what you had for lunch
and somebody tells you the thing about
one specific thing you can't because now
you're thinking about thinking about
things causing you to not think about
what you're supposed to be thinking
about detects something that makes
absolutely no sense because someone was
talking to you and you write out what
they were saying instead I can remember
a full phone number by repeating the
numbers in your head
the moment you start putting into the
keypad all the different sounds and the
key tones throw you off and you forget
you have to buy a lot of shampoo because
when you're in the shower you have the
most thoughts and you don't even realize
that you just wash your hair three times
you hate working in groups not because
of other people have bad ideas it's just
that their ideas distract yours you
overly set reminders for yourself when
important things are coming up because
you know you're gonna forget you always
have these silent awkward moments with
people because when you're talking to
them you always forget what you're about
to say mid-sentence and when you do it's
like like you have these you're very
indecisive I mean I guess this one kind
of applies to everyone or not or maybe
I'm last but not least you have ADHD
every single thought leads to another
thought and I can actually kind of learn
how to use that to my advantage when I'm
coming up with videos for example I'm
just gonna freestyle something right now
just to show you all my brain works see
you could be thinking about this video
and your mind could still go off in like
an infinite amount erections which is
the opposite of one direction maybe
that's how they got their name because
they all have ADHD ADHD like attention
deficit hyperactive disorder disorder I
mean who says it's a disorder anyway
speaking of disorder who came up with
the word disorder it kind of sounds like
a rapper trying to order at a bakery hey
let me get this ordered doe a deer a
female deer like Bambi Bambi whatever
happened to BAM a-and BAM see what is a
BAM see maybe they meant see BAM is when
the seagull is BAM that's like the waves
crashing and waves are created by win
and win can go in every single direction
which is the opposite of one direction
and that's what they got their name
that's how they got their name from the
multi-directional wind causing the waves
to crash agassiz bam bam see
and be dear like a rapper trying to get
disordered Oh creating the word disorder
and ADHD which is what all the guys in
one direction have which is the complete
opposite of the different direction this
video could go in I honestly don't know
how I remembered all that I mean it was
a freestyle so I didn't have to like
memorize anything but at the same time I
had to remember how to say it backwards
I had to pay attention to what I was
saying I mean I guess to a certain
degree I don't have ADHD oh look a bird
fly the hell are all these things so
once again thank you guys so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the right if you
want to see the bloopers and behind the
scenes click the one on the left and if
you want to see the coolest thing in the
world click the little red but oh look a
butterfly oh look at it look oh there's
so many oh yeah