hey guys so I what does it look so
different in here huh anyway um hey guys
so over the 10 - almost 11 years that
I've been on YouTube I've gotten to do a
lot of things that I never thought I'd
be able to do before and I'm sure if you
ask any other youtubers that have been
around for that amount of time and
they'll agree with me when I say that
people start treating you like you're
some kind of genius professional social
media expert and I'm sure it is true for
a lot of those youtubers who actually do
consider themselves geniuses but for me
even after 10 years of doing this I
still don't think I know exactly what
I'm doing I'm borderline dumb when it
comes to this stuff I just make the
videos that I like making and luckily
people watch they don't have some genius
strategy or like expertise that I could
share with everyone which is why I bring
this up I get asked all the time to
attend these like huge business
conferences and meetings where people
pretty much just asked for my expertise
on social media and they treat me like
I'm one of the all-knowing of social
media and to be honest when I go to
these things I feel completely out of
place people that attend these things
are like millionaire billionaire and and
women that owned multiple businesses
they're all taking notes and advice from
this 26 year old college dropout with
stupid looking hair talk about YouTube
and and all the expertise and knowledge
that I have to share with them I mean I
don't like to brag but I think I pretty
much killed it so tell us Ryan how does
one get started on YouTube well you see
you have to make an account by clicking
the sign up button okay are there any
complications or problems that one might
run into when starting a channel and if
so how do you solve them I mean
sometimes your user name can already be
taken so you solve that by adding like a
number to it or you could you know
change the letters like can we go e into
it like a three like a backwards e
alright one last question how do you
come up with your ideas well ideas are
just thoughts and everyone has thoughts
I mean I have thoughts right now this
meeting could be a video idea you know
like I could make literally this meeting
a video well let's hope you don't do
that because this is a very confidential
meeting I mean it's already happening
what right in the video right now you
really can't do this too late this is
gonna be a video can and we will sue you
if you make a video blog this event okay
sure
oh yeah that's why I have no stuff I'm
just plain but in all seriousness having
to hang out with these uh maybe you will
call them
Jewett's I started noticing some
patterns between them not just the
successful ones but more so with the
unsuccessful ones that are appearing to
be successful and today I'm gonna be
teaching you just that how to sound
smarter than you really are
[Music]
one of the easiest ways to appear
smarter than you really are is to dress
the way they dress that you see if you
dress poorly you'll look stupid for
example if you dress like a hobo or like
a poor person you'll never get any
respect and people will never think
you're smart let me take a look at this
guy you think people actually think this
guy is smart and successful no or even
if you wear like a plain shirt like this
guy you think anybody's gonna think
you're smart dressed like that if you
want people to take you seriously if you
want people to think that you're smart
you have to dress smart Dress for
Success and only then people believe
that your genius like this pretty
self-explanatory
normal people like you and I have a
dictionary they have the thesaurus
some people just like to use words that
people don't use as often for example if
someone's giving you the choice to pick
between two options rather than just
saying which option you want you say
I'll take the ladder so which one would
you like a or b no I'll take the ladder
uh but which one would you like the
ladder
oh the latter okay so you want the
second one no the ladders oh you want
the first one just the ladders so you
want both of them oh my god I'm just
gonna get in myself in the ladders smart
people always want to know what you do
they always make their job sound way
more important than it really is
school janitor more like certified
educational hygienist cashier more like
financial training delivery operator
stripper more like prostitution Oh
entertainer that does not engage in
sexual activity for money see any job
Kim sound important even if you're not
employed right now its 2017 everybody is
working they think what did you say you
did again oh I am a freelance
independent entrepreneur a leader in
social media marketing and research
relations meaning you're unemployed and
you post in read comments on Facebook
and Twitter
- I see well congratulations you're
hired
really yeah you can start as early as
this evening oh this is a night job what
exactly was my job title again oh well a
prostitution elendor tarrant that does
not engage in sexual activity for money
oh except - the latter part of the
latter part what is that it'll probably
have to engage
doesn't matter how smart you are if you
hang out with people smarter than you
you're gonna be the dumb one but what's
simple just hang out with people less
intelligent than you you think you're
the dumbest person out of everyone you
know then what you still have options
hey Marley you want bread you want the
bread go get the real test to show that
you're really smart art truly
intelligent people can see art in
everything no matter how hard it is to
see for the rest of you dummies oh my
god it's so beautiful it's a masterpiece
how is this part of the art exhibit
don't you see this represents life life
itself look you start from nothing and
you slowly make your way to the top for
only a moment before falling all the way
back down to nothing excuse me what are
you doing wait are you guys looking for
the art exhibit that's across the street
I've come to find that this last one is
a hundred percent accurate all smart
people must talk about politics and if
you're anything like me you probably
know very little to nothing about
politics so if you ever happen to get
caught in a discussion with a smart
person talking about politics just agree
with them that way they'll just keep
talking again you won't have to what's
the deal with that it's pretty crazy
what you think right I'm sorry what you
know about Trump and the wall between us
and Mexico what do you think about it
well I mean like clearly where it's
talked about all over on the news and
where all three of us are talking about
it three guys at a table during the day
so obviously yeah like a hundred percent
agree yep but yeah Trump is doing a
great job a great job at being a
horrible for the economy just awful I
mean some people think he's actually
helped the economy since I became
president right he's been awfully great
he's a man that I just love but come on
as a president he's killing it right now
it's full successful men that I just
love love loving all of our
international time to make fun of
because he's just so bad
that's right it's a badass man that's
why I completely support that no
countries you know work with the other
guy that he was running against what I
support the guy he was running again
you're talking about Hillary Clinton
exactly right
Hillary Clinton Bill Clinton's mother
sis bills and you know but Obama though
right everybody loves him she's got my
boat locked in if you know what I mean
but you do know that he's not gonna be
in the next show in the next election
exactly what I was just about to say he
can't running he should not be running
he's getting old he should be walking
this is his final term he can't have a
third term exactly why he needs to ace
it I mean he you know the final is
always worth more than the mid term yeah
I can't really tell if you're joking or
if you're just stupid I really just pull
that off oh my god do you think he knew
that was a letter mean I don't know but
again with all jokes aside it doesn't
matter if you talk about politics a lot
or if you use big words like the ladder
everybody's different who's to say
what's considered smart and what isn't
yeah maybe you did grow up being a
straight-a student your whole life and
you got a perfect SAT score and maybe
you did graduate from Harvard and got a
PhD and yes maybe you did start your own
billion-dollar company from scratch let
me ask you this do you know how to get
your hair to this color and how to
maintain it do you know how to cook and
prepare a three-course meal do you know
how to change a tire or or fix a leaking
toilet or or write film and edit a video
that's not too long and keeps the
viewers attention all the way to the end
without anyone clicking away because if
you do I would love to learn please
teach me