warning no toys were using the making of
this video except for crack shrooms
heroin PCP snow blow into dust crystal
methamphetamines and not to mention
spellcheck but seriously note those were
used with your host there's no host you
might think apart it looks like this but
the pot heads we're talking about today
look more like this meet Tommy he's your
typical pothead notice how his eyes are
small you've been for an age stupid dumb
guy look on your face clothes that look
like they haven't been washed in years
just watch this Jesse shut up you're
probably wondering what's so bad about a
plant every pot heads are dangerous to
society we clearly see here that this
man is stoned and up to no good
notice the messy hair and smiling
illegally nobody wants to see a crime
like this in their neighborhood that's
why we have our criminal justice system
downtown no more crime in this town
buddy see potheads never win that's
where the acronym comes from people
ought to think about how bad pot can be
for you especially at dinner tables
Tommy I told you know smoking pot of
identity come on pop it's just weed what
could happen should I listen to your
mother
Tommy Boy here's a few more ways to spot
a pothead if he listens to Bob Marley
Snoop Dogg Wiz Khalifa or Taylor Swift
chances are
you've got a pothead and if you were
born in the 60s the 1860s calm down
parents chances are you're a hothead if
he carries a lighter ha if he carries
eye drops pothead and if he carries a
boombox pothead if he likes the color
green he's a father if he wears the
color green he's a hothead if he is
green he recycle and if he owns a plant
he's definitely a father and those
plants are most likely hard
speaking of pot heads let's check in
with Tommy I don't smoke weed anymore
I'm clean now I'm actually a gardener so
don't blow me up
wait this was a count right again Tommy
girl heat is weed and if you have it you
will explode Oh dead giveaway for a
pothead is when an individual defends
the use of pot it's a plant it comes
from the ground everything from the
ground is natural dude every time I
weighed pot backwards is tough unless
you're a plant hater and when you're on
top you are high like a vegetarian and
when you're high you're on hey you
stupid pot heads I got two words for you
weed is illegal so cut it out right
Tommy
now I stopped smoking weed I don't even
pull weeds anymore anything to do with
weed I stopped so stop blowing me up I'm
done I'm done
not like this not like this