hey guys so I like to think of myself as
a pretty positive thinker but at the
same time a lot of the closest people
around me seem to think the opposite I
always have to hear things like why are
you so pessimistic don't be so negative
all the time why can't you see the glass
half full instead of half empty for once
by the way that saying is not always
true because it depends on what the
glass is filled with if the glass is
half full with spoiled milk it's
probably more positive to see it half
empty just saying but moving on I'm not
gonna live in times the things I say can
be a little negative for example
whenever I took final exams in high
school I would always assume that I got
the lowest grade possible just so I
could mentally prepare myself in case I
fail or when I was wrestling for a state
championship I told myself before the
match means second place is still good
or especially when it came to girls
whenever I will try to prepare myself to
ask what a girl I would think of every
single way that I would be rejected so I
would know how to react in that scenario
which consequently made me not know what
to do when they said yes and that made
it super awkward but anyway whenever I
voiced these opinions to my friends or
family they would always criticize me
for being negative and I'm sure you guys
can relate to this we all know that one
friend or a family member that's mr. and
mrs. positive and gets on everybody's
case whenever you say the slightest bit
thing that's a little bit negative but
what people don't know about me even my
closest friends and family is that I'm
actually a really really positive
thinker like all really positive just in
my own head in my head I see the glass
half-full even when it's empty I pretty
much taught myself how to see the good
in every scenario no matter how bad it
might look I just don't say these things
out loud because when bad things happen
to people and you're overly positive a
lot of times it comes off as insensitive
or rude thinking like this actually
helped me through a lot of tough times
and rough situation but again I'm just
giving you guys these examples so that
you can see how I try to stay positive
in my own head I would never say these
things out loud and you shouldn't either
trust me you do not want to say these
things out loud my thought process is
that no matter how bad things get even
in the worst case scenario wherever
there's a negative there has to be a
positive you just have to find it
hey what's wrong man I just found out my
girlfriend's been cheating on me what
I'm so sorry that's terrible and that's
probably what I would say in that
scenario but that's not quite what I
would be thinking like I said I'm an
overly positive person in my head and
this is what it would look like if I
said what I was really thinking hey
what's wrong man
I just found out my girlfriend's been
cheating on me that's a wonderful bro
you don't have to waste any more time
wondering if she's the one hey what's up
man my grandfather just passed away such
a great guy so unfair
so sorry bro that's so sad again that
something I would say but my mind is
messed up and I would search for the
positive even in that it would something
my grandfather just passed away such a
great guy so fair sorry to hear that man
but I guess everyone has to die sometime
right I mean if everyone lived forever
we'd all be dead due to the exponential
growth of the human population we
wouldn't have enough resources so in a
way it's not the worst thing in the
world what happen somebody stole all her
clothes from the laundromat like
literally a hundred dollars worth that
sucks I mean like who would even do that
you know the drill what happened
somebody stole all her clothes from the
laundry
like literally a hundred dollars worth
hey good for you that's a compliment
that means you have really good taste in
fashion see technically these are all
positive things but now you probably
know why I'm telling you to keep this in
your own head having these overly
positive thoughts didn't necessarily fix
any of the scenarios but they definitely
helped you to get through them and I
know sometimes it's hard to think
positive when you're sad or upset but
when you do have those moments you tend
that I'm they're giving you positive
thoughts oh my god
I'm only 16 what are they gonna do now
you don't have to worry about getting
pregnant for another nine months I could
never fall asleep I hate having insomnia
it's better than not being able to wake
up and being in a coma damn it they
forget my chalupas every single time wow
that is really courteous of them to be
helping you with your diet like that Oh
there's a dog poop all the places I
could have stepped hey man it could have
been worse at least I was in human poop
or like the dog itself or like HIV
contaminating or Lego damn my stomach
hurts so bad
maybe if I fart just a little bit you
won't smell it and I'll feel better Oh
[Music]
God
at least you didn't wear your white
undies today undies today undies today
undies today you can't believe my cat is
gone forever at least it wasn't your dog
you can't believe my dog is gone forever
at least it wasn't your cat you can't
believe I lost my cat and dog on the
same day well at least you can still
watch cat dog online to make yourself
feel better
what's cat dog you don't know what cat
dog is and I feel so old now if yours
I'm gonna get that reference or you
could just get rid of this scene and not
put it in the video ah but I can't take
the scene out now the video is already
online so you can take it out we're
still filming it and it's not even
edited yet man the scene is so confusing
I should just take it out or maybe some
people will get it my cat and dog were
still gone well at least this scene made
the video don't ask I don't even know
anyway you see no matter how bad things
get or how bad things may seem there's
always a positive in everything because
our world runs on balance and there
can't be a negative without a positive
life may give you a glass that looks
half empty at times but it's you and
only you that has the power of choice to
make that glass half full and if you can
do that there's nothing in this universe
that can ever bring you down again
Cheers Oh yep that's definitely spoiled
I should probably go to the bathroom
before I Oh God well at least I'm not
wearing my white undies today
[Applause]
[Music]
so thank you guys so much for watching
if you want to see bloopers and
behind-the-scenes for this video click
the one on the left if you want to see
the previous video click the one on the
right or if you want to seem to the very
end of the video and do what I do every
single time I see this part and just
sing along to this video then go ahead
[Music]