you
hey guys so as many of you guys have
probably already heard YouTube has
recently been sending out these diamond
play buttons for youtubers that have
over 10 million subscriber you know it's
like when they sent out those gold play
buttons for youtubers over a million
subscribers or like the silver ones for
youtubers over 100,000 which by the way
I have not gotten yet for either of my
channels this one or higatv you know
what it's fine I don't it's not like I
care you want to know why I don't care
I'll tell you why this one has two
thumbs in the 10 million subscriber
diamond play button ha ha ha that's
right this guy oh yeah and also I have
one too woo
Sehun is the hundred thousand silver
button when you got the gold and the
time I don't care at all most of the
time I mean I do care a little bit but
it's not like it's on my mind all the
time it's a little weird you know don't
you think it's freaking weird it's like
if you have a Wartortle and a Blastoise
but no spoon squared glad we're not but
anyway I'm getting totally off topic
video was not meant to be about what we
don't have but what we do have it for me
what I do have is a 10 million
subscriber diamond play button I can
honestly say to that change my life
oh my oh my god it's so bright
everything changed the day I got my
diamond play button I just got this
sense of empowerment knowledge I could
see the world for what it really was
water felt wetter I could suddenly see
the air move I couldn't smell music but
with this neat gift the vision I could
now see what this award really meant to
me wasn't about the fame that came with
it it wasn't even about the fortune it
was about making my dad proud my dad
want you to have this what is the Sun
theá-- 10 million subscriber diamond
play button there's only a few people in
the world that happened and I want you
to have it so that you'll finally be
proud of me Oh son you don't have to
give me anything that might not say it a
lot but I've always been proud of you I
love you son
you too dad okay yeah obviously I
exaggerated a lot receiving the diamond
play button didn't actually change that
much at least in terms of fame and
fortune like I said those things
fame fortune they never mattered to me
they never did it was and always has
been
about making my dad proud and that is
what the diamond play button really
meant to me dad want you to have this
what is this son to dia ten million
subscriber diamond play button there's
only a few people in the world that have
it and I want you to have it so you'll
finally be proud of what this [ __ ] oh
okay yeah maybe this award isn't
something that everybody understands and
appreciates it's a big deal I'm sure
maybe the award is a few years late cuz
most of us you know that celebrated 10
million subscribers did so about a few
years ago yeah it's not an Oscar an Emmy
so by having it you don't get more
famous or more wealthy in fact it's not
even made out of diamonds so it doesn't
add really any monetary value at all
what you don't want bro you naysayers
and doubters this this award is still
awesome oh yeah there's a lot that this
award can still do okay first of all it
still makes a great house decoration I
mean for you have to probably put on the
ground or like on a table or something
because it's too heavy to hang on the
wall but it's still nice to look at or
you could just carry it around with you
at all times because it makes a great
conversation starter
whose heavy season here has I got so
there's shine what is this oh yeah oh
wow a trophy or ten million subscribers
that's a lot of subscribers and if you
ask me you know like you say something
what what huh did you say something no I
don't think so
I didn't say okay cool cool look at this
no see and that's just a little taste of
how valuable and useful the diamond play
button really is I didn't even start
talking about how great of a paperweight
it is or a door stopper booster seat for
the short tin cans were like thin can
leave it out in the Sun it's a frying
pan in the freezer and you guys don't
want to talk right I'm sorry I actually
started this video as a thank-you video
to you guys clearly that didn't happen
obviously I was just joking earlier well
I mean kinda you really can't use those
words for all those things I mean
literally when I first opened it and
looked at the awards straight on I first
thought that actually came to mind what
I finally know what I would look like
from the point of view of spiders ken
went off track again in all seriousness
despite all the jokes I just want to
thank all of you guys and of course
YouTube as well many of you guys already
know this but I'm actually not that big
on award I don't normally watch any
award shows like most people do like the
Oscars Grammys Emmys Teen Choice VMAs
whatever nothing against them I just
don't find it interesting just my
opinion I mean it's human nature it's
all it always feels nice to get
recognized for something but my thought
process is and has always been that we
put a little too much value into these
awards and that's a whole nother topic
and don't get me wrong I am so
appreciative of this award like YouTube
didn't have to send us anything for 10
million subscribers but they still did
but what I'm even more appreciative of
is the fact that all of you are still
watching and supporting and I'm super
thankful to youtube not just for the
award itself but this award gave me an
excuse to make this video and thank all
the people that got me this or in the
first place all of you that subscribe
seriously thank you guys so much you
guys hear that all the time but it
hasn't changed you guys know that
literally 90% of my time sleeping is
like 50 40 percent 30 percent eating is
another 20 percent it's 50/50 percent
all my time goes into making these
videos I literally work on something
every single day and I hope you guys
know that it's because I I want to
create good content calm this video
still haven't gotten that hundred
thousand silver button but you know I
like I said I don't care it's not like
I'm waiting for it I don't lose sleep
over it at night it's not like I
carefully listen all day long for the
doorbell to ring you know hoping that
it's the mailman bringing my no yeah see
I don't it doesn't matter and that's the
lesson of this video okay I don't need
an award to validate my existence and
you guys don't need an award to validate
you're much too confident and my
self-esteem is so high plus like I said
I already cut the diamond play button
okay so why would I even want a little
silver
sorry it took so long without further
ado this is for our favorite Asian on
YouTube congratulations for surpassing
100,000 subscribers rice gum oh there it
is
finally thanks man hey is that Evan from
vanossgaming Nana must be kept jumbo