hey guys so it is the first video of the
year and it and it's two weeks into the
year so we're already behind schedule
sorry guys I was in Hawaii and hence the
long hair I don't know what that has to
do with Hawaii
I don't know Hawaii back to the topic so
it's about two weeks into the new year
and it's right about that time or half
the people who made New Year's
resolutions have already given up the
other half are about to give up and of
course is the half that you know never
made resolutions plus the half of people
that actually keep their resolutions
that's four halves not starting off
strong right but anyway I don't know
about you guys but I always make new
year's resolutions and to be completely
honest I don't think I've ever kept one
throughout the entire year I mean last
year my resolution was to stop drinking
energy drinks and if you guys watch the
behind the scenes you know that I didn't
even come close and after really
thinking about it and questioning why I
always fill my New Year's resolutions I
think I figured it out I always start
the year off strong but then over time I
slowly start biessing myself and
convincing myself that I'm not cheating
on my goals but I am it sounds confusing
let me just show you here's at the
beginning of last year kind of look like
for me this ain't so bad I feel like I
energy drink which tonight do have to
work today so maybe just one for
emergencies push to mean last year I was
drinking five a day so two a day is
still improvement last time I checked
three is still less than five so was
four five would be a tie with last
year's so I probably shouldn't but then
again a tie does hang from a neck and
the neck is connected to the head so
this area could be called the NED or the
heck is going on with the heck but this
year nope
this year's gonna be different I'm not
gonna be asked myself this year and to
be sure of that I'm gonna hold myself
accountable with me here's your list of
resolutions eat healthier go offend
people and no more cursing fart jokes
dark jokes bad puns dad's and Red Bull
actually that should say energy drinks
not really that's probably another thing
you should stop doing you're always
promoting random brands for free alright
add it to the list then okay see once
you have your resolutions all you have
to do is not BS yourself or yourself a
carnival and just stick with it
especially because right now two weeks
into the new year that's when everybody
gives up on their goals like that's
statistically proven when people don't
fact-check me because I made that up but
you get the point here's some examples
of some types of people that you don't
want to be two weeks into the new year
starting with the New Year's
person we have all seen it before and
I'm not gonna lie I've been guilty of it
too the new year's high person is
exactly what it sounds like it's
somebody who's overly hyped for the new
year they're so sick of what happened in
the previous year that they're ready to
move on they spend so much time telling
other people and themselves how great
this new year is gonna be and how it's
nothing compared to the last year that
they actually don't make any changes at
all you've seen them before they all say
the same old common basic bit huh
what cursing remember right they say all
the same old common basic types of
things such as I am so ready for 2017
but it's 2017 ready for me don't live in
the past live in the now hashtag 2017
hashtag ready man I'm so ready for 2017
I'm ready to put it work
what no this shouldn't count I was just
acting as someone else you still cursed
I didn't know what content in my videos
to do or not okay well I didn't know
that see so can I just start over fine
but no more chances after that the
technicality cheater basically this is a
guy who cheats on the resolution by a
technicality like I mentioned earlier
people who PS themselves something I am
guilty of actually I'm probably guilty
of everything you guys see here because
I if not I wouldn't have thought of it I
wrote this thinking about myself in the
past
yeah I'm annoying but anyway this is a
guy who PS is himself into thinking that
he's not cheating on his goals when he
really is basically they're cheating so
it defeats the whole purpose
looks something like this one drink a
day I'm just gonna have one a day I'm
just gonna have one slice what what that
was just for the skit I didn't even need
it right I'm you okay I see all the
behind the scenes - you can't hide
things from me the unrealistic goals
person I know this is gonna sound like
the opposite of every inspirational
speaker sometimes I don't think it's
good to set your goals too high at least
right away especially for one year if
you set your goal too high and you don't
see any progress like it's unmotivated
this is actually another big part of not
being yourself you have to be realistic
yep this is gonna be the year is the
year I become a billionaire nice man I
mean you could do it if you really
believed
and I'm gonna practice basketball every
single day and finally make an NBA team
an go for us I'm gonna travel the entire
world and go to every single country who
it man
we're ruled you know what this is
finally gonna be the year that I get a
girlfriend the way to easy goals person
pretty much the opposite of the
unrealistic goals person this guy who
sets there goes way too easy to the
point where it's like why do you even
have that goal I need to stop using vine
the person in denial probably all know
at least one of these people this is the
person that makes resolutions about
everything other than the actual obvious
problem that they have no more I feel
better already the person from China is
not even New Year's yet so she's on my
way she Bushido dance reproof and she uh
yeah the reset button person button
button I don't know why people think I
say that weird button how are you
supposed to set button button there's
two teas you gotta say one of them
button this is the guy who thinks that
just because it's a new year it's a
reset button on everything that happened
in the past year hey man I know we
haven't talked in a while but there's
figure since is a new year maybe we
could just start over
you know I mean I'm willing to put
everything that happened between us
behind me if you are so what do you say
you stole my wallet made out with cat
warriors still dating and you ran over
my grandmother with your car
yes and as bad as those things were you
know I am still willing to put it all
behind me wait is that my wallet is that
you cat wait Oh see it's all behind me
now you're feeling two of them now the
pun wasn't even that bad and how was
this a dark joke who killed her
grandmother and you threw her ashes on
the ground yes yes okay I see your point
but the pun wasn't that bad really was
though and that's your opinion my
opinion was that it's fine we're the
same person
fine then let's ask somebody else then
was the pun that bad it's not see it
come on you can't take the pun go away
from me I'm actually working really hard
on that one fine
would you still lose the dark jokes
resolution deal the secretive person now
these are for people who have
resolutions that they don't want to tell
anyone about because it's probably
embarrassing and these are the hardest
resolutions to keep because they're
secretive it's literally all on you hey
Ryan can I borrow your
were you just it's not what it looks
like Debbie I have a problem hey just
curious but why the lotion if you're
just dabbing
well why not I mean I do use it
throughout my entire day after all it is
Vaseline intensive care advanced repair
which can heal your dry damaged skin in
less than five days you seem to know a
lot about moisturizing lotion yeah I
guess you could say I dabble you know
what I give up wait what it's only been
one day and I've already like ruined all
my resolutions already not all of them I
mean you still have no cursing no red
bow no fart jokes surprisingly I
actually thought that was gonna be the
first one to go and the most important
one of all don't BS yourself remember
and if you ask me I actually think
you're doing a really good job with that
one I mean you didn't lie to yourself
when you failed you accepted it and now
you can learn from your failures and
improve yeah yeah you know what you're
right it doesn't matter if you fail your
resolutions as long as you don't BS
yourself actually I don't even need to
say BS anymore I'm just gonna say it
don't push yourself oh wow okay I think
you're kind of missing the point
oh but I'm a furnace matter that I fail
all my resolutions in fact I should fail
them so that I can improve no you
shouldn't try to fill them I think no
you know what you're right I need to
stop both myself and just be me someone
that makes bad puns and fart jokes and
and kills grandmothers and throws their
ashes on the ground well just being
honest with yourself and acknowledging
your flaws and your fails are really the
only way anyone can actually improve oh
I guess that last part was kind accurate
either that or you could also improve
yourself with a nice coat of icing sugar
free rainbow energy drink
now that is some good bull
[Music]