warning the following video sarcastic
over-exaggerating may becomes it to be
extremely offensive to a certain person
if you find that you yourself are easily
offended have no sense of humor and/or
content to be company PC definitely
don't watch this video and you're about
to kill hundreds come unless I'm saying
blah you viewer discretion is advised hi
I'm Ryan Higa and I'm currently
attending the university of college
state where I'm majoring in political
correctness so you know that I know what
I'm talking about I can tell you exactly
what is considered offensive and what is
it I mean I've taken all the classes on
political correctness such as facebook
comments 101 Twitter trends 102 whoo
Wikipedia I've even taken an advanced
class on the subject collating news
articles that other people write to tell
me how I should feel about controversial
topics 205 with my vast knowledge on
this subject I'm gonna be teaching you
how to be the most politically correct
you've ever been it was offending me
welcome to how to be politically correct
so those of you who don't know what that
means being politically correct or PC
basically means to avoid offending
people because we all know that
offending someone's feelings - the worst
thing a human being can do so let's get
started the first lesson in being PC is
to avoid the trendy topic if an issue is
trending on social media or talked about
on the news chances are you should
probably avoid that topic because all of
a sudden everybody really cares about it
now and no matter which side you pick
her probably gonna offend someone here's
an example of a trendy controversial
topic net you guys buy remember can you
believe this what this is Starbucks
Christmas cup so so there's no Christmas
on the cop this is a blatant attack on
my religion a blatant attack on
Christianity plus the cup is red that's
the same color as hell and the devil and
fire and pimples that are not ready to
be popped yet well I think they're right
for not putting Christmas on the clubs
did you just say well I'm not a
Christian and if they did have Christmas
designs on the cup then that's
infringing on my First Amendment right
of freedom of religion how dare you see
something just a cup see it might seem
like a silly petty argument but since it
was trending in the news it's really
important now if you really want to be
PC avoid the trendy topics this is what
he should have said guys it's just uh
never mind
no comment
you know what you're worse than both of
us by keeping quiet you're not doing
anything so the next lesson in being PC
is no more jokes jokes are a thing of
the past I mean you might think that
some jokes are not that bad but in 2017
all jokes are offensive hey you want to
hear this joke I just read okay all
right so three guys walk into the bar Oh
three guys huh do you know you guys were
against women's rights what why do they
have to be guys they don't well then
it's sexist why are there no women women
go to bars too yeah I know dude it's
just a joke oh it's just a joke what
women aren't funny enough to be a part
of your little joke it fine it doesn't
really matter okay
three women good walk into the bar in
the middle of the day right the middle
of the day Wow what is it now oh you're
saying all women are alcoholics you a
bunch of misogynist hey why did the duck
cross the road why to prove you wasn't
chicken are you implying that all
chickens are cowards or that somehow
Ducks are above chickens in some way why
because ducks and chickens are equal
okay and people like you were support
ducks supremacy are part of the problem
what are you talking about I don't see
how this is offensive yeah of course you
don't you don't see it because you're a
little privileged duck boy I grew up in
the safety of your little ranch so of
course you're not afraid chickens
chickens we grew up in fear we get drugs
GMOs forced him to us at the mills were
forced to watch each other get
slaughtered just for food it ducks get
eaten - yeah they do but tell me how
often do you come across duck eggs at
the supermarket huh how often do you
pass by a fast-food chain called KFD you
see all bird lives do matter but right
now
chicken lives those are the lives that
are in danger and that's what's trending
what do you call someone with no cell
phone I don't know what a houseful
because with no cell phone you got a
closet with a household as somebody who
finds Jonah Hill on my casseras comedy
inappropriate I take offense to that
joke what they've never even said this
joke how is this even related to either
of them because it was super bad and
finally the last lesson in being PC is
for you to know that everything is
offensive if you don't think that
something is offensive chances are
you're a bad person and you're not
looking hard enough here let me make it
easy for you I'll give you some examples
now take a look at this x-men poster
does it offend you at all because if it
doesn't you hate women it's clearly
showing a man choking a woman's that
means you think that it's okay for men
to choke women not to mention at the top
of the Billboard it says only the strong
survive implying that men are stronger
than women but that's not it this poster
isn't just sexist it's racist I mean why
is the light-skinned blue person talking
the dark-skinned blue person and not the
other way around take a look at the date
on the bottom don't tell me it's just a
coincidence that they conspired the
release date to be on May 27th the exact
same day the race riots in East Saint
Louis took place in 1917 and the title
itself is not just sexist it's a hate
crime I mean the title of the franchise
is X Men Y not X women I'll tell you why
because x-men apocalypse is an attack on
the LGBT community that's right x-men
stands for transgender their x-men they
used to be men other women so they're
x-men so when they say x-men apocalypse
what they're really trying to say is
that this is the end of the world for
the transgender community I will not
stand for that I will remain sitting I
will not this is old news it's not
trending anymore it's no big deal then
next so in closing I know there's a lot
of things to remember so I'm gonna
simplify it and try and wrap everything
up in order to be a truly politically
correct person avoid all the trendy
controversial topics which basically
means that if something is being talked
about by somebody somewhere about
something you may not have an opinion
about it because you're wrong and it's
gonna offend someone must also remember
no more jokes jokes are a thing of the
past
so remember to never laugh or make
anyone else laugh because if you do that
means you're laughing at the issue
issues like war and rape and racism so
if you laugh you're a racist war rapists
and last but not least and most
importantly everything is offensive it's
not rocket science if you don't want to
offend others it's simple don't have
opinions don't take any action
don't walk talk move where or share
anything you're thinking about
especially if it's about an issue and
everything is an issue and at the same
time keep in mind there with all these
issues if you don't speak up and take
action you guys are part of the problem
so stop having opinions stop taking
action and step up and do something and
take
hey cut cut what no no it's not you the
video is great message is clear just
we're missing something I don't think
we're gonna get the views this way
unless hi I'm Ryan Higa and I'm