yo what's up my name is mystery cab
Dawson smashing G boom productions
hey it's Freddie Wong and we're going to
be teaching you how to be a YouTube
celebrity lesson 1 in order to be a
YouTube celebrity you need to have a
good video like a cute baby or a cute
cat me or a cute person or even a cute
triangle lesson to every YouTube
celebrity travels less than three if you
are YouTube celebrity you're always on
red carpets lesson for every YouTube
celebrity has fans
blessed by your YouTube celebrity
everyone knows you hey aren't you that
uh that KevJumba yeah hey man
yeah bar you prince charming no nobody I
need it for now my pencils I go it's
dull no if you follow all of these
lessons it should look a little
something like this
we're going to be teaching you how to be
right one degree from here yeah trap
what