hey guys so I've been watching just a
tiny bit of anime more than usual and to
be honest I I did not do my hair you
know what give me one second there we go
like I said I've been watching a little
bit of anime lately and if you grow up
watching anime your whole life like I
did you tend to not hear about or even
notice all the really weird things that
happen in anime well for a while like I
kind of stopped watching enemies and
only recently got back into it you know
I'm one of those binge watches when it
comes to show us I like to watch a bunch
of episodes in a row and then stop for a
while so the episodes filled up so that
I can watch a bunch again I don't know
it just it's upsetting to me you know it
really pisses me off they always end on
a cliffhanger and then we make you want
to know what's gonna happen next but you
can't know until a week from now and you
know what's even more upsetting with
animes is when you wait the whole week
for an episode and you finally tuned in
and it's time to watch the new episode
and it turns out that that episode is a
dare I say a filler that what are you
guys doing in here if vlog is taking too
long
seriously you complain about fillers and
this is literally turning into one yeah
so get to the point already
okay um welcome to how to how to be
anime stuff
welcome to how to be an anime superhero
let's let's get started lesson 1 the
characters the first step in being an
anime superhero is to know the different
characters Oh anime have very similar
characters to one another first off
there's the main character who's either
really cool and super strong or he's
really goofy and funny and receptively
strong then there's the main supporting
character who's either the main
characters best friend or the main
characters rival and this supporting
character is based off of the main
character he's literally the opposite of
what the main character is the main
character
cool then this guy is goofy if the main
characters goofy then this guy's cool
after that we have another main
supporting character known as the
attractive but abusive girl which for
some reason always abuses one of the
other main characters whoever's playing
the goofy one also there might be a
random type of bet that follows the gang
around as well and that's pretty much
your group of main characters of course
there's also the lesser important
characters as well such as the perverted
old man character the cute girl will
always talks while she smiles with her
eyes closed the guy who was animated
differently from the others for some
reason the chubby guy that's always
eating or the really skinny girl that
eats like a chubby guy and so on
put it honestly you don't really need to
know anything about those characters cuz
they're not as important to the
storyline even though you probably will
eventually learn everything about them
because of the dam fillers lesson -
anime emotions now that you know all the
enemy characters it's time to act like
well here are some very basic anime
motions that all anime superheroes need
to use such as the cheek blush the cheek
blush is basically or whenever your love
interest enters the room the hands
overhead lap very nervous situations or
trying to hide a secret of some sort do
you use the hands overhead laugh the
thumbs up shiny teeth ding the I pull
tongue dis the wide mouth stutter and of
course you cannot forget the classics
the nosebleed whenever a man
specifically an old man sees something
even the tiniest bit sexual for some
reason he has a tiny little nosebleed
don't worry about
I love that lipstick thank you so here
on you let me try okay
[Music]
lesson three battling every good anime
has some kind of battle in it whether
it's actual fighting or supernatural
fighting sometimes it's not even
fighting at all regardless there's
always some kind of battle and in order
to make it an anime battle you have to
follow a specific set of rules for
example in most real fights you want to
win as fast as possible but anatomies
the opposite you want to prolong the
fight as long as you can by talking to
your opponent the entire time even right
in the middle of the fight wait jeez man
what can we do at least take a moment so
I can say something like wow you're a
lot stronger than I thought you were
something I guess okay wow wow much
stronger than I thought you were hello
what don't you have something to say
back to me like oh uh thank you another
very important rule for battling like an
anime hero is to take turns yeah in a
real fight you might want to dominate
the entire fight and just win right away
but in anime battles you and your
opponent need to take turns having the
upper hand and also very important while
you guys are doing the back and forth
make sure that you're thinking about it
loudly in your head so that the viewer
knows who's winning at the time don't
want them to be confused
matched no it's getting even stronger
yes the upper hand now this rate I'll be
destroyed now or never
[Music]
was but now I guess I can new your mind
yeah
told him this is crazy have you done
this before oh this is my first spot
same here I guess we can only read each
other's minds
wonder what that mean maybe like we're
related some spoiler less than for
google it now this is a very important
lesson to being an enemy superhero
especially for someone like me every
great anime is in Japanese and if you're
just like me you don't speak a single
word of it hence lesson for googling all
you have to do is type in what you want
to say listen to what it sounds like and
then repeat it back perfectly it's 100%
accurate every single time or should I
say my gosh accent doe say aku this mic
I go say anchor tag yeah lesson 5 make
an episode the last lesson you need to
know to be a true anime superhero is to
make a true anime episode yes there's
rules here as well you can't just jump
right into the story that's not how it
works in the anime world first of all
you need an opening theme song which
pretty much sounds like Japanese rock
music with the occasional English line
and you accompany that theme song with a
bunch of random scenes from the show
whether it's characters or people
punching and kicking or trees or water
whatever it is it doesn't really matter
because this is the part the viewers
gonna skip anyway next you have to recap
the previous episodes we all know that
anime watchers have the memory capacity
of a two-year-old and last but not least
all you have to do is show the title and
the episode number that the viewer is on
and you're ready to begin the episode
right after you recap the recap that the
viewer just saw there you have it if you
follow all of these lessons and put it
all together congratulations you are an
anime superhero and it should look a
little something like this
[Music]
[Applause]
tonight water wash your nah y'all
goodness what a walk hokku not comedy
Joshua shooting good s so stay what does
she want
[Music]
Donnie Moore watashi no UI although
that's your kazoo sukeroku and I know
what
water hole by 1700 washed up honey watch
you got a gun Naga denied ah she got
caught in me also a leap alla pugacheva
hit Ishita by gosh you all matcha guy
not cool us already know do you also
have much time buddy watch Shikata got
knock of the night
watashi go accordingly or Sawadee better
when he did
I don't at all Joshua you get it Tommy
no chikara one it su-ure myself Joshua
did sue you this oh boy and you do so
with the Kuniko cazuca somebody says fun
technique with a scar over a three must
not get you the most great idea
[Music]