hi I'm Randy I'm sean fujiyoshi oh
you're not yes I am but you're allowed
that's right okay and we're gonna be
teaching you how to be and the minded
Sean's not so actually the adventure
premier lesson one you can't be a lamp
what listen to if you live in Hawaii on
Oahu go to the restaurant row theater
box office and buy your tickets for this
Saturday lesson three you still can be a
lamp oh that's in four if you want to
the heel premiere on Sunday make sure
you go to go Montcalm or go to the
Prince Kuhio Plaza theaters and get your
ticket today let's invite it if you
can't make it on premiere don't worry
about it because our movie will be so
many other places as well also if our
movie does not come to where you live
you can preorder our DVD on Bryan and
Sean's movie calm and the first 1500
DVDs will also give an autograph by shot
and I want that shut up lamp if you
follow all of these lessons it shouldn't
leave something like this hey can I come
to your premiere no haha just kidding
but seriously no that's allowed or
vacuums what
you
okay hey no lip from you get back here