man it's been like three days and we
only have five you yeah we worked like
two weeks on that one too plus there's
four of us if we all watched it
technically there's only one of you
actually I've watched it twice so what
we're gonna do gave up my job so we
could take this seriously yeah we all
did hey guys check this out real quick
why hello there are you having a hard
time getting people to view your videos
are you in a tight spot right now
because you gave up your job to pursue
YouTube as a career oh that's caught on
huh are you four guys spinning red on a
beat up apartment sitting on a long
brown college surrounded by garbage and
a red finger vase that's held together
by blue painters tape to hell for one of
the four of you has a secret
embarrassing addiction to eating his own
boogers
I bet it Shawn well if that's the case
you've come to the right place
welcome to how to get views on YouTube
so you made us see the clip funny scared
something new uploaded it but you barely
got a single view still passionate and
you wanna stay true to you failing again
then you just don't have a clue youtuber
tips and do what you wanna do that's
nice and all but we all know that is not
that you fit in 2010 there's a whole set
of new rules he's the real ways to get
views on YouTube
[Music]
take the latest wrench of it in the
title make a fake challenge or just buy
an iPhone could take a couple fingers
missing go get that original sketch on
this headset is about politics and
pushes an idea that's already been said
so the lowest common denominator or
Nothing heads don't become a chance in
life be sure to mention they could clean
up us if they subscribe it if you're
still not getting to is just offend the
entire nation changer you're resourceful
culture appropriation
[Music]
play a game Q&A you can do most anything
so long as this ten minutes on and you
keep posting everyday quantity or
quality what do people want to see it
ain't that hard if you reread only one
answer the CT and people might say
you're selling out this way but on the
few so come in in actions are louder
they say so no I'm not trying to hate
and no I'm not doing say the struts an
art in itself that takes a lot of Monet
so what else can get you news about a
house to Urdu type your own name into
Google or a Connie Sharif do it if your
code is still so slow maybe it's time
for G emotions head down to the one
thing oh you need some pink if you want
a rose take the shot you take shots back
you call it where I say collapse your
clonus Patti what is left over yet us
babe all these bands now you're finally
Kenny views oh wait there's one last
step to do here's the number one way for
you to get views on YouTube sign a card
or YouTube TV go to FanFest maker
YouTube Red Sea redesigned it back and
you'll be trending
[Music]
they will take care of you play ball and
you will benefit to know she to spread
the truth these are all the best ways to
get using YouTube for video comply oh
yeah that's what's up
no this bunny we are set for life all
right guys guys guys I just found out
how we can make even more money what how
there's ads on Facebook now we could
take all the same videos that we've been
uploading on here and upload them on
Facebook and make twice as much money
ooh that sucks what's up well you guys
just said the F word twice so that's two
strikes in your college two strikes one
more and you guys are pretty - shave the
f words yeah we were just talking about
how there's ads on Facebook now and
there's strike number three man sucks
who are you
these rods dance losers like way more
tricky on purpose