[Music]
I'm gonna vlog okay all right I knew I
knew you're gonna do that all right the
last time I was here with David was a
great rap on the round we made mumble
rap last time last time we made mom
we're up because it was popular this
time we're making something that is well
we hope becomes popular again we heard
we heard turn down for what recently and
we're like there hasn't been like a big
I guess we have to look it up we didn't
know what a club banger all this is that
the right term it's a club banger hey
where you go to clubs and then you just
don't say it we can how do you describe
what it's a club banger it's gonna get
sick eating like those do this it's a
song it gets people to really like get
hyped up yeah is there to break free
we're gonna know you guys will know a
bunch of shouting drop spills drop bill
drop bill okay like what makes a club
banger so you need a sin like this
that's see if we did something
that's cool oh we need yep yeah these
yep and that's an you go like it's some
kind of like it was yeah yeah we do some
kind of shouting thing there yeah what
should the song be about because we're
talking about going to the club and
having a great time but me and you are
like the opposite of that I mean I like
those kinds songs but I'm not like a
clubber and you're not a clubber either
I'm not a closer you know what we should
do we should make our own like other
since we're introverted we should make
like an introverted version of that song
it'll be like the introvert anthem ooh I
like that
yeah you're pretty good I like it it
doesn't work though is your friend
something like it has to be like you
know a something quick get introverted
screaming go louder
oh we should do a what - like a what
what oh okay my voice already Express
keep talking about some other lyrics
that we could put in like what else yeah
you know what I do when I go to clubs I
like to go to the bathroom why not
because I would need to go to the
bathroom but because I like to hide out
in there oh that is true like they're
like regain your energy yeah every like
party like house parties is that one guy
yeah I like that group of people who are
like super extroverted and they want to
get everybody to hell yeah we all know
somebody like super annoying I'm finding
a name that it won't offend somebody
Trevor I don't know what I don't even
know if I just look up introvert just
interpreting with you introverted people
do well just shout out a bunch of things
that introverts would do like I said
like put your hands out would be like
put your hands down yourself like get
freaky what would like put keep your
hands to yourself yeah don't touch me
just be introverted David do yourself
but dad's down keep it to yourself oh
crap it's really sore dude out if I
should keep doing this it's like some
Dragon Ball voice like what Dragon Ball
Z character actors have to do calm
that's it that's all I got so what do we
do now like it is that it last time we
have to write all this lyrics I'll put
it together for this we need to but
[Music]
now it's recharged ain't nobody
but it
[Applause]
[Music]
Jane a right to put on scamper to be
overly hot scarce we gonna say goodbye
and avoiding any more conversations