warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact we create a
reincarnated of following stunts tears
and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video your discretion
is advised we take your dares put them
in a hat and if we draw at the fair
console that decides how many points is
worth based on how daring of a deity if
the player passes and whether player can
take the steal the first player to get
10 points doing something amazingly not
amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of Fame no just kidding they get
the ball of name basically write your
name on a ball of aluminum foil it's
pretty lame
so those of you that don't know we have
mr. Dominic d-trix and ball back here
hey what's up guys this dish from the
Dominic show a night here I'm here all
the we gotta breathe hey guys it's green
right Runnings so what we're gonna be
doing now this is a new rule that we
came up with the loser of the game is
gonna have to do it there as well it
gives incentives so that you can't just
do nothing and basically what we're
gonna do we're just gonna write a dare
go into the loser Club and the loser has
to draw and do it oh ma ones in alright
everyone's in good way first how we're
going to side this we do the golf way so
you flip it and we're pointing at
they'll go first and we'll just keep
backing it out okay alright okay
right great
I dare you to mix up a spoon of ice
cream with mayonnaise and eat it
luminous easy to go to blender points
how much I thought water
sorry green I said to you say 1 you say
1 you say to 1.5 all right I say we do
oh my god ice-cream sandwich what's
expired
look mail on it doing a meal so yeah
that's horse radish let's make it home
make a horseradish come on
they have this big of horseradish oh
it's all we got that's all I got hey
what you got would you do horseradish
I'll give you two points a few points ah
doing all right
is it doing the moving low expires right
smells like bro that's little over there
yeah that is a library you do not need
to put that much it smells pretty bad
it's so good do that son don't think
just go ah that old a little bit is it a
little bit
no way just watch me a little spicy keep
going green if you get is like somebody
just oh he's gone
yo hey hey timeout yeah I give them an
extra half or something because that's
expired yeah yeah all right yeah all
right so Sean
I dare you to duct-tape the person next
to you through the you'll get the duct
taped to the wall will he stay I'm here
I'm I don't think you they have the
arrow I got to to the wall ones and as
long yeah I don't know this is gonna
work good where if we duct tape a piece
of wall to him well the rest of the game
find a fine line what I think this is
the one
nice it's not like a piece of orange
right on arm to do oh yeah you might
report all right let's go right oh
that's the Tuesday I was good I dare you
to lick the person in your right in his
bed Oh easy one point for me I didn't
what ha ha ha ha ha for a half a point
you all right quick lick ooh - [ __ ] I'll
do point 1 point 1 all over point 0 5
like it matters was nobody at one point
if you want to do it 0.5 your point 0.05
you can do 8 every point counts all
right Shawn bend over
that's that's discovered we're looking
for nothing major
no it's always for something yeah I say
we give shot and pour 0-5 as well
already go go from ask Lauren and Kendra
I dare you to rub everyone in the room
spit on your face don't spin to your
hand you go oh I'll tell you what you
spin your head and you get to slap me
girl boy four point each person come on
okay that's right yeah I'm gonna go
first you go first okay oh let me see
that girls look thick mm-hmm
I'm going for it
just watch my hair Oh do that Salutin oh
you are the man man duh duh duh duh duh
duh duh alright gray what's up kingly
capping Lisa
I dated a belly flop in a pool for if
you do it in your outfit oh I would say
five if you jump from the top of the
yeah waterfall okay Sam get him a towel
a house always hit the stain they all
fit the entire rest of the round yes
okay ever turn up the AC let's go great
Wow yeah it's gonna hurt Oh more than my
head slippers Chippendales
hey hi dare you to get slapped in the
butt by others in rooms I think
eventually we can go like easy hard-on
oh yeah so we're gonna do is we're all
gonna take turns hitting his ass and
then we're gonna first-person gonna go
kind of hard then a little harder and
the last guys in me as hard as you can
for two point two point two points do it
let's do it go
oh right here I don't know I hit my head
on the board a really good bit scared oh
sorry
you got any uh words her um oh I'm so
sorry that wasn't even a good laugh Oh
what do you get I cried shopping pretty
hard 33.3 I say three alright let's go
shop yeah big boy I do you guys break
dance in a Walmart for 15 seconds while
other guys like this hey how about the
first person to walk up to Walmart you
see you have to just battle them right
away I do it yeah I'm look I'm a past
yes but you do it then I gotta put on
the board shirt I mean Sean losing the
board yeah I'd be cold and you get
transferred you get more foots out the
wheel are so good fine I'll say it clean
fine I'll give you five for it damn and
I gotta keep the board I'll do it oh
yeah what I Ryan I like your outfit
thank you that's cruel sorry hello Sean
you got the board
that counsel hey what did they walk away
from me
a bruit Boyd never lunch someone walk
away okay
Oh
I'm going again for the wind
oh hey good one I dare you to change
clothes with a person to your right one
point five in one daddy get this bag and
I get a one point 95 it's free all right
one point nine five and I get what one
what okay I'll do it
Sean's make it more poor Oh Sean your
balls kujan armpit farts are hella cold
shot pick mine keep my feet oh all right
I'm picking up some booze I dare you to
become a human mom hey you might want to
pass them at me for picking you up and
we're mopping you coming boys that's at
least a 30 dude if there's dirt on the
ground you get four points or something
something off the ground
well what is it something that matters
what do you want make my spit a
horseradish whoops I spilled horseradish
good thing I have my DDT to dumb mom
damn it alright I'm done okay yeah
points
oh this looks like a good day for some
horseradish sauce whoa oh I fell it
looks like we have to use our dawn mop
and again
oh I'll do my headed nose done it's all
Whaley and all the way oh okay okay okay
it's Prince
I can smell so bad in my hair all right
great
I dare you to let them hold you down
while tickle yes yes perfect for you
point five for every five seconds so one
point for every ten Capet thirty cool
that fair yeah all right let's do it
all right guys we're starting in five
four three two one
five seconds 20 seconds oh oh you got 25
seconds alright let's go green yeah I do
drink soda with a Mentos in your mouth
you ever see feel like they drop it in
the bottle and they'd be like spread in
there man alright our three three three
strong that's good oh yeah yeah let's do
it let's go
greenery - I dare you ready yep I cannot
hold on throw a ha he does have any
points no no I dare you to put your own
big toe in your mouth for 15 seconds oh
wait you reach oh yeah okay that's hella
cramping my for 15 seconds 15 I just had
an ingrown toenail oh I'm not doing that
I'm insecure don't show that pass
somebody else oh dude arms toll
I don't know for four points yeah a
great maybe the winning weight right so
my days I could custom I'll let you know
right now the great I used to know the
brave would play high school class of
2005 Timberwolves I'll do it so you're
gonna suck the toe I'm gonna suck on
some toes oh my god I just explained how
Julian cutting my nail Cole weeks ago
did it got offset so grew inside the toe
and I believe ago I think Ron toenail so
- yeah you guys suck that tool for 15
seconds 15 seconds all right you know
what I don't say it's inger let's say
Ted has been your mouth the whole time
lips closed wins the wafer you suck his
ingrown toe your dessert ready okay
three two one
Ted hey Savion I put click six five four
haha Hank is our winner
yeah I believe Shawn has the least
points right now I lost so that means we
gotta pull from the green Cup yeah I'll
pull from the looser Cup this is there I
always thought my my suck yes
it's not oh this is mine later Legos on
ground by stairs go up four steps Oh
jump oh yeah you have to do it dump it
Oh Shawn I believe in you oh so have a
lazy mention two three four there you go
okay okay all right so great is our
winner
sighs prize right now so you will do
whatever you want one two three right
right oh great and not only are you in
what do you not only win you get a side
of the ball every other side are you
you
good let's say flaps is the ball is
growing yeah that's kind of scary do it
almost Eric wait didn't we say plane oh
yeah oh thank you guys so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the left if you
want to see the last I dare you video
click the one on the right and be sure
to leave your dares in the comments
section below that's a throwback wears
rain these days