warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact we create a
reincarnate and the following stunts
tears and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video if your
discretion is advised we take your dares
put them in a hat and if we draw at the
playground so then decides how many
points is worth based on holiday of a
dare it is if the player passes another
player can take the steal the first
player to get 10 points do something
amazingly not amazing as well as their
name in the Hall of Fame no just kidding
they get the ball of name basically
write your name on a ball of aluminum
foil we have some changes normally we
don't win anything we didn't know where
to get this to so we just said the wind
up idea if you win anyway so the winner
actually gets a prize the first time
we're giving away a prize and it's
pretty decent it's a real laptop it is
not a trick and well what do we do next
oh you waited to the loser
so the limited air basically I'm hoping
though that is we all write down our own
dares and the loser of I dare you ask
the poll from the cop
anyone watch how she's undefeated all
right loser Cup we've got our dares
right here from all of you guys how do
we decide who goes first whoever has the
biggest lips I dare you to sprint into a
wall with exercise ball oh my gosh how
many points this isn't that hard
that's good okay so what two points you
know how science works inertia actually
you know what we should judge it based
on how hard he goes yeah kind of math
point all right all right right that's
nice I dare you to take your toothbrush
and stick it in the toilet and then
brush your teeth oh no what is this work
let's be real boys I got a delicious
smile
I'm passing this and wants to do this
I'm doing Oh
just dip it in the pool water and brush
your teeth with it easy she wants it she
want to take the steal more points this
is like more point is this disgusting
sorely needs oh my god I don't know when
this was last clean be honest I'm not
getting shown up today so I need to take
a few answers next there we go here we
go
dear one of you guys to pick someone's
nose with someone else's tall
[Music]
[Laughter]
use the pinky toe or something shoes the
big one that's what you got will I dare
to get hit with an egg by every person
who is playing lying down are you doing
it I'll steal them right now I'm good
huh you cannot if you do you have to
lose a point okay yes I agree
all right okay so what will we get this
normally I'm mistaken we cracking eggs
outside no I mean on his body was it
there's no lights
you like to throw you should we like
break it break it a little
the greats gonna whip this let's go dare
you to eat Marnie's food you got any
like clean handful out of the bowl
without using your hands
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe three depending how convincing you
are yes eat right now there it is three
boys let's go Greg digit hacks use a
belt and whip the person to your left
it's better best bit gets points I'll
take you
I need the point where I'll do about
what is your I get spanked we can do
escalating pains oh good old-fashioned
okay I like the three three for the
toilet so four hits escalating strengths
are any points okay let's do it
I'm flexing right now so you set the bar
oh that's pretty high bar oh that's a
good boy
the laser actor party he'll come and oh
hi
you getting a running start Gilmore is
right now that's the one there you go
kick the corner of the table as far as
give you points based on how hard maybe
the Apple yeah yeah we'll do an Apple
box no blood no blood
we're good I'm there nice pink where's
the whip 1.8 whatever I can get I want
to go to the car and look at the
steering wheel suggestion points for I
have the steering wheel that's pretty
much pretty dirty
there it is
I don't do that all right you big
roasting I two points I guess you ready
[Music]
I dare you to her in I think your face
is the middle of a high yeah yeah I'd
like to
[Music]
oh that's a lot of okay okay three two
one go oh this is not safe if you get
this in your eyes you're dead pouring my
hand I'm like slapping oh yeah
fair do I get a point in my hand you
know point one okay
we're gonna change it to this tell me
how much I should put on it as much as
you want
you're getting a point one for it oh
that's a one good yeah give me
countdowns right to slap ready three two
one all right what do you say four
points
oh that's the one there you bash your
face it to the table
oh okay all the week I'll take one
all right let's go Miranda peanut butter
the hairiest armpit in there oh yeah
Shawn my gosh you know it's for the win
[Music]
there's sweat great oh boy this is very
weird
oh my god
young was not good what kind of deal
right dunya wall she won
[Applause]
so there's our winner and then we also
have our other our favorite part which
is the loser will take a bite of
lipstick oh there you go
and it's Miranda sings lipsticks it's
rather sling less almighty ready
a big chunk picture oh it's weird like
what yeah good job will with that being
said I guess retinas are a winner
literally Lily wanted one second guess
Twitter tweet Julian long in third yes
that's my shirt make a very faint to
there's no she wins so you can break it
see it's extra safe try no why don't you
see and not only goes this way but it
also goes this way
[Music]
so in addition to a brand new laptop you
all seem to sign our trophy which is the
foil fall of shape
[Music]
Ronda sings make sure you guys check out
our channel she also has I don't know
actually in relation with Colinas to you
she's in she's yeah don't subscribe to
me but check out Miranda sings channel
coming up right here so thank you guys
again so much for watching if you want
to see the previous video click the one
the left if you want to see the previous
I dare you video click the one on the
right and remember to leave your dares
in the comment section below and check
out for asthma sings channel on who's
Brandon sings that's that's our channel
and also again leave the dares and who
you want to see next
Brandon sings channel