warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact we create a
reincarnate and the following stunts
tears and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video for your
discretion is advised
[Music]
and if we draw at the player concert
then decides how many points is worth
based on how daring of Adara tease if
the player passes another player can
take the steal the first player to get
10 points with something amazingly not
amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of Fame no just kidding they get
the ball of name basically write your
name how do we decide the boys first
play we usually do it whoever has the
longest pinkie I dare you to a spoonful
of mayo a male is one oh it's like an
egg I guess we could just decide when we
get the spoon how much it's worth I'm
thinking like that
[Music]
[Laughter]
I dare you to get punched by everyone in
the arm or stomach your choice alright
fine for fun
no I mean it depends how hard we're
punching here I'm like a man okay
hey hit him up in multiple ways yeah hit
him up I choose I will arm because I
kind of just ate the really frontal this
farmers and hits like be kind of
decently hard wants to go first
Oliver's a solid just go let's go around
a punch
just believe in yourself just believe
yep oh great oh you guys want to change
it you want to say four points cuz
that's pretty good before point four
points oh why are we shaking I dare you
to rip off one eyelash I'll just do one
yeah is it good yeah that's a good see
oh I did feel it hello my eyes are
watering buddy come on
that you see a nervy dirty Ola not heard
that one
so nervy cuz real high to the face where
high down low to high this is like two
or three which one would you want this
looks nice and it smells good big paper
once our words know I dare you to pour
water into my nose all right well then
drown you I love you snort vinegar don't
try this at home
oh yeah real good well a little eh
[Laughter]
put your head in a bucket of ice in the
water let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
I dare you belly flop off onto the
ground
or we could go to the pool and you do a
legit belly [ __ ] from online like that's
safer with the pool okay because we
don't want shun actually jumping we're
gonna teach it a little bit was just
three points we're gonna make Shawn
belly flop into the pool well you guys
are gonna score me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh here we go
don't keep your hands and legs together
and go mistake this if I can get up from
a full flight what is that word game
over you just be there how will we be
the points out yeah alright yeah this is
perfect
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
- a beautiful shade of like this call
for an extra point oh my god
I can't believe it wait really
that is disgusting a male pocket I dare
you to have someone do the surra de
bunda on you okay you guys never watch
that video huh we cannot do that two
points I mean I'm good but I feel like
I'm gonna hurt you yeah break your face
in my ass for sure I'm not doing
[Laughter]
we did you already know what's gonna pop
up in the yeah we've ever done I
[Music]
remember I would go up and it comes my
do to lick the dust three laughs pretty
grody pretty gross I'll give you a good
point for laughs wait for love wait for
like a solid blue
[ __ ] do you think Nikki does not
freelance and go with the sexual come
before you ruin oh you went under tongue
taste like that birdies like lava
oh she here we go for two points I'll
give you you get a chair and you do the
air man because there's no anyone cleans
that no way do you go for the wind right
now Oh mom someone to stick your head
down the toilet
Oh would you this is a good for ya
you're passing do that for 100 she's
taking it on this is like common in
movies but I've never seen this happen
yeah you're a trooper view on let's tell
me when you're ready
Oh five four three two
[Applause]
good job but you also in hydraulic
[Laughter]
[Music]
so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
I dare you with Jeremy Lin and KEF jumbo
click the one on the left if you want to
see the previous video click the one on
the right and also a huge shout out to
lily and Tyler for being a part of this
madness that we call the show and be
sure you guys leave more I dare use in
the comments and well you want to see
next I don't know why my voice is
getting higher