apparently it didn't do that yeah and
with that Bert come from huh yeah what's
your just a good effort Wendy's oh gee I
had a triple bacon either cheeseburger
the double chili fries sandwich and
ginger help ginger yeah I had teaching
your bacon cheeseburgers and medium
fries of any mustard to please when you
sponsor this welcome back to another
episode of we take your dares put them
in a hat and if we draw it the player
comes with any pens how many points is
worth based on how daring of adara tees
if the player passes another player can
take the steal
but first player to get ten points with
something amazingly not amazing as well
as their name in the Hall of Fame no
just kidding they get the ball of name
basically write your name on a ball of
aluminum foil it's pretty late so we are
back at it with a loser I dare you
episode we have our very good friends
with sobbing productions with us we have
Alex my name is Alex avi and I'm gonna
win this game because I have the
determination the muscles and the power
and Roy hi I'm Roy wasabi I love pandas
I love you too charlie
Vanessa whoever's watching you guys are
great no it's time for it to lose your
dares basically we all write our own
dare you don't make youtube crazy
because you might be the loser loser
asked to pick from the loser Jericho hmm
actually me crazy if you want oh boy
alright everyone in everybody building
Israel how we decided to go first person
with the biggest hands I don't know
Oh Long's here all right I dare you to
get a raspberry by someone on your face
what's a really good like I'm gonna be
something yeah okay guy should do it I
thought you're ill tickle the most am i
doing I'm ready it's like a two-pointer
I think don't be why I'm down for two
where do I do it what do I hear anyway
this is wait it says anywhere anywhere
on your feet anymore just do it
somewhere make it more concise eye
twitches I'm gonna get pinkeye guys pull
out your own leg hairs burn with the
most Lakers get oh damn it you animates
look it up look at this whoa I said one
grab and we all take turns
Oh first I can just believe you sir all
right all remapped I do leave one go I
gotta know I know I got what score baby
I'm scared three two one Oh what is that
verse seven yeah oh my god we're bellroy
oh my god you're are always multi-finger
technique okay go slow
whoa that is five sorry for no voice
rosin on the ground I will have more
than seven yeah that's yeah give me two
points the whole thing all right two
points all the roads pigs we also thank
Lee first for the same kind of hard
yeah okay doing good oh whoa whoa are
you go for a second run but he's no good
Wow a hard start one two three okay all
right here's a tone setter sorry there's
no more break
so vibrating I would say at least
immediately three really three I dare
you to beat but slapped with a belt by
the strongest oh god that's gonna hurt
way more than that
does this mean I get revenge you over oh
ma I said we go based on how hard to
heal ya bend over Greg hey you want
something holding your alcohol at shades
all ready three two one oh my guessing
that's like more right I think that's a
sword
yeah three three are three I'm down to
three Afton 303 huh we got all right
first there's a day Jerry to get hit in
the face with a yoga ball but I do that
who's the thrower top prize a grower or
one of these athletic people oh he's
having I know I get though I volunteer
oh you points any point two points all
right
Oh your nose no my things a little sorry
I dare you to smash your head in a
chocolate cake damn the person to your
right to throw it in like that you how
can we make this better so we made us a
little bit more interesting we're gonna
blindfold Roy and basically what he has
to do it with no hands is to come here
and smash as many eggs and hate as he
can these are worth half a point and the
cake is gonna be worth a full point in
ten seconds you have to give much as you
can
hi let's make a lemon I always Hollis
alright so this is the thing tonight or
it is okay put your hands behind your
back count it down whatever right three
two one go let's get going I go when
laughing okay three two one that's one
two three points yeah so I got all over
a shirt with the three points there you
go you guys have a pillar yeah okay
girls the one I dare you to pick five
lady Cosmetics and apply it
Oh house matches just makeup yeah no can
you lead us to it
I'm one of his work where's his worth to
to okay not only you are interesting let
us put it on with our feet though I'm
digging a basically feet to the face no
make up yeah make up okay I'll do that
for three okay okay all right
barefoot you ready okay what you do is
you want to apply very holy my yard it's
so cold why is it moist liest invoice
you ever watched our Father now what we
have here is blue lip liner lipstick you
know it oh okay now other side we got to
play other side a little oh man
alright good guy really good feet
control are you trying my eyes you're
not even close I'll try to draw a smiley
face there you're not doing it right
okay my pedaling
oh this lipstick cherry on top oh hey
put that in more wasn't awful there's no
reason your foot needs to know like so
oh my god
okay done
now you're ready for the gal I sure have
just kissed me other way that's three
points my turn my turn I dare you to
drop your most precious thing oh yeah I
just got my phone fixed yesterday after
cracked screen Oh drop it on the carpet
you can drop it over you want but you
realize whatever your most valuable
thing is removing from here it's like
okay this is two three what a match
again oh nothing go break Oh
bring out the carpet five on the seam
and definitely I break on the cement oh
he oh that's way low ah that's too low
that's crazy
you're crazy it's gonna break
I dare you to duct-tape the palm of your
hand to the person to the left but for
the rest of the game is that what I
should do a quick you take me you can
take me away he says it like this I mean
the crack points for you I'll pay points
for this so put your we gotta go around
the whole body of the ham let it go
nice but I know this hands about to get
so hot all right I guess that's two
points report
oh you got it oh you feel the vibration
yeah oh yeah here we go get wedgie bye
everyone
how many points we talking I'm thinking
like a three all right
by who everyone all right good good
manis progressive again why would you do
all at once what if we lift him up yeah
oh okay all right
three two one whoo you guys with the
Mohawk all right let me make a 20-minute
break so you can dig that out
let's go Roy I dare you to get Indian oh
that's very little sorry it's like when
you do this oh yeah oh it's a it's a
fruit yeah
one three parter so you should go like
kinda hard I'll go hard and you guys go
as hard as you can all right
three two oh I still feel like oh I
still feel it like even when you take it
out any oh oh
without figuring that we're gonna have
more than one person
let's go Ryan
squeeze a clamp on your table for 60
seconds oh that mapper will cramp we can
like all flick your tongue we get where
a band and pop your tongue oh wow how
many parts before you know what is he
won I think by the high what is a one
two and three one is like right here
yeah i Rove up there nothing much that's
gonna hurt this is three no let me do a
test of my tongue
oh yes time magnify I might do the two
one that hurt doing it but rolls to you
guys that's a no but your eye you
lipstick I need a [ __ ]
Oh dirty four mystery foods blindfolded
Oh actually let me just say if you're
gonna get the win dennit racing I want
to go crazy look good by us before
things all right anything a painting
really gross
we're a bigger concoction right now some
coffee yup right there asking some salsa
okay we're gonna put something that's
good disco dude like that he might die
hey woman anyone I did so people however
who live yeah it's um cool a dinner why
not please like some sweetness no it
doesn't like share pan berries alright
so that your for think on during the
blindfold because he's already seen his
face his mercy as his old
very then we got some good old-fashioned
King Oscar anchovies - got some cat food
hospitality she gets just a strip of
cranberry juice okay you lie this is
coffee grinds salsa salsa and merengue
rule eight and Hansel and everybody's
right here ah all right I'm saying at
least a fight right each thing a big sip
of that
here we go get it all down here we go oh
is it this one little easier oh that's
so rocking some iced tea
yeah oh the rock and enjoy oh it's the
peel I got goose bumps
Oh came up and step out the knife knife
cuts up
anchovies Oh looks like baby people eat
that in pizza that's true yeah no that
was very large super salty
wow this one's nice oh oh YUM oh my gosh
let's do it yeah yeah
call it don't even taste it just wallet
there you go oh yeah all right not least
hey hey 100 swallows almost it's also Oh
Oh such a big big can do it I thought I
saw something all right
so alex is our winner we are going to
presenting with you with his prize right
now I don't even know what it is but it
was cool and your prize is thank you
very much data oh yeah not only do you
win the big robot you also get the sign
of the infamous full blame yeah
since I one can request they're always
going to do yeah you want to honor the
team yeah I know the week so we have to
do our loser dares I believe Reagan's
our loser let's go loser dear brave
yesterday lick her from one side of the
roof another goal good boy what you want
to just put your tongue out and I'll
pull you go go on the line go we're
Rhines putting his uh his trail
everybody's a little hairs they're
greedy uh-huh rinses oh yeah wasn't
earning gee washing well good job I
guess great once again thank you thank
you so much to us on your action Oh Alex
every way
and you guys so much for watching we'll
talk to you guys next time leave your
dares to comment section below
you can be completely watch out on rose
and take this I didn't do it I use more
dairy sweater your bed day a lot of
stuff today okay thing is again so much
for watching and thank you again so much
- wasabi productions make sure you guys
go check out their channel by clicking
the one below and oh and also um
remember to put your dares in the
comments below as well because we're
running out of there you need better
dares the creative more dares