warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact recreate a
reincarnated of following stunts tears
and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video if your
discretion is advised I want to talk
about how I almost set up the whole
partner you tell me where we were
because I was the gala Frankie episode
and if we draw it the players home so
they decide how many points is Worth
based on how sharing of a charity if the
player passes another player can take
the steal the first player to get ten
points do something amazingly not
amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of Fame
no just kidding they get the ball of
flame you basically write your name on a
ball of aluminum foil for the old set up
batch baking bag I have the most vine
followers in the world Guinness Book of
World Records
what's up see where these don't power I
look super for a bowling the least
amount has to do a loser dare you all
wake up our own dares throw it in a cup
and those recipe for me we try to figure
out a way Michael is a longest
fingernails
rock-paper-scissors right now alright
YouTube Labor real night Rock Paper
Scissors shoot
Oh
you can't see where you are
I mean the thing in the house is licking
your socks are a crazy streak going
always be able to watch bumping in that
way you modeling the foot you want to
make sure there's no leaves on the area
coverage is wing boom is the heavy I
might throw up
so what let you running a drug
just read like this I know I beg you to
tie your hands to your anklet
damn you guys to do other day yes if you
do like that in this do you want more
points for TVA the whole game but I'm
gonna do all their rescue the match you
can get a spot by every time it makes it
back to you and your yeah if you throw
up again
you know moody challenge how you pick
one thing what if we do with the Oreo
that's a good point no point five next
we pitched up and then depending on how
gross we decide how much is worth no I
need to know what my I don't know
that's it after the watch Discovery
Channel I think Ian's lizards and frogs
and to go this yeah you eat a roach this
is the base man we're replacing the
cream filling you know some eating
something that looks like this is my
yeah this is stinger right here it's
been do some damage
let's start the basis the spider is it
nice there we go here we go this is the
base that's a good doesn't matter the
ground dude look at this juicy dude
juicy points what I want to do this for
less than three porch like 3.5 come on
I'll do it for one I got a problem with
spicy spicy food you like spicy from I
live because I'm black you said
understand me it's stuck that's what's
this and you go halfway it does not
go all the way down when you got about
halfway down you're going to I'm cool
with two points the worst cookie
identities yeah you too duck kick
yourself to the pressing on your
yeah yeah yeah Oh
like back in the old toy you stand
between them and they both back slap at
the same time it both sides your face
alright one point hey don't hit my eyes
I miss the one he don't know how to
throw paper and he would have done it
like this you would have gets the little
bit to a point if he's good oh my oh my
foot wasn't sure he said therefore don't
boy and it's gotta be hard I gotta be
harder ago account let's go you gotta
hit him with the point then we looking
at one and a half okay
two and a half points Oh do it hard
oh just stuff it in between some so
don't fall out yeah one of the straws
hitting there bro oh man they're one of
them such a you wanted about to help him
nice buddy no come on be extra points no
you don't let the jury see how he busts
the pimple it doesn't count did you put
that up holidays from a breaking point
I'll give extra fun I made an extra
point for everybody that's a the black
so much intent when it comes out that
time that's like usual
what in toilet and Acuto oh I just peed
in their questions three times that's
all there you go new water mm-hmm bring
your mom put in mom oh my god what you
makes it look easier than I thought it
was gonna be my dear you rub a piece of
bread on four different body parts than
eat it no water
laughing else wedding night for ten
points do it do it
No
okay
in the world
I turn you for everyone cannot go in the
water hard kick you in the buff kick
your ass it goes like this someone keeps
their moderately and harder harder I am
the strongest okay alright you got ones
first kick you set the bar I don't want
the first game what's the nuts
all true king
having said we have the blame all right
we also have your price all raised our
DXT drift so once again they just to do
that here you thank you so much the King
bathroom dance store make sure you guys
like the channels are gonna be popping
up at the end so thank you guys again so
much for watching if you want to say the
last I dare you video click the one in
the middle if you want to subscribe to
batch or day story throw in the left and
right and of course last but not least
make sure you guys leave your idea
comments in the comment section below so
that we have more day as you do