warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact we create a
reincarnate and the following stunts
tears and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video your discretion
is advised
so that went on the hot side it's like
can I get a cut it'll be like a little
bit bubble up and if we draw it the
player console then decides how many
points is aware to get something amazing
hey nice that's nice
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I'm actually behind judo amateur
right here
[Music]
every time from the toilet oh that
courtesy flush or something is gonna be
so weird
[Music]
my boobs are down here buddy you know my
pocket oh this is worth four point now
[Laughter]
[Music]
- duct tape your heads together to the
present ear right
so I'm gonna get points to do 20
push-ups while everyone is tickling you
so here's the deal every pushup she
completes is point 1 but if she reaches
20 push-ups is what we wanted
oh yeah all right stub your toe in a
table today oh oh these are all burning
what this hair and you drop soup on your
feet
[Music]
on your knees
[Applause]
[Music]
ice water down everybody you are
[Applause]
all right wow congratz off inside the
ball god this has been impressive but on
the same side I think believe Kim has
the least amount points yes I don't know
why hey loser dare use the prize on
yourself you got to do it all my jumps
oh you caught it down no not good okay
it feels like just someone hit you what
a needle
[Applause]
all right thanks for teens I dare you
that's what we might see next
[Music]