blue red purple Google I just have a
happened to you I hate cops but rocking
for you I'm going to be talk about this
product right here
the necklace is what for and I know what
you say I don't need new phone a
headphone
why can't your phone do this I don't
think so
and did you know that the Nexus One is a
5 megapixel camera so you can now take
good pictures yourself Apple is not
funky book and right and you are ugly so
that people disagree with you but really
you are ugly what you still don't
understand and here I draw picture for
you there is all different type of phone
you know get a chocolate chip or the
blueberry the ice phone but what you
really want is this one the next is one
so now that you understand the neck