hey guys so I've been having a really
bad week couple weeks actually if you
don't already know a bunch of people
have been getting hacked on Instagram
for the past like couple weeks and well
I was wonderful they hacked into my
account they changed my username my
password they deleted all of my photos
for whatever reason they even took the
time to block a bunch of people that I
was following and a bunch of random fan
accounts that you guys made and I know
it's just Instagram and you might think
that I'm being overdramatic or just
overreacting but you weren't there
didn't know what it was like it's not an
easy story to tell but it went something
like this started off simple I clicked
on my Instagram and I was signed out
didn't think much of it maybe I just
needed to update it there was no update
so then I tried signing in with my
account name not Ryan he guy my
incredibly complex password a and it
still wasn't working at this point I
knew something was off so then I went to
Twitter and almost all of the tweets
were telling me that I got hacked so
then I thought well that's new at that
point I went into my email and I was
shocked I had not tens not hundreds not
thousands but seven emails from
Instagram requesting to change my
password which I know I didn't request
so finally after all the clues were
adding up I did what any other man would
think to do and said hey Shawn
he said yeah and then I said can you
check to see my Instagram got hacked and
he said okay and it was if time Stood
Still as I watched on going to my
profile and at that very moment I knew
exactly what he was going to say cuz his
face said it all it said what was your
account name again not Ryan Higa I
answered oh yeah and that's when I heard
the words that would eventually lead to
my inevitable doom yep you got act and
that's when I realized my Instagram my
life my everything was gone forever
populated with no Instagram account how
will I remember anything I've ever done
how will people know what I've been
heating why would I even work out again
if I have nowhere to show people that I
did it all of these questions had led me
to this very spot the edge of a balcony
I thought there was nowhere else to go
but down but then Sean said well you
could also come back in and we could
gonna like talk about or something
mm okay yeah you already know it
happened nothing like that that's all I
looked at my head at least this is what
it really looked like damn someone just
texted me to my Instagram got hacked
what for real yeah all your pictures are
gone dude way all of them
yeah damn that sucks so you guys wanna
go get Taco Bell yeah dude that's not
even a joke that's what really happened
we wouldn't to talk about the most pain
I felt that I was probably when I was
sitting on a toilet but in all
seriousness I really did get my
Instagram hack fortunately I was able to
get my comm back and like some of the
pictures but I still lost like over over
my life thousands of pictures that's a
crazy part the hacker had to go and
delete every single picture one by one
that there's no delete all button he has
to take the time to go and delete every
single picture and I know most people
would be extremely upset by this I'm not
gonna lie I was a little upset not even
upset I was just confused I was just
like why why would anybody do this like
what do you have to gain from this
literally this was done on a pure hey
cuz like what do you have to gain from
deleting all my pictures and blocking
people you know that I follow and
blocking fanuc owns like at least those
Anonymous hackers you know the ones that
you know where those V for Vendetta mask
like when they hack people at least
they're hacking like really important
people or like gigantic corporations and
they have reasons for why they're
hacking them not saying that that's how
it should be handled but at least they
have some kind of purpose you know this
hacking had no purpose like the only
reason to do that was to hurt me and the
people with the fan accounts that got
blogged and just because I already know
the comments no I didn't get hacked by
the anonymous people they only hacked
like really important people and like
big businesses and it's I'm not
important enough to get hacked by them I
probably should not say that asking for
don't hack me but anyway off-topic the
reason why I wasn't upset by this
hacking was because it was actually
pretty eye-opening I mean didn't make me
upset it made me realize that I'm
actually really happy because honestly
when it first happened after the shock
cleared I thought I was actually gonna
be a lot more upset than I was Instagram
Facebook YouTube that's like my entire
life and somebody tried to take away a
big part of that and honestly I felt
almost no difference I mean obviously I
was a little annoyed at first but
overall I was still Pappy you take away
my pictures I'll just post more take
away my entire Instagram account I'll
just make another same with my Facebook
and even my YouTube you take away my
YouTube channels
granted YouTube can restore them because
they have everything backed up but even
if they didn't you take away my YouTube
channels I'll just make another channel
sure I'd lose all the subscribers and
views but you actually helped me to
realize that that's not why I started
making these videos in the first place
if all I cared about was views and subs
I wouldn't have posted that 30 minute
video that I just posted last week could
easily turn that video into six
five-minute videos and upload it no 6
different videos and get literally like
six times the views but again that's not
why I do it to the hacker that did this
um I know your intention was to hurt me
or make me feel bad but really all you
were to me was an inconvenience and
honestly I'm not upset with you at all
you hacked my account deleted my photos
inconvenience me and yet I feel sorry
for you because if your life sucks that
much that you have that much hate inside
of you to do something like this I'm not
trying to say this to make you more
upset but I legitimately feel sorry for
you because I can empathize with you
I've been there I've been depressed in
the past it's not a secret if you watch
my draw my life it's all there as much
as I hate to admit it I know what it's
like to have so much hate inside of you
that you just want to spread that hate
you want the rest of the world to feel
the same pain that you feel and it makes
you even more upset when you see happy
people because you're like that that's
not fair the world's unfair trust me I
get it
I was literally you growing up except
probably not as smart cuz I don't know
how to hack things basically what I'm
trying to say is not just to the hacker
but to all of you that are watching
rather than getting mad and feeling like
the world is unfair and that you have to
get even by making someone else feel
that pain just know that these people do
these hateful things for a reason their
life sucks you don't need to get payback
they're already suffering getting angry
and wanting to spread more hate is not
gonna make you feel any better it's just
gonna turn you into one of them somebody
whose life sucks sorry this video turned
out to be such a bore I just felt that
rather than complaining to you guys and
making you feel more negativity towards
this hacker for doing this I tried to
turn this whole situation into a
positive like a learning experience I
actually had another video idea that
literally was just making fun of the
hacker and you know breaking down why he
did everything and making fun of him
then I realized that literally goes
against everything I'm saying right now
just add more negativity this video was
just to let all of you guys know that if
you're unhappy with your life making
others feel your pain is not gonna make
you feel any better I still believe that
happiness is a choice and it's on you to
make your life better no one else if you
choose to do more hateful things you're
choosing to suffer that's your own fault
the terrible things happen to everyone
but it's your own choice it's your own
decision how you deal with my situation
is the perfect example I got hacked and
right
getting upset and posting a more
negative funny video I posted this one
instead probably sure to post it the
funny one with that being said once
again I just want to thank every single
person who's still continuing to watch
my videos again I'm sorry this is not my
normal video and it turned out to be so
preachy but you know I just want to live
in a world you know where one day not
just hackers but all hateful people will
somehow turn to loathe we are anonymous
before we gosh this is such an honor
this is me Ryan I mean I I never wanted
to get hacked but the fact that it's you
guys it's such an honor I never would
have thought of myself to be that
important or so this is impurity part
gnome I'm Ryan he bought wrong browsers
new I shall posted the negative funny
video wait oh the thing is again so much
for watching if you wanna see last
week's video clicked on the lever you
want to see the previous rad video
clicked on the right and let me just say
if you're gonna click last week's video
it's 30 minutes long so make sure you
guys have at least an hour