hey guys so this video is something that
I never thought I would actually do
clickbait I'm not quitting YouTube well
I didn't actually say that I was gonna
quit but you know having the words quit
and YouTube in the title it kind of you
know it's kind of quick beat but it's
not I promise and at the same time it's
still not completely untrue let me
explain the truth is guys over the past
year or so i am i sorry it's just um
it's just really hard for me to gather
my thoughts when there's loud cheesy
emotional music just playing right in my
ear as it was saying I already told you
guys I'm not quitting but there are
gonna be a lot of changes and let me
just let me just start for the top so
that I can explain over the past year I
really have been considering quitting
YouTube see this is why I can't have a
serious heart-to-heart talk with you
guys because I keep cutting away from
random things it's my own fault and him
trying to make this all sad it's not
saying look guys all jokes aside let me
just be real for a sec it's not that I
don't want to do YouTube and I trust me
I do realize how great of an opportunity
it has been for me and and still is but
I just wasn't having fun making YouTube
videos anymore and I know it's a
first-world problem okay I'm not having
fun in my job I'm not everybody's
supposed to have fun at their job but in
order to create really good content and
unique things you have to have fun doing
it at least that's what I believe in not
a machine like other youtubers I need
inspiration I mean that's one of the
reasons why I hardly posted last year
and it took me pretty much the entire
year to realize why I found myself
falling into the typical youtuber trap
of trying to create videos that work
versus trying to create videos that well
you're inspired to make things that you
want to even if that means creating
videos that I know for a fact that a lot
of you guys probably not like or
understand are most likely be offensive
the kind of videos I used to make when I
first started to you know when I wasn't
afraid of disappointing people or being
too offensive or getting less views or
whatever I just finally realized at the
in the last year that I was forcing
myself to create videos that I don't
even feel like me
and I was holding back so many different
things that I really wanted to make I
just was too afraid to do it by the way
I'm not talking about all the videos
last year in fact towards the end of
last year I started posting some of the
videos that I wanted to post n I felt
the consequences I mean I saw the views
drop the dislikes go up but honestly I
feel better because I it's something
I've been wanting to say I'm sure you
can figure out which videos I'm talking
about but anyway once I made the
realization that I wasn't having fun
anymore
towards the end of last year I knew that
I had to do something about it and make
a decision either I need to just do
something else and quit youtube entirely
or I need to make changes and make
YouTube fun for me again and just start
posting you know whatever the hell I
want to post and do the shows that I
want to do despite all the negative
consequences that come with it the
dislikes and the bad comments and you
know you losing subs whatever it is just
I just have to do those things because
that's the whole reason why I started
YouTube in the first place all I had to
do was stop caring stop caring about the
things that don't matter stop being
afraid of failure and take chances and
try new things things that I would have
never done you know in the previous
years but if that's what it takes to
allow me to continue to do this and and
have fun doing it then then I'm just
gonna do it that's what I decided until
I realize just how much easier it would
be to just quit YouTube entirely and
just do something else so I went with
that so over the holidays I really
thought about if I were to quit YouTube
I can't just do nothing I had to think
what else could I possibly do and
obviously my first instinct was to do
something similar to what I already do
entertainment I always wanted to be an
actor and right now specifically for
Asians it's a great time to be an actor
the whole Asian movie going on you know
spring diversity and one now Asian
actors are kind of a hot commodity right
now trust me I know what Hollywood's
looking for hi I'm Ryan Higa and I'm
here to the audition for the role of
Glenn okay whenever you're ready
[Music]
I need you to promise me that if I don't
come back for the pharmacy I need you to
be strong live on and do we put a little
more because I just give you what are
you doing acting yeah and I'm sorry what
kind of accent what are you doing I
didn't like the race not sure if you
know that knows what Glen is an Asian
American character who was born and
raised in Georgia I'm so sorry I just
assumed because this is Hollywood and I
saw Asian written the character
Elizabeth that's okay
what does take from the top again okay
remember that he's born and raised in
Georgia Georgia got it okay
I am from Georgia and I need I think
we're what no no no please I I can do
better
just give me notes or anything to find
one more time on the top and just lose
the accent but the character it says he
has a slight accent a southern one
because he's born and raised in Georgia
Southern oh my god I can do southern I
can do southern last time Maggie I need
you to promise me I don't come back for
that one mercy
I need you
bing-bong linglong do it over ding dong
eating John little and scene
I am improv the song at the end I'm sure
you guys can get the rights I even
thought about some other jobs that are
not entertainment related I mean I've
never been opposed to a regular
nine-to-five job or a part time job I
probably won't initially get the best
job because I dropped out of college so
I'd like a normal job you know one that
requires basic skill I mean I have a ton
of amazing advanced basic skill I could
wait tables I mean I've done that before
just in case it gets you know a little
windy or out here anything else you guys
need and you you know what I didn't take
your order yet huh
I'll be back Oh was that me Dwayne
Johnson yeah oh she could be a
babysitter I mean I raised my dogs is
they were puppies it's basically the
same thing if no one wants to hire me
uber driving I'll be my own boss I
actually think I would be an amazing
uber driver I mean look at me I'm aja
you know what they say about Asian
drivers Rex oh great
driver yep better buckle up and if none
of the other things work out the very
last thing I thought about doing and
trust me this is the last thing I could
think of I thought about going back to
school and getting my degree in nuclear
medicine which was my original plan
before I dropped out but the thing is
I'm a different person now okay a whole
decade has passed since I've been in
college with all the knowledge that I
gained over the years here on YouTube
this time around college is gonna be
like nothing hey you um you wanted to
see me yes Ryan this was supposed to be
your final thesis essay and you starting
it off with hey guys yes I know it is
it's a little rough in the beginning but
it builds it's a pillar essay and it
gets better like by the conclusion it's
pretty strong with that being said thank
you for reading if you like this thesis
please leave an A and be sure to
subscribe for more essays coming soon
they are coming
you can't honestly expect me to accept
this can you I mean this is ridiculous
what first off you didn't even type it
out and not only did you not type it out
but you never write in a pen you use
pencil well note that I could definitely
and I can convert that if you give me
like two or three days and how many
times have I told you I do not want you
using puns in your essays I honestly do
not recall writing the single one in
there like if if there is a point it's
probably my thesis I will prove that a
plant can survive off the flash of a
camera guess you could call it my
photosynthesis lol yeah I should have
took the lol oh right students at this
university has been months months
working on their essays and we spent one
maybe an hour and tops okay no okay that
is that part is untrue okay you know
what that is that is just a that is a
sort of machine that doesn't take coins
it's nonsense
because the ending statement alone took
me over an hour maybe even more than
that really
yeah this just took you an hour the four
sentences four sentences that that's
ending see that's a conclusion on the
back of that back of one at the end
[Music]
it's supposed to get out okay overall
what I'm trying to say is there's gonna
be changes on this channel and I know
that a lot of you praise me and respect
me for not changing my content over the
years but this is something I have to do
for myself now that doesn't mean that
I'm gonna stop posting the videos that
you guys are used to it just means that
in between those videos because you know
those videos take a lot longer to make
sometimes a couple weeks to a month
sometimes two months I am gonna be
posting other things as well the other
things that I've been too afraid to pull
it's like rants that don't necessarily
have skits in them or skits that don't
necessarily have vlogs ridiculous songs
that we've made that make me and my
friends laugh probably not you guys know
podcast that I've been wanting to do and
I know it's not something completely
unique every youtuber has one now but
we've already done a few and I just love
doing them I love being able to just
talk about things on a deeper level with
people and not not just comedy things
that actually matter to the world it's a
whole nother side to me that you're
gonna see you're gonna see that I'm a
serious person and we discuss very
important issues contrary to most guys I
don't like gigantic boobs do you guys
think that um ninja is authentic you
don't love skirts just listen tomato
fresh cheese yes I see ways Oh simple to
say uh sir mustard Dijon I got really
deep we start talking about bestiality
my grades all important things that
really matter to this world off the pill
podcast coming soon anyway I know a lot
of you aren't gonna be sticking around
for all these changes and these
different types of videos maybe we'll
only see you on the you know the bigger
videos it wasn't you guys are used to or
maybe never again but I just want to
take this time to say thank you to
everybody who stuck around all the
people who have been watching over the
years I mean if you made it this far
into the video you're probably one of
them because it's pretty boring thank
you guys for being a loyal thank you
guys for continuing to why especially if
they're last year where I barely posted
anything ever since I really consider
quitting YouTube I actually had time to
think about it and it's honestly amazing
that I have been able to do this for so
long and it's really all because of you
guys some of you have been here over 10
years it's crazy sorry I know this is
weird for me especially for you people
who have been around for so long you
guys know me I don't like ending videos
cheesy like this but like I said changes
and I know it sounds selfish but I need
to do it for myself and I just think
it's time for me to just you know be
more open and honest and real with you
guys because again all jokes aside and
take away all the skits from this video
you guys are one of the main reasons why
not only do I want to continue doing
this but why I'm even able to just thank
you okay thank you guys I like I said I
hate those emotion over the emotional
video there just seems so fake but you
guys have no idea how much this one is
good yeah kind of see this is why I need
the podcast I can't ever have a serious
moment in here
oh yeah speaking of changes I'm droppin
a music video next week and I don't know
if it's a diss track but it's the
closest thing I've ever gotten to one
it's not really a diss is just basically
telling the truth because I am going to
be exposing a bunch of youtubers that
I've met over the years not all of them
just the ones that I've met in person
the ones that I feel need to show their
fans what they're really like outside of
YouTube so get ready because in a week
everyone
well not everyone like I mean like I
said just buried the specific youtubers
that I met that I feel like their fans
should know what that just next week
doesn't there's a music video coming out
next weekend just check it out I don't
know whatever