it is a war that has raged for centuries
rebel forces have slowly been wiped out
by the ever going on we have neglected
Empire you find out why are you reading
it at that angle huh just hold it up oh
yeah this is way easier we find her here
on a companion look
[Music]
have passed since the force last working
when there was the last Jedi that's when
I first awoke him
[Music]
that's impossible
I've never seen anything like that
before what force know an Asian lead
character why wake me after all this
time because we need you
there's a force it's more powerful than
ever led by an individual known as Darth
something this side which opposes ours
has grown and contained more than ever
before this side which has keep saying
this side are you talking about a dark
side or what don't just say that they
can say don't use terms like dark and
light anymore it's incredibly offensive
just all our side and the other side now
didn't know like just woke up you know
like one hour side the other side
everything we worked for
[Music]
Oh what are you supposed to be what do
you mean I'm I'm a stormtrooper you
don't look like the other guys I know
Darth suck me he cut the stormtrooper
budget so I got stuck with the old gear
okay well
[Music]
I mean two lightsabers
my god the FTE walkers to Stacey Walker
so that's ancient technology those are
athe gliders much faster physically
they're gonna be popular for like two
months and then suddenly disappear her
[Music]
why didn't you just do that in the first
place
[Music]
Tom you knew that
[Applause]
[Music]