hey guys so I was at the gym playing
basketball not very long ago that was
pretty much inspired to make this video
I witnessed two grown men almost get
into a fistfight over who got to play
the next game and that was actually
gonna do a cutaway reenact me exactly
what happened then but I feel like this
next cutaway shows it even better get
over it now it's my turn to swing it's
not your turn it's my turn out no I
called yeah so you want next
[Music]
that's pretty much exactly what happened
when men actually that immature has got
to be one of the most annoying things
ever that's why from now on looking at
the new and improved mature Orion that
was supposed to be the transition you
know going into the next
[Music]
ya know this jacket is way too hot to
film inside shut up
anyway as I was saying grown immature
men are one of the most annoying things
ever don't get me wrong there's immature
girls as well but everyone knows that
it's a scientifical fact that women
mature faster than guys I think I mean
take Justin Timberlake for example he's
trying to look more mature and and
trying to be more grown-up by doing this
whole suit-and-tie thing what about
Justin Bieber he's trying to change his
image as well no longer known as that
innocent teenybopper star anymore I mean
he used to be just didn't even and now
he's like Justin Bieber now that works
out and gets tattoos and gets caught
with drugs and and post pictures of
himself half-naked on Instagram I like
them and seeing all these changes happen
you know I want to be cool too I can
mature I can grow up I can have the name
Justin so for all of you guys I want to
be more mature like me gives mature
sounds like manure oh here's some things
that I learned want maturing myself up
let's start with the whole reason I
started this video fighting
see immature guys always want to fight
over everything whether it's because
they can't control the anger or the
charm Poupon tough they are it's just
really immature
see I can pitch a price like 45 I mean I
can only bench friends like to plays but
pretty soon it's gonna be three deep
like I'm thinking sup bro what you
checking out my girl yeah and what if I
was where you want go right now let's go
now take that same situation but with
mature guy it's probably handled that
situation in a much more civilized
manner what you checking out my girl
yeah and what if I was where you want go
right now let's go where you want to go
why we talk this over some coffee at
Starbucks Starbucks is kind of expensive
what about McDonald only got no
blueberry schools they got hella
chuckling gym Google ain't no blueberry
school does the same thing it's not but
why don't we make a drive-through stop
at McDonald's and meet at Starbucks in
ten minutes why not okay good I'll see
you soon can I catch a ride with you my
car's lower gas oh yeah there's nothing
wrong with playing video games as long
as you manage your time wisely see if
you're immature like how I used to be
from personal experience it probably
looks something like this
[Music]
go go go go go
damn it see you took so long another all
day all my blueberries see a mature
person would be a lot smarter I think we
need to stop playing video games can be
good for our health you know what I mean
what else is there to do though play
video games the real life like what
really fruit ninja I guess it couldn't
hurt to try
damn you all right dude immature people
listen to mature music but mature people
we listen to the classic like subida or
queen or Jerry or but your men have
matured diets it's important to eat
healthy when you're a grown man
hey man I'm actually headed to the store
right now you need anything no I'm good
dude
all right Oh actually pick me about hot
pocket just like the pizza one yeah sure
actually you know what just give me a
whole box of those okay and why don't
they could you pick me up some top ramen
the chicken and the beef and oh look
they have the spicy want me to get that
- OH
ah while you're there you should give me
some subjects some chips just get like
two three bags you probably Oh pretzels
lots of pretzels mustard pretzel slow
now I'm not they still have that but if
not just get some pretzels and then get
some muscly one beforelol speaking of
mustard could you get me like two or
three thirty boxes of pop-tarts
seriously cinnamon ones and then maybe
like 20 blueberries 20 strawberries I
don't know you can make some ketchup
chips pose her soul balm I don't know if
we got them in this it's in Canada but
if you're stopping by
Canada that'd be nice maybe some Cheetos
Hot Cheetos talkies talkies Hot Cheetos
and takis least getting that because we
can do like the song eat anything else
Prince Ryan skittles lots of skittles
starburst pickles detergent oh Tulear
bottle Pepsi that was good actually no I
think about it this one's kind of hell
diet pepsi in hot pockets it may have
been entertaining in the past with grow
up real men don't watch cartoons hey do
you watch Naruto
no do you I don't know do you I mean I
guess like sometimes like everything's
united told me and when the first comes
out online so you do watch it yeah hey
do you watch Naruto no what other than
your own do you what kind of question is
that anyway what are you trying to say
that I'm immature then I'm the kind of
immature guy that would watch cartoons
just like bullies get a life grow up
read a book the number one way to spot
an immature person about what they find
fun if you want to be mature
you must never again make any Bartos sex
jokes fat jokes
your mom your mama's so fat that when
she sat in the chair it broke bro and of
course the most immature penis jokes
[Applause]
obviously I exaggerated all these
example but you know what I'm trying to
say at some point in time all you
immature guys out there need to go I'm a
guy too so I understand how fun video
games are and how funny penis jokes in
and fart jokes can but the fact of the
matter is and the real reason I made
this video is because I'm getting older
and I'm tired of being called immature
in real life so if you're looking for
any more cheap laughs or or immature
comedy I suggest you look somewhere else
oh yeah I'm thinking about starting a
gaming channel