can we got popular for sex tape I got
famous off of a booty pick on history
everyone's human I have days where I
wake up and I feel this disgusting and
fat I like you at myself you know I
looking at me on like disgusting damn
Christian Baja but I think no that works
alright we're just gonna start with this
and we don't need the intro song welcome
back to another episode about the peel
podcast I got David with me in the
moderator see we got Paco right here I'm
Ryan and we have a very special guest
miss summer Rae
so some for people who don't know on
Instagram you have 2.20 1.8 million
followers and on YouTube 1.5 million
subscribers but you were on Instagram
first YouTube just to kind of mess
around with it I did it for like six
months and then I stopped doing it like
just cold turkey just stopped I'm trying
to do it again because I feel like that
was like the most like authentic fanbase
ever like Instagram it's just not the
same so I was like I need to get back to
you so you actually see the difference
between the two yeah well like what it
is exactly yeah why is it more engaging
on YouTube than Instagram I think is
because like on Instagram
you just sir on there you like scroll
you see a picture you think of girls ha
blah
you don't like know them you don't know
anything about them you know on YouTube
you go on you watch someone you could be
in your room watch these kids are in the
room watching you for hours like they
know everything about you they're so
connected to you like I've had kids come
up to me and say things my home why do I
know you like it's so weird but like on
Instagram before I did YouTube it's not
like that it's just like they recognize
you but they don't know you and it's
like more of like a personal connection
that I like right but you did it for
like six months and you stopped is it
because you what burnout or what um I
don't know I just like I don't think I'm
a great youtuber so I don't really know
I don't know what to do on YouTube I'm
like
they want to see like cuz I would do
vlogs but like I had friends or
youtubers and it was kind of fun to like
just do it with them but I find myself
I'm like what do they want to see so now
I'm starting to do like more fitness
stuff I want to like do like Fitness
Fridays and I want to like show them
like like I feel like no one really
knows me as a part like even on my
youtube channel I just was like messing
around like I knew I want people to like
like get to know me as like a person
yeah but that's what I mean you said
you're thinking about starting again oh
I'm just starting again but it's so
weird cause if you're not consistent the
views go yep
oh way and they don't come back you have
to like work it from scratch again I'm
like damn it and I just have to like not
care about music who cares about you
guys I mean we care a little bit but you
know you just have let that you go down
go and be like I don't care [ __ ] usually
the people are able to say who cares
about the views get good enough use
usually Oh mine are sucking right now
yeah pretty bad but it's fine it's all
relative right yeah I'm not a youtuber
I'm just doing it for fun right what do
you consider yourself ah I don't know I
hate when people say I G model like it's
not that I don't like this not that I
one um like cuz I feel like I've like
really been like a big part of the
making Instagram models I have been an
Instagram model forever I'm like an OG
Instagram model but now what girls post
on Instagram I don't like to be
associated with it like no one has any
respect for themselves they post the
most raunchy things I'm just like okay I
don't like Instagram model now because
it's like no respect like obviously I
post pictures on my body but I have
respect for myself and there's certain
things that I just wants the line that
you don't cross like I don't do like new
like I hardly do any like implied like
girls are literally posting but I saw
this girl like her whole page she's just
like posting pictures of her she puts a
little thing over her nipples like in
her vagina like naked cuz I'm like I
just can't like it's like there's a fine
line there's like classy like I work
hard for my body I'm gonna show it off
because I mean I got me where I am today
and like but there's a fine line of just
like you go to their page you're like
okay this is too much like I won't want
my mom seen this was porn right yeah
it's like porn so a lot of things like I
think I don't like being called
Instagram model because there's no
respect you know it's like I deserve
respects you guys come on well you said
you that you don't want you there's some
things you're you wouldn't want your mom
to see yeah and I mean how do you feel
about the current stuff that you're
posting right well they are they cool
with it like funny because I actually
when I was a kid I'm from 16 to 18 I was
a bodybuilder like bikini so I'm in a
bikini on stage in my dad's my coach so
I literally would be posing and all this
kinda stuff in a tiny bikini he's my dad
and it's not a sexual thing like when
you're in that industry and stuff it's a
whole like world and it's not like it's
not gross it's not sexual it's this is
my body this is heart like I've sculpted
my body to look this way it's like that
it's so I've been raised in a different
way to view bodies like I view bodies as
art like I don't view it like I've never
even watched porn like I've never been
on I don't like I wanna watch porn
people are probably like a liar I'm like
no I really have never watched porn and
by accident while on Twitter I'm like oh
my gosh
but yeah I've just like been raised not
to think of the human body like how
people like think of it you know people
think of a naked body whatever like oh I
wanna never I wanna I think wow that
probably took a lot of hard work in the
gym like you know so it's like a
different way to look at it like I I
mean I saw a video I'm not sure where it
was from I can't remember but you said
something about like you really like
enjoy eating but that's why you work out
yeah so I think life is really short so
why I have those views is because I used
to compete 16 to 18 like a cheap meal
would be having a protein bar like that
is like okay like having a like Lily
your diet has to be so strict you have
camp any fatty or whatever and like Mike
I was so young and my quality of life
sucked like I was just like wow like
every side like I got into like an
eating disorder like like messed up my
mind with food and everything because
it's like it was really like
traumatizing and now I just moderation
that's my thing there's a balance like
I'm not just gonna eat cheeseburgers
every day have fun I'm gonna have a
cheeseburger and then I'm a salad it's
called balance so often though we're
coping you probably work out like every
day right yeah I try to work out every
day I mean I used to be really really
consistent but like I'm so busy now the
like sometimes I get off-track but yeah
I mean Ally I eat what I want but the
I'm also blessed with a good metabolism
cuz like I can really eat what I want
and I burn it off really quick but yeah
I think that everybody is different in
somebody some people like can't eat what
they want because they gain weight and
stuff so it's just like to eat teach
their own you know it's like everyone's
different but I just live my truth like
people don't want you to live your life
like you say like no you can't get
that's like no I'm doing I'm not saying
you can't do it or can do it I'm saying
this is what I do I mean so you you said
you wanted to get into wellness and what
was it fitness and stuff and yeah I mean
a channel oh yeah like I like came like
when I first got popular off Instagram
it's like Fitness like fitness videos on
all the fitness stuff and then I kind of
like went out of the fitness world a
little bit and I want to get back in
this mm-hmm and like teaching people
yeah it's like I'm working out videos
like teaching girls how to work out farm
like telling them what I eat how to work
out like I'm also I'm like doing a
fitness app with fit plans so they can
like download that up and hang out with
me that already not yet okay I have
something coming soon yeah is that what
you're using you've been more busy is
that wood you've been working on I've
been working on a lot of fun stuff but
yeah so I have like a clothing line
called shop summer-rae whatever it's
just like athletic wear but like stuff I
have in the works it's um you know like
subscription box are really in right now
so I'm like you know I'm gonna have like
a buy monthly subscription box $39.99
like bimonthly and it's gonna be filled
with like fitness stuff beauty stuff
like lifestyle like a big box of stuff
that gets sent to your house and I'm
having a boy
box to a girl and boy so like the boy
box will have boy stuff and the girl box
box it's called some things like Somm e
th ing s like summer things like
something like Christmas every month
every other month because I don't want
to overdo it you know it's like it's fun
like I love getting stuff in the mail
like an you forget about it you get like
a package it's like oh wow it every
month it's different like it's gonna be
really fun like things that you'd never
would even think til I go by or like
fine and you get sent them you're right
oh I'm I can't live it
this now so do you have a peel box for
fans yeah I actually have one in saans
and like on Sunset in Hollywood but I
never go to it because I used to live
like up this street from there so now I
like never go that I swear that they
throw away my email
cuz I'll go in there like I'll send me
back no they do something because I'll
get emails that I have boxes and stuff
and then I go in there and pick them up
they're like oh you have nothing here
I'm like hmm
really I'm pretty sure they send it back
because it got hold on I'm sure you get
a lot of mail right well I don't really
give out my PA box like that I mean I
give it to like brands and stuff I don't
just give it to like I don't know I
don't know what they wanna say yeah well
I mean speak maybe I should do a fun uh
you
I mean I'm gonna just assume you have
some pretty crazy stories there right
that's a shock
cuz every girl we've had on here has had
their own story and especially for you I
would feel like you would have some
pretty crazy stalker stories or
something like some some really weird
fan experiences
yeah like sliding people weird people
sliding in stuff like that but I think I
just don't even think about it just like
that was weird yeah it's hard I've been
so often it's just like I don't even
know what is weird like maybe like some
of the stories I thought girls would say
I'm like that's not weird that happens
to me every day yeah
are you or were you at living at the
cloud house mm-hmm so your current is
that where you're currently yet no so
that's when I lived in Hollywood I live
with them it's so funny because everyone
thinks it as a cloud house so actually
Brian rice is what I'm like like really
early good friends like when we first
kind of started popping off on the
internet we like met up and we like just
really been like really good friends
since then so a few years ago like a
year ago maybe almost two yeah two years
ago it's crazy time flies he hit me up
and he was like hey I'm moving into this
house like we're looking for some
influencers if you want to come live
with us and I was like I was already
living summer at the time so I just
couldn't but then it was weird cuz a
couple months went by and I actually
needed somewhere to live I'd even think
about it again but he called me again
and asked me I was like oh yeah actually
well so the time I was only him and
Ricky banks and
yeah I was me him and and then that's
before like Alyssa like started dating
him around that time it didn't really
live there were just like stay there all
the time and then she moved in and then
it like kind of formed into a class
house but everyone thinks I like moved
into the class house and it I had to
look up what that was
oh oh you know Brian yeah well yeah so
we met up before he moved out there we
need hang out a lot we played basketball
and stuff like that but yeah okay well
that's good to know I thought we were
just wondering you're like one of the
founding fathers of it than in the way
yeah no one really does anything with it
anymore like Clubhouse but I mean the
clock and also like the phase house you
know like phase yeah yeah but yeah those
are like I love them like family so I
just moved out because I have so much
crap that I was like I don't have enough
room for this stuff so just because just
because it was tweeted to us a lot
mm-hmm
did you and Brian ever everything it's
so funny cuz everyone thinks that yeah
but you know he needs to do it for the
the views he would like kind of make it
seem so he would like put in the
thumbnail like me and my girlfriend and
then in the description it would be
because she's my friend and she's a girl
but no one would catch that you know
right you wanted to kind of like click
bake that like we're dating we've never
had a thing we've it's like literally
he's like a brother to me like I've said
that so many times in videos your videos
your brother to me but it's like I mean
I just me if people like but helps with
the views helps with the views you know
if some kids want to carry on the rest
of their life thinking that we are
boyfriend/girlfriend so be it but yeah
it's not true open are you about that
part of your life
I like relationships an Instagram I mean
you can show what you want to show right
yeah am I like um like I always say like
things I really really care about things
are the most important to me that I love
I like to keep private because people
like to get involved they like to like
kill your happiness like true so it's
like if they don't what they don't know
about they can't mingle with or like try
to kill so that's a very private and
you're you're actually uh I guess kind
of younger like you're 22 yeah how long
have you been doing this cuz you
kind of started pretty early in yeah
like four years ago like that's like
four or five years ago like probably I
don't know guys
time flies flies by I'm like what I was
like I started when I was like 17 18 and
now I'm 22 so but I didn't like really
start like getting popular until I was
like 18 19 Wow did that change like what
changed what what made you pop off ah at
one moment or is it gradual I like
that's before I moved to LA and stuff
and I started working with photographers
I got something like really viral
content like the stuff I was posting all
when like viral and stuff and I don't
know I think that people just like liked
the naturalness about me and like my
booty and everything like a lot of girls
that were on Instagram like not doing
like the fitness I like booty stuff that
I was doing but they're like everyone
has fake boobs fake everything fake
slips it's like I'm just like
authentically me and like I've always
been I feel like people can see that and
I think they just liked it and yeah I
always liked booty stuff is out so weird
but it's like I work really hard for my
video okay I that's like my like my
struggle is like I don't ever I don't
want to be like girl or whatever but
that is just like but that's like that's
like a guys pecs in it yeah but I can't
step away from like what got me popular
I mean Kim got popular off a sex tape I
got famous off of a booty pic on
Instagram it's fine that you worked hard
for it looked hard for it okay yeah I
got these games Kay Wow issue with it I
mean I think that it's in my head cuz
you're coming in to other people right
yeah like I look at other girls and I'm
like I hope people don't think of me
like all right so if there's a younger
let's say someone I guess we were 17
when you started someone like a 17 year
old who wants to follow that path what
would you say to them I would say just
like stay - oh my my advice is like see
authentic to you so that really is your
goal and you literally love working out
and you really like like if that's what
you love and you're not doing it because
you saw someone do it and got popular
off of it but it's because you want to
do it because when I did it I didn't see
anyone do it and be like oh I want to
copy that and follow that and do it I
didn't know what it was gonna be I was
just doing what I love and posting it on
the Internet posting my pictures of
working out and stuff and it turned into
this so it wasn't like I saw someone
and I was like I'm gonna do that you
know so it's like I think the real like
pioneers in life are the originators who
like create and like try it like do
something that you're really passionate
about that is new and like original and
that's how you succeed so I agree with
that totally like I think the only way
to become as because you have on
Instagram is like you just said
originators ten years you did your own
thing you didn't really imitate others
yeah they're people on the platform
that's my thing my whole messaging is
like be you and it's like because I
always see girls always like copying
everyone copying me and it's not
anything like I just feel bad for them
because it's like I just want them to
like find themselves and like just
embrace who they are because if you're
always gonna be copying people you're
always gonna change you're never gonna
know who you are because that girl that
you're obsessing over right now
might change next year you're gonna be
another girl it's like it's like be you
like you can find inspiration like
obviously what I have done and graded
it's not like I'm the only one who can
do it it's just like put your own twist
on it do different things like don't
copy like you can find inspiration but
it's different you know when you say
people copying you what exactly do you
what can you like specify on like what
specific thing it's not really copying
or whatever but you know like I I was
one of the first like girls on the
internet who posted pictures of her body
on Instagram you know and I like there
was other girls doing it like booty pics
and stuff but I took it to the next
level okay and I like started posting
like booty videos like bounce around my
buttons up and like no one did videos
and then I did so it's now it's like you
go to any girls video page just trying
to be a booty model they have like the
pictures the videos and seven the thing
is it's hard to get like really popular
off doing that now cuz its oversaturated
like everyone's trying to do it so I was
like one of the first so it's like that
but it's not really copying it's like
every everyone copies everyone that is
the thing of life it's like no you have
to learn it from somewhere you have to
agree so I start copying me it's just I
know where they're finding their
inspiration but you start noting that I
said and I find it interesting you start
if you said body building right so and
your dad was your coach I'm assuming
he's jacked
oh yeah so yeah he's body building is
that because you grew up on a branch
you said I mean I grew up on
branch but before I was even born he was
like a bodybuilder that's like what he
did and they got married then he kind of
got out of it but my mom and him got
divorced and then he started
bodybuilding again but yeah I've grew
I've worked out my whole life we had a
gym in the basement in my house growing
up I was a daddy's girl I was always
with him always working out yeah so
working on just in my blood it's like
what I love so it's like if girls want
that to be their lifestyle then live it
and if you come back successful off of
it that's amazing and your method is
work out so that you can still eat not
starve I work I just work out what I
want
moderation balance and yeah a lot of
girls like they think like not eating is
gonna get the like so many people always
like oh I'm trying to lose weight I'm
not gonna eat people don't understand
that when you don't eat your body
we're machines like our bodies are like
brilliant like we're always in like like
like trying to live like that's art like
our body's purpose you know so when you
starve yourself and then you eat your
body will like store it as fat you guys
starvation mode so you're not not ever
gonna eat these girls who are starving
themselves for like five days then
they're just gonna go and eat a ton
because you're starving and then your
body's gonna store as fat so my advice
five small meals a day like are you
still so that that does work for you
then yeah it does work for everyone
some things work for other people but
that's like what I look for me
I don't think starving works for anyone
yeah you're gonna lose weight but right
it's not the right type of weight you
know because it's not healthy it's more
what am i and how do you feel about like
intermittent fasting I think it about
fasting fasting no like it is good if
you really intermediate that's what
that's called right yeah close enough
yeah it's good if you really have a good
schedule and you know exactly what
you're doing a lot of people are doing
it and they think that they know what
we're doing and like what do you have no
idea like it's all times and like a
certain amount of time not to eat to eat
they just hear someone's time so like oh
I'm gonna do that too right I'm like pay
but that's not matching your lifestyle
like you have to like plan it out for
you like in The Times and everything so
you have to actually like
knowledgeable about it before you do it
so many so many fads like oh I'm gonna
do that so once I was doing it it's like
okay but you have to like sculpt it to
your your day not always fun like those
diets I mean the fads they work right to
a certain degree I think if you do it
that the problem is for a lot of people
they don't necessarily have your mindset
of having two how would you how would
you say that you created this to be your
lifestyle because that seems to be the
key because you want to work out a lot
of people don't want that's the thing I
I make it a lifestyle you know some
people they're like I'm gonna go to the
gym and that's like a thing that I'm
gonna dread and I'm just gonna do it
because I have to do it like I have to
go to the gym me I'm like I'm gonna go
to the gym that's a part of my life it's
a part of my day I'm excited to go like
me and my mama boys made go in the gym
like the highlight of her day like the
fun part like we didn't go to the gym
and I gotta go to the gym got hard work
me and mom hang out there for hours we
have millions of friends really having
the best time like I think it's just all
I'm like like how I just find shame it's
right I mean I think everyone has like
if you've ever liked your past
experience is like if you're gonna go at
Disneyland you're gonna have the worst
time ever you're not gonna always think
back you make oh my god I love
Disneyland like I think back and think
of all the great times I've had working
out and I'm like oh my god I love
working out
so check you have to make it fun the
moment you make it a job it's a job so
I've never made working out a job it's
just a fun I'm sure but I'm sure there
has to be some days where you're just
like I don't want oh yeah for sure
sometimes I'm like definition and do you
go normal right I mean I I don't work
out every single day like obviously I'm
not like some crazy person but yeah
sometimes I have days sometimes five
days where I'm even like a bad mood I'm
I'm down on myself like with things like
that people don't understand it's like
everyone's human I have days where I
wake up and I feel this disgusting and
fat and I like you at myself you know I
look at me I'm like disgusting so we're
as girls we just like have this like and
every girl's is saying like it doesn't
matter like girls that think girls like
are the most beautiful girl in the world
trust me they wake up and they hate
themselves somedays - it's just like
life as a girl and as humans like you
know so yeah I have days I'm very
unmotivated and I think my body sucks
and I want to knock it out of bed all
day so in life but
I fight there like how I find my
motivation is like I don't look for
motivation like oh I want to get in
shape for this pool-party or I want to
get in shape because I'm going on
vacation like coz right when that is
over you're gonna forget about working
out and you don't care about working out
anymore you have to do it for like a
real reason that's not going to go away
you know and it seems like a you know
the whole thing with like nature versus
nurture where like this how you
naturally are this is how you're raised
it seems like a lot of things that are
very positive about you is because of
your how we were raised
yeah your upbringing and a lot of things
that you credit so you know being with
your dad he was constantly working out
so you were you saw that work ethic you
know that was built into you and just
the positivity in your mindset and how
you view things optimistically it's
almost like all of that together is
built up a lot of your brand so you went
from like og IG model and to become kind
of like a role model now and you're
turning that into that aspect so I'm
just curious it's like what is your
future because we're discussing a lot
about your past right now but like what
are the future steps for you a future I
just want to UM like I feel like in the
world today like there's no like really
really amazing like role models or
models or anyone that little girls can
look up to that are all natural just
embrace themselves have their big bushy
eyebrows natural everything and never
gone like any surgeries done or anything
and like no offense of people who do get
surgeries but I think that there should
be someone in the world for girls to
look up to and be like that's my role
model you know and there's just no one
in the world right now really like that
so I want to be that role model for
girls I want to teach them to love their
natural selves and they don't have to
change anything to be like perfect or
fit into society because how boring
would it be a world that we all look the
same because with surgeries people start
looking the same it's not fun anymore
like surgery is also unhealthy like very
dangerous to go under the knife just for
your looks and stuff so it's like I want
to teach girls that there is no standard
of beauty you're beautiful because
that's how you look and you're beautiful
the way you are look I understand when
girls like are born they have like
really big noses and they don't feel
confident they you really need get that
but people take it a little overboard
and they have already butyl
features and then they ruin them you
know and now it's like oh well you were
so beautiful before why'd you do that to
yourself so I want to be like a really
good role model for girls and I just
want to be like a mogul you know like
you know those people that are like so
big and you're like how are they in this
movie how are they major and you're just
like they're just like a name that like
you just they can do what they want I
just want to be able to do whatever I
want mm-hmm that's a good goal yeah and
people like how she do it I don't know
like you know like you don't know like
why they're so big they just art right
what are you not doing right now that
you wish you could do in the future
um well you mentioned like movies you
just mentioned like oh my I mean that
you want to be I would I would probably
wanna be I've never had like I've never
gone to an acting coach or never done
anything so it's like I think um if I
give a shine I love it but it's one of
those things I like to do things I love
so if I did it I hated it I just won't
pursue it because it's not something I
love but if I did it I loved it I want
to pursue it because I I don't want to
do anything that feels like work and
it's not not fun like I think everything
should be fun and like do stuff there's
so many things you can do in the world
do something you love you know so okay
life is short
she said eat yeah what's your favorite
food it was for so long before I lived
here but now I'm like hi happy for you
then I've lived
oh and I live in Colorado because
there's nine and out oh but I literally
eight have eaten it so many times not
kidding don't get me wrong guys I love
me some in and out but you know
chick-fil-a is kind of like my day one a
one for life this I mean he went to
their headquarters he's such a fan dude
I will go there I got I'm hanging out
there all day I got to meet Dan Cathy
and oh all those people like whose is
amazing and I like like I'm RELIGIOUS
and like I love God so it's like I love
what they stand for and stuff it's just
a really amazing company so love them
guys and I love their chuckle a sauce do
you love that I am a fan of the Texas
Pete hot sauce and the commercial and
the honey honey mustard
and my two favorite sauces all-time [ __ ]
about like well I it was in an interview
as well where you said you will go to
chick-fil-a and do that kind of stuff
and go there and just eat or whatever do
you get any like pushback from that
Oh like I mean you know there's a stigma
of like Oh chick-fil-a supporters don't
support gay people Oh
I mean he's gotten pushback for his love
for chick-fil-a I see you know what I
think though this is my approach we
don't know the company the people who
created this microphone company they
could be supporting terrorism they could
be supporting animal cruelty we don't
know these things and you know when I
when I go to chick-fil-a I I go to the
one in Hollywood
I see the gay community eating there too
so I'm like you know what I'm gonna eat
here too because they have good service
and their sauces are good their
sandwiches are good mm-hm and well the
thing is if you're receiving that kind
of pushback and you have you know 20
almost 22 million followers and I'm
assuming you're gonna see even more of a
pushback and the thing with that is
weird because I've gone a chick-fil-a
countless times and had gay people like
working for me like working there so I'm
like where is this info coming from like
where the real facts at chick-fil-a do
those real facts because then they need
to go and fire all the gay people
working for them so I've see it so I
don't know I don't believe stuff that
the media like I need to see real facts
coming from so I don't believe that so
people said that I'd be like where's
your proof that's good I mean you're bit
like it like you said and you want to be
genuine right so how do you feel about
like censoring yourself when it comes to
like you know the whole cancel culture
thing right like being yourself do you
how much do you worry about what you're
saying is being offensive to someone or
you know you might want to hold back
because you don't want to get cancelled
yeah I don't know I feel like I don't
really talk I don't talk politics and I
don't talk any of that kind of stuff so
I mean if people are just offended with
me just being mic you don't care bubbly
self like who I am as a person I don't
care I don't really talk about it I
don't want to get into that because
everyone
their own opinion you're never gonna be
able to please everybody I care about my
opinion it's my secret thoughts and no
one needs to know about it except my
family so you're very wise for your age
for your age yeah I have to say your
answers and the way you approach
different things thank you you're very
wise I've an old soul 80s music is my
favorite music all I listen to is
probably why ha ha that's why why are
most people who talk to you that are a
lot older than you are they kind of
surprised at how you carry yourself it's
funny because my my only friend cuz I
dropped out of high school when I was 14
I have freshman year I dropped out of
high school and I was home-schooled
before that and stuff so my mom is like
my bestest friend the world like she is
like my best friend like I've haven't
really ever had like a friend my age
that's really my like I've had friends
and then they're not my friends anymore
I'm like I've never had like a best
friend that's my age my mom is my best
friend and uh when I was through and I
dropped out she was in cosmetology
school like to do like a cetacean so I
was in school like before I dropped out
I wasn't ever a school I I just would
never go go to schools my mom and I'm
from I was every single friend was her
friend my friend like I was best friend
like all my friends have always been
older my best friend other than my mom
is 35 so I always have gotten along with
older women I don't know why I never can
relate to girls my age those want to do
things I don't want to do they talk
about things I'm like and then older
women I can relate to them we're best
friends like they I feel like they don't
even think cuz when I was like 17 I met
my best friend and she's 10 years older
than me and she's like she's sometimes
like think like wow you're only 7 I
could like mine blow her like like you
how are you this young because you're
more mature than most of my friends that
are my age so I think it's just I think
some people are just old souls right
that's me I don't want to look back
though I'm like in my 40s I'm like [ __ ]
I wish I woulda live my you're 16 I do
not I know I don't do anything fun like
I'm really a homebody I don't like to go
to the club like I'm like I don't want
to regret not having fun but to me it's
not fun like you know how I'm having fun
is like when I'm home with my dogs going
to dinner let's go to another angle you
can keep that will highlight in what was
on that so guys I'm a little I have a
lot of saliva okay well that's good
that's an old person trait yeah no no no
that is it guys you guys are probably
like let's never have summer on this
podcast again she doesn't let us go
you're welcome back every time yes it's
very entertaining don't worry we'll wipe
it down with that being said we would
take a quick cheesy break and we'll be
right back okay what's up I have a
question can I go ahead okay okay so I
have a question here so you make a lot
of references to Scripture I mean you
mentioned that you you're Christian did
you did you grow up in a Christian give
myself like I don't like say I'm
Christian or anything just because I
like Christians not like a bad rap
sometimes really really judgmental like
some people think of it's like this
Sigma about it like I just say I have a
relationship with my Lord and I love
Jesus and I have my own walk with him
and that's what it is see but don't you
think that's kind of sad that you have
to say that though like that you're have
to be afraid but I think that I've come
across a lot of Christians that are very
judgmental that make me don't want to
associate with them similar to the IG
models well because the thing I am
Christian like if we were gonna say a
religion but I just feel like there's so
many judgmental Christians and they do
like the trying to like make you feel
like a horrible person like we're all
sinners and we're all like we can't be
perfect that's why we have Jesus you
know so I feel like some people try to
like say things make it's just like not
good enough it's because they make their
own agenda with their spewing their
words in their own way use the scripture
to like make you and it's just not cool
like if you live God God is loving and
in all this good stuff is the true
message of Christianity is to love one
another
yeah they're like hypocrites I hate they
don't they're like hating and it also
we're not supposed to judge other people
and they're literally judging every
single thing and saying that you're
going to help you know that's not me and
that's not like what I preach so did you
grow up in it or did or was it something
you discovered later on and were friends
I grew up with it yeah but I'm not one
of those people like oh just cuz I grew
up it is what I believe like I've done
my own research my own stuff
I'm not she's gonna believe and do what
my parents say like I do it for myself
so yeah I love have you I mean when did
you move out here um three years ago now
yeah I would actually come out here for
a month like an air B&B and then go home
from us cuz I just didn't really want to
live fully out here because like I just
heard crazy stories about the people out
here and like even just be down here for
a month it's just like hard to know
who's real and who's true and who's like
you know I just don't want to get Rick
wrapped up in the wrong things but now I
live here and I think I'm just morally
very straight so I don't get caught up
in the wrong things so have you uh not
that you're out here have you found a
friend who's more your age I guess you
know cuz you said you didn't really have
that I'm like I guess though yeah well
yeah actually I do I have one of my
really really really good friends her
name is NAS and like she's actually
gonna be my I'm hiring her to be my
assistant actually because she's like
one of the few people I can trust
she's like amazing and I always has had
my back you know like I'll meet friends
I'll have friends and like I just feel
like they don't want to really be my
friend like I just I'm like if you're my
friend like I think that you're like my
sister like we're friends like I want to
be besties like I want to tell you each
other everything I want to be so close
like girls don't want to be like that
with me like they have their other
friend and then they don't invite me and
they don't want to really be friends I'm
like they want to be friends but they
don't want to be friends so that's why I
don't really I'm not friends with like
other like influencer girls or anything
a lot I'm just like friends with like
girls who are like normal because they
actually want to be my friend like I
don't like fake [ __ ] like I'm not gonna
free friends with you on the internet
and then
friends outside the inner you know I
want to actually meet friends right oh
it sounds like I mean it seemed that we
the reason I ask is because it does seem
like you have this mindset of someone
who is from like a small town or
something and you said you grew up on a
ranch in Colorado yeah yeah and I was
just curious is how long you've been
here because I mean I grew up in a small
town in Hawaii and when I moved here I
found probably the same things I was it
kind of shocked and not prepared for the
people that live here I'm not saying
that all the people here are like that
but there's a lot of um on how to
describe it just manipulation I guess
and the thing if you think about
everyone here has a reason to be here
and they are trying to break cessful
mm-hmm so you're a target yeah and
people's tactics to getting famous are
getting to where their success is like
stepping on people to get there you know
and if you're not that type of person
you can get stepped on very easy exactly
so you just have to kind of be mindful
of those type people not everyone's like
that like I know there are people who
love people and want to because you can
get successful and you can collab with
people and you can do things you know
loving way and uplift each other not hey
I'm gonna step on you to get to where
I'm going right but it's as more people
are very insecure in themselves that
they don't feel that's possible because
it's like oh this this relationship
couldn't be authentic because I can't
fathom having one like that right so
they're so used to just taking an
advantage of others because they're
afraid of being taken advantage of
themselves yeah but do you find it
that's one of the reasons why you're
more of a homebody as well yeah I don't
know everyone just wants to go out and
LA like the clubs I'm like you you
there's nothing worse in life than
standing at this dirty couch with a
bunch of girls spilling drinks on me to
get on this couch I'm like cool
take my spot stop stepping on my toes
have it I'm leaving like why do we have
to stand on this couch anyways why do we
have to stay around this couch can we
like go oh like somewhere else like more
room like we get these couches out of
here and like because my mom tells me
stories about like and when she was like
younger my age going it was like a dance
floor and people are having fun now it's
like ratchet music and we're on a couch
and there's drinks being spilt on me and
like people are stepping on my toes
trying to get on this couch like because
drunk girls trying to get like on the
couch sometimes I'm like and I'm not
like a crazy partier I'm just kind
chillin there I'm like I don't want to
be here but if it was like a dance floor
and we had a room and we could actually
like drink and have fun and like the
answers I mean it'd be a lot more fun I
just don't really like the couches and
the vibe like I mean I have to be really
drunk to go to club it kind of sound
like Ryan a little bit surprised right
now I don't like those couches either -
the dancing part
you would actually dance well sir when
I'm sober
okay I've seen I'm drunk I'm like okay
because I all cares got the world like
I'm friends with everyone like that's
probably a little intense like when I'm
drunk
I go up to every single person I'm like
hi my name is summer and I give him a
hug like I wake up the next day and I
like hope to God like that was a dream
because it's like I'm overly friendly
where it's like but I mean I can't be
that's just like my inner self is very
friendly and I want to be friends with
everyone so it comes out and then I'm
like but you have to be careful because
people are mean no they'll take that on
in a completely different way yeah
oh guys probably do take it a different
way even girls too because they're like
oh why is she so friendly what does she
want
yeah it's just a different which is why
I was saying it's a little different
here sure like you everyone's on like
the lookout for like everything so even
if someone's not even being like that
you you could think every little
movement that they're doing it could be
like that because we're on the lookout
for someone to mess up like [ __ ] us over
something so yeah so it's a well it's a
real weird place in Vegas you guys go
out a lot no no no no we don't we don't
go I mean when the reason I moved to
Vegas I lived here for like a year and a
half and then I just wasn't a fan so I
moved back to it
well Vegas is close enough to LA we're
like an hour flight and and surprisingly
it's it's super chill it's not the strip
if that's what you're thinking
yeah yeah yeah people it's just like
anything people think like Oh Vegas I
think that you're on the strip every day
we're walking around with one of those
big like icy looking yeah
walking around I'm like that's Vegas
yeah
no you're probably something like a
little suburban house like chillin far
far from the strip yeah yeah my head
goes to the strip I think you guys are
just like I didn't know people go
clubbing here
no yeah I'm my friend her name so
another really good friend I have out
here
she's like a clothing designer and she
like has these clothes like she writes
on jackets like pants on jackets and she
has this one that says loss and bottle
service killed Los Angeles and it's so
true like bottle service killed Lawson
oh you mean the like the couches and
stuff that's what you're talking about
the couch is yeah oh yes because back in
the day like my momma tell me there's no
bottle service there's a VIP room and
then there and there's bars you just go
buy your own stuff but this bottle
service comes and you need a couch and a
table for the bottle service and that's
how you get alcohol and stuff I mean
there's still bar but it's a whole
different vibe now I should have been
born in a different time baby
I always say I want I wish I was a
teenager with my mom that sounds weird
right you're like I couldn't none of you
see her as your best friend yeah I was
about the same age in the 80s we would
tear [ __ ] she had the same kind of
energy as you oh yeah I mean she's a
little bit more laid-back I'm a little
bit more crazy but no she's like them so
what your dad is cool is mom and my my
me and my dad are so alike like he's
actually a lot like me he's a lot higher
energy it's kind of crazy that's me I
think that's why you guys I think you
naturally have a lot of energy and I
think that also aids your workout
schedule yeah oh I feel like that's why
you love doing it cuz you have to exert
oh what would happen to me just chilling
yeah you just explode I have really dude
I really like I'm I like I'm very
short-fused sometimes and when I'm not
working out I'm like I just freak out
but then I'm like fine two seconds later
and I forget that I haven't freaked out
everyone's like I can't like I did
something I'm like what I think that's
why you are the way you are I think you
have so much and you said your
metabolism is high you just have so much
energy you have to do something with not
here can expose a hospital speaking of
exerting energy I saw I saw one of your
recent videos what
I saw one of your recent YouTube videos
that you were in the challenger games
then the Paul brothers put on your super
athletic I saw you running on that track
pissed off about this because the girl
who won has a scholarship in track you
can't be here that's like playing like
um tag football whatever with LeBron I
don't know does he play football that's
like playing a game of like basketball
like pickup out with LeBron James like
that's not fair yeah like if you have a
scholarship who's a girl charity yes I
can place then or well okay so the gun
went off word I've said this so many
times people are gonna be like what the
hell summer we get it so everyone's like
I thought like they said I don't have
never run track before mhm
I did it like before I dropped out I
like did just a few practices but I
never like I dropped out of school so I
got a min like finish track or whatever
but I guess they're not supposed to say
2 3 1 or 1 2 3
and just like iron shop but I thought
they were gonna say like 1 2 3 anything
guy there gunshot went off and everyone
win then I was like and then I went so
if you would like watch the think clip I
don't go right away so and the start is
everything so if you don't go when
another girl who won she's like a track
person so she did the blocks and
everything I don't know how to use a
block so it was just wasn't fair I
probably could have won if I left that
girl wasn't in it like we're not
supposed to be here and then and then um
yeah and then if I had a good start
because I caught up with everyone except
her cuz she's like really fast you were
second third because I really had a bad
start if you watch it I literally go
like 4 or 5 like it's a lot it's a
little thought when you're like on the
race that's kind of similar with the
guys too cuz Toby was second but the guy
who got first
he's like an actual sprinter or an
athlete or something like that
you shouldn't have no like this is
charity we're having fun like are you
competitive you see bags with it I was
just gonna say
like I'm very but I think that's why I
can be sick like I'm in just a go-getter
and like if I put my mind to something
if I want something I work hard for it
and I think that's but even if she has a
scholarship in track if she's an
entertainer she should still be allowed
to compete okay that's fine that's fine
well [ __ ] she was a youtuber I'm
assuming she had to be arranged or like
her some kind of influencer yeah it
assumes like an Olympian influencer like
yeah we can tell you care about it so
that's what I'm passionate about
everything I'm just a passionate person
you want and I what you won Thanks no
but the thing is I have not run in so
long at it pride I was camping like the
whole week but I came home early from my
campaign trip in Colorado to do it so
like is whatever I'm just too
competitive I'm so hard on myself so I'm
like huh but it's like fine yeah I mean
scholarship and all she can compete it's
fine guys other your other hobbies
um I mean I like to paint like I was
telling you guys I'm painting all over
my arms I like to eat that's like a
hobby I like to say that's like a good
one like I could be you ever do
competitive eating
you have the metabolism for it yeah and
you work hard enough so I think that's
what it is
no yeah there's actually youtubers this
guy Matt Stoney who eats like ridiculous
amounts of food yeah
and like certain amounts of time and
it's just like it's it's so impressive
Wow
yeah I just want to stretch out my
stomach no he's mad skinny dude yeah
it's over he's like the sharpest jawline
ever to Wow well maybe any I go against
him okay eating and what was it sorry
Oh painting painting eating um yeah I
like to be out in nature I mean I grew
up riding horses and stuff so I mean I
haven't ridden in a while but that's
like riding a bike like I always know
how to ride a horse that's like my like
foundation of life you know you go back
a lot um I was just back like around the
time of the Challenger Games wherever I
was in Colorado and then I came back
early for it and yeah so that's the
first time
I've been home in like a year so I don't
really go back too often I just feel
like when I go home I'm like I like see
my family and everything is like great
when I'm seeing them and then I see them
all and I'm like why am I here there's
just nothing to do like I need to go and
then I almost get depressed because I'm
like there's so much stuff I should be
doing like for work and stuff so that's
crazy so it's so similar to what I do
yeah backgrounds yeah but when I was at
that age - that's like riding horses I'm
not writing for going home into a small
town where it's literally nothing
there's nothing to do they don't live in
the small town like Larkspur anymore but
hmm it's a suburb like Denver and like
they live in the outskirts at Denver and
it's pretty it's just not the same as
here it's not fast paced like it's not
like it's tough to do like it's just
kind of like yeah okay like I just like
to do I like to I'm like a go-go type
person some huh you're a go-getter but
you're also homebody yeah like there's a
lot of things I can do at home hmm
like I have a gym at my house and I have
a paint studio so I don't really have to
go anywhere right everything you need
everything I need yeah actually maybe
you want to talk about kind of like cuz
you showed us earlier some paintings
that you did you did shoes and stuff
yeah okay so I have some like mail-merge
that I like so but like they're just
like late canvases like just white so
I've been painting them and I don't
really want to like sell them and so
because like how do you like what how do
I put a price on that anyways cuz like I
don't want to put it too low because
it's like this that's my hard work and I
don't want to put it too high and people
be like really [ __ ] like we're gonna
pay that for that like come on
so I want people kind of as if they want
them to decide what they would like to
pay so I I don't know any other like
auctioning like bidding site only eBay
so I put them on eBay yeah so I have
like three of them on there I just I
like to do like some crazy stuff I don't
even know that stuff like people would
like to wear but like whatever whoever
buys it I'm gonna like like I have to
personally ship it out for them and
stuff so I'm gonna go take a video of me
shipping it out I'm gonna put a little
note I'm gonna sign a stuff so it's like
pretty personal super personal I painted
that with my bare hands sweat and tears
guys blood too
was that used blood for paint my blood
my blood personal touch so so as an as
an influencer with 22 million followers
on Instagram do you for you know
Jennifer should generate revenue for
yourself do you do a lot of brand deals
or do you go out and model
professionally I know you have a fitness
app as well like where do you kind of
generate your revenue from being an
influencer yeah my goal like I'm not
really focused on like really working
for like a ton of other brands like I'm
really focused on like building my own
IP and like because like a lot of people
think about like salic and strands gone
tomorrow or they like do something with
Agoura them it's hard to grow you know
that's not ours like we're putting
everything into this platform that we
don't own like at the end of a I don't
own those followers and stuff so if they
took it away like they have the power to
do that so I'm just trying to build my
own IP in like my own like businesses
and stuff outside of Instagram so that's
kind of what I'm focusing on it's like
building my my own stuff like the
clothing Brandon yeah my clothing brand
and then the subscription box and then
I'm making it oil
I love argan oil so I'm doing like an
argan oil I think I'm gonna call it
summer rockin I was so Moroccan like
summer rockin like what is this like
Moroccan oil like argan oil you put on
my skin hair now it's like I'm on oil
okay
just oil yeah yeah and then I'm doing
another like brand fashion brand but I'm
not calling it like because my one brand
is I called summer-rae like it's a
fitness line but I'm doing another
fashion one but I'm not gonna like name
it my name and I don't want even people
to know that it's mine because then like
some girls aren't gonna support my brand
because it's like oh I don't I don't
like summer you know and it's more like
a personal like I like the clothes I
don't like her so then I'm gonna make
another line has nothing to do with me
and then they'll wear the clothes cuz
it's cute clothes right that's all it is
you'll need to be a fan - yeah it's not
fan like I'm not even gonna say it's
mine so yeah I'm just like focus and I'm
actually doing like PSD like the
underwear brand like the one I'm wearing
right now the boy briefs I'm doing a do
a collab with them I'm gonna do my own
underwear at them which will be fun and
I'm doing like you you have energy drink
like ninja but I'd like there's a
company called arrays it's weird because
like my last name is array and then it's
like RA what de they hit me up and they
want I make making my own flavor with
them I think I want to do it like
sunshine like it tastes like sunshine
like my own energy drink and I think of
it not like you have got your own brand
of energy drink I'm just gonna like
partner with them and make my own
flavors I think that one like run my own
company like that with energy drinks
it's a lot of words crazy you are doing
a lot of things how I mean I know you
have a lot of energy and I can tell but
I mean like how do you balance all of
that because I mean that's that's a lot
of things unless do you have help I mean
I have a business partner and I'm now
I'm gonna have an assistant like my
friend that I was talking about but yeah
I just kind of handle like creative and
like my decisions obviously cuz that's
my brand but then he kind of handles
more like the business aspect of it and
when it comes down to like being my like
like you know like the bad guy he like
saying like nope summer can do that cuz
I can't be and be like doing closing my
own deal like I'm the nice one
like I'm like and he's like no she needs
more you know so he's my um he's a bad
guy and then there's me just being sweet
smart oh and then also I have my own
podcast called
oh honey it's pretty fun yeah like your
little tagline we were singing it
earlier just get stuck in your head
that's with Amanda Cerny have a podcast
good she was so she was on she was on
vine first right you weren't on vine no
yeah never did vine no I know I did up
like you know when vines been around
like when I was in high school and stuff
so was my friends I would do like these
little vines but I was never like famous
or popular to get famous off fine yeah
I'm just trying to remember the timeline
of when I was big worse like Instagram
cuz Instagram was first right I think
the I think like people got famous off
we're getting famous off vine before
like yeah because I think Amanda I don't
really know the timeline she's older
than me she's 28 29 so and she's been
doing this for a while so I think that I
don't know it was like it was like vine
maybe then it's Grammer Instagram was
around when they were doing vine I was
doing Instagram I don't know guys I
think Instagram was like year it was a
for a long time and then vine like
popped off really hard and then
Instagram kind of adapted towards that
mm-hmm
there's no we're like Felix it all
happened so fast and it's like I'm
always curious I'm like where it's gonna
go yep like or they're just always gonna
be like what are the influencers gonna
turn into are they just gonna be
influencers like what's the difference
between like a modern-day celebrity and
an influencer or like what it's what's
gonna happen with it so it's so new and
like I feel like everyone's an
influencer nowadays like they talk about
influencers like this girl like has 100k
like I'm like oh so everyone's
influencers yeah my mom's an influencer
my sister's an influencer my my dad
could probably I mean it's just a matter
of how big they are right yeah I mean my
mom has almost like almost AM L right
like yeah she influences a million
people is creating stuff okay so um
looks like we got some Twitter questions
here for you got one here from never
noble opinions your thoughts on the
paranormal ghost you believe in ghosts
Oh paranormal um yeah I believe and like
if you believe in like God you believe
in the devil so I believe that there's
demonic beings in the world you know I
believe that so have you had any
experiences though um I actually have my
old house I lived I grew up in in
larkspur and it was built on a Indian
Indian burial ground homeless so I
actually collected I had a whole tub of
like arrowheads you know like the
Indians like make them so yeah I found
them all over the place like obviously
with it and you go yeah I don't know
where they are today they're so cool I
used to collect them it's like my thing
but yeah so up and I just have a lot of
stories I don't know if you guys like
want to hear them but like pretty
interesting well just tell one go ahead
or maybe two oh okay yeah but so my
grandma was watching my siblings I have
twin siblings like boy-girl twins and
they're like a year younger than me and
my mom and dad left them home and me and
my other sister went to Lake Powell with
them one time and my grandma was
watching them she put them upstairs to
go to bed and they kept like putting up
a fuss to go to bed like getting up
crying like you know like wouldn't lay
down to go to bed so she went up there a
few times like heard them like walk like
she was like go up there and get mad at
them like stop right and then like the
third or fourth time she did that she
heard them cry she swears like my
grandma told us the story
she's like swears that they were crying
like you know like making noise playing
with each other laughing she goes up
there dead asleep like that asleep so
that's kind of creepy he's at the same
place house yeah she was watching them
at my house okay and we always saw this
girl like oh my sister has long black
hair right and my aunt does too so I
would we would always see this like
girls like long black hair like you know
like um it was like a white like
bathroom like robe like you know like
dress type thing so we were like we'd
see him walk into rooms and stuff and
then we think we were like weren't you
just upstairs like it was weird we
always saw this like girls like long
black hair like all the time I've seen
her like she would walk into like rooms
like all the time and like my family
would tell you that okay with us I think
it was that's scary
yeah okay well that took a turn but the
first one you guys are probably like
thank you that's gonna be really intense
but it's like no I mean most times it's
not usually the I know a lot of times
when people tell those kind of stories
and it's so crazy I don't believe it but
that's so actually so minimal that I
kind of I believe it I know people say
they're like crazy mmm yeah the tricking
Panda do you have any weird or hidden
talents oh yeah for sure guys like
people say I have no talent and then I
do this whoa those were listening yeah
she is touching your nose with her
tongue I can pick my nose with my tongue
oh yeah yeah that's very deep
so I just feel like like people think I
have no talent but no way on the street
do that
like we've gone way back with that
talent hmm can either of your parents do
that my dad can do all this like weird
stuff with his tongue too he like makes
it into like a bowl like I hope I
haven't conquered that I'm not like that
level yet okay
well good to know how do you figure that
out as a talent like one day like where
you tied up as a kid one day like ma'am
I know it's really no my mom's like you
know like those ant eaters that have
like like that's me like I don't know I
feel like so like your parents would put
like Cheerios on life and your baby
because me and my siblings my family's
really weird like some of the stories
people probably think we made it up
because it's so weird but like we would
always act like we're animals like of
some sort like we'd be dogs or cats or
Wolf's or whatever and my mom would
actually give us our food like our
dinner and stuff on the floor like I
would like like we would be so in
character of like being an animal that
like I'm my mom's like okay like fine
here's your food and like you know those
like ice cream sandwiches we would like
take off the top of like the Ice Cream
Sandwich and put it on a plate and just
lick it I can see why you're friends
with your mom she's like I mean she's
most I mean you know my mom would be
like it gets get stand up like no right
no I like it she's cool right pants like
amazing she's really fun like a most
amazing like fun energy like you would
think that she's my age like no actually
she's older
like she's younger than me like I always
say that I'm her mom and she's like yeah
you're I'm her mom like I have to like
keep her on the up and up but yeah if
you like see my mom and his grandma
stuff you'll understand what kind of mom
she has and she's 55 she looks nothing
like that mm-hmm
this is this was nice this is very
interesting I think people will see a
different side of you for sure
you have anything that you want a plug
right now
[Music]
whoa check out your YouTube I'm excited
for that so my YouTube is just
summer-rae yeah I'm gonna start posting
and actually I didn't have like a
videographer editor before like I just
found like a really cool kid he's gonna
always be on the call for some cool
videos so awesome that up again and your
Instagram is also summer Rae somf that
she needs more publicity there but yes
everyone always thinks it's summer like
people I thought it was that it's always
a summer so I'm all right I'm like
summer that's your real name right
summer yeah everyone's like oh it's like
I'll meet people know what's your real
name
I'm like someone it's not a stage name
like yeah my name is summer Rae and then
my last name I like wait baby I've never
gone by baby because my dad's adopted
and I don't even know his side of the
family or anything and I don't really
like them so I've always gone by Ray my
whole life so that's my name like it's
not like a name I made up so all right
well yeah go check out our YouTube you
probably already see her on Instagram
thank you again so much for being here
seriously
make sure you can follow us at off the
pill on Twitter at off the pill podcast
on Instagram and yeah the way we end
these are basically just breathe into
the mic in three two one
we always say it's really bad he says
it's bad for the mics but we just did it
once and we just kidding we keep doing
it