hey guys oh so today I'm gonna be
telling you guys about something that's
really important to me I know a lot of
you probably won't care please do not
leave that stupid annoying and
unoriginal comment cool story bro don't
you take when people use those outdated
overuse things it's so unoriginal it's
like be yourself live your own life you
know you only live once I did not take
matter of today as you can tell anyway
thing I wanted to tell you guys is that
I can finally mark off one more thing on
my life goals list
[Music]
graduate high school Czech wrestling
state championship jack belt and judo
check it into Stanford I mean that
wasn't like my first to get into Harvard
I mean that schools for nerds get it
like any you see schools not so much
that I didn't get in they just didn't
want me to get into college duh so we
graduate college I mean you know you win
some you lose so I call it I totally did
not a big deal
and last but not least Creed and
starring a TV show check that's right I
created I'm gonna be starring in a real
TV show I'm gonna give you create like
the whole thing and I'm not exactly like
the star the entire time and and I'm and
it's not gonna be on TV it'll be on
online it's still cool guys yes this
show is gonna be on show was caught in
it and I know I gave you guys a really
good preview of my judging video to be a
judge on a new show called internet icon
here's a preview if you want to know but
I'm gonna give you guys a little bit
more basically the easiest way to
explain the show is that it's like
American Idol but for youtubers and like
every reality show you know there's
gonna be drama just a little scratch
there's happy times there's also gonna
be a lot of sad times as well I'm like
crying right now
sadder I have no idea it's good crying
sadder I'm sorry guys
and to be honest this show might make me
look like an ass but I was just being
myself and being completely honest
there's something I like a great great
great person now are something I didn't
like what's happening here like that's
what I was when I was like what why is
this happening to me
also we're gonna have a bunch of
wonderful guest judges on this show some
of them you might know so tough to judge
and I think cuz I'm just like them
there's one thing that I love about the
Internet is really new and fresh which
is like refreshing pass it around make
it viral I'm very excited to see what
the world thinks I could best show ever
created overall you just need to watch
the show you know there's gonna be a lot
of talented people smart good-looking
just all-around perfect best snazziest
dress good at math and chess is probably
is a super-high level character in
Diablo 3 overall just a impeccable human
being on this show I'm just kidding I
can't be that into myself when we have
people like this on our show one of
those stupid lines on their stomach
anyway you know that's that's why we
invented the iron nobody the one
sprinkle is just smooth so if you guys
are interested there's gonna be a link
at the end of the video and it'll take
you to our new channel but Yaya map or
Internet I come over here and I hate
when people pull this card but come on
it's my birthday today don't correct me
they didn't know what my real birthday
was that was a year ago you think
they're gonna remember that
no no you're an idiot you know that
right just watch just watch the show too
so make sure you guys subscribe to you
on your map or not I don't care I'm not
gonna judge I'm not a judge you're just
kidding I'm judging internet icon which
is premiering on y'all Yelp F so make
sure you subscribe or not so thank you
guys so much for watching I'll be
posting a regular video soon and until
the end I don't need your help
hate annotations