first off sorry I didn't post the video
last week I was actually in Australia
and Singapore for a couple weeks but
anyway I haven't done a rant in a very
long time I mean like a legit ran from
back in the day where I would just turn
on the camera wake up try to figure out
how I turned on the camera before waking
up you know what I mean just ranting in
one spot with no cutaways but I didn't
say anything about Tara ways hey bad
joke not a good start so back to the
topic last time in a rant about Justin
Bieber called Bieber fever you was the
biggest thing in entertainment surely
that should tell you how long ago that
was as I was basically talking about
this innocent humble 16 year old
heartthrob however four years later you
say Justin Bieber and you definitely
don't think innocent humble 16 year old
heartthrob any more anyway even if you
couldn't care less about Justin Bieber
we all know who he is and how he's been
getting into a lot of trouble from
vandalism to drugs and most recently a
little racism and for those of you that
might not know about a week ago there
was a video about Justin Bieber making a
black joke where he says the n-word and
pretty much everyone called him a racist
and obviously he publicly apologized for
it but then a few days later on another
video leads of him making another racist
comment this time in soft form if you
haven't seen that video it's basically
15 year old Justin Bieber singing in
song one less lonely girl and instead of
girl uses the n-word and sings it over
and over and just when you think it
couldn't get any worse he brings up the
KKK and if that first video wasn't
enough after the second one everyone is
calling him a racist he's been caught
with drugs doing so many other stupid
things and now this I could easily pick
the safe route and talk about how unfit
he is to be a role model because
honestly I agree with that he should not
be a role model for kids but that would
be boring because everyone else is doing
that right now or they're going to be
for the next couple of weeks so if the
question is if Justin Bieber is racist I
can honestly say that I see both sides
and I'm about to give you the side
that's probably a little more unpopular
like I said I still don't think Justin
Bieber should be a role model for kids
not because he does drugs or does other
stupid things it's because he gets
caught doing this he can take all the
drugs and do all the stupid thing he
wants it's his life but he has so many
kids looking up to him he has a
responsibility to not let those things
get out but that's just my opinion
and now because of those two leaked
videos everybody and their mothers are
saying that Justin Bieber is a racist
and personally I really don't think he
is I'm sure a lot of other people would
agree with me too but they don't want to
say it because they don't want to sound
racist let me tell you why
both of these videos are of Justin
Bieber when he was 14 or 15 years old
and as a teenager everybody says and
does stupid things I mean if you're in
your 20s and you can still see your
myspace I bet if you went back and read
it you
see how stupid you are you say things or
write things that you would never do now
and if you're a teenager now you might
think that the things you're saying and
doing aren't stupid now but check your
Facebook in five to ten years and I'm
pretty sure you're gonna think otherwise
and I know a lot of people are gonna say
that him being a kin at the time doesn't
make it any less racist I agree he
doesn't he said the n-word and some
pretty racist things that got out to the
public but like I said everyone does and
says regrettable things when they're
kids and even if you don't excuse him
for his age and you still think he's a
racist as bad as it may sound it was
clearly not serious about what he was
saying I mean in the first video he was
literally making the joke jokes aren't
meant to be serious if you were black or
a stand-up comedian that wasn't like and
he said what he said people would just
let that slide it's just because he's
Justin Bieber a lot of people don't like
him so he's instantly a racist in the
first video he was literally making a
joke it was a racist joke but still it
wasn't serious the second video is a
little edgier but it's still pretty
obvious that he was joking I mean he's
spoofing his own song while other people
are laughing with him it literally
looked like a video of a bunch of
friends goofing off together hanging out
in a room privately I'm sure he never
meant that video to be seen or heard
ever just like the Donald sterling
situation which brings up a good point
there's a big difference between the
Justin Bieber situation and Donald
sterling so yeah I do believe that
Donald sterling is a racist because in
his recording he says some things that
were clearly serious and not meant to be
a joke or make people laugh but the
thing that makes him racist is that he
actually sees other ethnicities as
inferior to his own and he acts upon it
see that's a real racist Justin Bieber
just said some racist things to make
people laugh sure call him an idiot but
he's not a racist there's no evidence of
him treating people differently because
of race even if sometimes he acts like
an ask to fans or flight attendant so
Seth Rogen's because they're black he's
an ass to everyone equally he's an equal
ass I mean look at his Instagram he has
black friends I'm pretty sure if he
didn't like black people he would not be
friends with them so overall to wrap up
no I do not think Justin Bieber should
be a role model for kids and in no way
am i defending him but he's not racist I
guess that is kind of different in him
but I'm not defending him because I'm a
believer I just don't think it's right
to be calling someone racist when
they're not College I'm gonna race this
is a big deal in this day and age and
you can't label someone a racist just
because of a couple of jokes they made
back when they were a kid I mean if you
can honestly say that you've never said
something as a kid that you wish you
didn't say and if you never repeated a
black joke or any racist joke that you
heard to a bunch of family and friends
in a private location thinking no one
else would hear it congratulations you
literally might be the best person in
the world the best person that I know at
least you should be the next justin
bieber the president the pole because
you're pretty damn close to perfect and
people should be following a role model
like you but then again if you really do
believe that you haven't done
wrong in your life and you think people
should follow what you do it's pretty
cocky of you to think that and now I
hate you see how that works and I'm
gonna say it again just because this
videos based on racism and I already
know the comments my last name is
Okinawan so it's pronounced Higa not
Higa so it's pronounced nigahiga if
you're interpreting it the other way
that's because you're reading it wrong
and that would make you a little racist
but anyway thank you guys so much for
watching like I said this was my first
friend in a long time without any
cutaways though I did have a lot of
urges to do so especially on that one
part of the video where I said we don't
edits couldn't pass to everyone equally
he's an equal apps so close
this feels racist man know what you
can't get away with singing all of this
you're not a stand-up comedian you're
not black and you don't have any black
people in it yes there is you're in it
get in the very beginning remember first
off sorry I didn't post a video last
week I was actually in Australia and
Singapore for a couple weeks
what up in the video see when I tell you
oh yeah