could you and Logan ever become friends
one of the bodyguards tried stopping me
and I threw him across the stage and
just ripped his suit but I would always
like going Google how to talk to girls
and like they don't what to say off the
high copy claps yeah all right so you
just clap in front of Mike welcome back
to another episode of off the peel
podcasts oh it's really quiet there you
go
[Applause]
today we have a very special edition we
have a special guest well we have Paco
first of all in the moderator seat and
we have a very special guest que si JJ
in the house visiting for actually how
long have you been here so what are you
hearing we just did a collab so yeah
little were just here as a sideman doing
collabs of everyone you'd say I'm out
just a clap yeah Oh literally just a
week of collabs well I guess that's good
I mean that's that's a lot of work who
else did you guys come up with face
faces yeah we did a few videos of them
and yeah that's that's gonna get lazy I
think we've in total recorded main
channel videos like four which is four
yeah we really don't like full main
channel videos Wow so now we're just
like enjoying ourselves and then you're
filming in tonight yes and tomorrow and
tomorrow is filming yeah it's crazy yeah
well I think this will be out before
your video but we will probably let you
know on other social media when that
video comes out just did some we did
some stuff today mm-hmm so we found out
this is your first podcast in the you it
you've done podcast but in the u.s.
claiming it you've taken my virginity
there you go that's the one thing we
wanted to do okay sighs podcast sherry
yep sweet delicious nutritious all right
there goes our money like so what else
have you been working on your album just
came out right so yeah all we came out
two weeks ago
and managed to get a 17 and the Official
Charts and number one on R&B charts
which is insane for us we've been
working on this album for so so long and
to finally put it out and for people to
absolutely love it it's just
unbelievable so yeah we're just yes
that's awesome all right now so I think
for listeners who don't really know who
you are it's not you and a side minutes
use Randolph right yeah Mia right now so
we did the joint album and we released
ten songs and you have people are just
going nuts over us I think the most
interesting thing about it that really
grabbed the headlines as well is you
guys I think talked about how you're not
if people use your songs in their videos
and stuff you're not gonna like
copyright strike that Yeah right
nothing literary will like why I mean I
grew up being able to use cover music
before the YouTube started like clamping
down on everything but I was just like I
wanted to essentially go back to that
and for me like it's not all about the
money I just want to just do use it cuz
I just enjoy it's just the hobby for me
so to be able to allow people to use
that means use my music in their videos
I think it's just I guess well it's the
whole new age yeah I'm trying to never
work with a label yeah that's why I'm
independent
yeah I'd literally the best thing yeah
to be able to be independent and let me
we'll just use your music and you know
just literally go against the system
essentially and yeah I think it's I
think it's a nice move
I mean you were signed I guess we can go
a little bit deeper on this because
you're one of the few YouTube musicians
who are actually signed to a label right
so maybe you can I was signed to Ireland
yeah and then it kind of just went a bit
self I don't know if you're allowed to
talk to it maybe NDA's or whatever but
what was your experience I guess pros
and cons with it you know I I guess pro
was you can be honest dude you don't
have to say think of any pros
I guess they allowed me to collab with
people I wouldn't be able to collab with
so Waka Flocka
I was able to do a song with him and not
like I wouldn't have been able to do
that yeah so they were able to get that
connection but uh
besides died that they didn't really
push me like as much as they could have
so I don't know I mean they guess I
guess they helped a bit but I'd say con
wise they they didn't really focus on
the music that much this way they focus
on everything but the music they just
saw my marketing they just yeah exactly
I saw my audience and were like okay
let's try and make an app for him and
let's try and monetize the app so that
we can get money through that let's try
and get a clothing line for him and
let's try and make money through that or
let's try and do this or this thing I
was like wait let's focus on the music
first like I have music let's you know
push that and they then they never
really got behind it so eventually I did
my did my term on the contract and then
peace down right so they were just
basically milking you yeah their
followers me so was this during the
whole like like when you were like a
like having the fight and stuff like no
no this is way before okay so this was a
like around - yeah - out 17 haha 2017
but you know 2017 maybe in a bit of 2016
yeah
so essentially like when I had my break
like my long six seven month
I was still signed to Ireland so they
were still expecting like an EP so I had
one more EPA of just like five songs to
give to them so I put out space what
because for me I want I thought space
cuz I was just like it's important for
me and then I put down and I thought
okay island do you want to take this not
know otherwise like now we're not gonna
take that one
and then the whole dish strikes
happening right right and then I made an
EP of that I know like yeah we'll take
this uh-huh because I saw the bars and
they're like oh yeah we can capitalize
on this yeah I think so I it's actually
crazy I can't like put little boy in my
video else I'll get claimed on it oh
sorry I sold all my discharge I can't
like use what they actually own the song
yeah yeah yes it's a bit annoying Wow
yeah labels well you you mentioned diss
tracks and I this was something that you
know it is older drama but it's kind of
a it's what really brought a lot of eyes
you know to you and your music and stuff
so you had diss tracks with like sideman
and stuff yes and that was huge you know
there's a lot of heat between it and you
you made a video where it talks about it
was all real right yes and uh I guess
how do you cuz there's a lot of Internet
drama that goes on between people so how
do you solve that off-camera you know
because these are your friends and stuff
and you guys did end up settling it I
think it's it's time time like like with
me and Harry it was a bit cagey like
especially after his second decide on me
like I was pissed yeah now one is just
legitimately yeah so like you guys are
just exaggerating we are friends right
but like the stuff we say is real like
everything we're saying it's like truth
so it still like sucks right I got you
well I said like it took some time to
like go over that boy that's nice issue
it's just time who extended the olive
branch like who was the first one to be
like oh that's not a saint yeah like a
peace thing got it got it I think it's
just it's just a thing that just
happened because obviously we do videos
together so we have to eventually like
sort out we couldn't have can just be
enemies forever yeah you and Logan never
become friends who would you be more
friends with Logan or Jake that's like
cocaine before Jake
come on that's it wait so you're are you
are you fighting Jake no I'm fine Logan
okay because I saw something I didn't I
was just trolling oh okay yeah so I was
just trying to be like on the YJ because
Logan's falling off of this right I was
always in the fallopian like yeah we've
literally been training to fight Logan
right why would you just switch it to
fight Jake but yeah I know well I mean I
I mean you already talked about like
your beef that you had with the Simon
and stuff but I always wondered I mean
we talked about it last time you were
here but um just I mean I to a certain
degree how real is that like how much do
you not like each other I just I see
somewhat me enlighten yeah I think it's
more like an ego thing like Oh see he
did the whole forest thing but it's like
precise I don't really have any real
like anger towards him I think it's more
just to show that I'm better than him
right right yeah like even though he's
had all of this all of the athletic
background and you know he thinks he's
mr. tough man I'm there like even after
your slice well no yeah go first yeah
you're fine so we have this so we could
just be ourselves like even your fight
that's why afterwards like he said he
talked about how he messed up and then
the fight kind of like you know gave him
an opportunity to reinvent himself and
he gave a lot of credit to you and then
when his dog died like you were like a
man like sorry to hear about it so it's
not like you guys have like it's not
like you're like ha good for you you're
not the worst for you some people are
like that like I am human as well Yeah
right who's your dog it's like losing a
baby yeah it hurt so I'm not gonna just
be like how you did your dog died low
yeah I exact it's just stupid it's just
it's inhumane so you know I was just
like and so you got a soft side then
it's just being
empathy isn't it like yeah yeah just
certain things like you've gotta be like
okay oh sorry so like and I don't mean
to bring it back to the music but this
is something I was like interested in
stuff because I wanted to continue like
you had the beef with the Seidman and
everything and then you had a beef with
Logan and you had his dish track towards
him for the fight and then you had a
diss track with quad deca hmm and you
guys were popping off on each other
alive yeah and then when New Age got
released he was actually on a track with
you which a lot before he wasn't on the
Trouble Man he's gonna travel Randolph
Oh see I'm not on it
oh you just didn't want to do it but so
the beef there's it's pretty real I mean
it's still kind of heated it's not it's
like I think we both respect each other
but it's more like we think we think
also like we think we're better than the
other so it's essentially like you and
Logan but now in rapping table yeah kind
of seems like writers like the way
fighters interact with each other yeah
they have respect for each other and
what they do they weren't fighting each
other it would be you know respect to
you but I'm so better than you that's
that's what it's like it's really okay
right it's not at that Conor McGregor
level of like I'm gonna throw up
he would laugh at the dog dying yeah
like I feel like you put a tweet out you
like a little too far but I mean it draw
it if you pulling back the punches now
just what what about Jake I mean I
haven't completely followed every detail
and I only see headlines you know like I
don't know that for details like what
about Jay is so much worse he's just
he's actually a [ __ ] like yeah I know
like he's actually about person like
Logan
right Logan I mean Jake is an actual
like prick he's an actual bad person
like his whole demeanor everything about
him just stinks man and I just don't
like it
and is it toward a direct interaction
that you had with him like between me
and him between just my people around us
like no none of my friends liked him
like some of my friends are still like
Logan right even though I'd find him
they still like like yeah it is like
this somehow no one likes Jake Jake I've
never met him
so I can't and I never I don't wanna say
anything cuz I never met him I've never
met him either
when I met Logan honestly it was and I
said this before it was only once and it
was short but he was seem like a normal
dude like he didn't wasn't like acting
the way he does in videos and stuff
um-hmm but I don't know I I don't know
I'm well enough but that's interesting
you have real beef with Jake that's in a
more logical foot I mean are you guys
alright so pretty much the plan is once
I get through Logan through drink was
Logan tricks that it wasn't Logan and
Drake like talking or something though
you know Jake and Drake oh my god Drake
and Jake yeah so now you gotta fight
Drake definitely yeah and you got our
rap in one round you guys are fighting
that's a good title for the fight there
are some punches she pitch it to him oh
I guess cut I guess I'm good at one all
right now taking oh man that is uh well
that I didn't know I didn't know I even
though I know you I mean that's not
something we've ever talked about but I
didn't know that that paid as well so
yeah I didn't really see that I mean I
know you guys were having issues and
stuff and yeah yeah I mean my bow
she's you guys good oh we're good now
yeah we saw that in some of their videos
like they bet they do together or
whatever like he'll straight-up punch
dead you like to punch him in the arm
with Nettie
he'll punch him in the stomach and he's
just like you know it's like oh you can
get away Oh brotherly love at the time
of his life
oh really living it it's nice right yeah
okay well we established it all that
stuff is real I'm coming from another
perspective really follow everything but
I'm just and I know behind the scenes a
lot you tubers are over I mean not that
it's fake I mean there is fake a lot of
fake stuff too
yes but a lot of the drama and stuff
it's kind of mutually understanding like
this is working for us both yeah so
let's I mean you know it's like oh it's
like two fighters like let's melt this
yeah I kind of struggle to do like fake
things the answers yes then I call it
just doesn't feel authentic right right
I don't know I can't really lie put my
all into it where ever it's real and I
can just go to freaking moon and just go
ahead and so but I guess I guess what I
was leading to you because you are a
personality you know a lot of youtubers
are like oh I'm a tech youtuber or I'm a
DIY you know and and they try to you
know eventually their personal and
personality comes out but you've always
been just like this is me that's just
yeah raw genuine like because when I
started just going back all the way back
I start with FIFA I was just like oh my
gosh like I I don't want to do it fee
for the whole of my life like I'm
eventually gonna get bored and then what
so I always made that an important thing
to words and the point thing for me
you're a good rapper and for me
was to make sure that I showed my
personality through all my content so
I'd always not just do the same thing I
do other things like music acting skits
and with just all other games always
just trying to show people like oh this
is me like you know get used to me so
that me so that in the future whenever I
wanted to do anything I'd be able to
just do it and be like oh [ __ ] yeah
what's he doing next okay that's cool I
got to do this so speaking about future
I mean like what I mean like you said
you're into so many different things but
uh what is uh I mean what's next I mean
not next actually there's a lot of
things coming up but like what's like
future what's end goal um is it ideally
music it seems like um well there's
quite a few things like I like to say
I'm like jack of all trades but master
of none
oh damn that's the first time you've
ever dissed yourselves exclusive in
person yeah there's quite a few things I
want to do so at the moment I'm doing
like little skits on my main channel
just I guess get my audience prepared
for what like ready from to see me
acting that make sense just to see like
for them to get comfortable with me
acting and you know eventually I want
you know to improve the content make it
better and better and better so
eventually in the future this could be
like a year two three years I can create
my own movie right so that's one of my
angles to do that but I know like it to
make a movie you know takes so much like
four and there's so many things you have
to deal with I'm nowhere near that point
so I'm like let me start with just
little like 10 15 minutes skits and
eventually create a movie through that
music I want to obviously do my own
album but I know with the album join
amor me and ran off like that's cool
but it's like okay
I want to take my oven to the next level
but for me to get to that part I still
need to I guess prove myself I feel like
well I mean like I feel like I proven
myself I mean like prove myself
musically like show that I am like on
another level right if I miss I mean
your albums did I mean it did well
though yeah isn't that it proof to
yourself - oh yeah I mean it's it's I
know I already know I'm sick
there we go confidence back where you
went why it's like I I need a literary
show people and it's just like sharing
people with different ways and
eventually once my album comes out
people be like oh my god like holy crap
he is a monster so that's that's my plan
with that with the boxing fight Logan
fight Jake and then do a pro fight and
then just go from there trying to a pro
fight yeah yeah I think I'll be sick so
just train up for that and obviously
side men as well do side men videos a
lot of things yeah so much time and
energy in the day I mean that is I mean
you've been doing it though that's it
like yeah like pretty much most of my
life it's just been this so yeah it's
just like you just keep going and just
see see what happens so yeah I just I
know for me it's a it's exciting but
it's not easy it's it's if anything it's
stressful
I've had several breakdowns off-camera
you saying
well what do you mean breakdowns in
terms of what oh just wanting to quit
things
oh no no just like mentally like oh my
god like I can't do this I'm doing too
much oh my god this is crazy bah bah bah
but uh my girlfriend is lit you been
like so helpful throughout through my
years essentially helping me out so yeah
it she she she's just calm me down
several times and I just put up put up
with me as well because I I'm a bit of a
handful
but now she's been seized she's been
amazing and she's always amazing so yeah
she's helped me loads of that I guess uh
to follow up on that when you say yeah
like mental breakdowns cuz you almost
seem like somebody who like would never
have that you know oh yeah hundred
percent like so for you to say there's
like scum something completely that you
would have never fathom oh yeah I think
I mean I don't know how often I haven't
seen everything you've been in so I
don't know is that something you talked
about or oh no no no I never talked
about yeah and that's why why I don't
know I I'm just like I guess maybe it's
maybe people might want to hear about
I'm just for me I'm sure like I'd like I
don't need to put this on them yeah yeah
alright let me just do what I'm doing
and show that I'm you know it's still
alright you still doing well yeah and if
I do freak out or if I have a mental
breakdown I just do it off camera you
know behind closed doors
no one's affected nothing happens I yeah
I don't get there oh you know I'm there
for you blah both not like no not simply
these stuff I'm just there like this is
yeah this is what I'm doing etc and just
leave it at that yeah I respect that
yeah yeah I just it's kind of like why
would I put my burden on someone else
and I sense a lot of people especially
on YouTube use that for themselves yeah
yeah yeah I guess it's not really my
thing
yeah I mean I don't think there's any
right or wrong yeah it's just
interesting for us to hear yeah
especially like you said you're ultra
saw you know he came with gifts today a
bunch of waters I know I'm such a good
guy man between each round he's like is
everybody hydrated I'm just telling
people down human no yeah
like I'm not like Superman I'm right I
mean I I I've seen a decent amount of
your videos hmm and I think this right
now is probably the most human that
you've ever looked on camera okay so in
a long time you know so to see this is
very different and it's very interesting
it's very unique that they get to see
this side of you and it's almost like
you know wow he's not like just this
egotistical God who's like just laughing
at everything like like it's crazy
because like literally every podcast I
go on they all say the same thing they
always like when I went on chat mates
and he was like oh I thought you'd give
me a [ __ ] [ __ ] yeah he was just like
I thought I was expecting to be an
absolute [ __ ]
yeah but you're just down to a normal
guy I was like yeah I want to go that
far I wanna go but I it's just like I
don't know I
yeah I don't know I just whenever the
cameras on I'm just like whatever it's
like it is what it is they're trying to
be entertaining yeah yeah I don't like
that right yeah I know for me there
isn't really a wall logic to what I do I
kind of just do and it just works I
guess
gotten you this far that's what people
like you're just doing whatever comes to
your mind that's it like it's great it's
crazy like people just so like screw it
so my bro says he does everything for
the fans like he's like he lets the fans
I guide him right where to go and for me
I'm like that's a terabyte you two have
like yeah you know my fans are cool and
all that but I did youtube for me
essentially I did YouTube to just well
just because I thought I wanted to make
entertaining videos and the people like
it cool people don't like it all right
yeah like it's just it's it's my life
essentially like I always feel like I I
don't want to be led by people if I make
sense I always want to just lead
by my Siddeley leave myself into what
direction I want to go in and I I feel
like it's it's what what yeah I mean I
think that's like to me that's what I
think is the secret to longevity yeah on
YouTube or any any platform because then
you're doing it for yourself exactly I
can relate to your brother in that I
used to the reason I'm doing this
podcast is because I had to figure out I
had my own version of a mental breakdown
yeah I was like man I keep making these
same skits and I'm like I know people
like them and people think they're smart
but I'm so sick of it like it's not that
I don't want to make skits anymore just
I got so tired of doing the same thing I
just wanted to do something more real
yeah so I mean that's why I want to do
this and it's super-new only dude and I
knew I was gonna suffer in terms of like
viewership and stuff but like it's the
only way I could have continued it's not
like losing my mind
ya know so I think that's why you're
able I mean you've been around like free
when did you start YouTube I think was
on 2010 2010 a long time started yeah
right like I mean I'm not gonna count it
like yeah I asked seven videos of
churches was in school just played FIFA
seven I just posted that I'd say I did
it properly around like 2010 he took it
serious that's what I wanted to really
go home on this so yeah look how far
you've come in and now you're fighting
Logan the thing is like that was huge
though oh my - nice to meet you just
coming yeah like I just come and I just
grasp it yes that's pretty much how
essentially I'm at this point like
whenever I see ya an opportunity I'm
they're like yeah I'm going you know
smashing through that and just gonna
obliterate it and it's annoying I didn't
be Logan because I was like oh this is
gonna work then I can do this bah bah
bah but I mean we just got tattoos wrong
so make sure also you injured your hand
right or something all right
yeah why lose like it wasn't too bad
like it's just like just the left a bit
I was kind of shocked how much bigger he
looked
yeah you know he's huge dude he's a big
guy yeah like both he's so he's like I
fled it background yeah yeah it fully
shows so yeah that's why we we do we
didn't even expect the stance we didn't
expect anything before he was just gonna
be conventional and he just switched on
us so we're like alright cool right so
we need to make sure we cover all bases
now and that's what we're doing
are you still training with we're down
no I'm trying I'm training with another
trainer Leone okay out here
I know so he he sometimes trains in
Vegas yeah but uh right now he's
training in the UK and he's got a fine
tube I think I believe next week yeah so
we bring a lot of boxers up in here but
I I think I just want to follow up with
one thing before we take this GG break
yeah
and just talking about the longevity of
your career because uh in the beginning
like you're really popping off you know
a lot of your videos did really well
Harlem shake
definitely and then you took this long
break mmm you know to kind of focus on
your music and stuff mm-hmm
do you feel like that kind of helped
regain your sanity or whatever you need
it yeah and 100 100 100 percent
literally thought 2017 break like
essentially saved my whole career like
with everything because I was just
knowing a good spot I was I was just
doing old types of things yo I went to
where like oh I wasn't Romania to see a
girl like that's just crazy for me like
and I only met her like once and this
isn't UK and then I flew all the way to
Romania in like not even like the
capital some like random area brush off
and literally just to see and just day
her and I was like
after outside what's wrong with me like
I'm literally just no I thought I just
didn't feel like right with myself and
eventually I just you know time to just
travel find myself oh my god find myself
but it's something you have to do and
eventually like you know I home did
Mycroft I figured out what do I want to
do with my life and I was like okay I've
got it all figured out and then just
things happened and it just wiped
perfectly and and what is I guess what
is one thing that like your Eureka
moment that hits you you know was there
a specific moment where like I know what
I need to do or this is where I regained
my sanity I think time just the break
and time was the best thing for me me
just separating myself from social media
and everything and just you know just
being with myself I think was the best
thing and if it took six months for me
to be like okay I'm good now but I feel
like it was necessary like it's just one
of those things like if you're so social
media this this data and it's just it's
just too much and I was just not happy
with like my content I wasn't happy with
where my music was I wasn't happy with
just everything I was just I just hate
like what I was at the time and now I'm
just so happy and I feel right now I
understand it more and now I know when
to take a break now I know okay
I've been going ham I need to just relax
here for a bit and you know I do have
those times where I just don't go on
social media and I just you know just
relax and I feel like that's just
important I feel like yeah time and just
separate yourself from this whole social
media buzz is important yeah that's a
brave thing I mean being a especially if
you're doing well you know online and
suddenly in anything for like even
instagramers everybody when you're on
that wave it's really hard to justify
I'm sure you can relate I'm gonna take a
break especially
know how long you renting that yeah
exactly it's it's a scary decision to be
like I am going to I mean you never know
if you fall off you're never coming back
so that's that's it but I feel like even
if I did fall off I would have just
still don't usually not just being a
happier place but for me it's not like
oh I need get this mile views and you
get this this that that right for me
it's like okay I want to make this type
of content and make it this good and I
want to put this out and you know I
won't make a track like this or I want
to you know put something out like this
like it's just for me like I just like
my music videos I just spend like this
stupid amounts I think when Allah I
spent like 90,000 pounds on yeah and I
think the videos on like 2.8 million
views and like people look at that like
well that was a flop but for me I was
like now I'd like that's exactly why I
wanted to put a video out like that
right and I wanted to spend that much on
something like that because for me it
was sick it was and that's what I mean
like for me I just want to make sick
stuff and do sick stuff right for me
it's it's never been about the money
it's always just about me enjoying what
I'm doing and I feel like a lot of
people just get caught up with the views
and the stats and all this and that yeah
it's good to always just separate
yourself from that and just be like okay
today I want to just make this type of
content made this type of song etc and
just you know enjoy it that's it like
that's YouTube is all about for me
having fun and if you're having fun and
what's the point exactly
yeah but like I told you I mean I'm sure
he liked your you understand as well
that's that's what I was doing even you
know and I get it - I was like okay this
works so I'm gonna keep doing it yeah
and it's it's a safe spot ya know
especially if you see views dropped and
all of a sudden like okay I got to do
even more stuff I don't just lucky if it
happens to be something like what you
did you found what you wanted to do and
luckily that is something everybody
wanted as well yeah I think that kind of
comes through with I mean that's that's
great for you people just like you for
you yeah you could be doing almost
anything
yeah you sure they'd be watching yeah
which is
yeah but just puts me in a really nice
spot and yeah I'm forever grateful but
you know ultimately I'm just gonna just
keep doing me and we're gonna call them
soft JJ's emotional one do we need to
take a shishi break yeah we're gonna dig
his cheesy break-in then after that
we'll discuss him fighting Dex
quick she break let's clap again and
we're back you should put that part in
I'm going I always put the claps in now
the second half I do
Oh cuz sometimes we say dumb stuff sorry
that was a longer break than usual that
was not a shishi break that was a
horrible though this was kind of a
shishi break for me pretty sure I had
food poisoning last night sorry guys um
yeah so where did we leave off we left
off talking about uh you know boxing and
what he wanted to do in his future plans
what'd you think I was gonna say darks
yeah that's what that is what text
that's kind of like it's good you don't
know no really I mean I throw when I
hate well if you want to explain a
little bit more yeah I don't in your
community that's kind of like a really
big joke yeah yeah it's just he's
becoming me so essentially he's just
this rapper
cult acts he wants to fight me
physically yeah okay
was he big I don't even know yeah I
don't know it's like way old sighs he's
ripped I'll give him that
but he thinks he could beat me in a box
in my she's six-foot - fix it - okay so
he's fairly tall yeah I think he thinks
he could beat me in the boxing match
and I'm like what if he's really good no
no I've seen I've seen him like punch
okay and no no do you only starch I mean
you were boxing even before all this
started happening right or did you just
start wars all right all right
that weller Joe Willis yeah were you
boxing before the fool not no literally
started when I was meant to fight Joella
uh-huh what how did that even come to I
mean I remember scene I was like oh this
is brilliant uh long story short I he
fought someone else is one of his mates
and I put it as a joke uh I'll fight the
winner and then he took that seriously
and then that's how you said it you said
something else you must have made it
more no that's Lily yeah and as you saw
like oh yeah yeah fight me then let's go
let's go
and I said no it's a joke Claire I don't
want you want to fight you and he's like
no no no and then we had a whole press
conference and then they go ahead and
right if I happen so yeah and that was
real too I was impressed cause that
wasn't planned I was very real for me
it's like because I know you you know I
mean so when I see these videos and
stuff like I don't know he'll be asking
me and stuff I'm be like I I don't know
I'm gonna ask you that's not how I
usually I got the one with the head the
fire I mean the press conference right
especially like that girl yes so like it
was like it was a right between me and
him but it wasn't because like we more
like friends friends but you know we
knew of each other we different deals
together and then it just not personal
it just turned mine like he just you
know switch something to try and I guess
just ruin room my career essentially I
know I just call it so angry and then I
just like lost my [ __ ] and I just went
red I am caught so angry to the point
where I was trying to like grab him like
hurt him
yeah so because he pushed me he did no
he nudged into me and I just as I do
what the [ __ ] are you doing
we're meant to just have this press
conference and then box didn't leave her
at that but he just you know took it way
farther with like what was said and why
he's the what he did
I just lost my [ __ ] to the point where
one of the bodyguards tried stopping me
and I threw him across the stage and
just ripped his suit the body goes yeah
fully ripped it and then they got more
and more people just to hold me back
and I thought boy I was like I'm going
to do this man I mean yeah yeah for
tomorrow I think is the referee stopped
early yeah it was taken who started the
side men who stir so it it kind of its
kind of just for former side man I
didn't make sure you this right it's me
Simon Josh and Ethan yeah no no I'm Toby
so it was all well pretty much we
started the GTA group and we were just
like I we should just make videos
together why why this would be good so I
think at the time there was another
group and we were just I wish she'd do
something similar it was it was do you
know like speedy and them all right so
those youtubers I forgot what the group
is called but they had like a little
group and like oh yeah we should just do
something similar so we had that and I
think then Vic wanted to join Vic was
quite interested so he did a few videos
with him and we weren't called the
Seidman at this point we were just doing
videos together and then we I think it's
so long ago um
so Harry was in the community but he
wasn't like like we knew of him but we
were told by another youtuber I don't
know if I should be saying this
oh [ __ ] it's not it's not too bad it's
not too bad it's not too bad
we were told by another youtuber Knapp
to pretty much take Harry under our wing
we take Harry under our wing because he
was going down like a bad rule with
other youtubers which I won't say who
but he was going down a bad route with
another other couple of youtubers so
Knapp was like oh you should definitely
like put her in your group just you know
to steer him in the right direction so
we're like yeah yeah sure we'll do it
and you know he was Steve's jokes you
know we divisions with him and
eventually just like I would you know we
should call ourselves something and um
yeah we decide Seidman was pretty jokes
like just Seidman is kind of like an
insult it's not anymore it's right now
it's like it's crazy like you'd you get
rapped it's always like calling like it
would be an insult to cool someone aside
man okay so you have rappers always be
saying like my mind's aside manland or
your side man this this that you know
I'm the main man your side my neck
cetera it's now no no rapper says it
because of us later because if so many
need something else now yeah but
literally it's like if you mean the side
menu like oh wait you mean the YouTube
group sorry it doesn't work it doesn't
work is watching more so it's crazy so
we're literally turning the word the
insole into just just our group name now
but um yeah we decided to just call
ourselves the side man this we thought
it just be jokes like well assignment of
each other's of each other just what I
said she's just dissing each other and
yeah over time we just just grew and
grew and grew and it's crazy yo the
Simon almost like wasn't a thing I think
is around 2017 is legend when I when I
left
during that whole period like the
sidemen were just like oh just in limbo
right like you know Simon and Josh and
Toby and a few others
we're still doing videos
you know did a few Simon videos here in
NAB like GTA and etc but it was like
getting to a point where we were like I
was might have to and this some point
died say yeah just like move on from
this whole Simon thing and then the
whole dish strikes happened and then
from then it was like a huge boom but
after that we were like okay we're back
to you know the point where we were
before
right like yeah we've got all these
views but it's like what do we do is
each other like what's what's going on
and the thing that saved the sideman was
a YouTube originals youtuber youtuber
original saves the sideman because
because of you two originals we needed
we had this seidman channel but we
didn't we hardly ever posted any content
uh-huh we didn't have the symbol we have
where we have now we post every single
week we just had a thing where we would
just post like charity matches and
that's pretty much it and just you know
what I was pretty yeah that's pretty
much it we didn't really post anything
else so we we had the salmon channel
like okay you two were like you guys
need to have more traffic on this
channel for us to like do this side man
originals series so okay we have to
think of a plan so we're thinking okay
what would work and we decided would do
videos together every week and post it
every Sunday at the start of 2018 just
to get some traffic right you know onto
the channel and you know over time it
just popped off like it got bigger and
bigger and bigger and then YouTube
originals happened and now it's like I
was alright it didn't really do much but
we gained so much from it not through
the views of the u2 original like the
YouTube regions didn't really do much
for us
but the stuff around it that helped so
it made us do videos every Sunday right
hey gosh like a rotor you know it goes
our
Paso manager to like so all of like
stuff it just got a six lead in the
group we kind of all take charge that's
the political answer no no no we always
take charge like take turns because it's
all like he could like the shares equal
everybody just gets the exact same out
so we all have to pull our weight yeah
so sometimes you're so on this and
pulling that weight we just get on them
and we're just like yo you know put that
weight and then they'll pull that weight
and then that's it and saw it yeah how
does a large group like that cuz wrong I
think from what I've heard I could be
wrong
everybody has to come up with a video
idea yeah well and they're in charge of
that we kind of we kind of come together
and we think of ideas and so yeah some
people are better ideas than others but
we were like I you know for me I had an
idea to do it in the video real-life -
in the video where us seven side men
we're in the line and we have a girl
several girls come in and they would
just rate us so they would like swipe
right or swipe left and if they swipe
left
we asked them why and we thought it'd be
funny just you know see what reason for
why girls would want to swipe swipe left
to us think so it's so like just stuff
like that and then I'll just set it all
up I'm you know make sure the studios
are sawing Tanya who's our personal
manager helps so much she is literally
the rock in the side man like she just
makes sure makes everything work without
her we just be all over the place so she
is like the best and we got her from the
YouTube originals she was already she's
working with a company that was working
with the whole you to originals and we
were just like yo like do you want to be
our personal manager and she's four by
it it's just like [ __ ] it let's go let's
see what happens and now she's like over
the moon
and yeah like just stuff like that's
well that's that's probably partly why
the sidemen is just thriving like and
why were in just such a good position
and it's crazy like in 2017 we were
close to like just ending it yeah yeah
that's crazy
it's something that like seems so small
it's just like the catalyst for like
great yeah youtubers who will follow
YouTube originals yeah save the Seidman
they're gonna take that quote and like
use it out of everything like we did
this you're welcome but they can't use
this you know because then you can
copyright strike them yeah
monetization I wouldn't be surprised if
this gets copyright actually I that's
that's an interesting thing
copyright monetization copywriting
things and monetization because both of
you guys your demographics are that's a
pretty different and the content that
you put out is very different you're a
lot edgier yeah I yeah Ryan is is more
safe you know like on the fence and
stuff um how do you deal with
monetization on things cuz without the I
dare you that we all did together you
just said that guide to monetize right
it I well first I think it got age
restricted and then I mean a lot of the
ideas I mean I get it because it's like
now they're trying to say like if
anything that is considered dangerous
even though we have a disclaimer in the
beginning I mean they're just looking
out for themselves
mmm yeah but um well I like so I have
two channels on my main channel I don't
really get to monetize or claimed much
because a lot of content there now it's
just original stuff and I we make sure
like there's no like operates yeah but
you like swear and you're just like yeah
it's I think I doesn't get to monetize
though like I think um so I think
swearing is alright if it's you know
like - if it's not too crazy and I think
YouTube definitely like the whole skits
and like music when it comes to music
and skits they're quite lenient yeah
whereas my second channel I've
like I get destroyed yeah I because I'm
just like myself and YouTube they're
like nope s'alright don't be yourself
yeah yeah I do
one question go I get to monetize and
you know like I do reaction videos and I
get copyright claims and the monetize so
it's literally like it's hard to like
make any money on my second channel I
like I just that's what the second
channel for yeah it's just waiting out
stuff I just want I just want to just do
like and I feel like for me it just
makes so much sense I it just works in
my head to have like premium content on
my main channel and in my second term I
can just sit back and just not care and
just do a [ __ ] out one right so I think
it's just like AI just White's me so
well no we know yeah we need to swear
and not be ourselves and do original
things do original things there's a
second channel we just got to start
dropping bombs
I know get more that's so inconsistent
though cuz yeah I heard that I don't
really get like we get but like even
like in the negative right now if you
have homeless oh this is like fake set
yes all green screen after this we have
to go to the strip we have to put on our
homeless gear by the way you have any
extra dollars for us Oh pound sorry
euros whatever take anything what your
scraps dude wherever you're going
tonight
lose your food oh I will for you'd be
like untouched ah a lot of stuff got
claimed is it just like copyright claims
there's some call a lot of a lot of
copyright claim from previous like stuff
in the past yeah pretty good about that
now yeah we have to be you know and a
lot of things like is it's it's
debatable and I could you know maybe
fight it but it's like it's such a
process yeah you know at that point I'm
just like I'm just gonna stop doing that
but yeah I mean I get it a lot and then
I heard I mean that had a title once
where it has like F asterisk asterisk
asterisk in it mmm and that gets like oh
it's demonetised yeah and it's old video
even a podcast that had M om oh oh yeah
oh yeah yeah well because when that was
going on we talked about it we're not
promoting it because the title that
podcast got like instantly did yeah yeah
I don't even think it was a person it's
just the system yeah Yugi would just
turn the cover there oh yeah yeah all
those type of things I see their
perspective because people are coming at
them but they're it's I think if they
keep going down this path it's just
gonna ruin it I think it's gonna be so
boring all the contents gonna be so
tense 'red yeah yeah it's crazy like
compared to like where YouTube was years
ago is now it's it's if anything it's
becoming really like TV yeah yeah with
the censorship and what you can and
can't say right well when money gets
involved then people start caring about
this that's a all right well I mean we
had a really good talk so far so why
don't we include some audience questions
we have Twitter question oh yeah
so we have some Twitter questions if you
guys have any questions for future guess
you can always follow us at off the pill
on twitter or on instagram at off the
pill podcast so a comment or yeah or
leave a comment oh one of the questions
that we have from twitter today is from
two cents spencer which is kiss i what
does the team look like creating your
videos is it just you you and an editor
give us a picture what would you mean
well because like you you kind of have
like different people for different
stuff like you worked with Randolph
right here the cameraman and then you
also have con yeah and then who edits
like you edit I mean there was one video
I one video no two videos I've edited
this year and usually you can kind of
tell which ones there were so the t food
versus ninja i added that and that to me
like through three days it's like
edit
is a long process so she's away I had it
I'm just so particular and it just
doesn't work for like especially with
the second channel because then your
daily almost and what one your job yeah
I've slowed down a bit just because
things have just got really really busy
but you get really hung over
I just use as an excuse I was just there
like yeah I just got too much going on
I'm still okay I'm all over guys sorry
oh my I go after we yeah but uh yeah
what if like yeah so I I have various
people so I've been who shoots certain
types of videos so he does quite a few
well he does most my skits sometimes he
does music videos I've gone he does my
music videos and he also does like Simon
videos I also have me I guess I film
myself when I just Chuck the hardest -
yeah I ask for me yeah the most work but
uh besides that no I don't I don't
really have any other I I mean how many
editors Diab usually just one yeah I've
just just like I was crazy I mean like
remained my main channel like if I was
to do a music video like I don't have
different random editors for that but
it's like I'm mind control of that at
uncon and been so I've combed once the
Edit he whether if condos weren't out
there he'll find someone else to edit
and say my bed so and how do you uh I
guess how do you have you how did you
get into working relationship with all
these people here literally just through
just YouTube just mutual I literally
like everyone we meet it's just all
natural it's just I I never go out or
reach out to people unless I'm dead like
yo we have to do something so with
quackity I don't know if you know crack
is he is but he's a youtuber who I look
to his video sounds like this guy's
and his videos are so well edited I have
to do something with him so I reached
out to him and did something with him
and it's not like I was like ah I wanted
now you have to do a video for my
channel but I just did a video for him
and he put on this channel and that was
it and I just left and he hit me up
saying like if you ever need me you know
just holler
and I was like yeah cool like of course
you know I'll let you know but it's like
I'm never a guy who's just like ah you
know you I scratch your back you scratch
mine
like I need to get something from for
doing something I'm there like if I
think you're you're sick is held and I'm
gonna do something with you so where was
I going with that that was good that's
very that came a lot from one question
but that's good we got a lot of we got
more another side of you yeah just do it
for you because he doesn't expect
anything in return good guy I'm just
kidding yeah I mean you came out and you
kicked the cactus for me and we didn't
even we filmed the video today yeah yeah
I guess yeah you came all the Vegas but
it's like sleeping for my channel yes I
was like damn thank you you have to do
it welcome to London eventually yes I
haven't actually I've been all over
we're not all over but is there any I
guess places UK like conventions or
anything
damn I get a lot of enquiries like Josh
Trey Leah and Southeast Asia India even
but not that many from the U and we have
a decent viewership out there but we
have we have a VidCon in the UK yeah and
I guess the final Twitter question is
from Andy Tien it's better be a good one
Andy who it is as oh jeez of YouTube
oh how difficult old was it to
transition to a different kind of
content from the one you've started with
we talked about that I mean you did
right it's going does mommy did FIFA yes
I saw a fever and then I was just like I
don't be doing FIFA with my life's I
just I mean you have to be a bit more
tactical with it you have to like slowly
feed in all the content to the point I'd
still like release the main content that
you're putting out just so people like
oh what are you doing no this is all
like no go back to what you're used to
but I yeah a lot of time you just have
to ignore people like people always
gonna say [ __ ] until eventually like
they just go away or you just find new
audience yeah love both things that
you're doing and then you find an
audience I love all the things that you
like you want to do etc so and I think
for you because they're there for your
personality yeah so you know it doesn't
really mother yeah they're there for you
no matter you could watch paint dry and
make that exciting no it's true
yeah that's just your person on and
that's something that you have like that
you're one of your talents you've
definitely grown that and push that side
of you yes I feel like just YouTube has
slight helped tremendously with that
yeah over the time look just
you always charismatic as ago no I was
very into red really extremely
introverted as you were when you were
growing up yes I mean I didn't talk to
girls like I remember there was a time I
think it was like yeah what year was it
year 12 so I was around 16 17 I think so
- 18 and a go came a girl just walk past
me and I really liked her so I said hi
and she said hi back and I just shot
myself
I think seriously hot was being and
everything I didn't I was like oh god
it's gonna sound so lame but I would
always like go on Google how to talk to
girls and like what to say after hi and
yeah literally is the worst I didn't
know what I remember I went on a date
and I like wrote stuff in my hand like
things to say so you know like Oh mal
just get so nervous non-web I said what
did you learn that how do you talk to
girls uh well it was the most important
thing I guess
it's not like it's you kind of just have
to experience it you can't like there
isn't like it go - yeah like before I
always looked a simple pickup and stuff
like that and just be like okay how how
do they pick up girls and how they make
make it look so easy unless you just
experience and just you know you build
up the confidence or would you like
failed a lot you made a lot of guys
saying you just have to fail yeah just
have to go in and fail to the point
where well I felt so many times I can't
get any worse than this and then
eventually just go up from there and
yeah you just I just got more
comfortable and then yeah I started just
going home with look at you know you got
a girlfriend and yeah six guy friends so
clearly something is working right
working out yeah Simon in the side
chicks don't let her see I'm just
kidding I'm making a joke she's like
what just nothing okay
I mean she watches this is like what
just sent her that Clinton made I guess
like the main stuff yeah so but like she
would never watch the whole of this you
guys have too much content okay no I
mean this is Demi you got to be like
there's a certain demographic to have to
watch a pocket or listen to a pop she's
just busy with oh yeah yeah yeah see
yeah I guess people go up to him you
like oh did you hear what JJ said about
you here and then she oh yeah yeah
that's that's normal yeah now she
doesn't have time to just it's just okay
well I mean yeah
that was a good one actually yeah I was
going with and on it wasn't it like hey
do you like green also I think the the
cool thing that that applies to us is a
lot of your older viewers are like oh am
I the only person who hates this podcast
or you know yeah but we knew I mean a
whole video with like talking about how
yeah you aren't gonna like it but again
a lot those people don't have the time
to watch every single video and I mean I
went from posting like once every like
three weeks sometimes sometimes once a
month and this is just extra yeah you
know just something I wanted to do but
goes back to
we were talking about earlier about
having to just figure out what I wanted
to do yeah yeah this is like my break
actually I think mmm how you took your
break yeah I think I needed to stop
creating stuff so I can get excited
about it it got to that's loot you know
just getting so like or that I couldn't
come up with ideas yeah but okay well
thanks for being here man you're in
Vegas to film there's like entertainment
capital yeah yeah literally like just
film yeah and you're here working
there's so many people yeah film with
job Okies tomorrow is gonna be he's
dancing I seen you dance earlier oh yeah
that was amazing get can you show I
guess da real quick no laughing yeah
that was great well thank you for being
on the show we already plugged our off
the pill at off the pill on Twitter and
at off the pillow podcast on Instagram I
almost forget which one go and find you
can find JJ ksi what do you have to plug
ya plug your show your torque alright so
going on tall so if you live in America
fly over to it's gonna be safe where
it's in all the way all the way okay
although England and Europe as well and
yeah man no show us here the wage knows
shows in America combs alright maybe
soon maybe in the future just do a show
right outside of Jake's house oh god no
no I wouldn't give him up his whole tone
changes yeah I do not like it much
that's perfect
all right well thanks for being here
pleasant off the pill podcast and talk
to you next podcast somehow we ended oh
yeah we didn't we didn't tell him but
should we just do it you could tell him
we just ended by breathing into the mic
in 3 2 1
it's actually really bad for the mics
but we just started doing it and we have
to keep doing it now okay all right