[Music]
what happened what did you do to my
stomach going on we stuck a package of
balls in your mother tongue and you're
gonna transport something very special
to us Oh God
this is definitely used
[Music]
no no no hey do you speak English no no
no no English do you speak English all
right I just said I know speaking take
it to the hospital somebody put a bag of
blue stuff inside of me I need to take
it out it's leakers most human beings
only use 10% of the frames capacity
imagine if we could access 100%
interesting things begin to help a guy
that's samuel l.jackson yes who suffer
l.jackson I just Rika PD at all your
research about the human brain it's a
little boring but at least there were
some pictures in it
I thank you seems this drug is actually
enabling you to use your brain nearly
three times the amount of the average
person which in theory should make you a
super genius I in UN but it also seems
your brain is helping how do I put this
politely
much much much dumber than the average
person so not only you're not a super
genius like you're still way below
average I knew it you currently have
access to 28% of your brain and it'll
only go from there wait what how would
that even finish out of my hands not
changing in size you're just using more
of but you just said I have 28 persons
brains
how would that not bigger no percent our
Center said percent are 78 percent
caution I can feel every living thing
this is a table I can do things that I
could never do before this is a book
why don't you start eating Chinese since
now Erica what happens when she reaches
a hundred percent I don't care I'm like
a superhero genius stop no you're not
[Music]
the blue stuff makes me smarter but then
I can answer it yesterday
[Music]
well there are tubes in the equation and
the number two sounds like the letter U
and the letter U is between the letters
T MB in the alphabet but chi-chi's are
really relevant anymore because
everybody has computers now so it's
kinda like if you have two TVs just like
was it even four that's right I knew it
I feel like I've exceeded my limits like
if there are limits for me before now
there's less of those limits if not no
limits at all I just feel limitless you
know like that one really with Bradley
Cooper in it the hung over you know what
I mean right
I have no idea so thank you guys so much
for watching if you want to see bloopers
and behind the scenes click the one on
the left if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the right and if
you haven't seen the actual Lucy trailer
and this video made those cents to you
then click the one on the bottom it's a
little bit better because scarlet
Johanson it and she's slightly prettier
then why did you get that I I just said
she's prettier to me and you're at