hey guys so you're probably wondering
why do I look like a complete nerd right
now it's the shirt I probably look like
one of those losers that stays home all
day and reads all night and doesn't have
a girlfriend it spends all his time
online on the computer well you're wrong
cuz I don't read no a lot you guys don't
know this especially if you don't watch
my second channel without my glasses or
contacts my vision is pretty much poorer
I mean I'm almost legally blind what did
you call me no blind
I said legally blind not blonde that's
not what I heard don't be stomping your
lessons and prada shoes that mija it's
not even product it's Louis Vuitton what
are you blind or something yes love that
movie
anyway I'm wearing my glasses because I
can't wear my contacts for about a week
and the reason for that is because I am
going to be having eyeball surgery what
that was terrible here trying to get
that's better it's really not that bit
supposed to be a really safe procedure
I've always been really careful about
protecting my eyes I mean think about
your eyeballs are so important and yet
there's nothing really protecting it
other than your eyelids yes these are
the joke of the body protection
committee what a muscle well bone look
at eyelid till they're all flimsy and my
pupil science shows right comes with the
glasses like I said I've always been
really protective over my I mean I wear
sunglasses all the time like when I
Drive when I'm by the pool when I'm
wearing sunglasses even when I'm indoors
douche I can't take my eyes in every
scenario even in a situation that you
would never think about kissing a girl
with a pointy nose I don't have a pointy
nose yeah I love you
doosh the only time I let my guard down
and I'm not proud of it but I broke
probably the biggest I rule of all time
come on keep up and that's the last time
I ever win running with scissors but
overall how can I lie I know it's a
common procedure but there's always that
one thought in my head like what did
they mess up and I go blind what if I
want to wear glasses again I don't want
to be a hipster and what about all the
memories all the memories with these
terrible eyes I mean I'll never be able
to see this way again
okay yeah I need the surgery it's gonna
happen in about a week whether I'm
afraid that it might go horribly wrong
or not so I guess there's just one last
thing I have to do it's not easy for me
to say this look I know you've always
been there for me through the good and
the bad for more than two years that we
shared you helped me see the world in a
whole new way but this surgery is gonna
happen and I'm gonna have to say the
diagnosis what just know that I will
always love you by Whitney Houston is a
great song I just know that I'll be
missing you
bye Puff Daddy and not be tinny there's
a difference
and if you ever feel like you're
lonelier or rolling in the deep' let me
guess by Adele right yes I mean I'm more
of a Mac person but you should
definitely buy Adele so we can stay in
content you want to keep in contact here
take them take all the classes don't do
this no I don't want to end this quick
clearly you wanted it to end right yes
come on get your class back here glasses
glasses goodbye right yeah well you guys
are fixing my eyes could you just do a
quick check on my brain thanks for
picking me up scissors no problem hop in