so I know it's not in the title and I
haven't done it in a while but this is
pretty much an off the pill vide for
those of you that are new and don't know
that series off the pill pretty much
means that I can get pregnant at any
time oh it means that I was diagnosed
with ADHD as a kid and off the pill it
means that I don't take my medication I
just turn on the camera and talk to it
and just let my mind flutter it's the
best word I could come up with see I
need I need my medication hey guys so
today I'm gonna be talking about some
lessons that I learned this year but
before I get into it first of all let me
say that I'm sorry I haven't posted a
video in a couple weeks the video I'm
currently working on is taking a lot
longer than I thought and it's been
something I really wanted to do all year
and just never had the time for it and I
still don't have the time for it that's
why I miss two weeks but it should be
done next week so I hope you guys
actually like it when it comes out may
not and I don't want to give away too
much but to get you guys excited here's
a quick preview here there's gonna be a
character with two eyes in it for sure
alright I didn't show you guys what it
was about because I don't want to spoil
it and also kind of because we don't
have that much done yet you know what is
this look like a lizard but we just
finished filming so it should be done by
next week I'll be on the lookout for it
back to the top before I distract myself
again here's all the lessons I learned
in 2013 for I thanks to vine I learned
how every different Ray's be like in
every case scenario another lesson I got
from mine is that you can be racist as
long as it's funny and online why people
be like white people be like black
people be like Latin people be lying I'm
all like hope still not gonna download
it I always saw these kids doing the cup
song and I never know how to do it but
thanks to Anna Kendrick nailed it yes
twerking show me that if dance keeps
continuing down this row one day there's
still hope that I can be a dancer EDM
music show me that lyrics don't matter
anymore [ __ ] more sexual the better
when it comes to getting views having
your shirt off in every single picture
and flexing a little making it seem like
you're not flexing does not make you a
douche it just makes you Justin Bieber
whenever anyone passes away it's sad but
if you're a homeless guy and you pass
away from a drug overdose most people
are like good riddance aleb rity that
passes away from a drug overdose it's
the saddest thing ever to be people
sympathize for you have an excuse your
celebrity no matter how successful
looking or how good of a person you are
it doesn't matter every time you get
into a car you're risking your life
especially if your speed because cars
treat everyone the same they don't care
who you are they're all about equality
they're not racist so stop racing them
Nelson Mandela passing away is such a
big event but I think people went a
little overboard with how sad they were
about it I honestly think both Cory and
Paul's death was way more sin Elson Ben
tell ellipta he was 95 people shouldn't
be crying over him they should be
celebrating him I honestly didn't learn
anything from this one but I couldn't
not include it granted I bought a 5
taught me that the only thing better
than killing and stealing is killing and
stealing with your friends whatever a
new iPhone comes out you probably
shouldn't get it because before you know
it next one's already here in Robin
Thicke song blurred lines the lyrics
what rhymes with hug me taught me that
if you don't have good lyrics to write
for your next line just ask what's a
good joke to end this one with seriously
I learned from Laura that harmonies make
everything sound good
Kanye West Tommy and the rest of the
world what it really means to be a
genius so you gotta be pretty clever and
genius to come up with such a catchy
ahead of the game name like North West
where your dog being the non genius that
I am I probably would have came up with
something stupid and delayed like
Southwest sorry Southwest I genuinely
love YouTube that YouTube is always
teaching me things this year I learned
that I should probably be into gaming
videos I also learned in your PowerPoint
up you can do whatever you want no
matter what anyone says or thinks for
example this year when they integrated
Google+
so yeah hope you guys learn something
anyway on a serious note there's one
last thing I wanted to say in this forum
thank you to every single person that
subscribe to this channel we recently
just passed 11 million subscribers and I
know that may not be considered a lot
anymore especially when you compared to
someone like PewDiePie who has way more
than that just know that I genuinely
100% appreciate each and every one of
you that continue to watch and support
and share my videos especially if you
made it this far into the video I know
this one's not the most interesting one
in the world no matter how much time
goes by its I'm always gonna appreciate
you guys and thank you guys so much and
like I always say and I know it sounds
super cheesy but from the bottom of my
heart which is also the middle of my
ribcage to the top of my thoracic cavity
right underneath the clavicles on the
right side of my sternum right here in
this general area thank you guys so much
I know there's no way I can know all of
you and I can't physically thank every
single one of you but you guys have done
so much for me and I know I physically
can't give you guys anything so I'll
leave you with this one last thing one
last lizard neck
looks like we're evenly matched I'm not
even getting started