like anytime I I wouldn't meet someone
and I walk in the room and I'm a 6-3
black guy and they're like basketball
right
that's usually what they assume when I
go back to the studio tomorrow there's
gonna be a bunch of boxes waiting for me
and I'm just pumped to open like his
Christmas every time if I'd only use one
phone that I would use the one plus
seven preps
welcome back to another episode about
the pill podcast today yeah we have
David the moderator see Paco's next to
me I'm Ryan and another very special
guest mr. marques Brownlee in the house
everybody oh wow beautiful that's all
you get we don't really use that know
one of the biggest if not the biggest
probably tech youtuber in fact you are
the biggest taking youtuber for sure
there's a bunch of other channels that
also do tagged you've been around a long
time but I've been doing just tech haha
okay and you're in town so thank you
again cuz you're normally in New York
right yeah New Jersey uh-huh east coast
okay and then you're here for I don't
know if you want to bring it up I do
you're here dude so I came out here
we're in LA for there is a Motorola
event where they they announced you know
you've probably had the razor one of the
most popular phones ever made a folding
screen version of it and so it was
they're having this announcement event
it was cool we got to see it in person
it was revealed mm-hmm but the event
itself was pretty bad
and I think kind of like roasting them
on in my video in other places but it's
a it's happened it's out there now it's
it's out there that Motorola doesn't
know how to throw events I can tell it's
been a while yeah well the last phone
they even had well we have a lot of
mid-range phones like their Moto G is
one of the most popular like $350 phones
and so they don't really have to do a
big showy fancy event for it they just
put it out and suddenly it's the most
well selling phone on Amazon because
people love cheap phones really oh but
you know big 900 this is a $1500 phone
they got to do some some showy stuff
they tried to put on an event Diplo was
there but it wasn't that great was the
music good no sorry but in general I
mean like you said you like the phone
though yeah I mean it was so I didn't
even use a razor but like I could tell
like just from holding it like wow this
is kind of cool a little folding screen
thing is still pretty sweet I don't know
if it's worth $1500 oh my gosh I think
you have to really love that nostalgia
that they're sort of wrapping it in and
I think a lot of people will try to get
it for that reason but yeah I mean I saw
a mean movie I thought it was fake but
that's I mean it does look cool I mean I
don't know at functionality-wise I don't
know but and that's kind of a thing that
uh other companies are pushing right the
foldable screen stuff yeah yeah yeah
Samsung has one Huawei has one this
company royal made one there's like a
couple floating out there but they're
all over $2,000 so on one hand this is
one of the cheaper folding screen phones
but it's still like an iPhone is you
know a thousand eleven hundred bucks and
most people are just just getting a new
iPhone right so you gotta you gotta have
a real reason to spend that much so
right they're trying so you're
constantly going to these different
events and releases and stuff because I
mean that's what you do yeah and I'm
sure people invite you and bring you out
because it benefits them the thing I
appreciate is that you're pretty honest
with your reviews like it's not always
positive and I'm sure they're bringing
out or even paying you how do you manage
that if some if someone's bringing you
out and even if I don't know maybe they
don't but I'm sure there must be like
some kind of compensation right since
you're doing them free promo there has
never been ever so I've done so I yeah
fly to events I go I pay for the flight
in the hotel really go out there they
always invite me and it'll be up to me
to decide is it worth going like is this
one of those things that people are
interested in should I go see it or not
the Motorola one I was like yeah people
who will care about this folding phone
like or the more interesting things this
year but yeah a lot of times there is
events that are just sort of more casual
or and I'll just not go or they'll
invite me in a
I have to decide it's worth it but in
general I just know that valuing my
honesty yeah like is actually that's the
reason I'm there is to give you my
impressions what I really think is the
product worth the money that either
they're announcing they're gonna charge
for it that's what I'm there to show so
if I'm not honest and none of that's
worth it for anyone right right right
right yeah okay well that's I mean
that's good to know
yeah so how long exactly have you been
doing it 2009 was the first video so
almost 11 years 11 years do you still I
mean it seems like you enjoy it but yeah
at some point I mean I'm sure it's
exciting as you you're really into it
but some point is there ever time where
you're just like man I just want try
other stuff kind of yes but also so much
of what I'm into is trying to make the
videos as good as possible
uh-huh and the more you do in this I'm
sure you know like in this world of like
trying to make videos unique and better
the more you find that you can also try
to do mm-hm and so we're in this like
crazy world of like we got this camera
robot that's specifically made for
moving a camera
it's you'd see a robot in like a factory
that would like move parts around mm-hmm
a company has like written software to
control it and keyframe it and so now
we're attaching the camera to it and
like having the robot do crazy camera
moves we're at this point now we're like
that's the type of fun that we have
making a video well that's kind of where
exactly where like if I was just doing
the same type of video I did eight years
ago I'd probably be really bored but
that's just just advancing your craft
actually exactly it just so happens to
be something you're still interested in
yeah yeah that's always gonna be new
tech exactly that's part of why my job
is easy I don't have to be interesting
and exciting and I mean I guess often
you know you have to be a little more
than my normal self but I like the tech
has to be interesting and so I don't
have to work as hard as the engineers
trying to get everyone's attention right
have you always been into tech like what
what got you started and all that yeah I
feel like I have pretty much always been
into tech somewhat of a nerd my dad was
an IT I don't know if that had anything
to do with it but you know finding you
know computer when I was in high school
and buying my first iPod touch and being
like this is amazing I went on box it in
front of a camera like that's probably a
pretty nerdy thing to do so like I've
always been into tech
someone I also read that you majored in
business and information technology that
that must also play into like what you
know your your passions right yeah yeah
I and I went to a tech school so that's
like almost everyone there was technical
in some way I've you know I always had
the my best score all nine times I took
the SAT it was always the math section
so I feel like I've always yeah had sort
of a technical inclination but then it's
just exciting like new gadgets are just
fun so it sounds like you were made for
this like with your dad being an IT do
you talk to him a lot about like
different gadgets that come out and was
that was that always like a part of your
life growing up uh yeah and his job is
like about like solutions in a way so
software solutions like custom you know
infrastructure type stuff so it's not
even like the gadgets he's like more
like behind the scenes but even that
like now that's like what we talk about
is like did you see this new phone or
are you trying out the Chromebooks right
now what's your deal so like yeah that's
just sort of always been part of what we
talk about and how old are you 25 25
yeah and you've been doing like
interested in tech stuff for a long time
since like a young age then yeah and was
it ever an issue where you were growing
up like that people because you know a
lot of people are like oh black people
should be athletic which you are because
you'd play on a professional Frisbee
team and currently yeah team yeah it's a
pretty new world a pro ultimate Ultimate
Frisbee is like 50 years old but yeah
row ultimate is pretty new yeah
does that mean you get paid to play the
game someone yeah it's almost nobody's
full-time job yeah everyone who plays
professional too prefers me pretty much
always also has there a doctor a teacher
or whatever uh-huh but yeah when we go
out and we play in front of a stand full
of fans and there's referees and it's
like it feels like a pro thing that's
like the craziest part yeah like what
else things like you're not only smart
you do have the athletic side so but did
you ever have to deal with people
teasing you because like oh why don't
you play like
or whatever yes dear - yeah I don't know
if it probably wasn't ever teasing as
much as it was just like it almost seems
like an innocent question like anytime I
like meet someone and I walk in the room
and I'm a 6-3 black guy and they're like
basketball right that's usually what
they assume I actually remember pretty
recently I like called an uber from
Newark Airport and I like timed it
perfectly so that I was walking out the
airport as the uber pulled up and I like
walk out the airport and as I was
getting in some like lady saw that and
literally was like I don't know who you
are but I'm sure you're probably an
athlete so hi whoa just because like she
assumed that that's like something like
and like a Giants player random just a
random person whoa do you take offense
to those things I don't take offense
well she's also not wrong she doesn't
dude you're a pro at yeah it's like it's
almost like the the implication is like
that's definitely what you're probably
gonna be doing and I watch basketball I
love basketball but yeah that's I get
the innocent assumptions I think you
have a tuna so kinda I watched the
Rockets games oh and that's because I
was following Chris Paul for like the
last like five or six years now that
he's not when he got to the Rockets I
started watching them and then James
Harden started having historic seasons
and now he's on the Thunder which is way
like the sighting so I'm just a Rockets
viewer now really but you're from New
York
like the nets are over the Nets I
started liking the New Jersey Nets
they moved to New York yep they're
pretty great but the Knicks voice - my
dad's a Knicks fan
I apologize every time that he's still
in expand to him but I yeah I've never
really had like an allegiance like to a
city I just want to respect some players
I I think something about his game like
I've been a defensive player in Ultimate
Frisbee and Chris Paul's defense
specifically we're the same height and I
feel like I watch him move and I'm like
that dudes like n basically I think he's
like 6 1 yeah there's something like
that but like he's an awesome defender
and his IQ is off the charts and I just
like watching smart players be at him no
because you've met a lot of I've met
some players yeah I have not met Chris
Paul but I have been to a couple Rockets
games
yeah yeah Bettina I have always been a
Spurs fan it's personal to get pick
rivals kinda they've ended the rocket
season once or twice yeah and well I
think we're we we've got we've have a
bigger rivalry with Dallas to be fair
from back in the day anyway we're
irrelevant now
so I think you can make the playoffs
here [ __ ] let's see man we'll see but
that's kinda surprising actually you're
a Houston fan and Chris Paul
but speaking of people that you've met I
mean you just a quick youtube search
Google search the people that you've
interviewed and talk to is it's kind of
amazing
and I just thought we'd bring it up I
mean like Bill Gates
Elon Musk Kobe Bryant Neil deGrasse
Tyson Will Smith in the most recent
rewind just said he's one of the first
things he says is your name yeah I mean
that's gotta be kind of cool pretty wild
yeah it's always fascinating when I do
like an interview or something like that
to figure out like every interview yeah
every interview has its own like
circumstance of like you know someone's
on a press tour or they're they're just
trying to do their YouTube presence
whatever they're trying to do Robles
yeah and it's always fascinating to like
try to figure out what that situation is
and yes some of them are just like they
just want it to be in a video they just
wanted to be on the channel Neil
deGrasse Tyson was doing he was shooting
some of his TV show called star talk
radio show
Macie million a radio show and there's
like we got to get you in and they just
saw in your work
yeah and I think obviously the audience
has part to do with that but like the
tech connection and a lot of times they
they want to be in this tech world and
they don't know exactly how to but
obviously they've watched some videos or
something that gets them interested
that's been a way to do that you want
had no other reason he's just like yeah
I'll do it
wasn't he doesn't have any reason to do
a press tour but like down to do yeah so
so was it a combination of you reaching
out to some folks and then some of them
reaching out to you definitely yeah
probably about half and half a lot of
people have their team's reach out and
it's always like their team's trying to
reach out to my team but my team's just
me so it's just me answering their email
are you not represented by neh
I do manager yeah I do have an agency
and they have worked it on like a couple
smaller like sponsored projects but
every single one of the interviews has
been through me so yeah it's just them
emailing me like who do we get in touch
with I'm like me oh wow you have a
personal touch on there I guess then
that exactly yeah and I can talk
creative with them pretty much right off
the bat usually they're like what can we
can we do a video and I'm like well
here's the talking tech series you've
probably seen this and we can talk about
whatever tech stuff that they're into so
yeah have you have you had good good
experiences with with having agents and
managers in the past being an online you
know concentrator yeah my experience is
pretty limited I've only had one agency
that I've worked with and so technically
one agent / manager but other than that
it's pretty I don't even do that much
like sponsored stuff or any crazy
extracurricular like outside of the
video stuff so I haven't really had too
notable of an experience does that mean
that the gear that you receive to review
are they are they just sending it to
your is it are you buying them a little
bit of both mostly really that's
probably so it depends on what kind of
gear the the stuff I'm reviewing like
the smartphones the the headphones the
gadgets that's probably like 80% sent to
me 20% and bought but it's gonna end up
in the video no matter what if they
don't send it I'll buy it but all the
other stuff people think I also get for
free like the cameras we use and the
studio lighting and the equipment and
the space like that's obviously all we
pay for it but yeah the the smartphones
are the main thing that sort of has it
down to a science now where they like
have a release date they'll send it out
to a bunch of press and some youtubers
five days before the release date and we
all get to use it and review it and then
by the time the release stage shows up
then our videos are all ready to go so I
see yeah that must be in a great feeling
to get something before like the rest of
the world does yeah like do you still
find enjoyment in that because like it
seems like you get every single phone
that ever exists or has ever created
yeah and your
you know it's like do you feel that like
Christmas feeling like I get to open a
new new thing it's still kind of a dream
job yeah I feels like when I go back to
the studio tomorrow there's gonna be a
bunch of boxes waiting for me and I'm
just pumped to open them like it's
Christmas every time sometimes it's
because I don't have a public like a p.o
box or anything for like anyone to send
stuff to so every time a package arrives
I like kind of know what it is but
sometimes it's like oh this agency has
my address they've sent me stuff in the
past this is from them but I don't know
what it is it's probably related to
something else like I can sort of piece
it together but it's usually pretty
sweet to just open gadgets time yeah
what do you do with all the other ones
you don't you other bad ones
I can either sell them give them away
give them back it would depend on what
it is I also some people out of old
giant storage somewhere it's not
actually that bad because a lot of
gadgets are pretty small and I'll either
throw away the box and then like give
away or ship back the item but I keep
like about two generations old of
smartphones from like every single maker
so I just have like a it's like a drawer
literally full of I have a CD rack and I
don't have CDs the only way yeah it's
like having shoes but it's phones I mean
how many phones do you have I can
imagine you have a ton Hey the drawer is
getting so heavy that I'm kind of
worried that if I open it all the way
it'll just snap off I think there's
about a hundred something phones in
there but I don't know how many phones
do you use though currently two two I
always have my main Android phone and my
iPhone and my main phone is my main SIM
card I have two SIM cards two which is
kind of annoying but my main number and
then like my iPhone number and that's
what I carry yeah so do you say your
androids your main because if I put my
sim card in the iPhone notoriously
iMessage will just start to like take
over that SIM cards messages okay and
ecosystem lock in is also very real and
I've been part of my job is to be to
have a foot in like both ecosystems and
constantly be using both so I yeah I'll
have like my main phone will be sort of
rotating between phones I'm testing
which right now I have the pixel four
before that it was the one plus seven
Pro I was just testing a Xiaomi me note
10 and there's just a long line of
phones before that but my other phone is
has been the iPhone 11 Pro for a couple
months so you're you're are you so would
you if you have to choose between oh boy
yeah at the moment let's just say at the
moment the current time right now yeah
which one would you choose if he had to
choose if you had to only use one phone
if I had only use one phone that I would
use the 1 plus 7 Pro Wow and that's an
Android phone and not a lot of people
even have heard about but I love the
performance it has an awesome high
refresh rate screen the camera is not
that great but a lot of the reasons
people use the iPhone are great about
that phone too
so I could do without like the iPhone or
the pixel if I just had to use one but
luckily I don't have to use one so I
don't did you at any point love Apple
more than Android in some worlds yes not
even in the video editing world I was a
premiere person for like 7 years or
something and I finally got convinced to
try Final Cut Pro and loved it so for my
computer I've been a Mac for like four
or five straight years and not even
close to switching back to a Windows
desktop I will probably be on a Mac as
long as I use Final Cut well I have to
be on a Mac as long as it's so
interesting so many people including us
we'd switched from Final Cut to premiere
right what do you like so much better
about Final Cut okay so a lot of people
switched cuz you were using Final Cut
like probably in like row eight or nine
I don't know and it went through this
like transition where it got like worse
like simpler and a lot of people dropped
it right around then that's when I was
on premiere
so I saw all that dropping and happening
and I was like I don't really care
whatever and then it was actually the
Kobe interview that I was doing with
another youtuber John TLD and he was
shooting the behind the scenes video so
we are literally like
next to each other both editing our
videos me the interview him the behind
the scenes we both finished editing
around the same time I hit export in
premiere he had export and final cut his
video finished upload exporting he
watched him back found a mistake went
back fixed it finished exporting again
before he uploaded it I was out like 19%
we went out to dinner came back it was
that like 70% it eventually finished the
fans are cranking I finally get to
upload the video but that was when I was
convinced I should at least try final
cut because this isn't hilarious you
can't edit on my laptop you're the same
laptops
yeah well the footage so when you edit
like regular ProRes for K it's actually
yeah it'll it'll handle it pretty well
but I've been editing this is a multicam
red project so this is three red raw
streams of 6k at the time that I was
trying to push through a laptop and it
was just not handling it well
I traveled here with an iMac Pro because
it's still really hard to edit red raw
on a laptop I could get away with it if
I was just shooting on like my Canon or
whatever but that's been my challenges
raw do you feel like it's difficult
because you are known for tech I mean
that's what you're known for if you feel
that pressure of always having to stay
at the top of your game quality wise and
I mean you do have to people look to you
right you're the guy so do you feel that
pressure like man I can't stoop down to
a lower quality and someone else or like
this is so much more work but I have to
use the red yeah I I don't look at his
pressure as much as I actually want to
push the game to the next level right I
would love if red made like a smaller
camera with like the same color science
and autofocus and I could take that
places because it would make my life
easier but when I watch back I've tried
this I've gone to events with like just
my rx100 or ESR or whatever and I edit
all the footage and I'm like I don't
like this as much this isn't as good
looking so something about my eye for it
is like the main reason why I want to
bring like the nice camera and deal with
the extra work yeah it's cuz you
genuinely just want to do something
better yeah okay so do you have like a
team that helps you because I know you
answer emails yourself but yeah what
does your team look like yes so I have
three people working with me Andrews my
full-time assistant and sort of like a
second pair of hands but he also
co-hosts the podcast and edits it and
then VIN and Brandon are the sort of
cinematography extra hands and they're
super talented in their own right but
they'll do things like their behind the
camera when I'm on camera they do set
design they do motion graphics sound
design all that stuff so when I do like
the main edit I can pass off clips to
them they can make that clip incredible
and we bring it back in and we'll do
like a robot shot is what we call it
bring that back in and we sort of mix it
all together and then I'll finish the
whole project she's still very hands-on
in your process then definitely yeah and
I sort of not struggled with that but
I've thought a lot about like what if I
just gave them the whole edit and we've
we tried that actually a couple times
and every time we do that it feels great
to not have to work as much because
they're editing but I feel like the the
personal touch is lobby's you have to go
back in and change it's gonna take a lot
of time anyway yeah little things and I
you know over time I'm sure we could
like hone that down for them to to
pretty much edit it exactly the way I
would but it definitely feels like I
should just keep doing the main edit and
if you're not I mean you say you still
get excited by it so it's not like yet a
chore right yeah no I I know that the
Edit is the most tedious part yeah but
it is the most personal like execution
and I think I think that's a similar
situation you and Greg have to go
through right yeah yeah we still do that
I've had to learn to I guess kind of I
was I was a lot worse I mean not Alan if
it's called worse I was very like not
perfectionist I just like things a
certain way and I was talking about
timing to point something of a second
you know like it makes a big difference
to me but I had to learn like okay I
know it bothers me but I know most
people it's not all people don't even
realize this and I've tested that theory
and it for the most part
I know exactly what you're talking about
I had to get okay with being like okay
this is realistically for them on time
that we have left to post this this is
enough yeah and it was it was it's a
tough thing to do and it hurts sometimes
yeah but I definitely know what you're
talking about have you gone back and
forth like you edit one and like you can
see how the audience reacts versus
someone else who edited a video and oh
for sure
yeah sure and it would just became a
thing of like the times that I really
care about something that's exciting and
new yeah then I won't like budge on it
yeah if it's something that I'm like not
that proud of that sounds bad I'm not
proud of stuff and then it's just like
well I this is enough you know what they
say to do like one for you one for them
that's like a general rule but like you
can sort of go back and forth where like
some things are just you know we already
kind of have a basic idea of what this
is gonna be and so we can easily pass
that off and then some of them are like
like more passion projects or whatever
gonna call it and then you end up I mean
I recently liked one that you did a
video you made that didn't I didn't know
you did that kind of video there wasn't
a review it was just you um I don't
remember what exactly do I think you
just exported the same video like over
and over I like this one I want to do
more of that I think you should do I
like that video how did that do for you
though it was fine actually updated well
I think it's because it ended up like a
fun video right I think the initial
performance of it was probably worse
because people are all used to like new
gadget new gadget tech new thing and
then what happens when you download and
read upload a video a thousand times or
like I don't know I guess I'll watch
that later but once people watched it
and start sharing it people like really
liked it I am I am the reason why I
thought that was great so you actually
did that then yeah I'm bloated yes so
Egypt I was like the download button
inside of it so we uploaded this 8k
beautiful like 40 second file downloaded
it and then uploaded that and they
downloaded that and uploaded that and we
did that a thousand times so what was
your internet bill like some people web
cap I'm like a fiber it was since it was
such a short file it wasn't so
it was more of like the tedious someone
every all the comments are like why
didn't you just write a script to do it
which we were like oh I didn't know I
could yeah it turns out there's a limit
of like a hundred uploads a day and so
once you get to that limit you have to
like wait 24 hours to start again so
that's at least 10 days of 100 uploads
but then some of them it was Andrew and
VIN and I all trying to do this but like
if you download a video and then upload
it and then download that too fast it
was like not done processing so you
didn't get the full quality and then if
you like didn't really check them for
like 50 and then you like look at it
you're like why is this 480p and you go
back 50 and you realize you messed up
you you lose those 50 towards the castle
is like a month project yeah exactly
worth it I thought that was one of the
best videos I've seen a long is good it
was just creative what do you use for
your camera to shoot with or do you
change it once in a while or yeah our
our main camera is a monster Oh 8k this
division direct their names are pretty
weird now but it's a red camera and it's
a huge nearly full-frame sensor which is
wild for video and then the image
processing pipeline just spits out a que
red raw with like 16 stops of dynamic
range or something crazy I could no
doubt about it forever but it's a that's
the primary camera
well no autofocus huge file size is kind
of terrible to use but the image is so
nice that I'm willing to work with it
and and sort of that I have that
pipeline pretty much down I mean for a
YouTube video like you may be using
probably the best camera out of any
youtuber right that's not shooting film
right yeah it's kind of funny it's like
I know another guy John who uses an Ari
Alexa mini one my friend Judd nur who's
also from New Jersey also uses a red
camera and it's something about the tech
crowd and maybe this is just because
we've been leading the way and a lot of
people are sort of copying it but for
whatever reason we just really like
crispy video and the better you can make
it out it's kind of funny you've noticed
like if you watch a bunch of other tech
videos even from like CNET or The Wall
Street Journal yep
suddenly all their videos
really cinematic in the past couple
years and that's because that's just the
look that's over kind of set this bar I
mean that's kind of like what you're
known for it to a certain degree right
like yes so I never really thought about
taking credit for it cuz there's sort of
a group of us that are all sort of
pushing the envelope and doing different
things but like if I see a robot shot
from one of them yeah I start right yeah
yeah uh you said there's a small group
if you guys that do that yeah do you
guys have like a group chat where you
discuss all do you try to this this like
exchanging tricks and trades yeah we not
a group chat but we all sort of it's
kind of funny at tech events because
like tech companies invite all the same
people to all their events we sort of
all collaborate and we'll chat at these
things so like CES every year we're all
there but like when Samsung comes out
with a new phone they invite all of us
so we're all there anyway so we all
talked there and then we're all at the
Apple event we all talk there and a
Motorola and like it just sort of
happens a lot during the year um but
yeah that's when we'll end up like just
talking about the techie Tube world or
do you feel like sometimes because
you're always hanging out together when
you guys talk about things sometimes
their opinions influence you so almost
like it bleeds into your commentary
probably yeah and I think even just
watching other videos like I know my my
edit style has changed watching other
people's videos like what you say about
like a point ii like 0.1 second
difference like if you watch a philip
defranco video you would know if the
Edit style changed because like the
cadence would be off right and i don't
know how many people would notice if my
edit was a quarter of a second off but
like that's the sort of thing i'll like
sort of hone based on like watching my
own in other people's videos and i think
that happens in a lot of things and in
tech and other genres too yeah well
we're about at that halfway mark okay
cool i guess we'll do a quick
shishi break and this is something we
just started doing since yesterday but
do you have any things for our halftime
show that you want to perform any skills
anything you can do
can you sing I will drink more of this
water and do a bottle flip do it right
now but it's gonna take a while okay
[Music]
you actually have to do it yeah I don't
even have any crazy yeah
well then we'll be right back and we're
back sweet awesome so I wanted to ask
you something about this cuz you know
you're definitely a tech channel have
you seen how like the youtubes Peace
Corps recently got leaked kind of I did
see that I don't think I saw myself in
that but I saw the articles but yeah and
I was like definitely pushing tech and
gaming and stuff like that yeah is it
explicitly pushing tech uh it talked
about that because that's like a great
consumer it's really that you can buy a
lot of right ad companies will probably
purchase into that area as well yeah uh
and so I was just curious how if you
felt like oh like this is good for us or
I feel like I've always sort of known
that what we're in one of these genres
that's like pretty clean for YouTube
like I know a lot of people like the ad
pocalypse happens like a lot of certain
genres of channels were like really
struggling to deal with it and if you
watch any of my videos or any tech
videos basically they're all pretty much
like clean the the normal demographic is
awesome for YouTube because it's like
people who are unreachable anywhere else
it's like 18 to 34 year old affluent
spending you know consumers that are
like ready they like like put our ad
dollars right there like it's perfect so
like I've always kind of known that's
it's a good safe place on YouTube and
it's kind of a happy coincidence that I
happen to love tech but yeah it's been
pretty smooth sailing as far as dealing
with YouTube so how do you um do you
guys have to like look at algorithms
constantly that's your thing are you
kind of just like oh no we're clean so
we know we're gonna be good yeah there's
still ways to play with algorithm
especially in the whole quantity over
quality game I think about that a lot
and we make about a hundred videos a
year which is like one every three days
like twice a week something like that
and I know for a fact because other
channels do this if I uploaded daily the
channel would do massively better on
paper it would get three times as many
views every month they
would get recommended in the algorithm
there would be a bigger category a
bigger library of things to recommend
but as far as sanity I don't think I can
like do that to myself so yeah we think
about the algorithm a little bit but
generally a title thumbnail in the
description make a great video yeah yeah
and uh just went with terminology I
forgot for audiences who don't know he's
like YouTube's P scores basically like
their preferential score what type of
videos they'll suggest you and your
recommended in your sidebar stuff like
that and as of a couple of days ago I
don't have you seen YouTube's new UI in
terms of uploading stuff like that not
uploading I saw the new homepage mm
which is like much bigger thumbnails
which I don't hate because I've our
thumbnails are like kind of like made to
be really tiny like it when I do a
thumbnail of like a phone like there's
only so many angles you can show a phone
where if you shrink it down to that
postage stamp-sized you can even tell
what it is so I kind of like the bigger
thumbnails but the new upload interface
I haven't seen so what do you do when
you're not making youtube videos I think
a lot of people are pretty interested in
knowing what your life is like outside
of that to have like a girlfriend you
just hang out with your friends like or
is it just work work work and frisbee
frisbee yeah well I was gonna say is
like usually if I'm not at work it's
some ultimate related thing like
weekends for the most part on the East
Coast when it's warm from like March
when is getting warm to like September
which is Nationals is Ultimate Frisbee
which is it's a lot because you have
practice during the week and then you
have games and tournaments on weekends
but that's mostly what I'm doing when
I'm not at work and that's like mainly
the reason I'm I wouldn't I would go
insane if I didn't have some sort of
especially cuz like when you're a
youtuber people know nothing about this
but you're like sitting down all day and
like I can't really sit down for more
than about three or four hours like I
hate cross-country flights because I
really just don't want to be sitting for
that long so something about like I can
get through sitting and editing for five
straight hours because I know you have
practice tonight like
we'll be the opposite Wars exactly like
chomping at the bit trying to get out of
that so I think that's like the the
balance of when I don't have to work
that's that's where I'm at what is a so
you said it's like games and tournaments
is it mostly tournament based your
season or how does because I've no no
idea yeah yeah yeah it's kind of complex
and anytime I try to explain it I try to
simplify it basically Club ultimate
which is like if you think of like club
soccer like area teams are that's like
the main version of ultimate college
kids will join an area team people who
are graduating things like that I play
for the New Jersey area team now I play
for the New York area team and those are
all it's a better team yeah we came in
30 Nationals Dan OH Congrats thank you
that just happened to you said September
yeah that was was it a month ago maybe
he's a month ago no I don't how many
teams because Nationals I think there
were 16 teams well and is it also kind
of like other sports we have to travel
to another city to play yes yeah so so
yeah tournaments will be in various
cities around the u.s. so we had a
tournament in Colorado this year
Nationals is in San Diego there's other
tournaments on both coasts generally but
anywhere you get like a huge field space
that's like generally like Minnesota and
is really popular with fields and and
certain states have much more fields
than others but it's tournament
basically you play like four games in a
day and hopefully you win but that's
your like your stress relief and
something you love doing yeah definitely
would you say that I guess let's say the
Ultimate Frisbee became the thing like
it became like the next big thing right
well would you leave the tech industry
and would you do that professionally if
it paid off
paid away more than you know let's say
you got a 20 million dollar contract to
be a frisbee player but you got to focus
on playing frisbee can't make tech
videos anymore
you could do it LeBron vlogging yeah
your new hate comments be like dog get
back to the field
get that disk going dang uh Wow I I
assume it's your stress relief right yes
they don't want compact this they want
frisbee this exactly uh I never thought
about that
I guess yeah I guess I would you would
enjoy it more
I would enjoy it but I think yeah my
offseason yeah like you know some sort
of creative outlet cuz I think I would
also go crazy right now if I never had
any creative outlet so I think they sort
of you know each other they keep each
other like in check or from overwhelming
the other do you find that your fan base
cuz allow your stuff is educational so
like if someone's interest in something
I would assume they type in something
and they find you and they what they
learn and they'd like you or they don't
and they trust you or whatever do you
find that your fans would care care more
about you or care more about your
content I think the content but I think
it helps to have a palatable personality
yeah I think there's a bunch of really
good examples of channels that are
successful because of their personality
and like the audience is there for them
right and oh they're so relatable
they're so funny they're so whatever and
I think I sort of mentioned earlier but
like the best the easiest part of my job
is like I don't have to be the most
entertaining person personally I'm like
covering the tech and that's what people
care about and hopefully my coverage of
the tech is also entertaining and that's
where we push the limits of like well
that's why you have fans because they
like you doing it right just some random
person ever eat every week or every
three days doing it right yeah yeah
there's a million places to get do you
think I mean I don't know if you have or
not but don't you think what if you did
something about you playing professional
frisbee you think they would care about
you or do you think they would not like
that because like what is this yeah I
think I have wanted to do that and I'm I
struggle to find the time to really give
it the time it deserves I think any time
we're playing I'm so that's the problem
I'm so hyper focused on playing that I
would be like annoyed that I couldn't
give my attention to how it was being
recorded filmed I'd have to honestly
like take a season where I'm injured or
something so I'm up I don't like to not
I'm not like worked like mad that I'm
not playing because I couldn't play so I
could focus on recording
but like usually the entire season I'm
like focused on like peaking physically
at the right time of year and like
eating right and like oh like everything
I'm doing on the field is like for very
purpose built so like it's really hard
to make something about that yeah yeah
using other people's footage so yeah
with yeah I know what you mean yeah I
would I would like to do that though and
you'd have to like get people to sign
like release forms exactly
but on the off season though what do you
do that's sure right now is the off
season it's a lot of just like working
out boring staring at a wall biking like
it's it's not as exciting we do have
like some winter leagues that you can
play in in New Jersey which is a lot of
like weekday night stuff randomly but I
do enjoy like having random time I I
took a day the other day and I just
played 2k for like I think the entire
day because it sunsets at like 4 o'clock
and I think from like from like 10 a.m.
to like 4 o'clock I just played 2k 2
whole day cuz I hadn't gotten 2k 20 yet
so I had to like get in get in the
storyline yeah yeah I usually get 2k
every year like right when it comes out
same and this year I slacked a little
bit and I didn't get to it until after
nationals
mm-hm and so I just got into it I got a
question I mean a shift modes a little
bit get a little more deep sure go ahead
what like so you know you're obviously
very very successful you've interviewed
some of the leaders of the world right
in technology and science and you've
been you know Oliver on every
publication and whatnot and you're
you're doing this thing that you really
enjoy right what what is what's driving
that like what is it like you do have
like a purpose or like a reason for
doing this I know it's very deep but but
I'm curious because you know that it's
obvious that a lot of people are super
drawn to your personality right even
though it may be something that's you're
just reviewing products right something
technical technology but but you know
seems like you had a really good
upbringing and you seem like a very you
know likeable
and I'm just wondering like what is
driving you to like what's your end goal
like what are you trying to accomplish
just I know it's not just you know
you're not just trying to review
products like there's yeah there must be
something there I think the the way it
all started was I wanted to make videos
that I would want to watch so it sort of
it was like created from I wanted to
create something that I wanted to exist
in the world and I sort of started to
pivot it but stopped because it was way
too much into creating like a website
where you could just like look up a
product and just like see if you should
buy it or not and I whether that was a
video or like some collection of videos
or some information or comparison or
whatever it was you could just find it
decide if you wanted to buy or not and I
think like the videos that I make are
like kind of the next best thing it's
like I think of a product I wonder if
it's any good I'm just curious about it
generally or some topic I wonder what
happens when I upload a thousand times
and download it upload it again and I'll
just go search it up find it and boom up
here's the best possible comprehensive
video about what I wanted to see that's
just kind of basically what it's based
around you know it's I guess it's
nothing too deep as far as like what is
my purpose what I what I want to do with
his time I feel like it's it's mainly
just creating what I want to exist and
making it better as we go it seems like
you're on a quest the way I see it at
least from this explanation just love it
I see it as a quest to create the best
library of reviews for any particular
phone or you know gadgets yeah yeah yeah
it kind of has end up ended up being
that and I think the like branching out
into other types of videos is the more
fun part that I want to do more and so
maybe it's less of a catalog of products
and more of a catalog of entertainment
but tech happens to be the common thread
that goes through it we're doing a retro
tech series that starts premiering in
December or it's like obviously no one's
buying these products anymore they're
all gonna be you know 20 30 40 year-old
iconic pieces of tech but it's like the
Aryans of diving back into what made
them iconic it's just sort of
entertainment instead of like product
based stuff yeah so yeah it's just a
lesson in history yeah yeah exactly and
still tech related some people aren't
good don't give you the past it's not
your usual stuff but it's still related
yeah common thread right yeah so we do
have some questions from fans here oh
boy
many many questions yeah I got a
question first okay for that I love it
because like you said I like what you
said palatable personality sure what is
the weirdest band interaction you've had
though we're just fan interaction
because I'm sure you're so likable that
they just come up and they're like I
know you
I'm just right into it you're right that
like when people come up to me they they
it's a it's a power a social
relationship everyone knows everything
already about you and you don't really
know them so it's kind of one-sided at
first but on one hand that actually does
produce a lot of like fun like
interactions I on my way here as I was
getting into the uber lady walking by
didn't even like do anything she just
walked by and went I really liked your
YouTube videos and then just kept
walking I was nice but yeah weird
weirdest fan interactions I'm trying to
think of like because I'm sure you have
to be at a lot of conventions stuff like
yeah well here's the thing about a tech
audience is a lot of nerds like me don't
go out too much or whatever so when we
get to like a tech convention imagine
filling a hall with all these people who
like are used to being like just on the
computer and now they're just sort of
checking out tech so it's sort of a like
everyone that comes up to me will have
like a different way of trying to
explain that they know who I am but it's
usually pretty awkward it'll be either
like oh my daughter knows who you are
YouTube right or they'll like say 410
they don't know I like I like the
everyone says in the acronym wrong I was
walking through the airport and someone
said mkb D or something like they just
said the
letters and I was like yeah that's me
not really but yeah everyone's got a
different way I noticed stuff like just
saying nothing too crazy nothing yeah
nothing like no crazy I don't want to
like jinx it but nothing like stalkerish
or anything wild because your audience
is a little more mature yeah they're all
at home alright so we have a question
here from three number three do you ever
want to produce or create your own tech
yeah that's a big challenge like a big
undertaking I've thought about and this
is come up before like why don't you
make yeah so much to say about phones
why don't you make your own phone it's
like well okay you need you need like a
manufacturing process you need to
basically partner with an entire
smartphone company
the thing about partnering with a
smartphone company when you have to
objectively review smart phones is that
compromises your relationship with at
least that company's products forever if
not the rest of those products so it
seems like that might be like an end
game like when I'm 50 I'd be like
alright I'm done making videos I'm gonna
make the perfect phone and I'm out of
here or when your professional ultimate
Blair yeah I'm your sponsor yeah by your
own bone exactly and then the logos on
the Jersey is perfect yeah
what this is actually Mike my question I
you know everybody knows that you are a
fan of Tesla yeah you drive a Tesla what
do you think about the future of Tesla
and what their automobiles like where
they're headed right now like do you
think they're headed in the right
direction
yeah whenever I look at Tesla and I
compare it to I try to stay objective
like I'm obviously fan of Tesla but I
look around at other electric cars and
every time I look around Tesla is miles
ahead in so many ways as far as electric
cars and I think we're just now getting
to the point where there is legitimate
competition to a couple of their models
the Porsche ty can seems like one of
them but it's still more of a driver's
car versus the everyday like the model 3
when you're out here it's everywhere
basically so they're kind of on a great
path i I was talking to someone recently
about a potentially unique way for
to exist which is just for them to sell
parts like they have the gigafactory
and they have such great drivetrain
technology they could sell electric
drivetrains cell batteries and then kind
of like Google just sell one car like a
Model S and Model 3 but still the rest
of those parts to make everyone else's
electric cars better the way Google
license is Android mm-hmm so there's an
Android phone from Samsung from Motorola
from Huawei from Xiaomi they can all use
that to make their phone better so they
don't have to build their own OS because
right now Ford doesn't really make great
electric drivetrain Toyota doesn't I
mean I have a hybrid but they don't make
their own great electric drivetrain so
if they just partnered up with Tesla and
use the supercharger network they'd
already have a much better car so I was
thinking about it in that unique way
recently and I think that could be
pretty cool but as it right now I just
want the Roadster
it's supposed to be 2020 but also for
sure delete Oh all right next question
here from Joseph Liu
what does mobile tech look like in the
future oh man if I knew I think also I
struggle with being maybe a little bit
short-sighted because people make these
like crazy renders of like Oh it'll be a
hologram that comes up out of your I
don't know maybe I just think like we'll
always have like ice and smartphones as
just like this object that you like pick
up use and put away and so on when we
get these like wearables and like I just
broke out Google glass again for like
the first time in years and I'm like
trying to understand like maybe VR is
the future maybe AR
but I don't quite see it yeah and I just
I go back to like well if we can make
phones better that'll be the future yeah
so uh maybe I'm sure it's sighted but I
feel like I just look at smart phones
the smaller phones aren't going away not
anytime soon
mm-hmm yeah I have a question actually
so yeah rewind we talked a little brief
about it but I touched on that yeah and
I feel like you kind of got thrown into
it yeah hard because you were like that
first big line sure yeah did you do you
feel the brunt of the hate yeah you
almost like a face of it that's why yeah
I don't know if you know it was funny
what on the face but he was one of the
biggest yeah yeah yeah it it I I don't
think I got that much hate for it
I think the memes in the comments were
relentless for like three months
mmm-hmm but as far as my involvement in
it like I kind of told my story and I
made a video about it but like we all
thought rewind was gonna be this
different thing this year I don't know
if you got like that email that was like
this is the first year everyone's gonna
feature creator voices and we've
narrowed it down to 50 creators instead
of 350 and I was like oh this is gonna
be different and then we did this shoot
and in the shoot the producers are all
telling us the same stuff like it's
gonna be great we did multiple takes of
different lines everyone gets a close-up
shot we're like wow this is different
and then you watch the video like this
is not different this is the same thing
so yeah it was like I don't feel like I
got thrown into it as much as I just I
along with everyone else involved didn't
have any control over the final product
and it just kind of happened mm-hm
hopefully this year is better if they
even do a rewind this is sure they will
think you're doing something yeah so
there's another question here I'm from
hot sure whoring your reviews are now
quoted by the biggest companies in the
world has that kind of pressure changed
how you approach reviews in any way and
it's it's I mean I would think that you
know when you're making these reviews
some of the biggest publications may
also quote you right I mean do you feel
that pressure or is it just just don't
think about that at all uh at most I
think maybe it might like make might
tempt me to use more quotable language
hmm but as far as like how I actually
talk about the product I don't think it
changes anything at all I think even
since like the the beginning day is
eight nine years ago I got a tell like
it is like if a products bad I'm gonna
tell you exactly why it's bad but the
good thing about that is a company who
makes that product when you put out a
review and say something's bad like
let's say the battery life for the
camera or whatever it's bad the fact
that I'm telling the truth about it
helps them to either improve it they can
do a software update or to make a better
one the next time and if no one told
them it was bad they kind of wouldn't
know like they put out a product the
best they can and hope for the best and
turns out the battery's bad no one wants
it good to know make the next one bigger
battery but if they don't get this
useful valuable feedback about why
something's bad it won't help the
consumer a good example of that was I'll
go back to when I was in college I
reviewed a Motorola phone and I'd worked
with him a bunch and the phone came out
and I reviewed it and I went to the the
specs and I was talking about the camera
about how like this is the worst part of
the phone if they only made the camera
better this would be a great phone and I
showed all these example photos and I
reached out and I sent them a bunch of
sample images I was pointing at circling
stuff in the videos like here's where
the coherent Hertz here's where dynamic
range would've been better and there was
software update like within weeks
specifically addressing what I had asked
about and sure enough like months later
people are talking about what this this
phones cameras gotten better that's
pretty good for them so that and I'm
sure the next phone had a better camera
too so thanks to you I think we all win
yeah when reviewers do their job what so
this is my personal question um what
what was the most exciting review that
you ever made what was the worst review
that you felt pain to have to make this
review okay and then yeah I guess those
two okay exciting review I don't know if
it even counts as a review but I got to
make it I've started this autofocus
video series pretty recently where we
talk about car tech which lets me review
cars we're like five six episodes in but
I've already I was given a McLaren 720's
for a week and easy we we shot it in
like December and it was impossibly cold
like every time we had to lean out a car
window to get a shot it was like the
camera would start to like freeze up and
we'd have to take it back in like it was
really hard to shoot but that was the
most exciting product I think I've ever
had damn you're upgrading man yeah
they're like hey here's our car our new
car the road out well that's every boxes
it's already a thing there is already
there's automotive journalists who kind
of do this already they regularly
receive cars to review and I know they
have like press cars that like go around
the country when I did the Tesla video
that was a press car they don't do it
very often but McLaren Toyota whoever
they have a fleet of cars that they will
give to press for a couple days and get
take back so it's already a market that
you can get into if you want I just had
never done car videos and I don't know a
lot about cars but as soon as I got my
car I was like oh I love cars so I got
started to get into that but yeah that's
that was pretty exciting most painful
yeah so the one that comes to mind was
last year I reviewed the red hydrogen
and I don't know if you heard about this
what red makes great cameras and they've
been in Hollywood they have the best
color science I love my red cameras so
red or last year about two years ago it
started hyping that they're gonna make a
smart phone oh that's gonna be a smart
phone okay it's gonna have like the best
camera in any phone right this is right
around the time when smartphone cameras
are getting really good Reds gonna get
in the game they're gonna change the
game all right I'm ready I'm ready for
the red smartphone they were taking a
while to make it there was all this hype
building up and you could kind of tell
that this was red not knowing how to
make a phone really like every time I'd
ask them for an update about it they'd
be like oh we're we're doing carrier
certifications so we're it's we're it's
too late a little bit but it's gonna be
great don't worry I was like I'm ready
any time I'm ready and I made a video
actually or they they gave me a world
exclusive first look at like one of
their first prototypes so people got
what what the design would look like and
so I'm everyone's ready for the phone
super excited for it it finally comes
out and when it comes out first of all
the parts are so old because they've
been working on it for two straight
years it had like a two year old CPU the
camera was an off-the-shelf Sony sensor
with really not great photo quality
didn't do high quality video which it's
made by read/write of all headings that
should be good exact
it had a really big battery but like
that it was a thick phone like it it had
one of the worst screens of any phone
where they were claiming it could do
like 3d really well but if you turn the
3d mode off the actual display was like
not nice so all these things flopped
fill hard on their faces and so my
review of the phone was like I wanted
this to be good so bad but it was a one
Maya my I do smartphone worth at the end
of every year it won my worst phone of
the Year award I get a little there they
did not ask for their trophy some of the
other companies asked for them they did
not want this yeah I mean I guess that
shows I go with show you you're honest
you know like I mean you love the brand
but you had to be honest so exactly and
I've been I went on and bought one of
their cameras last week so okay that's
just the love-hate relation we didn't
ask good yeah awesome man anything you
want plug right now uh check out my
youtube channel youtube channel
youtube.com slash mkbhd that's pretty
much it yeah new series coming out check
out his video where he uploads and
downloads that video 200 times short
short quick video yeah I just thought it
was funny small project yeah I think I
definitely you should do more of those I
will I will definitely that was I wasn't
expecting that
yeah anyway you can find us at off the
pill on twitter at off the pill podcast
on instagram and i guess with that being
said how we end this is we just breathe
into the mic I'm ready to one
we'll have to come to one of your
frisbee games