hey guys so before we get to the actual
video I have a huge announcement
I said huge announcement thank you I
just wanted that you guys know that I am
a genius now in the literal Li eyes
because I wrote a book well okay I start
working out again and I know this is
very sudden news for a lot of you
especially if you don't follow me on
Twitter at the real Ryan Higa or my
Instagram at not Ryan Higa
or on my facebook at facebook.com/ so
that but the reason for that is that I
don't like to promote myself or my own
products because I think that's very
selfish and conceited and I think
facebook.com slash Shiva TV that's what
it was
make sure you guys like my page share
all my videos and make sure you guys go
check it out right now yeah I wrote a
book it is called how to write good and
this is the cover this is not the actual
book I just print out the cover and put
it on a different book this is
radiographic pathology for technologists
fifth edition and obviously my book is
gonna be better because my book has
picture this has pictures of brains and
so I don't know why I'm why am i reading
but yeah I wrote the book taught how to
write good it's very I mean it came from
my mind so it's very different and I
mean I'm gonna be honest it's it's super
weird I don't think that most people who
casually read books are gonna like it
because it's so different but I say that
you have a big announcement I did that
in fact I say it was huge don't let the
fans know that this is a promo of course
not I'm not an idiot and very important
my book sound interesting to not call
book weird or anything else negative
towards this book how to write good is
so damn good it is sorry so damn well
can be making those kind of mistakes
anymore published author now
this is the best book ever it is not
weird it is not anything that I have to
say negative about it is exactly like
every other best-selling book out there
right now except for the fact that it
hasn't sold that much yet but other than
that it's the same thing there's a cover
with pictures in it there are words so
many words I have the best words huge
words I'm going off-topic the reason why
I bring this up other than the fact that
I am promote not promoting my book is
because writing a book is a very
important stage in a youtubers career it
means that I am in one of the final
stages of my youtube career and my
youtube life so yeah what are you guys
doing that means we can get out of here
right yeah it's really cramped back here
I have to poop so bad no I said one of
the final stages not the end just just
watch the video there are 10 major
stages in the life of a youtuber you
already know one of the final stages
called write a book but we'll get to
that later also keep in mind some of
these stages may be out of order for
some people but for the most part these
are stages that almost every youtuber
goes through at some point so let's
start with the first one stage one just
for fun not all but the majority of
youtubers first started creating their
YouTube channels because of an interest
that they had and they want to give it a
shot
not for fame not for money and they
basically started making videos just for
fun Stage two I'm smelling poo cuz cuz
you're famous now so you think you're
the you know you could have made a
better title than that ya feel like you
just said that because it rhymes you
know what guys can I just stage - I'm
smelling poop this is the stage where
you first start to discover your
popularity start getting recognized on
the streets you have fans you want pics
and autographs and for you you pretend
like you don't enjoy all this attention
because it happens all the time
deep down let's be real you love it cuz
you feel special stage 3 F everyone
hates Minh more successful you get the
more hate and negativity you will
receive and this is the stage where you
make your first video about haters and
why you can't understand why they're so
hateful because it bothers you a lot
knowing that even though you're so loved
there's a lot of people out there that
hate you Stage four haters don't bother
me no more Stage four is when you get
even more popular the
of your YouTube career and with all that
Fame you get more and more haters but
now that you've seen it so much you've
learned that hating on haters doesn't
work this is the part where you put on a
cool guy act and pretend that hater
comments don't affect you anymore but in
reality it still does stage 5 run is
died there's always that moment after
your peak of your YouTube career where
things start to slow down a little bit
and that's when you begin to freak out
and start questioning yourself you start
doubting your own content and eventually
you start to change your content in
order to try and bring your growth back
to what it used to be it's pretty much
desperation time this is where you start
using the old strategy such as clickbait
thumbnails and titles collabing with
other random youtubers so you can
increase your subs and this is also
where you start doing more of the
popular trendy challenges just anything
it takes to get you more viewers and
after a while of doing this you get to a
point where your content is not even
what you started out making you're just
making stuff to get views stage 6
Kumbaya positivity is you're depressed
now because your YouTube fame has been
dying down for a while now however this
is a stage that you magically turn that
all around by watching one inspirational
motivational speaker on Facebook talk
about happiness and then you take that
speaker's advice to heart and
over-exaggerated not just to yourself
but to all of your fans as well stage
setting the big dis saggin hope you're a
few months of being overly positive you
realize that you are putting up a front
and you weren't really as happy as you
were pretending to be or preaching
others to be now you must decide you
keep making youtube videos or do you
quit and go and pursue something else
like acting or making a movie and
regardless of what you decide you still
make a video telling all your fans that
you want to quit YouTube stage eh just
kidding Mike you told everyone you were
done with you too but you're back it was
a joke what a surprise after such a long
break from YouTube you feel hyped and
refreshed and ready to start taking
YouTube serious again you also found
that passion again um what first got you
start however this doesn't last very
long because of your long break from
YouTube your growth and your view
perhaps it's time to take drastic
measures maybe you should rebrand
yourself maybe start drama with another
youtuber maybe it's not about what kind
of videos you wanna make but what kind
of videos will get you more views stage
9 write a book yeah I started the whole
priming the title thing after the intro
so you know stage 9 write a book time
stage 9 write a book time is to write a
book like I mentioned earlier one of the
last stages in a youtubers life is to
write a book this is the point where you
believe that you've gone through so much
that you feel the need to write a book
first you finish writing the book then
you don't promote it at all which makes
the book publishing company very upset
with you and tells you that you need to
promote it or else which you then say I
don't care you don't scare me I'm not
gonna sell out and make a promotional
video just to sell books what kind of
person do you think I am someone would
just randomly promote my book how to
write good and say that oh it's
available for pre-order in Amazon right
now links are in the description next to
my tour dates that I am going to be
going on in the next month in the
following cities absolutely not
is what I you is what you say then stage
10 the end this is the stage after you
write your book the final stage you're
finally in a great place where you're
happy and satisfied and content with
what you've done with your YouTube
career and you finally think it's time
to make that last video it's a heartfelt
video where TZ music begins to play
where you start thanking everybody for
everything that they've done for you for
this incredible ten eleven year journey
whatever it is for you that you've been
on and you just try to show how much you
truly truly appreciate them and even
though you're known to be comedic and
you shouldn't be know taken seriously
this is the one time that you are
genuine with your viewers and you really
really just can't thank them enough for
everything that they've done
and you know it gets a little cheesy but
none of that really matters because it's
all about appreciation you have for the
fans and well it it's time it's the end
the end of stage 10 on to safety 11 what
stage 11 the same issue I had rhyming
which seven stage 11 set heaven heaven
no the stage is not even called 11 this
is stage 1 1 because in stage 1 1 you
repeat back to stage 1 but you have to
ice the fun because you finally
understand how to truly live like a
youtuber and enjoy because as we know
that was the whole goal to begin with to
have fun
it's one big completed circle do what
you want to make me what you want to
make who cares if it's a boring video
with no skits and it cares that there's
really poor drawings in there even if
you're not an animator and they look
pretty bad no I'm in there it doesn't
matter because you're having fun
twice the fun stage 1 1 so it's
completed then what stage 1 it's done so
it's over right we can finally leave
what
no it just repeats you just have to add
a 1 in front of it now from stage 1 1
twice the fun we go to stage 1 2 I'm
smiling oh I warned you