hey guys so I know it is that time of
the year again where everybody who's
kind of similar to me is once again left
out because we are single valentines day
if you didn't catch that and I actually
wasn't planning to do a Valentine's Day
video this year because it's always the
same thing every year I'll be your
Valentine ROI it's awesome but I don't
really know you but you're not even
really sick yes I am how are you still
single because I spend all my time
talking to myself I what's wrong with
that nothing at all okay good does that
love you love you too Ruth it kiss me
okay yeah anyway I was thinking about
what do I usually do on Valentine's Day
and what am I gonna do this Valentine's
Day and then it just digging like a
light bulb that turns on from a snap
apparently my Valentine's Day is my
video game that's been my relationship
the past few years every Valentine's Day
I end up playing video games because all
my other friends are busy so rather than
trying to pretend that I'm in something
that I'm not which is a real
relationship I decided to write some
poems for all the people that are like
gaming love form there's one of those
moments where I got really excited and
just started writing without thinking
this makes absolutely no sense
especially if you don't play any games
you might not get any references in this
video and if I don't mention your
favorite game maybe I'll do it another
time but these are the games that I play
or the games that I know so for all you
gamers out there's poems are for you and
they're also for people to give to
gamers I guess if that being said here's
a friggin ridiculously weird video so
I've been playing a lot of destiny it's
a new game for those of you that don't
know this forum right here is about
putting yourself out there and asking
someone else showing them how wonderful
life could be if they joined you
were you party with me I'm destiny I
could take you to places you never did
see from the moon to crota
to the vault of glass so high even
fallen cabal and vex you'll never need
worry about getting hurt I'll be there
by your side everyday on lexer from the
weekly tonight fall every bounty you see
will do it all
faster than a Thrall could rush your TV
so will you party with me and destiny
will you point and dance in my fireteam
I'll take you in as a new it is destined
for you to let me help you reach light
level 32 thank you dude that's pretty
good service when is dota 2 and I know a
lot of you guys play League of Legends
or on but I play dota 2 i played Frozen
Throne Warcraft so that's what I stuck
with this form right here is quite the
opposite of the destiny pool it's all
about equality this is a problem for
people who wants to take charge it's
saying that you don't always have to be
the Alpha you don't always have to bring
home the bacon you don't have to be the
carry because you're the support and
anyone that plays dota or league of
legends or Han or any of those games you
know exactly how important the support
is carry me o carry me I can be your
support I don't need any kills I'll
assist you in your be a draw be advised
I'll go cm or lit you solomid sniper
award that River ditch or no one will
gank you if any are missing at all over
miles apart I will never not call and
when you want to push you can always
count on me couriers on its way with the
smoke in some trees dive that's how hard
and finish that rax as your loyal
support I've got all of your backs and
then oh no no no no what
what the hell is
she's probably one of my favorite games
csgo
why not the gold part but counter-strike
counter-strike 1.6 whatever based on
Shakespeare's Romeo and Juliet there's
no skull here but you get the picture in
fact here that that's a light bulb this
is a story for all you romantic sout
there csgo may see us go yay for our
love is divided by T conceit a like
Romeo and Juliet our families will fight
they know not of all love they know not
of our lives we must meet in secret so
I'll write to you in riddle behind box
where cats walk weird or smoke in the
middle and when you arrive take my hand
we'll survive in the darkness of tunnels
like our love we will hide all the
memories will share Lowell tunnels by
stairs but in trouble draws near when
both families head here and as they
approach faster than p90s fire we know
all that is left last kiss we desire
and as they close in
there's one last decision CS go with the
blade name see us gold grenade yay
sometimes less is more and the proof is
in Minecraft this poem gets straight to
the point
I built block of you show all my love I
built block of you ground and above
graphics simple but meaning strong I
built block of you love lot I'm long
this form is for all those people out
there who absolutely love someone who
does not love them back and this is how
you can win them over with this story of
Slenderman that was so creepy we're in
love you don't know it I watch you from
afar the darkness of the night as you
walk home through the park you turn on
your cell phone to give yourself light
when you spot me no love just fright
please stop running I just want your
love it's the kiss I have non but I can
still give a hug but you keep on going I
guess that ends our date until next time
my love I'll be waiting at your place
last but not least I'm not gonna forget
all the people who actually are in a
relationship
fighting is inevitable it's gonna happen
and this poem based off of Super Smash
Brothers is for all you couples who have
been together for a very long time I
know that we fight and we argue a lot
you see I game every night without
giving a thought about you and me but
that's simply not true when I play Super
Smash Bros all I think about is you cuz
it's just like your peach spoiled
princess and whiney or maybe your Zelda
yelling at link to come find me when I
play as King Bowser it's like I'm
playing as you and you're hungry you're
tired or in a bad mood and like Kirby
and Jigglypuff you eat and then sleep
but when you wake up your breath is like
Donkey Kong's feet you're Mega Man and
Samus at the end of the day
you build up your rage and take it all
out on me and it makes me feel like
Sonic because I want to run from it all
fly away like a Charizard or like
Captain Falcon and fall but then I
remember you're not just a character in
this game you're my player number two
and no matter who you are we're on the
same team so although you may whine like
you are my mother although you annoy me
like a little brother although you may
smother me like no other
you will always and forever be my Super
Smash lover oh hey oh my god what your
breath is Tommy Kong's feet it's not my
breath it's my moustache but moustache
so thank guys so much for watching if
you want to see the previous video click
the one on the right if you want to see
bloopers and behind the scenes click the
one on the left and if you want to learn
more about the Doppler effect just
listen to what I'm doing because this is
science see that your tribute crack