hey guys so after much request I finally
played Minecraft for the first time and
I know a lot of you out there that don't
like Minecraft probably gonna be like oh
minecraft is for little kids well it's
not it's for big kids too and yeah I'm
not ashamed to admit it I enjoyed
playing it sure there's no storyline or
objectives and maybe it isn't meant for
people in their 20s in fact it's so easy
a five-year-old to play it and maybe it
does have the absolute worst graphics
I've ever seen in a game that's still
around today but I where was I going
with this but seriously the graphics are
so bad though I mean again the gameplay
is great it's just it's 2015 and the
characters look like this I feel like
just looking at them I can tell what
their voices sound like pretty normal
what were you expecting some kind of
primitive caveman type of voice dudes
versus anyway I played it I liked it and
I'm not afraid to admit it I enjoyed
playing minesweeper is so fun what's up
man dude I'm in the next room I can hear
you oh sorry about that keep the
minesweeper falling down pardon me added
version doesn't even have sound right
minority report the movie does and
that's probably what you heard me
talking about in the room next don't
he's still in the cage because I was
going to watch it later after I finished
watching my minor league football
baseball team play in the playoffs which
is being held in my Neapolis - oh no see
where the mining Apple is 40 miners look
I don't care if you play Minecraft just
keep it down I'm sick I'm trying to
study not lying I would love to be there
with my fellow 40 miners but I have a
torn meniscus in my knee and I can't get
it fixed because I have no my knee see
whatever man just keep it down alright
yeah whatever
as I was saying for those of you that
don't get minecraft at all I think it's
stupid I was just like you until I
played it how I understand it's actually
pretty deep it really makes you think
about life I mean the graphics still
suck so the gameplay is amazing and it
has such deep meaning and by the end of
this video you'll see exactly why with
that being said here is my first
minecraft experience in real life in the
form of a movie movie trailer not a real
movie trailer but a YouTube video skit
trailer just take a look
I was spawned into this world with
nothing but the clothes on my back and
legs and feet I actually wanted to be
naked but the clothes wouldn't come off
so whatevs I discovered so many
mysteries so many things that were just
physically impossible but then again who
decides what impossible is in this world
not me I never really believed in the
gods mo yang blizzard eval none of them
the ancient tome or terms of agreement
manuscript had all the answers but it
was way too long so I skipped it and as
the Sun went down there was still so
many things I didn't understand about
this world all I knew for sure was that
this entire day this entire world was
just beautiful it was perfect
I I had no idea what was to come at
night as a neck stickers tickle stick
I will continue to survive with no
purpose will continue to exist not live
what is life no purpose why are we here
all respond in this world to do how did
I know that I was gonna be dude oh hey
what's up man it's just a game game what
game are you talking about you were just
playing minecraft minecraft I don't play
minecraft that's for little kids and the
graphics are so bad in that game I don't
even want I don't want to get into this
again good because I'm trying to watch
my 40 miners play it's the bottom of the
ninth bases loaded we're down three and
whatever just keep it down okay okay
sick and tired how did I know that I was
gonna be interrupted these are all
questions I'll never know
just maybe maybe that's okay
your graphics suck all over folks the 40
miners take home the minor league
championship what an ending here's coach
Magee with the postgame interview coach
you have got to be going crazy a grand
slam down the game how are you feeling
you know I can't believe it myself first
off I want to thank all the fans out
there I want to thank this team ain't no
most importantly our fellow 40 miner who
couldn't be here right now Ryan Higa I
hope you get well soon thanks a lot guys
this is for you right so thank you guys
again so much for watching you want to
see bloopers and behind-the-scenes click
them on the left if you want to see the
previous video click though on the right
or if you want to watch me actually play
minecraft for the first time click on
the bottom it's pretty it's pretty sad I
know a lot of you gonna make fun of me
but check it out anyway