you're gonna want to get this on camera
to check today
oh it's racist dude critics rave chronic
was the best superhero movie since the
notebook so we found this breathing in a
hole critics rave
chronicle is incredible okay what is
this it's a glowing green thing if we
touch it we'll get powers me how many
have powers I don't know actually that
that wasn't explained critics Rea
critics rape chronic was a non scary
version of paranormal activity but it's
still scarier watch this watch this
what what oh no it's not leading
Washington's
oh yeah you men will laugh Andrew Andrew
why'd you do that man that was wrong
with you God huh
was that an accident what was his
accident Andrew wasn't a drew you need
to stop what's wrong I'm worried about
that he's changed did you do that on
purpose
Andrew this is a game Andrew look at me
and
Andrew stop oops I rewound much Andrew
back row Andrew Andrew shop wait if I'm
here and and you're there and Andrews
here then what is the camera
hey drew