this summer one man to men's will cheat
death no oh damn bro you're welcome
because of one vision of one man this is
summer
final destination that was so raven dark
I can't take this anymore everyone keeps
dying give up dumb we're the only ones
left the ones happening time we cheated
death and now that he or she wants us
dead
you can't control your own destiny well
I can
stop Dom don't do it bro don't get down
right now I've seen this hangout - bro
bro everything's gonna be okay I'm seen
this in the vision you jump off this
building you're knocking as if you're
gonna dive everything's gonna be just
fine
Dom is gonna be just fine everything's
good
see Ryan I'm fine I told you man I'm
totally fine Oh destination coming never
again I hope hey stop Dom don't do it
bro don't get down right now okay yeah
right yeah