did you ever make anything happen
anything you couldn't explain you're a
wizard Harry uh uh Spade oh boy uh I'm a
what wizard but I can't be a wizard I'm
just Harry
well would you hurry hurry up on my
stick my broomstick that is ma can I see
you Scott wicked Shh hi I'm Hermione and
you're Harry Potter and I'm wrong
pleasure Shh
Harry I could fix those glasses for you
but there's nothing wrong with them
oh no Harry I insist don't you dig well
nothing happened
well that's a shame can I try again Shh
and that's Dumbledore he's the
headmaster of Hogwarts oh yes sir but
who are you what do you want from me
Voldemort
then who are you
yeah
Jeremy anything happen Jeremy anything
happen hairy poor mix those glasses and
that's Dumbledore get out of it what can
you water
ah