warning the following videos very
serious and based on true events it is
in no way super for men to be funny
comedic or taken as a joke however I
didn't take my ADHD medication before I
started filming editing this video which
may cause this video to seem less
serious and more confusing and
invisibles to be viewer discretion is a
word we are good to go first vlog of the
year and I well that's what I'm supposed
to do today I'll supposed to cut my hair
like so poofy on so this video was
supposed to be the first video of the
year but as most of you know I fell
about 3 weeks behind schedule because
the last video took over a month to me
never ever doing that many effects in a
video ever you'll probably do another
one but I wanted to start the year with
something a little more personal and
today I'm gonna be talking about
something that I've never really said
publicly and it's something no one other
than my closest friends and some family
know but first let me start off by
saying my new year's resolutions this
year were pretty much your typical
resolutions exercising more and dieting
baby more mature the main one was I was
gonna keep making YouTube videos without
having to sacrifice my health most of
the time really goes into write I read
them all on my laptop in my phone but if
I were to print them on a paper the
stack would probably look something like
this ya know I didn't sell too many
scheme' whose back in all night I don't
even make like 99% of these ideas cuz
most of them make absolutely no sense
out of all these there's probably only a
few worth filming like Dragon Ball Z
fight in real life what a great idea
that doesn't sound overly time-consuming
difficult and all-around stressful to do
at all
ducking dragon I don't want to pick that
all up so I'm not gonna push it but you
know how mad I am anyway as fun as it is
and looking the behind the scenes and
whatnot you know just trying to keep up
with everything last year I was skipping
meals losing sleep feeling exhausted all
day and I ended up developing what was a
minor addiction I don't know where these
feelings come from or what they mean
but there's just something about doing
crystal meth finding the smallest animal
you can find and just strangling up to
just give you that rush you know yeah
doing a lot better this week thank you
guys let's run to Ryan hello everyone my
name is Ryan and why Ryan hi then over
the years I kind of developed an
addiction to energy drinks and caffeine
why freaking kidding me man
I do meth okay and I strangle animals
for fun
you see Wes over there he hooks up in IV
when he sleeps so he can drink alcohol
24/7 ted shoots up heroin just because
he loves the movie Twilight that much
you're like my own personal brand of
Bella and Phil I don't even want to tell
you what he's still just what is he I
still on MySpace Oh where'd you go see
you see these these are real problems
why don't you come back to this cutaway
when you have a real addiction no no
don't strangle him what no I wasn't
going to do that this is my dog he's
only here because he's addicted to
making immature people laugh what yeah I
don't know why I kept going with that
that was supposed to be a quick cutaway
anyway okay yeah it's not like I'm
addicted to anything crazy like crack
crystal meth though I did just start
getting into Breaking Bad and crystal
meth does look kind of interest now on
this on a joke do not ever do meth kids
they're not even once yes that long
cutaway was supposed to be a joke but
caffeine addiction is a real problem
it's a real thing and so was my space
I'm a real drug addict yes caffeine is
legal but it is a drug I think is it a
drug see I wouldn't know because I
didn't graduate college because of the
caffeine caffeine not even okay I didn't
graduate because I wanted to make
youtube videos making YouTube videos is
what led to the caffeine so you could
say that YouTube is a gateway drug
YouTube is a gateway drug YouTube the
gateway to caffeinated meth but
seriously the caffeine thing got pretty
bad last year I was literally drinking
about four Red Bulls every single day we
were filming the candy Chris video last
year which by the way if you watched
that video again and replace candy crush
with caffeine that's actually what I was
really talking about curse symbolism I
don't even know simple
zone is the right term because I didn't
graduate college because of the caffeine
but during that shoot I remember I was
so exhausted and burnt out just to
finish it up basically I ended up
drinking nine rebels in one day and that
night I ended up crashing from all the
rebels but I woke up like an hour later
with my hand like trembling and my chest
was like in so much pain and I knew I
had to stop drinking so much caffeine or
at least cut down so I told myself after
the last min of the year which as you
guys know is that one ahh I just need to
take a break from YouTube so I could
just stop drinking energy drinks for
like a month or so because I was
starting to get worried that I was
addicted to energy drinks which I didn't
think was possible before so why am I
telling you guys all this I know a lot
of you guys are younger than me and you
know when I was younger in high school
in college I was surrounded by people
that did drugs and I never did so that's
why I thought addiction could never
happen to me because I thought I won't
happen to weak minded druggies I guess
what I'm trying to say is that for all
you innocent kids out there you're gonna
be addicted to drugs
just kidding sorry this is a serious
topic addiction can happen to anyone so
be careful in terms of me I honestly
still do drink energy drinks but it's
definitely not for a day like it used to
be maybe one or two at the very most
baby steps all about the babies people
always make new year's resolutions and
they never follow through because I
think once they break it or slip up
they just say screw it and they just let
it go but it's all about the baby steps
I don't know why this babies moonwalking
like if your new year's resolution was
to be nicer to people because you are a
dick every single day last year try and
be a dick every other day and then once
a week and then once a month and then
you relapse and go through this all-out
dick week and that's came out wrong so
did that never give up just take baby
steps because nobody likes a dick and
nobody wants to have an addiction
especially if that addiction is to being
a dick which in that case makes sense
because nobody likes both those things
that's why the word dick is in the word
addiction but that doesn't have to be
you you can beat that addiction you can
beat that dick yeah my other resolution
was to be more mature that's clearly
working Oh anyway I made this video
pretty much as an update at the start of
the year I don't know a lot you guys
don't even care what the personal life
stuff and I probably like just drink
more energy drink so you can post more
videos like your goddess thank you guys
so much for watching I know I got off to
a slow start this year but I am back in
it and ready to make 2014 not just good
not just great but pretty average it's
gonna be another let's give me another
cool year it's gonna be weird and if you
thought this video wasn't weird then
chances are you've been watching me for
a bit and you're also weird now it's a
proven fact I make people
sorry so for all my labs out there I
can't wait to spend this year with you
guys but for all your new viewers out
there come on man all the cool kids are
doing it just do it
subscribe oh oh
subscribing to nigahiga not even once
ah at the edge of my bed
see you guys hey guys thank you again so
much for watching if you want to see
that video that took way too long to
make that we posted last week click the
one on the left if you want to see the
candy crush video that I referenced in
this video click the one on the right
and if you can't tell your left from
your right put your hands in front of
your face and make an L with both hands
now put on your right hand the other
ones the left there you go