hey guys so I know I'm late to the trend
as usual I finally did an escape room
for the first time and because it was my
first time you can probably already
guess but I was just kind of awesome I
don't know like really really good hands
down one of the best person I've ever
seen play this kind of game sorry I know
I don't want to sound like I'm bragging
but I mean I do have a hundred percent
success rate and I've only done one room
so far so like wait till I get some real
experience under my belt that number is
only gonna go up and then you can even
ask the people that I went with who've
actually done escape rooms in the past
like just how naturally good I am how
great I was for like my first time well
I mean you didn't ask them so but even
then you know you they were like okay
fine I suck okay I suck I suck I'm not
good at escape rooms okay and yes it
might seem like I'm making a big deal
out of nothing well it is to me because
I always thought I would be good at
escape rooms you know I love puzzles and
riddles and usually good at that stuff I
thought it'd be a natural fit but I
guess I just I don't know I'm just not
good at them yes I just some I'm not as
smart as I thought I was you know hey
this is the part where you guys are
supposed to be like hey come on he
wasn't that bad it was your first one
you know right look some people's brains
just work in different ways it doesn't
mean I'm stupid okay I'm not dumb look
just because I'm a college dropout and
yes I cheated a lot in high school and
middle school to get better grades so I
didn't really retain anything and yeah
okay sure they tested me as a child for
ADHD because I couldn't perform
so-called basic tasks like raising my
hand when I'm supposed to or not paying
attention or not punching a girl in the
stomach for cutting in front of me in
the lunch line even though she saw me
there first doesn't mean that I'm dumb
okay I just believe that I was there
first Hannah and Hannah if you ever end
up seeing this video for whatever reason
I am very very sorry for that
kindergarten Mia was just a jerk who was
first so anyway back to the topic one of
the worst feelings in the world is
finding out that you know something you
always thought you were good at and
maybe you've some pride in it you're not
only not good you're also the exact
opposite you're bad
and the only feeling worse than that is
when everyone else around you who
thought the same thing of you finds that
out as well people always used to ask me
to go to the escape room they would say
things like Brian you should come with
us dude you're not fun yeah you'd be
really good at it I think it'd be really
easy for you to yeah the way you think
outside of the box you'd be perfect for
it come on let's go yeah they said well
if you guys say so I mean I guess I
could give it a shot yeah that's kind of
why they're not the happiest campers
right now so it's not like I wasn't
trying I tried really hard maybe a
little too much to be honest I mean yes
sometimes thinking outside the box is
great for problem solved but I tend to
naturally already think outside the box
whether I want to or not if you've been
watching this channel long you know if
you probably already know why I would be
so bad at these things make it easier
for those of you that don't this is kind
of what it was like for me and this is
not a reenactment of what happened this
is just the kind of things that we're
going on in my mind while the actual
escape room was happening it's probably
easier to just watch it take a look okay
so one last time as we mentioned early
in the prep room we will be watching you
so just to reiterate no phones and
remember the key to escaping this room
is in this box and in order to open it
you need to figure out the clues leading
to it do not try to force this or
anything else in the room open if it's
not opening it's not broken
you just haven't figured it out yet
we've had people break things in the
past out of frustration and
unfortunately we've had to ask them to
leave that's not fun for anyone right
especially us because then we have to
fix it that's all right well if there's
no other questions I'll be no
interesting um what was that you said
the Baqi to escaping this room that
we're locked in is in that box yet you
know that we know that we have to think
outside the box to see into it oh okay
oh hell if there's no other questions
for me the timer begins as soon as this
door closes good luck and have fun
where do we start oh no I mean she just
said this is our way out well look on
the box of some writing or something
there's only unlock on here oh that
means we have to find a key of some sort
yeah I'll check the books I got the maps
I'll get the Destiny all right there's
definitely gonna be something with his
chest with these cups bo does that mean
I don't know Ryan why don't you look at
the inch right fine right Ryan what are
you doing I think I think I got it got
what I think I figured it out
what like the next clue know how we get
out of this room Ryan you're wasting our
time that's impossible
yeah we just started guys look remember
when she came in here to explain the
rules yeah what about it when she came
in wearing all white I started looking
around the room for all these other
white things and all of a sudden I just
realized all of the walls around us are
white and they're surrounding us like
we're in some kind of institution like
we're in some kind of box and then right
as I was meeting that realization she
goes and picks up another box and and
tries to open it in front of us what is
your point guys call me crazy call it a
hunch
call me maybe but I really think that if
we want to get out of this box we have
to figure out what's in that box
they've been serious yeah why she just
told us that Oh see told you we should
have brought him he's gonna slow us down
okay
okay she told you guys about the box but
in order to get it open I noticed that
there's actually a keyhole
yes we know that's the first thing we
talked about that's why we're looking
for hints to find the key actually
that's not what I was gonna say but if
you want to find the key I could
actually show you guys will we need help
actual help gold glow look at that deer
or whatever that is oh you mean the
sheep head that's not a sheep and sheep
same thing Oh bison Triceratops it's not
a dinosaur could be its two horns honey
dinosaurs what what what are you what
are you guys even look we've wasted so
much time that we haven't found a single
clue yet yeah I got nothing same on the
maps they're just random circles
everywhere yeah same here
yeah I got some different colored water
bottles but I don't really know
look guys all I'm saying is you guys
don't know where to even start I could
just get things going and just let you
guys know where we buy where do we go
huh where do we start well I mean I
would start with the hollowed-out book
what the hollowed-out book next to Greg
over there you know a third show from
the top and the right you have a big
lettering on it
[Music]
it should be like some kind of
wristwatch or something how did you know
that I mean I could tell you guys but
like you said I don't want to waste
everybody's time so okay we were wrong
we're sorry yeah yeah just tell us
what's next come on yeah okay well that
hollowed-out book had a watch which
shouldn't be working because when a
watch doesn't work you tend to look
we're at a clock which is also not
working so it might appear use this
until you see the bottom of the clock
which says Made in China probably
wouldn't think too much into that until
you realize that this whole room is
covered in maps and one of those Maps
happen to be China now the map of China
has a bunch of different cities circled
but since they provided us with some
kind of line graph of some sort with the
x-axis being the minutes and the y-axis
being the hours we can assume that they
want us to use the x on the broken clock
and the broken watch and basically use
them as coordinates to find our two
cities that are most important clock
says 3:45 mine says 6:40 it should come
on to Shanghai and Beijing then we take
the broken ruler which is also made in
China and measure the distance between
the two and it should come out to about
two inches it doesn't have to be an
exact measurement you just have to know
that they're saying two inches they're
saying two inches well technically no
not two inches two inch s chest oh yeah
see those weird colored bottles you
found earlier they're all different
colors but only two of them in the chest
or actually the same colors making the
two inch s the only couple just like the
cup pulls that Derek was figuring out
earlier and since we now know which
colored cup to pour the liquid into we
can follow the tube all the way to our
last puzzle the instruments and
obviously we all know we only mean piano
so we forget about the other one then we
get the shoot music do it what how is it
obvious how do we know it's the piano
the cups they're labeled PO remember
peel what P o P and old piano you think
I can't explain that one
okay fine but it still doesn't explain
why you think it's the last puzzle I
mean we knew from the very beginning
that we're looking for keys right what
has more keys than a piano
hey guys there's there's a note in here
just says to find the key you must play
the keys using all the keys that led you
here in the correct order all the keys
that led you here correct order what
does that mean
the clues things that led us here the
book was the first one oh that's right
yeah it's empty on the spine there's a
big egg yeah yeah that's how you knew
where to start and that thing stands out
more than a big a plane a key what else
we have um there's a G in here the G a
another egg is that it no nothing
happened that was the last clue it led
us to the piano all right yeah but maybe
try it again but all together all right
so the order was a G F G a a
doesn't it sound like mary had a little
bit
[Music]
I don't know how you did it but I'm
impressed well there's only one last
thing to do not man you do it you
deserve it
okay what the hell why would you do that
we have the key well you need to swallow
fine now you guys still don't get it huh
what look there was never a key in the
box to begin with congratulations you
guys set a new record from the very
beginning she mentioned that the key
tore escape was in the box
she didn't say there was actually a key
in the box the box was the key why when
I asked her about thinking outside the
box she gave me that weird look remember
people don't usually pick up on that so
fast well I did know something was up
but I wasn't like absolutely positive
that I had to break it yet you know
because it was two of the rules like
don't break things and don't use phones
then I started noticing all the random
phones in the room and I realized maybe
were supposed to break the rule but even
then I wasn't absolutely sure until I
saw the broken ruler exactly broken rule
alert clever rule no this is the
stupidest escape room ever hey it's okay
man some people just don't know how to
think outside the box some people just
can't break the rule they just do what
they're told and you know what we call
those people sheep
[Applause]
yeah you already know it didn't happen
that way like I said this was kind of
the fantasy version that was actually
going on my head during the escape I'll
try to make all these connections and
make things work I was overthinking
everything this was just to show you the
kind of things that were going on in my
head while the other guys were doing the
real work if you want to see how the
escape room actually was in real life I
uploaded a blog on Higa TV it's just
like a real tiny bit more accurate and
realistic than the one that you just saw
although I will say just thinking about
the escape room and writing that skit
you know the one you just saw I actually
think I developed a technique that will
help you or even experience escapers how
to get out of any escape room pretty
much with the same success rate as me
100% I'm not just talking in a fantasy
I'm talking reality because in reality
that other version would look a little
bit more like this nah man you do it you
deserve it okay what the hell why would
you do that
we have the key Paul you need to swallow
fine now you guys still don't get it huh
what why don't you guys take a closer
look there was never any key in the box
to begin with are you serious I just
that mean we win oh hey I'm sorry but
I'm gonna have to ask all of you to
leave right now oh okay and it's the
hell Ryan's you you did yeah I do you
want