hey guys so my birthday just passed a
couple weeks ago and to me that's
usually a sign and a reminder that a
bunch of kids just graduated whether
it's college or high school and it's
only a matter of time before we start
seeing a bunch of those you know
graduation speeches go viral all of like
some celebrity or some successful
business person seeing something really
inspirational to the crowd mate to be
able to inspire a bunch of people with
just your words especially live in front
of thousands of people and then
eventually millions within that video
goes viral that's that's the dream some
people just have a natural gift with the
words unlike people me I have not much
skill and it's not like I haven't been
given the opportunity to do it my old
high school asked me to speak a bunch of
times at their graduation or some reason
other high schools that I even go to
wanted me to speak at there's even some
colleges which is pretty ironic
considering I'm a college dropout and
I've turned them all down it's not
because I didn't want to do it or
because I hate public speaking I can
force myself to speak in public I turn
them down because I honestly believe
that if I were to give a speech at a
graduation ceremony
I would probably ruin it or so I've been
told by people that I've showed my rough
speeches to most of you guys already
know but I am pretty realistic and
honest and that's not the best qualities
to sound inspiration like you know those
sports movies like read at the end of
the movie where they have their biggest
toughest opponent and then the coach or
like a player stands up and gives some
inspirational speech to just get
everybody pumped up and fired up and
just ready to go and beat this team yeah
I could do that too but at least I'll be
honest about it I personally think that
being realistic and honest is more
inspiring so you're not being lied to
look I could tell you guys that we're
gonna be the best team stepping on that
Court tonight I could tell you guys that
we worked way too hard to be going down
like this I could tell you guys that it
doesn't matter that they're bigger
faster stronger more athletic that even
though the entire city the entire state
has already counted us out that we don't
need to believe it because if we play
with heart if we play as a team if we
play like we want it more than they do
there is no way we can fail
you know what it's like to be the ones
who are passed on we know what it's like
to be the ones to start at the bottom of
the pit and work our asses off to get
back to the top no one who's never been
on the bottom can keep up with people
who have and overcame it tell you all
that cuz we all know it's not accurate
what I can tell you the truth we will be
the second best team on that court
tonight we will play as a team but so
will they and they've been playing
together longer than us yes of course we
will want it but probably just as much
as they do because they want to win too
right because one thing something does
not war getting Johnson yes no when you
ask that girl to prom that night did you
want her to come with you
yeah and did she exactly
Callahan yes coach you're the shortest
guy on the team maybe the entire school
did you want to be four - mmm and yet
you still are aren't you mr. Ghoulies
jolly yes coach when I picked you up
with a game tonight did you want me to
run over you can't wait what I said when
I picked you up for the game tonight did
you want me to run over your cat and
throw it's half dead body in the bushes
by your house I do answer the question
mr. Cooley shall they go of course not
exactly see the lesson here is you can
want something more than anyone else in
the world and you still don't get it
because the world does not revolve
around all of you do you understand me
what was that yeah so what we gonna do
tonight how bad are we
we went to the state finals that year we
didn't play but we cheered really good
well but back to the whole graduation
speech thing when I would get these
graduation speech inquiries I would
start writing down a bunch of ideas in
my phone like how I would plan for a
video not planned very well I was just
trying to be completely honest and just
be me and it turns out that me being me
trying to give advice to a bunch of
graduates is not only not inspirational
but borderline inappropriate according
to some people not that they would know
anything they haven't given high school
graduation speeches I still think those
speeches are decent and not
inappropriate at all in fact I still
have the drafts on my phone so I can
read you guys some of the lines that I
had in these speeches that I was told to
take out because they're inappropriate
you guys will see if people are just too
sensitive these days I mean like
seriously it's a high school graduation
they're not teenagers and all jokes
aside these are actual lines that I
wrote for these speeches that I was told
to take out and I still don't see why
there you go gotta get into the whole
graduation speech voice burning
suppression or inspiration Robins 20
Robin Antin Robin Robin Burt Robin Hood
Batman what am i doing
do whatever it is you want to do in life
if you want to be a drug dealer go be a
drug dealer
people need college as much as they need
hair conditioner you can do it you don't
need it you already shampoo there are
gonna be times that you become so
overwhelmed by everything that you might
even get to the point where you're
thinking about killing yourself nobody
likes to study unless you're some kind
of freak it doesn't matter if you never
reach your goals or accomplish any of
your dreams you are going to fail
whether it's a test or a job interview
or even a relationship you will fail
life is like playing a video game
life is like a sane and DragonBall life
is like a box of chocolate some of us
have nuts and some of us go yeah I can
understand why I was recommended take
out some of that stuff not everyone is
gonna get the Dragon Ball or video game
references let alone the Forrest Gump
thing I don't see what's wrong with the
rest of it if I'm hearing it back now I
can see how out of context it sounds a
little inappropriate but it really isn't
in reality it's not something that high
schoolers haven't already heard they
have the internet I just feel like
people these days are so quick to get
upset over every little thing and if
they were to just take the time to
really listen to what's being said they
might find that they're getting mad and
raising an uproar over pretty much
nothing something that is not even being
said something that's being created in
their own head and for the exact reason
that's why I would never give a high
school graduation speech even though
it's one of my life goals and one of my
dream I'm not willing to censor myself
some of us have nuts and some don't
what's wrong with that I mean when I was
writing those speeches I was just
thinking what I would say to my high
school self and he he was fine with
everything okay he didn't have any
problems even though was not the most
inspirational he got it he appreciated
the honesty and honestly he got all the
references because he is me that's it me
I need to go to an actual graduation
ceremony I need to give some beautifully
crafted well-written appropriate speech
to the class of 2018 I can just give a
poorly written not appropriate yet on
his speech to the class of 2008 mieze I
mean not like 2008 different means I
meant like me from 2008 so I would be
speaking to myself as a high school
graduate and you know I'm not gonna
waste the time to clone a thousand
different means and now please welcome
our next speaker mr. Ryan Higa
now before I get started I just wanted
to say that I'm gonna do my best to keep
this clean and appropriate for all of
you while still being honest mmm good
evening class of 2000 and actually it's
still afternoon there's just really
cloudy right now so it looks kind of up
sorry let me just good afternoon class
of 2008 mieze now I know because I was
all of you ten years ago that you don't
like long speeches because of the whole
ADHD things so I will keep this short
and straight to the new iPhone yep
before not even know you hey come on
bunch of freaking idiots or swear oh you
really think we're gonna get that fat oh
look I'm just gonna get straight to the
point and start this off by asking the
simplest question you can ask a person
what is the meaning of life so many
people young and old have a tough time
answering that question but wouldn't you
think that should be the first thing
that we figure out the purpose of our
lives the reason why we're doing
everything that we're doing there's no
right or wrong everyone can have their
own answer but to me the meaning of life
is happiness I really believe that
everything that we do throughout our
lives is because we think it will either
make us happier or less unhappy than if
we didn't do it even things that we
don't want to do like studying for a
test all night you're not gonna gain
happiness from studying nobody likes to
study unless you're some kind of freak
you do it because you think it will
eventually lead you to happiness just
like everything else that we do studying
will help you pass a test and you'll be
a lot happier if you pass a test and if
you fail passing the test will lead to
better grades better grades leads to
better colleges better colleges
increases your chances of securing a
better job and oh sorry my phone locked
quick just 6-9 6-9 6-9 better colleges
increases your chance at securing a
better job that makes more money so you
get a nicer car or a nicer house or eat
it fancier restaurants whatever it is
you want to do later in life everyone
does what they do because they think
it's gonna make their overall lives
better than if they didn't do it and the
reason why I bring this up and why I
think it's so important to understand
the meaning of life is because life is
gonna become more and more hectic when
you go off on your own there's gonna be
so many more things that you have to
think about that you never had to think
about as a kid and there's gonna be
times that you get so overwhelmed by
everything that you might even get to
the point where you want to kill
yourselves I know I have because life is
like a box of chocolates it can be sweet
it can be
it can get a little nutty and you no
longer have your parents around anymore
to eat those disgusting raspberry ones
for you you got to deal with those on
your own now when also life is like a
box of chocolates because the more you
get into it the fatter you get as well
so these low points in your life are
going to happen to you if you want to
grow as a person maybe not to the point
of considering suicide but just know
that if it does get to that point that
it's not happening for no reason and
there can still be a benefit from it
because if you survive and figure your
way out of that situation and that
mindset you'll have the mental strength
to be able to deal with anything in the
future and you can't acquire that kind
of strength without going through
extreme adversity it's like a Saiyan and
Dragon Ball the more you beat up a sin
without killing him stronger he gets
when he recovers yep I understand that
is the first point I understood so far I
watched a bunch of those inspirational
speeches because I had no idea what
possible advice I could have for a bunch
of graduates and I want to get an idea
what those other speakers were talking
about and a common theme that kept
coming up that they were all giving
advice on how to strive for greatness or
how to reach your goals or how to become
successful like they are and it's
inspiring because they're telling you
how they were just like you when they
were younger and they weren't anybody
special and they failed over and over
and over before they found any success I
agree with that message like I mentioned
earlier you are gonna have low points
failure is a part of life whether it's a
job interview or becoming a parent or
starting a family whatever it is you're
going to fail I completely agree with
that a lot of these speeches were very
inspiring and they are helpful to help
you reach what our society defines as
success but before we figure out how to
reach success in life shouldn't we at
least try to figure out what success in
life is we spend so much time thinking
about all these goals and dreams that
we've had since we were little kids and
how we're gonna reach them that we
sometimes get so distracted that we
forget why we're trying to strive for
them in the first place you can set and
go after all the goals you want in life
but it all leads back to the same thing
the meaning of life happiness that
should be your primary number one going
everything else should come after and I
know that sounds super obvious and
cliche and easier said than done at
times but I personally think it's very
important to have that in the back of
your mind and keep reminding yourself
that way when you start to stray from it
you'll recognize it you'd be surprised
how many people including myself focus
so much on how to reach our individual
goals or what our society defines as
success that we don't even realize that
we're not even happy anymore
most of the time that unhappiness is
caused by ourselves it's fixable but we
don't even recognize it
so caught up chasing after these goals
and stress ourselves out so much to the
point that we're miserable but yet we
just suck it up and we just keep going
because we think that once we finally
reach these goal is that all this stress
and unhappiness is gonna go away and
we're just gonna live a happy jolly gay
life well I can tell you from personal
experience that's not how it works if
you're not happy with your life on the
journey to your end goal you're most
likely not gonna be happy even after you
reach it it's like playing a video game
you don't play a video game that you
hate just because you think it's gonna
be fun once you finally beat it it's
almost the exact opposite of that the
best part of the game is a journey the
moment you beat it the fun is over but
it's exactly that it's a moment of
happiness and that feeling will fade as
soon as the end credits come rolling by
then you're bored and it's time for a
new game my point is don't let society's
definition of success dictate your goals
and dreams and contrary to most
inspirational speeches I personally
think that it doesn't matter if you
never reach any one of your goals or
accomplish any one of your dreams if
you're enjoying the journey don't waste
your time playing a game that makes you
miserable just because you saw the
glorified trailers or because you heard
all the hype around it we're not having
fun playing it it's not gonna get any
more fun just because you beat it
there's a lot of other games out there
and the night is still young you guys
have the time find the game that's meant
for you and have fun playing that's the
whole purpose of playing the game that's
the whole purpose of this journey that's
the whole purpose of life that being
said once again congratulations class of
2008 mieze I hope you guys have a
wonderful journey and a happy afternoon
thank you
[Applause]
I just have to say that speech was
really long so it's not afternoon now
it's actually evening you can disrespect
with peace I hope you never find your
game yeah this is also my way of saying
stop sending me graduation inquiries
because clearly I've already mastered
that so why would I do it again