hey guys if you haven't noticed I've
been gone for a while now because I've
been sick with Bieber fee no I'm not
gonna make that joke again but I am sick
if you can't tell you anyway I've been
gone because I've been extremely busy
doing incredibly amazing things no not
no David I said see Lots not zerglings
huh okay that's not true kinda maybe the
real reason why I've been gone for such
a long time is because I've been working
on a short film with wongfuproductions
the film was completely created by us we
wrote it we filmed it we tossed it we
turned it you played it we fought it and
it's being edited right now it's gonna
be about 45 minutes long and they had
some of your favorite youtubers and more
I'm not gonna be releasing the trailer
until the movie is done but for now let
me tickle you with a teaser first things
first I'm not your average teenager I
never got to grow up with a family with
bikes and candy as long as I can
remember I've been training to become an
ass an agent of secret stuff you have
one more assignment you must complete
but but why already did all the hard
stuff
we are asses we do not complain when
things get you hard we push on through
take it hey Dan we have a special
assignment that only you can execute we
need an agent on the inside we believe
that the sins have already infiltrated
the school with Assassins of their own
your mission is to pose as a high school
student and protect Taylor from an
ending threats
this is a new world for you high school
students are the most dangerous and
misunderstood citizens that you will
ever come across
you
do