dear Ryan can you make a Naruto movie
here Ryan can you beat Naruto all right
no okay
Naruto is too good of a show to spoof
that's why I've never done it okay it
would take so much work and an effort
and I don't have to make the full movie
if I did it I would have to do it right
so no so stop asking okay I'm not gonna
do it what would it look like though if
I did it the pain of being alone is like
no other why me why am I always the one
that's different they look at me with
those eyes like some kind of monster or
one day they will acknowledge me I will
keep fighting I will keep pushing
through I will become the Hokage no
matter what because that is my way of
ninja not at all that's fine but we just
wanted to know where you wanted to eat
oh well sometimes I feel like ramen
other times its price
[Music]
I can't find them Peggy you gone don't
squint that's bad for your eyes here
whoa
[Music]
[Applause]
in order to
[Music]
hey socrata you're kind of dropping
comes i flora do you think you could
stop beating like that no that's good
now we can sweep the crumbs into the
crack
[Music]
Goku what are you doing here
you know I'm not quite sure but you guys
can't fly what
[Music]
huh yeah I guess I could just make a
parody trailer now that'd be too much
work