nice guys finish last that's why I'll
treat you I trash it not what I really
wanna do but you only date bad guys so
[Music]
me too
Spanish last last
like trash
[Applause]
see bad guys even
treat you the way you want me to
and i'ma beat you in every complication
going out with the girls you better get
my permission wait no I take that back
you can't go hannes magna that's my
favorite show
wait let me speak your language cows Moo
like smash
want me to
behind the scenes she means the world to
me I wanna tell that that she's
beautiful and showered that she's alone
she's scared
tell her how much I can
but that one winner
because
mom eats
oh is this the class where you learned
how to pick up girls nice guys
your language causal