hey guys so Thanksgiving was yesterday I
mean coasted a video called things that
ruin Thanksgiving part 2 where basically
we had to make a whole Thanksgiving
dinner as props for the video shoot my
parents actually came into town and
cooked a whole another Thanksgiving
dinner so now we have like way too much
food and rather than eating leftovers
until all the food goes bad and we have
to throw it away and waste it I thought
why not just pack it up right now while
it's still good and give it to somebody
who needs it more than we do and today
that's what we're gonna do we just
finished packing up all these meals and
we're gonna go deliver them to the
homeless people of Las Vegas which if
you don't know there's a lot of them and
yes we already called the Las Vegas
police department to make sure that it
was legal to do miss sadly it's illegal
to feed the homeless in certain states
believe it or not because the last time
I did this in a video called Christmas
ninja where I gave away food and
presents to kids and random homeless
people sadly I got a lot of people
saying that it was illegal to do and I
shouldn't be doing that I personally
think is ridiculous and discouraged is
helping other people but whatever we got
the okay so we're good to go but you
know what's even more fun than that
feeding the homeless and not getting
caught as a ninja this is the wrong way
this is still a wrong way it's almost
there there we go just like a vulnerable
spot for an enjoyment gotta fix this
here's a walk around this I guess
what's the play
[Music]
first one
later
ginger dinner weird huh good night man
I'm a great night what's up bro yeah
yeah I know he's hella scream was he
happy you seem happy
[Music]
after Thanks
we have a dog no I know we can give
another we're gonna give another one for
their dog
[Music]
now you're just like oh thank you so
much I don't have much but here can I
give you this sure he gave me some
papers it was really appreciative
actually how he thinks giving to get
comments thank you thank you
Happy Thanksgiving I hope you guys like
the food we're just trying to find
people to get food that need another
nuts oh yes that was a ninja I can't
believe I was visited by a ninja and he
snuck right up on yon I could not see
him coming
Happy Thanksgiving
[Music]
you
Nancy ninjas oh you know the normal like
doughnuts and stuff oh you want to see
the previous video keep them on the left
you want to see bloopers behind the
scenes click the one on the right or if
you want to see Christmas ninja so the
bottom do what this lower end guard ever
I'm leaving it