hey guys I have some good news and some
bad news the good news is I finally
finish editing the entire ninja milk
film and trailer and you're gonna be
seeing the trailer right after the bad
news the bad news is that the video is
still processing after like hours and
YouTube still has to accept it which is
going to be another couple days until it
goes up but hey more good news instead
of redirecting you to another site or
some place else to go watch it I'm just
gonna put it up on my channel so be sure
to check back in a day or two but for
now check out the trailer you will never
get bug joy because you're suffered to
an arrogant absolutely right I'll find
the replacement
and that's why this is my favorite door
our cue
Dumbledore
thank you master for teaching us the way
of a ninja
peace out losers I have faith in you
doing this
you
making my way downtown walking fast
faces pass and I'm home oh did it a
little Oh