warning the following video may contain
content not suitable for people who
can't take a joke if you are one of
these people please leave now or forever
hold your peace you may now kiss the
bride your discretion is advised
so at the end of the year people always
like to reminisce about all the great
times that they had and since Christmas
just ended and because I'm in such a
Christmas spirit mood I'm gonna be
telling you guys all the great wonderful
reasons why 2009 sucked palatable [ __ ]
2009 is finally gonna be over thank God
you woke him Ryan hmm
anyway like I was saying earlier people
like to think about all the good things
that happen in the year but I'm a
pessimistic person I see the glass
half-empty even when it's full so here
are a few reasons why 2009 sucked let's
start off with one of the biggest events
of all that's right Michael Jackson's
death and I'm not gonna be one of those
people talking about how sad Michael
Jackson's death because everybody knows
how sad his death was what about Farrah
Fawcett she died on the same day in fact
before him she was first she won yet
nobody gave a damn because apparently
Michael Jackson's death was more
important and I agree haha just kidding
but seriously nobody gave a damn let me
tell you when everybody was crying over
Michael I stood up and I said no I I'm
sorry I don't even know who Farrah
Fawcett is is that like a type of sync
cuz if it isn't it should be thanks the
new Farrah Fawcett your water will come
all where than ever I'm just playing you
should never make money off of someone
else's death that's horrible I mean
really who does that hey but anyway
moving on another horrible death that
took place this year one of my idols
Billy Mays you know who that is right
the spokesperson that would always shout
at you to buy his products he was an
inspiration he didn't just make me want
to buy OxiClean he made me want to buy
OxiClean so I did in my opinion he was
the best spokesperson better than the
ShamWow guy don't get me wrong I love
the ShamWow guy too but imagine if they
work together they would have been
unstoppable hi Billy Mays here and this
is the Farrah Fawcett this alright this
is gonna be fast make sure you keep up
we got your faucet we got your level we
listen ever the water comes out boom
you're done you get in this cover man Oh
what are you getting this what are you
getting this camera man oh yeah great so
let's try this again you let the lever
the water comes out it's all wet you're
done you'll be saying what's up every
time yeah maybe that wouldn't work out
so well but you know what I mean anyway
there's so many other horrible things
that happened this year Brittany Murphy
died Chris Brown beat Rihanna
I took Swayze died Taylor Swift picking
on Kanye all my Guppies died Asian Kate
is number one on YouTube and even Tiger
Woods cheating on his wife with a bunch
of other women then again he was just
following Nike slow
you know he just did it anyway there's a
lot more but it would take forever to
get through them all I don't want to
leave on a bad note so I'm gonna tell
you one good thing that happened this
year I finally been reunited with my big
green ball and guess what that's right
it's a boy