hey guys so today I'm gonna be talking
about girls feminists to be exact and if
you don't know what a feminist is they
are girls who are very Pro girls
and when I say Pro girls I don't mean
like lesbians or professional girl or
talking about girls who seek equality
between men and women actually wrote
this video a long time ago but I never
filmed it because I thought feminists
would be offended oh you think just
because we're girls we can't handle a
joke what no I never said that why do
you have to make the girl character
stupid well I have guy characters just
as stupid as you oh so now you're
calling me stupid ha yes then I thought
to myself there's no reason they should
be offended I'm all for equal rights
between men and women I agree that women
should get paid the same amount as a man
if they're doing the same job and a
woman should not be looked down on by a
man but if you want equality everything
has to be equal not just certain things
guys want equality too for example why
is it traditional for a guy to open a
girl's door but a girl never does it for
a guy why is it customary for guys to
have to risk rejection and ask out girls
all the time
girls hardly ever ask old guys wise and
gentlemanlike for a guy to pay for a
meal don't say it's so sweet when guys
bring them gifts and flowers and candies
and what do we get a free hug and why is
it that there's a girls day but when it
comes to boys it's Children's Day I'm
not saying that I want all of these
things it's just that if you're talking
about equality you're basically asking
us to treat you like a dude which we
would love to do if it were acceptable
one of the most popular complaints from
girls is that guys don't spend enough
time with their girlfriends well when
you think about it it goes both ways
that's what he said see what I did there
equality come on I don't wanna watch you
play video games all day why don't you
spend some time with me pull up a
controller there's two of them but I
don't like my video game and I don't
like shopping well you know what I'm a
girl I want attention and I'm a guy I
want another complaint that girls always
have is that guys are all shallow and
they only care about sex and how girls
bodies look then why is it okay for
girls to say it dear Ryan can you
introduce your abs to us less than three
and then if we say dear girl take your
shirt off it's offensive girls are just
as bad as guys it's just that they get
more offended girl you got a nice boobs
could you imagine if guys were that
sensitive oh I like your muscles my
point is that it doesn't matter if
you're a male or a female so again don't
think that I hate feminists because
that's not true at all I'm just raising
a point that both sexes have positives
and negatives so stop complaining about
the other sex and just love yourself for
who you are nobody's perfect stand up do
it like a dude and abracadabra I just
named like for Jessie J songs I don't
know
wine anyway thank you so much for
watching hope you guys enjoyed it peace
out guys and girls yeah this video is
not gonna help you get a girlfriend
- ah