warning the following video is performed
enacted by professionals please do not
attempt to reenact recreate or
reincarnate any of the following stunts
only 32 animals were hurt in the making
of this film viewer discretion is
advised
so today I'm going to be talking about
something I really don't like that's
right nosy people what no intro for this
one guess not so one day I was pretty no
because nobody wants to live in a world
without cookies so that was rude anyway
so like I said earlier I'm gonna be
talking about nosy people and that
really irritates me but the nosy people
irritate me not that talking about it so
like any other average day I was in my
room talking to myself when all of a
sudden hi right hi how is me doing me
it's good how is I I'm good good hey
guys what am I talking about nothing
it's not my business ok ok maybe it
didn't happen exactly like that but see
how irritating nosy people are you know
what people I'm talking about right it's
those people that you weren't even
talking to you but they try to sneak
into your conversation because they
think that they know that they know what
you're talking about when actually they
know that we know that they know that
they don't know what we're talking about
you know you know what it might be
easier if I just show you an example
take a look dude that guy definitely
farted didn't he did it did I heard I
could smell it could smell ass from my
honey no tried to cover it up with his
dead logically yeah who is that what
happened who is that who is that who is
that who is that who is that who is that
who is that you know see people stay
home nobody likes you go talk to your
cat or something and I know it may seem
like I'm overreacting but I have to do
it nosy people every freaking day like
when I went to the market earlier oh I
see you got the marshmallows nice choice
all right that'll be 40 to 90 9 would
that be cash or credit I'm gonna say
credit and one last thing would you like
paper or plastic you son of a [ __ ] and
then after I went to go get some food hi
can I take your order
No
and then later when I found out I was
dying oh my god I'm dying god I won Nam
when one what's your emergency
wouldn't you like to know nosy [ __ ] see
how nosy the world can be but let me
tell you the nosiest of all people have
got to be parents what time you're gonna
be hard going did you take out the trash
why didn't you take it I was the capital
of Thailand it's just far with your
daddy and my favorite question of all
how was your day you want to know how my
day was you want to know how my day was
it was alright but seriously of all you
nosy people out there I hope you know
that we know that you don't know what we
know so stop pretending like you know
even though you don't because every time
you returned to know what you know even
though you don't know what you know
you're just lessening the value of
knowing and if you keep lessening the
value of knowing then pretty soon we're
not gonna have no no and if we have no
know that Harvey suppose to know when no
means no you know what I'm getting at no
exactly