so as you know it's a very important
time all around the world because the
Olympics are funny I'm learning how to
harmonize yet I still don't know how to
split screen but one day hey guys so
Summer Olympics are finally back again
the Olympics are a time for friendship
hey it's a time for competition ah it's
a time for friendly competition it
sounds like a donkey Hey ah it's a time
for five major regions all around the
world to come together and compete in
peace hence the five Olympic rings it's
kind of funny how the yellow one stands
for Asian the black one stands for
Africa and of course the entire
background is gonna be white it's a time
for your older not-so-funny uncle to
make those lame Olympic jokes that'll
say it was pretty good so maybe you
should join the Olympics huh it's a time
to win medals upon medals upon medals
upon Meadows whether you like it or not
the Summer Olympics takes over the world
every four years and I just have to ask
you guys am I the only one that doesn't
like watching the Olympics I'm just
being completely honest with you guys I
don't find it to be very entertaining
mean don't get me wrong I'll watch
gymnastics now and then not because I
like the sport but because we're good at
it for some reason and because of my
opinion I have to deal with people every
four years who give me crap for not
watching the Olympics I mean I don't
mind if it's like this hey you want to
come over and watch the living's with me
no I don't really like watching the
Olympics what the Olympics are so
exciting then why I'm it's just a
personal preference I don't like all the
sports of this no I mean why are you
here then Oh see I told you I'd learn on
a split screen maybe you should join the
Olympics were editing hope anyway I
don't care the people love the Olympics
I mean I've tried to force myself to
watch it and be like hey Ryan this is
really fun it's not but I can't stand
when people give me crap for an opinion
alright I deliver sir I'm gonna watch
now I'm not really into the Olympics oh
wow I guess I didn't realize that you
hated the US I don't yeah you don't
support your own country what if you
don't like their culture then move I
don't support my country I don't support
my country well I guess I actually don't
do that much I'm not like in the army or
anything
but I love my country I love my country
more than that person that seems the
laughter my high school sporting events
and tries way too hard to show off their
voice
I might not be the most patriotic person
but just because you watch the Olympics
it doesn't mean you support our country
any more than I you're not being
supported by watching it on TV only
thing you're supporting is that's
keeping that work you're watching it on
and plus people don't watch the Olympics
because they want to be supported they
watch because they want to win for
example your country were a child you
wouldn't be one of those supportive
parents because if you were it would
look like this hey USA yeah win or lose
today
doesn't matter to me I just want you to
do your best okay thanks dad
see that would be supportive but we're
not like that we'll be one of those
competitive parents we try to live all
their dreams through their kid and USA
yeah yeah we better win today bring home
that gold medal all right buddy
hanging out a trial to my bed no no you
need to win okay we ain't losing to the
damn Chinese again but the tag is
Japanese Japanese Chinese whatever they
all look the same so you don't watch the
Olympics to support your country you're
just that part that wants their kid to
win so that you can be like my kids
better than all the other ones but over
off the Olympics are supposed to stand
up for peace between the five major
regions of the world it's the complete
opposite of why people walk so I don't
have I get a lot of hate for this
opinion because I already do in real
life but ask yourself this if your
family and friends didn't watch what you
still watch if it wasn't so conveniently
broadcasted on so many channels would
you still watch we didn't have amazing
athletes like Michael Phelps or the
entire US basketball team would you
still watch because the supportive
person would say yes if not maybe you
should stop we didn't like your being
supportive stop pretend like you're
helping our country and stop giving
people like me crap for not watching hey
you're pretty fast talker there maybe
you should join the shot up that was
washed hey that was me