like when they stab people it's like
okay I know you stab a normal person it
doesn't go right through them like that
or come out as easy yeah well they are
decomposed how do you know that because
I stab people
all I know is that when Steve Jobs was
around my phone was amazing everything
was great about it I would say I I would
agree with that after he was a lot
better it just Tim I don't know if Tim
Cook is right you know you know he
wasn't the visionary was illegal yeah it
is right mm-hmm
it's just it's not just like that's
weird gross I don't it's legal should it
be illegal or I think it shouldn't be
illegal
sorry rollers for rollers we still never
figured out we never figured out a way
to start it we know we have the
breathing thing to end it
oh we got a clap but that's just like
for camera everybody put your hands
together put your hands to get you know
an audio you know what we call it and
recording we call it the church clap oh
I say can we guess really oh is it the
church clap good guess hey so there's
this thing an audio anyway we had a lot
of technical difficulties it's our third
time trying to start this podcast and it
looks like it's finally working right
everything good we good I hope so we
don't have an intro so we're just gonna
clap that's what we've been doing for
Audio sake no just just once for your
camera just Sacre - you know sync the
audio and stuff I think you should start
doing high minute you should say
something like my name is Ryan welcome
to the off-the-field podcast today we
have David Choi why are you just do it
you just did it just did it okay yeah
welcome to off the pill podcast today we
have mr. Ryan Higa you're are you trying
to end the podcast by breathing right
now into the mic audience David Choi
special guest himself someone introduced
me smile oh and then and then and then
we'll so you know sounds whatsoever for
you
the science guy well um yeah I mean we
got new chairs you know what we should
do
we did get new chairs see this pocket is
just coming together dude just coming to
getting this better than the other room
though realistically it's better than
the other room I think so
because it's bigger yeah the other one I
felt like I was stuck in a corner
bigger is better as they say what like
the other day the other day David and I
we were talking about how we can how
things come come to I don't know I guess
get society and become like a real thing
yeah and we're trying to make up a new
one we're trying to are the ones we were
saying we made up some ridiculous ones
like what are some sayings that are like
that's that's the thing that I always
want to look up but I can never find it
right and it's got a kiss your fish in
the water
wait did you make that up or is that one
I made that up right now you gotta catch
your fish in the water I mean that I
guess I was watching an old like western
movie and one of the guys was saying
they were like old cowboy robbers and
they were like nah man that was back
when we were young and we were full of
beans I like that one that's a gallon
like man that got the beans like he'd if
he were watching em being do like a slam
does that mean though dude or just
energy powerful is full of be like his
beans are goofy you know maybe energy
yeah I don't know yeah or maybe he was
Filipino Filipino Philippines Latinos
oh well but our Filipino friends are the
ones who made that up it it might be but
on reg just because you're filipino does
not mean that you're full of beans
I always thought full of evil like if
you said man that person is full of
beans that they were like not telling
the truth
oh yeah that person is full of beans
yeah yeah but the way they said it they
were talking they were describing it
like a compliment like man that was back
when we were young and full of beans oh
like energy I guess beans are this is
the kind of stuff of energy I know that
that's what used to eat back in yeah the
way
and so sometimes sometime in society it
changed from full energy to full of poop
you're so full of poop and before that
is full of beans yep
what was it before hey that sounds like
a full of anything rice yeah so you're
so full of it dude you're full of beer
you know but maybe back then when they
would use that term you're full of
blight maybe it was a great thing like a
positive guy yeah compliment you're full
of happiness is that bad what full of
happy now now I'm like questioning no
it's it's a bad thing when I say to you
if I were seeing you like you guys are
full of full of they're full of it
you're full of joy that's a bad thing
that means you're a bullshitter
yeah what if you're full of joy you're
still full of it dude I would want to be
filled with joy David you're just full
of it bro
you're full of it but what's it though
it doesn't matter what it is it just
means you're full of it like you're
alive full of water well there was one
on what is the one that comes from like
God is so it sucks when I can't remember
references but it it comes from see if
you can figure out what this thing is
but it comes from the top of them when
they when you make milk oh the cream of
the crop that comes from when they make
milk or something like that and the top
of the milk was known as the the best
cream I guess a crop yeah so that's like
that's where that I had to look it I
looked it up because we were asking the
girl where does that even come from I'm
pretty sure that's that's correct I
might be wrong I think you're right
thing I googled it and then what is the
crop though is it milk it is milk right
I thought so yeah so maybe in the milk
when it separates the top is the cream
and that's the most valuable maybe it's
kind of like something here that you
know like the foam like what you Neal
nobody there's a perfect pour as the
right amount of foam the hands just
enough to just like make that beer
experience just amazing new saying you
know David do it right what you're the
foam of the beer oh damn that does yeah
that's like oh you got a nuke yo you got
that version of the car through that's
the phone with the beard it could be a
good
thing though bunch too much foam yeah
it's not good
damn this is getting deep when there's
right enough
Oh Mike you're the right enough foam
with the beer the perfect amount of foam
on that you're the perfect amount of
foam on the beer that's like a pickup
line
hey thanks what are you gonna go to a
girl and say hey you know what you're
you just have the perfect amount of foam
with the beard that does not sound if I
was a girl I would care that and be like
what can I be my number I kind of like
you know what is a fun game that we were
playing the other night I was like man
this we should did this in the podcast
what's that is when you were asking if
we were doing like the would you rather
mmm
but it was a little r-rated yeah so if
we were to head out a little bit okay
all right everybody think of a would you
rather and we'll has really good all
right options you can start you go next
and I'll good last why do you get to go
last I got to think about would you
rather go first or second go ahead this
is a completely random one zombie
apocalypse would you rather have you
always go there a spear all right like a
long spear sharp yep durable or or a
fire axe like a you know what's a fire I
think you know the ones that you see
like a fireman's at fireman's axe yeah
oh I you know what I've held both okay
in my life jump out a spear and have
iraq's heard I felt I have held both
okay and experience referencing the
laziness of the people in Wally and me
wanting to be one of those people I
would choose a spear because it's a
little lighter honestly smart I would
also pick a spear but it's because of
the distance because they can only harm
you from touching you sure so if you
have a spear I would like in Walking
Dead I think it's easier to pierce them
yeah they make it look like they're made
of butter in Walking Dead like when they
stab people it's like okay I know you
stabbed a normal person it doesn't go
right through them like that or come out
as easy yeah well they are decomposed
how do you know that because I stabbed
people
I
people yeah here okay how about you acts
really because I could chop wood with it
that is also true
Zambia luckily we didn't think about
that but you know what you can't do go
spearfishing Oh too late you have an axe
oh I have axe body spray what if though
that was the secret we should write up
we should run a zombie
no wait zombies are out dude walking day
just ended and I stopped watching a long
time ago yeah didn't it feel like they
like it was such it was like one of my
favorite shows we used to all watch it
together when it came out and then they
felt like they just kept like every
episode was like okay this whole season
could happend in one episode yeah that's
what I felt like I've only seen a few
episodes so no no it was good you know
we have Gilligan's Island over that show
don't I know people where there's like a
group of people we're stuck on an island
how about what do you live if you guys
continue this cuz I really have to pee
that's why I keep moving I got a pee -
should we take a quick pee blink PB can
we give it a quick B beep a PB pee break
PPE break alright people I really have
to be bad jira back sorry and we are
back from our shishi break you know I
said in Hawaii we say sheshe but I
didn't who was it I said oh I have to go
sheshe oh it was a Maya and Alex you
know the skaters Olympians bronze mm-hmm
I said huh oh yeah yeah well we were
filming like oh yeah hold on I go she
she real quick cuz I was talking to I
guess I was talking to them I don't know
it's my pigeon my pigeon came out my
Hawaii accent and I said I gotta go she
she real quick they were just dying dude
they're like dying it was like that's
what little kids say I was like what
really I thought it was a Hawaii thing
you guys didn't hear that growing up
mm-hmm cause she she know okay well
should PP f me then I say God take a
piss
even as a little kid your parents oh you
got you got piss no I said you gotta go
potty
oh no I mean like that's like a
five-year-old yeah ten-year-old
ten year old what do you say oh I gotta
go pee bathroom all or I gotta go pee
yeah back to the segment oh yeah
sorry I got distracted that's a new show
we put in our show actually wasn't even
thinking about it rather all right okay
would you rather well you ready did one
you can do as many as you want
David you do one you do one David I was
trying to think of one by couldn't I
wasn't thinking this whole time I forgot
yeah I came up with one but I couldn't
come up with the other maybe we can come
up with the other okay
say would you rather have eight wives in
your king-size bed with you every night
when you go to bed Oh eight wives for
the rest of your life every night okay
or blank what so I'm telling you right
now I don't even need the other one I
don't want that many people in my bed
that's what my that's you know a lot it
would be the rather well why don't why
don't you make it worse than one just
just say eight other dudes eight why
don't know but that's more depends what
the other is or
the other dudes yeah three dogs in a
twin oh my your bed in your bed all
right out of the dogs big dogs you know
but that's a king-size bed number eight
people you know how many eight people is
like that's how about how about five how
about four Great Danes in a set of twins
and a set of twins yeah babies that will
always be babies the rest of their lives
this is the one of the weirdest yes you
got a choose button they're both bad
probably take the dogs and babies find
six great day oh my god you can't keep
changing it fine six great think because
it's too easy for you two to come up
with that six great gains in a spare
twin so we heard and two puppies have to
take care of the babies no just in your
there just in your bed okay they live
they this office is raining there always
do they cry of course they cry their
babies okay then I'm going back to the
wives
me too crying babies and what kind of
wives are they like really nice or they
like they're just sleeping oh that's so
just the new idea I'd stack them in a
pyramid some of them would be snoring
some of them it's fine better than
crying I have Bo I would stack them in a
pyramid shape and they're all 500 pounds
and you just keep changing it down let's
have a really nice bed frame I know it's
true that's true yeah I got a disgusting
one all right go who would you rather
eat a sandwich mm-hmm that the meat in
it is dog poop oh yeah or or you have to
eat a rot in like a super expired taco
like that the meat is all disgusting and
moldy and like the lettuce and the
cheese is all like super old I mean
that's a mean scientifically there is
both just filled with bacteria yeah
organisms mm-hmm science that can
definitely damage your body and
potentially kill you but you have to
pick one it's a mental thing at this
point
they're both disgusting I would go to
the taco
I go to talk with you this is I know it
came from food it wasn't yeah okay
you're gonna get sick either way but you
know what I think the poop would just
try out you're gonna try the poop even
though you don't know but yeah it would
be dry versus like all's grind spory
yeah you gotta think she's kind of in
the sandwich yeah only one ingredient is
disgusting which is what doc boom all
right everything else is a fresh bread
fresh there's lettuce and tomato fresh
cheese yes a sandwich a simple disaster
yeah mustard Dijon yeah regular whatever
you want can I put it how big is the
piece poop it's like it's much like you
know if you take a piece of roast beef
yeah it would be like a couple pieces or
maybe like a short ride this is exactly
why we have more megameters dry or it
can be wet oh gosh so it's better if you
went to Subway that only served ugh it's
okay to be cleared dog poop and not cat
poop because cat poop is has a crazy
like dog poop salary stench to it okay
from experience of smelling dog poop
sandwich you know what I might take the
dog poop because I I know that with food
that has spoiled yeah
it's extremely dangerous and you could
die from like salmonella poisoning
really yeah you could die you know if
you know any a food poisoning yeah
that's just from eating like a little
bit of like young guy but imagine if it
was sitting there for like you're still
on the year spoiled taco yep
rather die dude rather enjoy that
sandwich there's that game and that was
I like that game
it'll get better as we get better at it
yeah well next time we'll be prepared
for it we're new is using thinking about
new be podcast trips well I was trying
to think of it but it is a tough part is
keeping it clean mm-hmm but maybe it
doesn't have to we can do we can do
clean ones that are interesting why
don't you do a vote what do you think
people would say keep it clean or keep
it keep it dirty I think it's a dirty
they would but it's but like what's the
point if everything gets like
age-restricted injury sponsor this is
what this is what that is well that as
well but that's not even the issue is
the age restriction yeah it's YouTube's
got into this place
mmm we always end up oh yeah it always
see the fact that we are even talking
about this
shows what's wrong with you - that's
deep right it is it's true though
because yeah I never used to feel like
this even writing anything like I was
always clean yeah like consciously but
like I never felt like I couldn't be
yourself yeah where it's like and they
promote the whole be yourself thing they
do promote that but it's like okay well
be yourself would be the the self that
we want exactly yeah the fact that it's
so that's is even that it's exhausting
to talk about shows you there's a
problem with it yeah there's no way we
could do that would you rather as we did
last night without
me there's no way yeah yeah what's new
we you need a new platform so do we want
to talk about YouTube not really do you
want to talk about you - we can talk
about it but I don't want to buy you -
everybody's always just complaining you
- I'm American they forced us to hide
their nose it you know what I tried
deleting it from my phone you can't but
every time I go I turn on my bluetooth
in my car yuichi starts playing and I'm
like this what is this great music
that's playing what is this great music
that's not an epistle actually I'm very
yeah I really don't like the fact that
it's playing like Otto plays and Michael
yeah it's I don't know what you do it's
upsetting stop using Apple yeah anyway
products yeah just shows everyone is
biased and they have their own agendas
to push myself you're just talking about
like the whole Apple thing the other day
and like we were comparing like the
sides of like you can see it from
Apple's perspective or like we were
talking about how we'll see yeah and
also how it they I think they tried to
like literally stop the market of
third-party repairs and they like they
would like sue these other small
companies that were doing that and I
know there's a youtuber online that like
shows all the information of like he
takes apart Apple products and says like
they were gonna charge you $600 for this
it literally cost $2 and this is how you
do it and they were trying to take it
down mm-hmm but on the flip side with
the other argument is that because Apple
is you know they want to control your
experience right which is good and a bad
thing right it's it's positive because
they they maintain a very high quality
level of service product design all
these things and they want people to
join their world and say hey we have
this amazing experience that you can
have going to the Apple Genius Bar these
products are 100% you know tested in our
facilities right with our highest
quality of standards whereas these third
parties may take a shortcut they may you
know find the same part in China that's
you know super cheap but on the other
side not everyone can afford these
ridiculous prices
yeah I was a repair so I can see kind of
both sides mm-hmm right you know what do
you think about that no I just we were
talking about the other day oh really
like off like somewhere I mean I get it
nicely politicize too
yeah but I mean I just no matter what
yeah I think no matter what though like
with anything not just Apple YouTube
everything no you can't satisfy everyone
yeah and the thing is most people don't
think in the same way where we're
thinking from their perspective and like
if you were to from a business person's
perspective but put yourself in their
shoes if you're starting a business or
you're doing things a certain way
I mean if you really believe you know
what's best and start your own business
goal rival Apple if you know that much
yeah I think that's I mean you can
complain as much as we want about
YouTube and stuff but if they're not
willing to change that's why I've
stopped trying to change there's no way
you can change you too they're too big
right so if they want to make it this
way you have to adjust it sucks but the
only way we can show we can do anything
about it is either people stop using it
cuz it's not good or there's a
competitor right and they're just so big
it's hard to compete with the company
that's generating billions of dollars
they have a monopoly on this system I'm
on both sides I but I I would yeah I get
it certainly for me I'm actually a
little more on the other side as far as
the experience mm-hmm because I mean
first off I am an Apple fanboy but I
also the reason why I am is because I
actually love their products now do they
charge a ton of money for like their
laptops and their phones yes they do it
is more expensive and but they've done
an amazing job of branding in marketing
which is what which is a little bit that
that doesn't hold that much weight
because marketing can mean it's all
about like kind of manipulation right in
a way but I do think that Apple products
like because I guess I come from like
the artistic side right and creative
side like when I see an Apple product
versus anything else for me personally I
see it as like oh wow this is a
beautiful thing like yeah it's clean
it's clean it's consistent and I guess
that aligns with like my
which you somewhat OCD kind of like but
he's oh yeah like even like I think cuz
I for me even just walking around you
know like town square or a mall or
something and you see an Apple store it
just looks so clean yeah and for me I
personally hate the heat something like
that looks so cleaning cold I just want
to go in there you know what hold it
it's not a warm that kind of place it's
not a warm place it's like always leak
very sleek I know it's gonna be cold in
there so that's where I go if it was
always freezing I grew up like if I grew
up in the Arctic then I would probably
go into something that looks more like a
warm home they're like Hollister yeah
even though holidays are really cold but
it looks like a house yeah something
more like bright and I guess I don't
know what's a warm looking store like I
think Hollister is pretty good looks
like a log cabin but it's very dark
though and dark looks cold - that's your
Abercrombie & Fitch that's another
that's the same thing do you mean the
buy warm store I could say orange
brownish yeah yeah yeah that's just a
visual that's a visual my cycle it's
psychology yeah so yeah like going back
to that I just I'm a big fan of it I
know people are gonna disagree me like
no like Samsung's better and whatnot you
know what I've seen Samsung phones are
great mm-hmm actually technology wise
there are a lot more advanced in a lot
of ways right they actually like try to
improve and do all these things but once
you do too much of that it may allow
other people other you know there's too
many ideas in that phone in my opinion
and in just the general direction and is
what what I'm talking about
right I don't you mean hey and and it
gets a little clunky and a little bit
like what so what are you guys exactly
what what are you trying to I know what
you're trying to do but like where's
your identity that's how my mind works
right I think once some of these other
competitors they start branding better
and they have more of a design sense in
terms of like the product and the way
that they package everything together
that's that's a type of thing I have
appreciation for oh yeah I mean I
literally just went through like getting
the Apple watch and so I went through
like the looking through the market and
seemed like what am i other opportunity
or other options I guess yeah and it was
basically just like either do Android
mm-hmm or you do smart walk or the Apple
watch hmm and I will say after I went
and got the Apple watch the packaging
and everything like I opened it I was
like this is pretty sick like just
opening it I was like yeah and they
really control that whole expansion to
detail which is I appreciate like you
said that coming from like an artistic
minds yeah like perspective like even
like on the back side you know they had
like a print on the inside that you
couldn't even see until you open it it
was just very that part was very and
it's consistent with all not just their
watch but like yeah product yeah I sound
like a Apple sales guy right now
would you say that so it's interesting
because and I just thought about this
now but like wouldn't so you're kind of
saying that Samsung is met like in a way
it's Messier and Apple is cleaner right
that's what you're saying kinda to a
certain degree when you look at it I
usually I kind of am right but they're
okay so so I made my point for Apple and
their beauty and all that right the
other side that I think is great about
you know companies like Google and you
know basically Android phones is that
they they push innovation right and and
they actually allow people to kind of
freely be creative and do their own
things as opposed to conforming to what
Apple's brand standards are right right
like so Apple says we built this you
need to build according to this yeah
right mm-hmm the Google kind of mindset
is like hey this is an open field you be
as creative as you want you build
whatever you want and in here you go
my thing is I wish that there was a
company that literally promotes both of
those it's hard but I mean like in a
sense of like it's an open thing but the
experience is still very important and
like the sleek look and something like
that you know I mean I don't I
the problem I have is like it's very
much one or the other you know it's like
red and blue
you know take the red pill or the blue
pill yep she's a red side or the blue
side but I was really excited for
Google's modular phone I don't think
they're do any more pics not the picture
I don't remember what it was but it was
like I remember there was like a very
big buzz about having like a phone where
instead of replacing the phone you
replaced upgraded components almost like
a motherboard in a computer oh I see
yeah and so it would reduce electronic
waste and it would reduce like the
consumers cost because they didn't have
to continually so I was like oh we came
out with a 30 megapixel camera
you know here buy it and then you just
pop it out like a card and you punch it
back in and you essentially just
upgraded your phone to a certain degree
yeah I don't I I see it why you won't
make as much money yeah because you're
not forcing the consumer to buy an
actual phone right the entire thing so
business from a business perspective it
would make no it wouldn't make as much
sense because why would I want to
upgrade it if I'm if I have this right
well yeah I mean I'm not saying it's
gonna make money I was just saying like
for me personally that I'd but it is
cool yeah yeah like that is like an
innovative idea that pushes the industry
you know yeah yeah it does it does which
is why I think some people had like
problems with Apple because I feel like
in the beginning they were very much
like an innovative idea Steve Jobs was
around yeah and now it's just kind of
like like you were saying they've kind
of scaled back to just the experience or
having like this brand that they keep
consistent which is still pretty pretty
cool and it's it is kind of like it is a
slightly more shallow type of thing you
know the branding and all that I mean
it's very important because the branding
it's more of a psychological thing yeah
the actual innovation of Technology I
think you know Android and Google is
that they've done a much better job of
like pushing that yeah and then Apple
just kind of copies what they did right
yeah but they perfect it yeah packaged
it better so so yeah at the end of the
day androids a lot better another thing
is weird too is like when I was thinking
like do I want to switch to Android
mm-hmm
no out because everyone has I phones if
I were the only one that doesn't have
one well in our group yeah like a
message for what we do I think it's
easier but if we all were to switch or
say you were like the minority right
with a iPhone I think it's an easy
switch you mean iPhone to Android no I
think the only reason I'm still getting
iPhones is because it's easier it's got
a everyone already has it cuz they've
created this whole ecosystem they did
yeah that's brilliant yeah and you look
at really you look at iMessage for
example yeah if you text each other I'm
with iMessage I'm on iPhones it's a nice
blue and white or blue and gray kind of
messaging visual but when you message
with anyone outside of Apple you get
this like neon green thing that just
yeah look good it's like kind of ugly
and Android they do it on purpose and
it's color of droid I hate that I think
they do it on purpose I mean yeah it's a
brilliant idea to click like you said an
ecosystem that's a very good word to do
and I hate it yeah I'm in it I'm stuck
in it yeah yeah they got us on a hook
yeah
so they can do things that I hate and I
will still be loyal because I mean not
loyal I have to it's just out of
convenience yeah I like the whole like
when a new phone comes out I don't know
there was a study I don't know if it's
true or not but I personally know for a
fact that always happens like every time
when you phone comes out my phone for
whatever reason I would say the last
four phones consistently get slower and
maybe I think there was a study or
something about it
maybe it's an update they released I
don't know what it is but whenever like
it's not my phone it's not that old
well didn't a police a statement saying
they do slow down older phones they do
they do and the reason being is because
you know because then because with the
new phone right the hardware you have to
release new software right and software
generally gets better right it doesn't
get more slimmed down it gets bulkier
right so when you have a bulky or
software with more features and more
more tools and different you know
powerful phone can't handle it your
phone can't handle it because it's not
as powerful as right
new phone that comes ok so so when you
come out with the new software right you
have an old phone the old phones
Hardware can't keep up with the software
so it disables certain things in the
hardware sure or in the software or vice
versa right that so so it forces you to
but that's my point though like that's
my point like the fact that they're
releasing this every single and there's
not much change they could have you know
for a fact that Apple has so many things
that they're currently working on that's
not gonna be in the in the next phone
yeah I think they hold stuff back and
they're doing it because they want to
release more phones because they know
that you have to get the next one
because your phone is gonna slow down
and can't handle it when they could have
easily done something that they could
have released a version that could
handle the next update if not then why
don't they have somebody thinking about
that like why don't they have somebody
like saying because everybody's
complaining about it there's other
conspiracies about how they're doing
this to your phones yeah like they are
aware of the problem they've already
addressed it I think it's less about
that it's more about its it's like if
you had a restaurant right and then you
decide to change so you had customers
coming for a decade
they're so used to like everything on
the menu and the way that the chairs
feel and then one day they're like ok
you know what from a business
perspective we got to evolve with the
times where people are getting more
sophisticated you know we don't want to
just serve this like this the same
patrons that come into our you know a
restaurant we want the young kids to
come but our place looks old yeah so
bringing in all these new furniture but
you can't really do half in half because
it's just gonna be weird with the
branding and all that but if you if you
have the same you know if you bring in a
bunch of new furniture and make it look
more hip because you want to draw the
audience and the old people you know
they're gonna complain because it's not
as a hip and forward-thinking so that's
that's the difference though this is not
like when you're going into this
restaurant for the old people mm-hmm
like they're not they're not allowed to
like you can still go there for free
mmm like you're not being forced to do
something that you don't want to do yeah
like it's not like the it's it's not
like you're destroying that restaurant
you have my analogy is and then making
you pay for another play
yeah but like their what they're doing
is they're saying like hey you bought
this from us right yeah no no it doesn't
work the same way yeah but you have to
upgrade you can't not upgrade right
eventually it makes you upgrade yeah if
they were to let you just let your form
work the way it is like it my my phone
worked the way it did yeah
like how I bought it and how it was
intended to work mm-hmm I don't care let
me you can have the coolest stuff the
next one I'll get the next one after
that maybe yeah but the fact that
they're making you get this product the
next product because they ruin your
other your previous product but they're
not really is a response but they're not
really making you fit whether or not
they are making you because they're
there if it switch to Android well
that's what I mean but like out of
convene it's it's messed that's why I'm
saying it's messed up but like I didn't
I have to stay with they're
intentionally making the product you
bought like obsolete so that you have to
say no I don't I don't think it's that
no no that's what you're saying like I
don't mean if it's not even if it's not
intentional they're not they don't care
because about their you know they're
because her in does he care about moving
consumers they care about improving
technology they care about not being
stuck in the past but like moving on to
better and newer things because that's
what their job is right but it's you
know they're doing it on purpose because
like you said I mean yeah considering
you're developing an app you know that
when they put an update yeah they are
forcing other people who have apps to
conform to their update yeah so because
you suck it could be just as simple to
help to fix Ryan's problem would be if
you have a phone that's let's say the
six it caps at a certain update so that
then when you don't upgrade into the
next software to mess up your phone so
you could say like well you could buy a
six but it only goes up to software XYZ
right and so it won't it won't get
messed up but usually few features of
the new one so they do they do do that
within the software itself they have to
but I guess I mean I'm not an engineer
but from what I understand is if you
create how do I explain this so if you
create a new software update it's
addressing certain bugs but it's also
helping the new phone it's a it's a
software that fits into the hardware of
the new phones that come out right right
new and better better better and faster
and more powerful right an overall
update it's an overall update now for
Apple to spend their resources and their
engineering power on creating and they
do already have this they have an iPhone
16 right now right for all the iPhones
right even though we're on iPhone 10
right but then how long are they gonna
keep this going and have people fix bugs
that are still appearing in time from
six they want to move on to the next
phones they want to get it more so what
you're saying is Wendy so the bugs that
they're fixing right and like on the
iPhone which are always there yeah yeah
they're always there but like if you're
satisfied with how your phone is when
you buy it yeah which you know if it can
run that way can they maintain that that
current farm even with the bugs that are
currently there but that's what you
bought like that's what the phone is
that's fine so the thing with the
convenient een so here's the thing so
from Apple's perspective why would they
put spend millions and millions of
dollars more into a software into a team
that just cares about that's what I'm
asking because they need an
accessibility because they don't make up
money then they would they need another
team they need another so then that's
then that's what I'm saying yeah it
makes no sense financial then what they
should do is I mean I guess it then it
becomes this point is at what point like
is there really if they really wanted to
so by this logic why not just release a
new phone every month and force you to
why a new phone they do health software
but not know but why not just a new
phone every month and you'd force it's
too expensive exactly but for a lot of
people it's too expensive already
because of how frequently they're
releasing phones and that's the point
they need to make something that and
this is only I mean you don't have to do
whatever they want yeah but I'm saying
like the more this happens and the more
frequently this happens the more I'm
gonna try and compete the campaign yeah
until people like I'm ready to switch
I'm until all my friends and then as far
as Apple's perspective is if they don't
release phones at this rate yeah then
they have to lay people off yeah which
is fine like this
if that's the way they're gonna yeah if
that's the way they're gonna be like
their company yeah I get it like I
understand it but that's just how it
works like if you people can't afford it
and it keeps coming out like we're
fortunate that we can afford it but if
it keeps coming out what's stopping them
from going every single month and the
next time the next month it comes out
your phone starts getting slower after
that your phone gets even slower than
that like there's nothing stopping them
other than it's not a good idea now it's
it's like you know I'll go back to the
restaurant analogy let's say you're max
max capacity every night right and you
hire people and then you're you've hired
enough people to to have a good business
right it comes down to capitalism right
do you want to create more jobs for
people
mm-hmm right if you're at the top of
this restaurant in your max capacity
every night and you're you make a
certain amount of money right it's like
should this company be able to open
you're not worried they're not worried
about other people they're worried about
themselves no that's what I mean yeah
they're not worried about people losing
their jobs um trust they're not worried
about it don't worry but it would happen
no because if you really were worried
about and you weren't being selfish what
you would do is what you exactly what
you said you create another team right
it cost them more money yeah but it'll
keep their people happy people like me
and will that will have the oath not
just me and will but like I'm saying
like for this is my example yeah yeah
they would create another team which
creates more jobs cost them more money
right but it's like are they the ones
they're gonna lose money but they're
people are hacked their customers are
happier I think this goes into a much
deeper conversation about capitalism so
like let's say you have this restaurant
right and you were doing your making um
ten million dollars a year right they
could open another restaurant another
chain and open another one and then they
can open a franchise and become the next
in and out the next chick-fil-a the next
whatever that depends on their goal now
with this phone company do they want to
just be a mom-and-pop like phone shop or
do they want to compete with Samsung and
all these other companies do they want
to change the world sure they want to
have influence over a country do they
want to influence around the world and
who doesn't want and be in and kind of
have you know create create this like
brand that's rep
since America and American goods right
that gives you influence and power over
all the other countries in terms of
Technology you want to be a leader in
that you can't be a leader if you don't
expand and if you don't expand you're
not generating more revenue of course
and you can't you will never have that
that sort of it's a balancing act yeah
but what I'm saying is and they're
getting to the point where I think
they're not gonna generate more revenue
they can't they're done right now
actually so as far as phones mm-hmm most
people in the they've already kind of
like maxed out the number of people who
can buy phones from Apple because
everyone has iPhones but I mean like
there's always gonna be kids and people
growing like there's populations
increasingly yeah yeah but not not at
the rate where it's like what's worth it
that's why right now they're focusing on
software upgrades as opposed to hardware
right right because everybody already
has an iPhone so you're like how often
you know but you just sit like oh I
guess if they're at the maximum like the
perfect device which doesn't exist then
that one can handle the most updates
like the because you're not building new
phones yeah I have to build a new phone
it's because they have updates that
can't be handled there's there's a rest
of things so are they done making new
phones I don't think they are
oh no no no they're never done making
new phones but yeah but they're having
like within the latest iPhone that came
out yeah you had the least amount of
buzz because everyone has an iPhone like
I'll wait it out for the next next next
next right cuz I'm happy wait wait you
can't though because when the next one
comes out your phone's not gonna stop
working once you update yeah I think
that's what I'm saying that's um I would
say this is somewhat of a simple
solution but it's kind of like a
compromise between them having a team
and the team moving on or whatever it
may be
yeah but when they have a phone in the
beginning when you buy a brand new phone
it has bugs and people are like yeah fix
this fix this and then in like a year
later maybe two years later it gets to a
point where it works good and you want
to keep it the exact way it is even if
it has like maybe one bug here it's very
solid doable yeah yeah there's a problem
when it switches over to the new phone
that everyone complains again or says
screw it I'm gonna buy a new phone there
needs to be a way to like solidify so
so in that zone that phone will not slow
down if you don't upgrade - OH - what my
knots really buggy
I don't even update that when you don't
update 100% that's all we're talking
about actually okay there's something to
be said about that that's probably true
in some ways yeah because at that point
Apple is already invested in improving
their overall system the backend not
necessary that one update yeah iPhone 6
software but the entire back-end
infrastructure because they need to grow
right to make better things they may
know AR as a future and they need to
build and hoarding Lea now that doesn't
make sense maybe it does slow down a
little bit yeah yeah but that's the
problem is for the consumers like I see
where Ryan well Ryan says about if I buy
a phone at this one point and it's
working up to the standards that you as
a consumer want it - mm-hmm
it's kind of like I would say again the
word I'm using a slimy that the company
isn't really like doing something
actively for that for that specific
problem right and the reason is you know
it's money they want you to essentially
it's not as you can't argue against it
the earlier you don't upgrade your phone
it's just not a priority well they
should just disclose yeah hey this phone
only lasts a year until it starts
slowing down you know what that the same
problem it's the same exact problem that
every phone company has whether your
Apple or Android Samsung it's the same
thing it Apple just gets that that sort
of you know well I don't I don't know
that because yeah it's no it is because
that's how software I can't even say
that agree with that because I don't
know yeah I don't yeah I'm speaking from
personal experience because there's no
there was no release telling us this
until recently right and I always
suspect it I always I called it out in
videos a long time ago and then this
article came out within the last I don't
know year or so yeah cuz some heart did
some Harvard study or something like
that but I when that came out I was not
I was shocked even though I knew it was
happening I just didn't know that's just
a conspiracy I'm just it's in my head
like yeah yeah you know but it makes
sense cuz I'm like man I have to spend
money again I just got this could I I
don't get phone when they just come out
yeah yeah I mean I just got I forget
when it was and could have been the five
or six it just like it just came out
like well I'm standing and then two
months later next week and my phone
stopped working because for me there's
no excuse that this phone that's one
soul should stop working for that price
yeah well that's that's a different
that's it probably the phone itself but
like for example I'm honest I've known
seven okay my phone works completely
fine and are now yes update for now so
for me I'm like I know some people have
that problem of where their slows down a
lot yeah
but why not me maybe maybe just for your
phone I don't know see so that's why
maybe it's not maybe it is but it's just
in your not slowing down it's not really
it's fast enough for me too
so then what we're saying that it's not
then it is just they have faulty
products like a lot of it could be that
it could be that because most people I
know agree with what we're talking about
mine what really creeped me out was mine
only started messing up I mean this is
gonna sound like huge conspiracy yeah
mine only started like getting really
glitchy when they started having new
releases and I was watching videos on
the new phones and radix and that's when
I was like this is weird but that's
there is like I mean there's already
talked about that with whole like Alexa
and that's Amazon and yeah Google home
and there's already like things again
and your phone there's that Sunspear see
and it's and it's been proven and I'm
people have tested it yeah like not
simple like slow down I'm talking like I
would type I'd be typing that's
Facebook's thing and it wouldn't type
and then it would go that's what I had
anyone like and they would type like
really fast yeah it would and it would
like interesting and there was otherwise
just didn't work I never had that
problem and I try to push the off let
that sleep button and it wouldn't do it
and then like two minutes later it would
go to sleep and then come up again I've
had that I've had that one yeah it was
only after I started and then I started
thinking it was like how sick would it
be I mean this is gonna be really
concerned if they did on purpose if
there's a team yeah at Google that of
saw 15 Apple I mean excuse me at Apple
that are in charge of writing code to
bug your phone like that would be I mean
I honestly make you sick honestly I
would not even if I heard that now be
like man that's messed up but like
they've already been doing it
in my head like I know like I mean until
there's a better I don't think they have
teams that do that in my opinion I don't
think either horrible press really like
right but I mean there are some
conspiracy
obviously never gonna get caught what I
will secret but I will say that that
they are aware yeah of what that would
do and maybe there are some problems
that all I know is that when Steve Jobs
was around my phone was amazing
everything was great about it I would
say I I would agree with that after he
was a lot better it just Tim I don't
know if Tim Cook is right you know yeah
he wasn't the visionary he was I don't
know I mean I I just know my own
personal experiences yeah I don't know
like that Ike Ike for all I know I could
be talking about of my whole maybe necks
on Holly uh maybe the next upgrades we
have to switch to Android together to
experience it maybe but that's that's
the thing I would have to convince all
of you guys and my phones I do it unless
like me give me like two or three years
on this let's watch yeah and then you
like your watch right I love it until
they release the next one yeah this is
the most brand-new one and I was like
okay this has about maybe two years
right which is sad conspiracy wait so
like okay like would you guys want to
keep the same exact phone for how long
like until you get tired of it and you
want to improve generally because you're
not because you're forced but alright
your own preference I think when it
would naturally break down or in turn
there's features where I feel like holy
crap that's so awesome I'm gonna upgrade
yeah saying normally the the phone one
phone away is not big enough maybe like
two three phones away is a holy crap I
need to get anything like use for
universe I would say how about three to
three to five three or five because like
the phone should still work and I know
they used to work that long before yeah
why all of a sudden after like see this
is all I know it's not the phone when I
got my last phone like I said I got it
late I think it was the five I got the
five really late and they were just had
released the six like two months later
that's what my phone start getting super
buggy a brand new phone and you know
it's not the phone honest it's just that
one and it's unfortunate it worked
perfectly right when that other one came
out
I don't remember if I updated right away
or not I probably I probably updated it
I probably just did it
it got so bad everything was like what
will is talking about I think it was the
five going to the six it also be the six
going to the seven but regardless I was
like okay well I know for a fact because
I used to think okay maybe the phones
just kind of you know maybe they
overheat over like a year and then I
kind of break down but that wasn't the
case I was a brand if it was a brand new
two months in brand new phone same with
what they were talking about with the
battery life did you hear that someone
tried to sue them so now they have to
like if your phone dies in the first
like one of my my cousin actually had to
do this her phone basically you in like
a couple hours we'll go from a hundred
percent to like 20 percent brand-new
it's like the new I fo she's got a bad
battery yeah so so now they're because
they're getting sued not you can go to
any Apple store and tell them matter
yeah yeah you can get a free chain but
like no one had know one thing you got
to do it before the end of this
something something like that but I
think if had no one tried to sue them do
you think they would offer that probably
not of course not because they don't
care about like oh because it wasn't a
big deal to them because no one really
don't know I'm late as much yeah because
people thought like oh maybe it's just
like I'm using it and my phone's getting
old that's what I used to say but then I
realized that's not that's not how the
phones they don't they don't die that
fast right
only when the next ones coming up yeah
and that's only for one reason to make
more money to make you buy it the next
thing and that's why I think is messed
up
I think there's more than just that I
think it's more than just money I think
it's about influence it's about power
it's like if this if Apple didn't have
power it wasn't one of its power yes I
formed them so the way that I see it is
if if it wasn't Apple yeah it's gonna be
someone else and don't watch that what
it does what is the leader in in phones
in soft wind phone technology right so
it's if it's gonna be so I want someone
else to do that then I want someone to
have more influence because everybody
needs a competitor yeah or else things
become for me kind of a monopoly yeah
absolutely and for me it's like you know
who would I want to be bigger as a hi
murder I know I keep talking about food
Ferb's love looks like I don't mind that
in and out yeah is massive okay I
wouldn't mind actually if they took over
the world because I just like me into no
no but what if like when I want them to
take over there's a difference what if
they do take over the hamburger industry
yeah and I would be fine because much no
but they have a high standard say they
double a triple their prices yeah you
would still support them no no no no of
course not exactly it's the same thing
but I know that they have higher
standard of hamburgers than like they do
when like a McDonald's sure but let's
say McDonald's kept their prices do you
think they'd be able to take back in and
out if in and out is Apple in my eyes
McDonald's is Android yeah okay no okay
well let's say for example right yeah I
think so for me in and out just uses
higher quality you're just doing an
analogy yeah it's just okay so just as
in the example yeah what I'm saying is
if they were a trip with their prices
because they can cuz they know how good
they are and let's say they're doing
better than McDonald's
yes significantly so they have such a
huge fan base Apple right and they
tripled their prices mm-hmm right or
they kept raising it more and more and
more how what is that what Apple's doing
though that in a way they are because
they are making you buy and you they're
increasing the revenue they're becoming
more powerful sure right so at what
point do all these in and out fancy you
know what this is a great product but
screw these guys are greedy hmm you know
OB is in a big new hamburgers they're
all great I you got a stay there cuz
they're so good but at what point is
maybe they need depending - I need
another company another competitor came
around and they're almost as good bond
there's something yeah one-third the
price that's great why wouldn't you
support all of course but that doesn't
that's just right now that's what I'm
saying we need that in a no is not Apple
no in and out if you are looking in and
out yeah they have kept the same thing
because they know it's good you know
what I mean it's high quality they have
their own farms but they have the cows
they haven't like tried to like get you
to pay for a little little bit more and
they can keep increase enterprise you
know I mean like stereotypically in and
out right you got a picture
in your head as a person as a compliment
I would think it's like some old farmer
guy who's just like wah just been making
the same thing for a hundred years I'm
not gonna change it and I'm gonna charge
you a dollar you know what David was
just using that as his analogy because
he loves it yes yeah yeah and that's
great no and I love McDonald's for their
own reasons yeah but I just know that as
far as the ingredients I think I was
talking more ingredients
yeah quality quality of ingredients with
McDonald's versus in and out is a world
of a difference
sure less processed you know that type
of thing yeah in terms like the yeah
like the raising of the prices and you
know having people like the money part
I'm not the money part see there that's
the difference because there's so many
burger places back in the box whatever
Burger King that they can't afford to do
that the reason why Apple cans because
they have such a stranglehold the weight
the reason why YouTube can do what they
do is because they have a stranglehold
on the market and that's the difference
and that's why I say there needs to be
competition bar is low to fur to create
a hamburger joint versus a phone company
well it's yeah it's yeah there's not
many competitors yeah that's why I was
so excited for like that modular phone
because if you think of like all the
people who are upset like I don't want
to buy a new phone every year it's like
yeah that is kind of a solution yeah
here's like a base processor or a phone
right
you just have to upgrade the parts right
so it is essentially kind of a solution
to that that bubble or whatever in the
market of people who don't want to do
that but I think the only thing about
the modular phone is like you know what
what can you upgrade in that I don't
know I looking at it I just thought it
was like a very cool exciting would yeah
that's a cool idea but it's I like to
execute that because like if your phone
comes let's just say they come to the
screen yeah right and then you have you
can upgrade every other piece but the
screen right then it's kind of like now
I need to get a new screen again well
maybe that's why I think Google stopped
the project or maybe they maybe they
reached a dead end and said like it's
not really feasible right now right
something like the idea is great yeah
concept itself like having something
that on the market that's an alternative
you know it's like yeah like an
attachment yeah and something like that
would be very new and very exciting
almost like a invent reinventing the
smartphone and I do remember you're
right about that phone and like I Oh
still it's like politics right zette as
I get over this even when it's proven
yeah
I'm under the spell me too it's not even
a spell I'm committed because everyone
else is you know does that make sense
I literally have yeah it's a good
product until they update until a new
phone comes on yeah yeah I agree it's
like when you first get it and it's new
even with bugs it's like holy crap the
fact that this is a real thing that
didn't exist ten years ago ten years ago
yeah the iPhone yeah okay well whatever
year you know that I won't even exist at
one point yeah and how far it's gone is
like this is an amazing about 14 years I
think
yeah it's regardless even in the first
iPhone compared to now it's amazing it's
a great brilliant product and maybe they
needed all that all our money to make it
to get it that far get it to that point
yeah maybe maybe maybe that's the only
way they're surviving but I highly
highly doubt that I think they're making
so much money yeah I don't think that's
the problem to create a company like
that it's a a lot of work and it's it is
money to company you know like each
engineer you know they have like I don't
even how many staff they have probably
like hundreds of thousands I'm guessing
obably yeah like one engineer in for AR
yeah it cost like 300 grand a year
yeah right that's like not even
including like health insurance right so
let's say four hundred thousand a year
yeah for one person what if they but
think about it like this
they're they have that many they have to
pay a lot obviously alright but it
that's not the issue like they they're
making money they're making like they
make a ton of my guy at the top is made
Oney the people at Hilltop they all make
a lot exactly like a ridiculous amount
yeah so it's not the issue that they're
like they need to do this to to stay
competitive like they're doing it
because it makes it makes
and money yeah you know it's not about
like because they're not making money
they're dying no they can be making
money but there's a difference between
making money and being greedy that's it
that's another conversation there's some
philosophy in there a lot of philosophy
in that one you know what else is greedy
when you agreed he agreed with me oh oh
because the word greed let me bring it
back to the beginning point yes I said
that because I do you knew we were gonna
be DejaVu I'm starting to feel tingly of
greed holy crap ASMR seat time in space
I'm time in space all this whole podcast
there's no order everything's happening
at the same time did you have the very
first iPhone
I don't think Levi did I think I only
got like the second third I was on I
came in at before I think I was really
late I was a blackberry guy or awesome
dude you like the buttons you could text
without looking yeah I like those and
you know else you could do is play that
little ball game where you bounce it off
the walls and break all the things pong
pong no you break like the block brick
breaker yeah that see you don't even
know dude Rick Baker was you know kids
don't even know did you why does an
iPhone have to it's like a simple game
yeah they probably do they're starting
to get into the you know software so
they're gonna have a bunch of guys
remember um the little block dude you
know your ti-83 Spidey use your
calculators had that that block dude
game oh like and you would like have to
like solve puzzles you remember that I
don't remember that I never had a TI you
never had ti a tattoo or didn't get into
calculus so I think I don't need it for
account you need it for geometry I only
got up to Algebra one that's a lie such
a lie hey you know if there's people out
there who've got only into algebra one
it's okay
it is okay Einstein didn't even get to
anything he's a nobody he got somewhere
he didn't even know what gravity was
loser
that guy is who is that guy rest in
peace you know I know he dated his
cousin what I'm discussing really I
watch the documentary I think so yeah he
left his wife deformed his cousin or
something like that
yeah wait I heard it was his sister
okay well regardless it's still weird
hey but if you're dating your cousin
it's okay guys yeah I've heard some
stories about people dating their
cousins there's some at what point you
know how like we're like it's okay that
we're saying this yeah like well that's
weird
at what point is PC culture gonna reach
that you know I mean do you know I mean
cuz that's kind of the route you know
what you know before you could be like
oh and not that I'm saying this but back
in the day they power like try think of
a good example like being gay was so
wrong and now if you were to say oh
that's weird you would get so much flak
for it yeah I mean but then I yeah so
what if in the future it's like dude
they love is love dude like if you want
to love your sister and cousin like how
dare you say it's weird you know what at
what point does it stop because it might
not it won't I don't think it will
what you don't think about what I think
it's okay I think it's okay if a guy
loves your sister I think so too
I don't know except yeah I don't think
it's acceptable it's not except on and
there's also health reasons for that I
think if you have kids I don't like it
there you know but there's also health
reasons for a lot of things I don't
think so either but I'm just saying it
might we don't know it nobody thought it
was gonna be at a time when everybody
was like you know what there shouldn't
be any laws against it if people want to
yeah but like at what point is it but
how is that dangerous to society or in
menace I don't know I don't get the kid
maybe there's more complications I guess
you don't think just because people want
to do it there shouldn't be laws against
it no with with it with your system
siblings siblings sibling love so in
assessed instances illegal yeah it is
right mm-hmm
it's just it's not just like that's
weird and gross
I don't it's legal should it be illegal
or I think it shouldn't be illegal as
long as you don't have kids because
there's complications there if we're
getting into politics about it oh you
always fall takes me out yeah but do you
know what I'm saying though right like
at what point the freedom does it stop
if you want to if you want to marry your
cow you should be able to seed so that
so there's our you miss there too but
like I think it's cute your
you're late I get to that point where
who's to determine what love is
no but I'm but that's what we're art
that's what we're saying yeah so I'm I'm
saying it's okay okay so you're already
at that point I'm already there yeah we
got legal paper so you think you're
you're taking like a libertarian side
where the government should not regulate
personal right like love interest or
like laws know what love we're already
we already have that but but the
argument there is that people when you
get married there's benefits oh you're
talking about the benefits part no but
no but I that's what I'm saying that's
why you should or that's the argument
for like why people don't want to allow
gay marriage or you know if gay if gay
transsexual lesbian whatever else yes
I'm missing if any of those people can
benefit from from these laws because
because what defines that is love their
definition of love Yeah right right
so if love is what it is if I love my
dog but it's also consider them it's not
considered maybe not my dog if I have a
like brother or sister whatever right if
that if that relationship is based off
of old quote unquote love right yeah but
how same exact it's different with a dog
because a dog can't reciprocate okay so
your sister like incest yeah like yeah
your sister yeah that I get that
perspective I just haven't thought about
that much I don't think about it either
I don't want to know but I know what
you're saying disgusts me to think about
it I know but so we're allowed to see
that right now if they see this in like
20 years when it's allowed maybe what
I'm saying yeah I mean we're gonna be
we're bigots know so what I'm saying it
disgusts me personally yeah but other
people that's what I'm saying but back
then 20 years ago it was disgusting
people to be gay like I don't want to
kiss a dude I know you don't straight I
know you don't you guys to want to kiss
a dude for myself
yeah and that's okay I don't judge if to
the other guys wanna do it that's fine
your think what I'm saying you're not
even allowed to say that anymore so you
what what I just said yeah I just said
it
no you're not about to just you're
disgusting like that's disgusting you're
not allowed to say that you were oh no
what I don't even like it when two
couples we're allowed to kiss in front
of me I don't
like that right now I know sure well
we're we're allowed to say right now
here what we're pushing down a slippery
slope no but I'm saying this is that's I
it's interesting someone it is it is
we're allowed right not to say oh my
gosh that guy and girl brother and
sister are in love and they're hooking
up that is weird I had that is
disgusting I think it's disgusting I
think it's fine to say that because I
feel that I know but I'm just saying why
myself doing that my soul but I'm just
saying we're allowed socially to say it
yeah yes we are we are you say like oh
my gosh you saw the news like this this
mom was dating her 30-something your own
son okay that's disgusting I know but
you can't you can say that yeah if you
see two people who write no matter what
you believe I yeah I think anyone should
be able to say anything they want yeah
as long as it doesn't incite I know but
I'm like paying a Wiley point or you're
like you know I don't know I just
he said no offence and he was talking
about people who are in like who are in
no no offense no that's what I'm saying
it's my free speech yeah but as far as
what other people do in their lives it's
none of my business I agree with that
there's a wall right there but I agree
with between me and that same like like
a sister something like you know like
that's off limits right first like I'll
take it to the crazy extreme for for
human beings that have sexual relations
with animals which does exist yeah like
you know bestiality I don't watch that
stuff never even actually even seen one
sure but I know it exists right because
people told me yeah and it's illegal Who
am I to say though that like what that
person does and feels what if they
really feel in love like maybe there's
psychologically a little bit strange
from my perspective but if they are
actually super in love sexually with a
monkey and the monkey maybe feels the
same way
honey that's the thing how do you how do
you know that the monkey could that's
okay fine let's let's take you
brother-sister relationship yeah brother
and sister sexuality and love and
romantic and I would never do that
let me put that out there and no offense
no offense anyone like for voice no but
it is offensive to them but it's in
society it's not offense okay because we
all agree that it's disgusting right but
there are until that there are people
who are okay with that there's very
there's less and I'm sure they do exist
but what I'm saying all this up is like
what where do we draw the line because
we used to draw the lines in different
places so right now this same podcast
video in let not even maybe like 20
years yeah that's not a lot of time
we'll still be alive
30 years even at what point does this PC
culture make it not okay to say what we
just said that we're gonna be a
considered yeah like just incest phobic
we're bringing incest what you're an SS
phone it sounds like something that's
yeah like it's like yeah of course we
could say that now but you're saying in
10 years because before they thought
being gay was wrong they did yeah they
thought it would like every majority of
people thought it was wrong they felt
that even gay people vote they had to
hide it yeah yeah so that's all I'm
saying is to like let's say 40 50 years
ago or same thing as being black they
thought it was wrong to have that skin
color to be Asian or whatever at some
point yeah so as much as we believe
something right now that incest is
disgusting it is is a very part there's
a possibility right yeah in in 20 30 40
100 years I'm gonna get we're gonna I'm
gonna be in trouble for having said what
I said or everyone in this generation
like wow they were so close-minded right
yeah exactly but that's what I'm saying
that was it stop so I'm progressing I'm
like fast forwarding to 20 years later
and saying right it's I know you do your
thing I know you are I don't want to
participate in it but you do your thing
yeah but not for the animals that's
different unless you can get animal
intelligence level I'm just taking that
the animal thing that's different but
I'm talking about human human
interaction yeah okay but here's the
other argument yeah what about a 17 year
old kid or like a 15 year old and an
adult or a 12 year old and an adult who
consents the government what if at some
point yeah it does but what if at some
point it becomes it becomes that where
it's like okay well who decides how old
you are when you can make choices
conscious choices man it could you never
know it could it could become that
when you could didn't well you know
because we can say I think pedophiles
are disgusting I don't know what age
yeah you know because some people you
can consent when you're 17 years old
that's the 18 right you have to be right
to be allowed to get married or okay
well let's say 16 to get love or to be
macked you would know like you remember
you as a kid maybe you only the smartest
thing but like you could also say that
about your 20 year old self or your 30
year old self like maybe your 40 year
old self would be like my 30 year old
self should have never gotten married he
didn't know better
yeah should we make it illegal for him
to get thirty year olds and under you
get married marriage is a different
thing from what I mean that's just my
best my want that you know what I'm
saying yeah yeah I think no but where do
you where do you stand where do you guys
stand somewhere right I follow the law
yeah but like I think people pedophiles
and some like that like I I think it's
right for it I don't think it I don't
think it's right to that someone up that
age gap so what is that age gap for you
I mean it's whatever to me it's been
defined by what's the law what the last
legal yeah I agree I'm in the same boat
too right that's the only reason why
though yeah but if you really think
about and break it down it's like it's
already weird if like say one one is 18
which is legal and the other one's 50 I
think that's weird I think it's like
we're offending we could offend people
most people society agrees that's
probably weird but then you're also like
a 8 Age Discrimination NIST yeah because
back in the day I'm pretty sure like
back like you know yeah maybe like
during Genghis Khan era or something
right mm-hmm
even further back I'm sure there were
marriages that looked like that yeah I
don't know if the word pedophilia really
do you think it existed I guess the
whole there the cultural thing maybe it
was more of it religiously there was a
set up right like you know what do you
call arranged marriages at certain point
maybe the parents thought okay my child
here my son or daughter is at the age
that I believe who that that can be and
should be married well yeah I mean if
you're talking about a long time ago you
probably would get married and start
being an adult as soon as it's like 13
yeah soon as you get your period when
they're fertile pedophilia and stuff
like that it's probably I would assume
more of a modern term that describes
like predators
right like modern society like the
Predators who are into this thing behind
closed doors and they they try to right
right all right as a as opposed to
having like an arranged yeah which is
which was coming through culture a
little bit something like that sense so
what I'm saying and the whole reason why
I brought it up is like it's not crazy
yeah isn't it crazy to think and this
goes back to like facts right right like
as we know for a fact right now that's
gross
to me I mean I think so but we're doing
it on camera and this will live forever
we know that it's disgusting right now
to people what oh yeah but like I'm just
saying isn't it crazy to think that one
day it might not be to be yes exactly
that's what I that's what I think you
think it won't that is so crazy
most people I would say most people even
people listening probably queer crazy
but like it's true if you really think
about it yeah that many years ago people
thought it was crazy that black people
are on the same level as everyone else
even Asian that's true yeah same thing
with especially gay people yeah it was
illegal and now it's legal yeah so go
back like a 100 I don't know hundred on
my history but how many years and tell
them there's gonna be a black president
this this slave ancestor is gonna be in
charge of all you guys mm-hmm I
guarantee nobody would believe that
nobody be like that's disgusting
yeah but what if what if in the future
we're saying then that pedophile
disgusting you're sick you deserve to be
shot comes normal and then right yeah
this is scary I see what you're saying
yeah it's crazy to think that that could
happen it's not impossible it's not it
cost nothing is impossible because it's
happened yeah it was started off with
gays like being okay like being you know
homophobia was a big deal it was like
wrong to be homophobic like it was it
wasn't and then it slowly we saw the
change grow yeah I don't know about you
but for me and oh yeah yeah like you
could say the FA G you could say that
yeah because I even said in a video back
then and nobody blinked about it
actually when I even said that word it
doesn't bother junior high yeah like it
wasn't it bad it wasn't it wasn't I'd
even tie that with like me neither
I just said because it was like this
person came and then I stopped saying
exactly yeah because we're finding the
rules yeah society right Society yeah
but like even even now like just seeing
the progression of like I guess the most
recent one in our lifetime our
generation is the LGBT like thing but it
wasn't a beauty it was just gay and
lesbians yes and then after that and
when that start movements aren't
happening then transgenders and that's
happening right now all right I think in
I'm talking like law large face yes it's
becoming a very normal and modern thing
and then there's people fighting back
there's always gonna be people
especially because it doesn't go with
like if we would they believe that's why
I'm saying so at what point does it
become not that trying so not time let
me just say I'm not tying this like I'm
not saying a pedophile is a gate like a
gay person yeah yeah yeah your types of
combinations of people and yeah that we
looked at as being wrong and disgusting
yeah and I just thought it was it was
just a weird thought that's why alcohol
that's why for me when you asked me the
incest rule thing and I was like already
fast-forwarding twenty years later
having seen what happened in the past
and saying yeah it should be legal yeah
I know I know what you're saying yeah so
I'm just putting that hat on and yeah
like but you know what actually not
think about it yeah the whole animal
thing bestiality yeah if you really
really know
remember digging ourselves a hole but
I'm just gonna say it if you were
already really yeah it's fine that
rabbits do to hole yeah the rabbit hole
basically if you really if you really
break it down you can get to a point
where people who's to say it might not
get to a point where people are like
okay this guy can consent this animal
can't consent or can't consent but who's
who's to say that we don't get to a
point where you're like well that is
animalist you're being an animal like a
animal for that animal has the right how
do you know I can't make decisions how
do you know that animal doesn't are you
saying it's like a like you know like
being a feminist are you saying like oh
this you're treating this animal is less
than you you think humans are that much
superior that animals can't make
decisions I feel like there's probably a
subculture that's already like that yeah
yeah but what I'm saying is we that's
it's pretty ridiculous yeah
but who knows it happened yeah that's
the crazy thing and in my I mean I think
it will I think you know what I mean the
way the way we're going I don't think it
will I think because I think it's
there's gonna be this we're still riding
this wave of like legalizing and being
accepting of everything but I think
there's gonna be a corner culture that
be like its back to the rules of the old
days yeah and I think it's starting to
already happen cuz of Trump no not no
not just because of Trump I think that's
a that's possible I think it's just
effect of what's happening cuz of Obama
I've been going to extreme exactly I
think I think that's what's with
extremeness
you know with extremeness comes
extremeness right right there's balance
and hopefully yeah it lands somewhere in
the middle yeah there's always there's
always I mean everything in life is a
sine and cosine graph and you know like
even in the three of us I'm sure there's
there would be things that you know just
even on this in this in this tiny room
like there are things that we would
disagree with and there would have to be
that balance in the middle of what we
all agree to yeah but if we bring in one
more person that balance might that that
middle point might need to shift over to
the left or right or whatever right so
else that's just that's the president
human condition that's the president
president is the president
that's the influential people of the
world they shifted which way they want
yeah the majority so that's what Apple
is in tech yep well that got really deep
we started talking about bestiality I
agree definitely agree all right so that
was a nice that was a great while we
really went we went deep to some faraway
places on that one yeah but you know
what that I know that's the kind of this
is what I want this blog has to be its
called off the pill we didn't none of us
took it's not planned it's not planned I
like it like this I know I know this
better to have things planned but I
don't like planning for one sure so too
bad and this is honestly stuff that we
probably would have talked about in the
kitchen we do one minutes later and you
David sometimes yeah even though like
it's gonna sound really weird but we'll
be on FaceTime working
like a song or something yeah and then
we'll end up like looking at my phone
it's like three hours later I was like
what are we talked to we're not even
working on the song did we talk about
it's usually really weird things it's
the same thing we just talked about we
talked about incest all the diversity oh
just kidding just kidding guys this is
actually the first time we talked about
this I think it is the first time yeah
other things we talked about that we
should probably bring up another time it
always starts with what do you think
about bla bla bla bla bla bla or what do
you think
bla bla bla bla and then it's like goes
on forever that's called a TD that's got
off the pill yeah that's a ADHD moment
yeah anyway thank you guys for tuning in
to another off the pill podcast we'll
talk to you on the next pot and you can
hear this podcast on all platforms all
platicas exist in there actually might
be more the next time you listen to this
again because there might be onion
another platform yeah make sure you
follow Ryan Higa at nah that's just what
come what no it's not it's not your
website well find david at david choice
nagas at instagram.com find David Choi
at queena Grannis dot-com just a
different hardness anyway we're going on
too long
thanks David thank you guys David being
here thanks for having me and we will do
our outro ready in three two one
I can't wait to get what if we give
people the tingles right now how dope
would that be you know what what's that
why'd you do that
pigeon all right that's done bye guys