I've been preparing for zombies for a
while can ghosts be racist I'm pretty
time five just test everybody test first
testing test tests good tests testicles
testicles by P claps yeah get started
okay let's get right back to it but
before we do that welcome back to
another episode of auth appeal podcast
we have very special guest he's not
really special
no I was gonna say we're gonna will and
Greg but wills always here Greg is the
special guest today yes come on okay
well okay normally he's he puts the clap
he was you know that's that's what he
gets because of you you weren't prepared
plague
say my name London will is also good
yeah okay I just wanted to get the intro
all the way because what are you talking
about waiting me introduce me know
that's why does he get that thing no I
don't know are you yeah it was supposed
to be for me I just didn't get the seed
yeah I don't get my decisions here set
this whole thing up for you guys and you
guys ruined it all yeah well you know
what that is this is what you guys do
and when I'm not around yeah this is
yeah Paco pretty much just takes the
good job I need to add I wanted to do a
person to do things we could add yeah
that would be nice and put it next to
you the surprise I think we should be
discussing outside of the pocket people
are gonna be like and we need a new
table yeah in this complaining hour
right now we're just gonna whine about
all right to work in progress it is yeah
okay so Greg's never been you weren't
even on it when we first started I never
even watched these things yeah it's too
long anyway the reason why Greg is never
has never been on a podcast is most of
the time Greg is editing oh yeah pretty
much all the time that's the only reason
why and if he's on here he's not editing
he's not editing we're probably gonna be
an additional an additional week behind
so that's true but then but then this
week I think we're gonna make it work
yeah no mmm well will said no but he's
doing editing this one but that's always
a tough far with these podcasts because
we're not gonna miss a week so like I I
don't know if we should talk about the
video that we're about to put out cuz I
don't know if it's gonna be out yet just
like the Valentine's Day :
well it won't it won't mean it needs to
be out it's like the biggest most
largest amount of footage we've had yeah
on one person in a really long time yeah
it needs to be out oh you mean this last
video yeah the video coming out yeah no
I mean we can talk about it like tape I
mean we pretty much exposed the Ardon
thing before the video came out which
kind of made the video not make sense
but it's the worst intro ever it is
we're not talking about anything now on
that is complaining oh yeah where's the
one wearing give me some
yeah we decided to do a four-person
podcast today don't worry we're gonna
get a Dana Yin at some point we wanted
to keep Greg and Dana separate though
they're not the same person hey they're
not like twins we're there the same /
I'm just kidding we get that all that
wins that we're related you're twins you
see that you're related yeah actually
well know what I don't see that at all I
mean because of racism yeah they're both
short Dana it's pretty hairy just jump
into some of these stands what kind of
topics we guys I want to try and do
something different this week we didn't
really get to do it you said last week
yeah but we jumped in it with Ian that's
why but I want to try and do something
where like you know at the start of the
podcast just to get it rolling a little
bit better since our second half is
always better I wanted to try and see if
we could start off like with what made
you laugh the hardest most recent cuz
then you kind of get the giggles going
and then you kind of get into
storytelling mode and you're ready to
just alright you start then all right
idea definitely get alright well that's
life the funniest thing to me this week
was interacting with Ryan's dad because
at the last video we're outside and it
was really cold for us at least and it
was outside it was in the 40s but for
Ryan's dad he's from Hawaii which is a
lot warmer so we were like he asked oh
what's the temperature and we're like oh
it's it's about like 40 degrees and he's
like what no it's not and then we pulled
out a phone and showed him 40 degrees
and he goes yeah but that was in your
pocket so it's probably warmer in there
and we all started dying cuz he thought
it was a thermometer and it was the
greatest it was the greatest thing well
you have to understand he has a flip
phone still doesn't know how to answer
calls he knows how to send calls which
is a huge upgrade over the past couple
years he doesn't he doesn't answer any
of my calls or
my mom's and he yeah I mean that he only
can make calls I don't know why he
doesn't answer it yeah
just outside you saw me uh what the SD
cards for the cameras and he was like
what is that and I was like oh this is
like this before the cameras this is
what we film on this is a film he said
no I didn't hear this story yeah I'm
pretty sure he is did not understand
technology at all like he probably
couldn't turn on a computer I can't
actually probably I would like to see it
well it's he's a rare breed that of
people who don't understand technology
that's whatever how about you guys what
is something that made you laugh really
hard recently no honestly depressing
week for me nobody laughs here yeah I
mean I wish you would have told us your
asses like you were really prepared or
we aren't yeah you think I want to try
something new that I thought I've been
prepared yeah but uh yeah you guys feel
good on the spot no I have nothing that
I can think of right now that is the
thing that I like that is yeah but then
that again that leads us right back to
what we are not sure we're gonna talk
about which I think we can let's just
say it go for it yes
it probably will be out right we'll know
it'll be out so we did a ryan tries
ghost hunting video and it's kind of
based off of and inspired by Ghost
Adventures
I just always wanted to do that I don't
know if you guys actually I didn't ask
you guys what you guys believe in ghosts
we talked about are we talking about
before or after our experience no I mean
okay before and after has it changed you
do you believe in ghosts it's changed a
little bit for me I would say how so
from the video from this last video from
the last video yeah because you know
like for Mia I don't have any hard
evidence that they did exist I don't
have any hard evidence that they didn't
exist I don't know what yeah and so I
just like I was just going into it with
an open mind like we'll see what happens
you know so you didn't really I know you
don't have evidence buyer did you
believe
I was more inclined to be open to the
idea of ghosts after that oh yeah
what Oh was it just like the whole
experience yeah kind of like certain
things that just couldn't be explained
like what that Wow how does that happen
yeah yeah okay I was like I don't know
why I thought you were very like Ghostly
yeah like super believer even before
that yeah yeah I just get scared very
easily but that's me Greg does too I'm a
scaredy cat for sure and that experience
just kind of solidified it for me yeah
that whole thing was just it was I felt
like going into it it was kind of like a
gimmick thing like I thought it was
gonna be just like this cheesy tour that
we take and people were gonna be kind of
like you know overhyping it but man I'm
a firm believer now I'm relieved before
though no extra firm yeah I mean I
always just had it I mean I believe in a
lot of things it's a ghost is you smile
those things that are one of the things
I believe I believe in in and zombies
I've been preparing for zombies for a
while so like seriously I mean you
believe that there's it's a possibility
sure or that they already exist no not
it could already exist but I mean it's a
possibility that they could happen I
guess it's just fun to kind of keep that
in the back of my mind and prepare for
it yeah I guess so
me yeah go ahead I feel like I'm pretty
neutral on it still I feel like last
time we talked about it I feel very much
the same way like I'm not gonna
discredit people from having their own
experiences so that's why I can't really
say like oh they don't exist like I'm
not gonna be like you know Paco had this
experience and say that wasn't real
because obviously it was real to him I
just haven't had like a personal
experience right and and going there at
that tour it was really it was fun like
it was a really awesome experience to
like play with the tools and like get to
all the tools that you see on like those
ghosts exactly
yeah was it called a dick that's go spa
talk ball yeah that was crazy box yeah
all those things it was just like it's
very interesting
yeah they had like five devices that
each one did something different yeah
and it's cool to see what each one did
yeah yeah so I don't know I'm still
maybe I'm like a little bit in leaning a
little bit more towards believing after
that experience because everything adds
up to what you know your all your
experiences let's you know create your
whatever you believe in but for me I
don't know that you never so that you
never had any personal experiences
that's why you're I mean that's cool
yeah yeah I mean I was I wouldn't say
that I was a super skeptic I mean I told
the story already on the other podcast
yeah about my experience so I'm not
gonna go through that again but like I
was you know growing up in Hawaii Sean
and I used to go Sun all the time and we
used to go like all the most haunted
spots everywhere all the legends never
saw anything so I never believed and
then just randomly that one night
happened and I kind of leaned the other
way but I'm even then even before we did
the tour I was still kind of uh
I don't know kind of skeptic right even
when she brought that the other devices
I was like man they could have easily
tampered with this stuff to make it
maybe somebody's like controlling it but
then there was some just some things
like Paco said I I couldn't really
explain this doesn't make sense right so
that was a little freaky I think there's
one experience that we'll had that you
didn't really share with people with the
the box that when it kind of like
glitched out and the battery died yeah
well I mean it's it was one that well I
mean we'll try to put in the video but
it was we never really had like an
ending to that segment really yeah
that's like the scary part because it
just kind of ended and we're all like
wait what just happened yeah like
basically there was like a tool that it
was like a dictionary of words and
somehow like through energy or whatever
the its they think that the ghost can
you know essentially manipulate the
device to pick a certain word it's kind
of a modern-day Ouija board yeah exactly
exactly without you having to spell it
out like they just like text it to you
yeah and so when we were like it just we
were really like into finding this
Ryan was getting like a big meter and
like the device was going off and then
all of a sudden like we hadn't really
had too much activity on this thing this
thing like goes crazy and it put out
like six or seven words and I can only
pick out like two or three but two of
them were Japanese and present and I
immediately thought like okay of course
they're like they're understanding that
we have a lot of Japanese people here
and they're saying that you're Japanese
well to me I instantly thought like made
me think I talk very well this was like
would they be okay with that because
like really it's like a they're from a
completely yeah time no no that's what I
was saying I was like because there was
also before that it was like believe or
like go or not what was it was like it
you're like not in the way there was
something there's other words I really
believe yeah so and then I was thinking
like okay this is okay this place was
built or around in 1913 and you know
that's like around the time when that's
not around the time but let's say these
people you know we're 20 years old or 30
years old and this it's around what
world World War two yeah right well is
that 1949 which is very poor not it was
around then those people could have been
around then and that's when you know the
Japanese bombed Pearl Harbor I mean it
could be some animosity I don't know
yeah I was probably the most Japanese
people in that here's the real question
soundbite you ready can ghosts be racist
shoot I mean for their time make sense
cuz yeah they didn't have PC culture
back then yeah well I mean they probably
had their version of it yes probably
super inappropriate but that's exactly
what I thought like immediately as I saw
I saw it no way hmm
like I really thought about that like if
you know different time yeah there's a
completely different time like would
that affect them how they want in
interact with you know people know it's
kind of crazy it is crazy
so alright well if you guys were ghosts
and you you could select what time era
that you could haunt and where what
would it be
select look correct question I'm Errol
you type that out
no I'm just talking about goes will be
you know so we're trying to keep this
podcast under 60 minutes um yeah I would
probably hunt right now hunt you guys
we're asking that question would you
just start just keep unplugging each
other's mics I don't know we always have
issues when we start podcasts from
whatever reason there might be a ghost
thing one of the Shaun's ghosts like
he's not dead but he just has a ghost or
we just suck at audio equipment yeah
that's really mean dude why would you
say that about Sean what whoa what do
you say you're going too dark you said
something about Sean being dead I like
what nobody hears anyway that actually
could lead to her another topic we want
to bring up is very dark man this is
started off pretty dark how do you how
did you guys feel and hear about the
whole momona thing
oh just hearing that word mmm that was
the name of my brothers cat by the way
yeah when I was in videos normal so we
put up the cap of Momo in the podcast
okay right now it's scary uh anyway um
the first I mean I saw it on my Facebook
Timeline and it's one of the I don't get
scared easily
yeah but I just was scrolling I was just
like what like I thought was one my
friends like they edited their photos or
whatever apparently was this was a
sculpture or something like that art
piece of some sort yeah Japanese art
piece
yeah but it was very I actually felt
weird by it
like I was like I don't want to see this
you don't get scared easily yep but um
it's good art it was a hoax right it was
like reported supposedly supposedly
people believed that it would get
younger kids or audiences to do
dangerous challenges that could lead to
death such as like turning the gas stove
on and then just letting get was Ruffolo
it was reported on that someone in
sacramento raised some lady in
sacramento had a daughter who said that
a Gregan one 6a anyway they she had a
daughter supposedly
that turned on the gas stove because a
YouTube video of Momo told her to do
that personally is like a moment
challenge or something like that I don't
know but it was it was debunked that
that person was making that up
Wow that's crazy it's actually a
challenge huh challenge yeah people were
saying that oh this is such a basically
people were it I feel like it was like
that lady was just like or I don't know
who it was who started it was just like
hey I want like some kind of attention
like I can't believe like somebody you
know what people like to post I can't
believe this is what's wrong with the
world or whatever like those kind of
polls I don't know I I'm Trent a lot of
older people these girls like they'd
like to be outraged
yeah I'll read yeah or something but
that's like that's I mean I when I saw
those like dan that's crazy but like she
does like that could actually happen now
that could start because somebody
created that that whole you know I mean
yeah it's so there's no reported
incidences of like actual things that
happen right not yet not not according
to the Articles that I read or anything
like that
yeah not that I know of that is scary I
think it just it's really a shame too
because it kind of sheds like negative
light a little bit on YouTube in a sense
to people who don't really maybe maybe
someone will never know about this being
a hoax you know like from older
generation wherever and now they have
you know it's kind of giving them
another reason to not I mean that's kind
of what I think when I hear it is like
meant that it I'm glad it's a hoax of
course but it's like it's kind of kind
of unfortunate you know it's kind of
like I don't know do you guys remember
any like hoaxes or stuff when you were a
kid cuz I don't even know if there were
hoaxes or not but I remember as a kid my
mom would constantly get these emails
that would alert her like kids in like
Western us have been getting getting
dealt drugs that are passed off as pop
rocks and then when you eat them like it
can be so strong that children die and
so she would be like you can't eat pop
rocks anymore I never heard of that yeah
so that's why I don't know if those are
ever real or if those are hoaxes seems
like the same kind of thing though yeah
but there was a one thing that isn't a
hoax that sounds like one and it's call
jenkum have you guys ever heard that
right Kinkos Jake oh geez
Jenga jenkem jenkum jumbles
yeah and it's it's a hallucinating drug
where people would pee and poop into a
balloon and then smell it afterwards oh
you get high off of the PM poop smell
something like it like for men's or
something like that and like like that a
porta potty yeah so people go into a
port-a-potty he's gonna start breathing
like this is a hoax to get people to go
into portable and smell poop some people
learn to feet some people aren't SAP in
poop apparently I mean that's all yeah
that's a hundred percent it's that I
remember like actually think about that
so I mean if I'm wrong I'm wrong I mean
don't knock it until you try
no we are not condoning that Duke Duke
moonshine oh my gosh yeah don't try it
is this a joke
in the mid 1990s it was reported to be a
popular street drug amongst Zambian
Street children what does ambien Zambo
do an exam I don't know bone really bad
with yogurt geez well I mean on the Momo
topic that artists kudos to them for
making something so yeah Gary yeah last
time I was scared of a face like that
was probably like uh like The Grudge
face or something like yeah I've been
scared I've been swiped past pictures of
my feet so fast ever since like I was in
high school of your feet my feet Wow
holy cow no but I mean that's that's one
of the reasons why I was like kind of
impressed that you came I mean like I
get I asked you I was like are you
willing to film this ghost-hunting
episode because I know yeah more than
anyone in the group greg is probably the
most afraid of those babies Dana maybe
Dana no I
cuz Dena came with us to watch the
conjuring - Greg what Greg I mean he
wasn't there but I'm sure he would not
have wanted to go watch that Tina did I
don't even like watching the movies you
guys watch like conjuring all that I
said you don't come with us
I hate those movies they're scary
yeah do you think what um I guess it's
because you're a believer I think it's
just like all right so I'm not scared of
like just aam be sand werewolves and
vampires cuz like you can you can fight
those things right but like ghosts and
stuff like they're demons
yeah I'm defenseless eminence I can't do
anything towards them that's why I
thought about like Chucky's like I mean
it was a scary movie it as a kid but
when I got yeah a little toy like if it
kills me I deserve to die but same wait
like the grudge girl I was like dude
this little tour the ring girl I was
like if she crawls it on my TV I was
like thinking like you know like in a
scary movie 3 where she crawled through
the TV and then what's that lady the
black girl on that she starts beating
her ass and I was just like that's
exactly how I think it would go you know
if you died to this little girl
it was decomposed I mean like she's like
she should be able to break you know I
mean like your skin's breaking your
bones probably rotting she probably
smells like that Zimbabwe weird we don't
know things you're also probably doing
judo when you watch out huh you were
probably mean I mean I definitely was
but yeah I was like I see how she would
come at me and I'm already playing home
I'm gonna take her down get behind her
I'd snap her neck Chris is there such
thing as a dude judo chop there's no
such thing as a judo chop actually you
know what if someone's grabbing your
lapel yeah you could chop your hand down
but it's not a real thing that's not
what he says judo chop there's no judo
kick either come on Austin Powers come
on
they done did life is a lie yeah but
anyway I just thought it was um I was
kind of shocked so even at some points
because Greg will go off and get
equipment and you know do things on his
own without anybody else around the
other night when we were filming I was
that you were like just going off on
your own I turned on like when I get
into film mode yeah I just don't even
think anymore just like autopilot yeah I
was just filming so the crazy thing was
when I was filming later on down to
during the day like we just kept having
camera equipment failure like our
batteries kept dying and stuff like that
and that was the stuff that was creeping
me out of broken me out of my you know
my yeah yeah that's like wait all these
stuff is charged and I just keeps dying
yeah and that never happened yeah it
never happens and he said it might
because it's supposedly like the ghosts
are pulling energy from you know
electronics or whatever and Paco's phone
went off randomly even though he had
full service and even then I was still
skeptical I was like okay what if they
have a device that's making our like a
DJ exactly yeah but then my phone was
fine the whole time everybody else it
was just like random you know moments
that we didn't even get to get on camera
a lot of times cuz it was just like
we're setting up yeah it was old I was
getting I was getting scared that we
weren't gonna be able get to shot
honestly because I was like I have two
batteries they died instantly
and I have to use this specific infrared
camera to get these shots and it was
like kind of that was making me scared
like yeah I want to get this shot so I
can't so I don't know I feel like you
could fight a ghost Oh sage but when you
cross when you think about it like when
there is a ghost most times they're just
scaring you like it you don't hear about
a ghost like killing anyone that's true
yeah maybe like if it's a demon and you
got possessed but how often do you hear
about that in your life yeah or same
with most times it's somebody you know
just scaring getting scared because they
saw something but they'd never like oh
it grabs my hair it's like well okay
that's not even assault
yeah actually I don't know that's
probably a song if someone like touched
your hair like well I mean I don't want
to get too much into the video because
we're just giving away the whole thing
yeah just in case but how about this
then instead of talking about this video
let's talk about the is synergy between
both Greg and Ryan so a lot of people
losses the process yeah yeah and how how
well you guys work together
um so like with a lot of the videos most
Ryan will write the full scrip have like
some wild ideas cuz like he said another
podcast he likes to push his ideas and
see like oh is this possible make I want
to try something new every time and
he'll come up to Greg and Greg is
someone who never says no he just I was
like yeah okay we can do that yeah so
speaking on that even just recently I
made over he was fixing another edit and
I just text him randomly I had this idea
and basically I was just like hey do you
think it's possible to do this
and before you mean I had a chance to
answer I was like wait I have to
rephrase that because Greg is always
gonna say it's possible cuz you'll find
a way but it's a matter of like okay is
this gonna be worth us putting the time
into and yeah because Greg always
figures out how to do anything it might
take two months yeah but you'll figure
it out just like we I mean like I mean
we let's talk about it like cuz there's
some videos like I wasn't too worried
about the fortnight one I mean obviously
there's a lot of effects in that and
stuff like that but I ask you is that
how possible is this to build a entire
fort you know do we have to build it in
real life
frança is it easier to make an effect
for it yeah um and you says possible so
I'm like okay but it's a matter of like
how possible and in a realistic time
right right usually it's I I look at the
thing on paper or your text message or
whatever and on paper looks it looks way
more doable then you know
in actuality so yeah III I often times
jump the gun and I usually just say yes
just kind of like you know it's just so
I can start thinking about it because
once I know something we're actually
gonna do something that's when like my
brain kind of starts putting the pieces
together and doing all the logistics but
sometimes it is impossible
yeah but we're too far into it right
it's like we can't turn back now well so
likely a good example is you know on the
exposed video yeah the music video we
did we're I was just pitching ideas with
with you and I was like
this is so much post work like I didn't
I didn't have an idea for that bridge
part I know what I wanted to see I want
to see all these little screens right as
we're spinning around which we did but I
didn't know how it was and then your
idea you're like oh and what if all
those screens ends up being you I was
like yeah yeah that's awesome and
because you said it I was like okay then
it's doable
yeah but I mean and you did you did it
yeah I mean most of times the effects
and stuff that we do I mean it's there
me see all over Hollywood all the time
like anything is possible nowadays
especially with today's technology what
they have a lot of time and yes that's
what yeah that's what kind of holds us
back it's just you know like technology
manpower and just time overall and but
like the ideas that's kind of like where
I guess me and Ryan kind of shine
because he'll write something and I will
kind of see it a completely different
way and we don't really combine our
ideas until like midway when we're kind
of we both got an idea of where we're
heads are at
so sometimes it's like two completely
different videos or two completely
different ideas coming together mm-hmm
and sometimes it works sometimes it
sometimes it's you know sometimes it's
like mid like filming yeah like oh this
is not what I was exactly but for
whatever we it ends up most times we try
to at least make it work yeah even if
that means getting rid of something yeah
but I mean that's that's usually the
process for that for the most part yeah
sometimes Ryan like fully leaves some
sections blank you know like whenever we
do like a connection type video like a
like a Miley Cyrus well you call that
video like conspiracy conspiracy theory
I guess yeah when Ryan goes into his
Ryan math stuff where he's just
connecting the dots and he doesn't
really know how to visually yeah so he
just leaves it blank and then you know
it's up to us to kind of connect
together yeah like like if there's no
specific direction on those then what a
lot of times what Greg's good at is
figure like visually
I think you see everything visually yeah
that's where I see things more like
almost like a math equation right right
and that's why it helps because it's
like we're working two different parts
of our brains if that makes sense it's
like well we're packin de but yeah
that's uh that's kind of like what yeah
mostly the processes like I will say the
very first kind of experience that kind
of relates to this like your question is
like when we first started working with
Ryan were in Los Angeles and it was me
and Greg and like I was gonna be
starting to do BTS and Greg was just
starting to do effects on first channel
and it was the I one you were there for
that yeah you were there for dear Ryan
can you open your eyes no my first video
I do know we did your first one I think
I think with movies and minutes Avengers
that's the first one I like that's the
one who came out to Vegas yeah but that
one was I feel like New York I literally
opened him oh you were like holy cow
like I've always had these ideas and I
want to do but you couldn't do them on
your own so when you had literally like
the capability to now do these like
graphic or CGI kind of bigger ideas
they're kind of more I don't know you
just can't edit them like cutting scenes
it's like you obviously had to spend
time if you're not familiar with it
someone where it's dear Ryan can you
open your eyes and he goes is really
really big and Greg like made these 3d
is too big it destroys the room and the
building and then for whatever reason it
starts teasing Dietrich's you know but
the thing is that's I didn't even think
like even if I could see it in my head
I've never done anything like that was
like how the hell cuz I was on like
iMovie I think exactly there's no way
unless you feel like green screen which
I kind experimented with did not know
what I was doing but uh I didn't know
that was possible and I just open the
door for so much work exactly
so much more time spiraled out of
control
yep and then we went downhill from there
just
just stress the stress it's like alright
well that I mean that seems like an
interesting you guys started talking
about your origin story almost yeah
but before we go into our origin story I
think it's about time we hit that
halfway mark we are we're there already
yes we are yeah we were talking about
goals for a while huh she should break
she should break do you guys have to she
she not she could she she again again I
agree the quids you guys she she a
balloon ooh try it out and doodle good
all right she should do the break just
she should
all right break change it up a little
bit you know what else is something that
we've changed up what I feel like we've
gone to big league like we mean I'm
about to explain whoa why are you so mad
because you cut me off like always
what does that mean though but uh I
think we got two big lis cuz once we got
one sponsor
we've never begged for another that is
true yeah I remember you guys did this
one podcast where like you guys were
trying to get Shauna a piping job that's
no we're trying to get him a
volunteering job and I think he actually
got a job
oh really yeah for real I just talked to
him well I don't I I don't know if I
should say I don't it's not my place but
and I don't know for sure but I'm pretty
I'm pretty sure he may or may not have
gotten a job I'm not saying because of
the podcast by the way it's I he was
looking to get a fallen he was trying to
just volunteer yeah cuz they weren't
letting him volunteer which I thought
was weird but it makes sense no but yeah
he's uh I think he may or may not have
gotten a job well maybe Congrats Sean
maybe Congrats John so kind of like man
we're back and we're back yeah they said
that nobody sees that part yeah what
were you talking about
we'll watch you beg for a sponsor real
quick and then we could jump in here
orange this is the part where we're
supposed to be like hey and thank you so
much to something we're sponsoring this
shishi break yeah I think that turns
away sponsors to be that we call it a
shisha break hell I don't even know what
it is okay let's keep it that way then
yeah we explained it though before yeah
but they don't watch the befores they
just look at the views oh good yeah yeah
those went down let's talk about yeah we
I guess we could bring up origin story
again the one thing that I read the most
was how did you guys meet and it kind of
includes all three of you yeah it
includes more than me a lot it's like a
lot of people so this is the real story
because we made the animated thing that
was I mean it was it was in the right
order kind of it was kind of the story
but I was like a joke but I'm not a
stripper so many people have asked and
be like you were a stripper and you took
that seriously no but the people took it
serious that's why I was I think they
did I think the joke no they actually
asked they think you they really think
they thought you were super but I'm like
look at my body do I look like I have
the value for that yeah you're very
muscular probably pay a couple bucks
yeah yeah I mean you ain't gonna do it
right now ain't gonna do it I can't cuz
if I show my legs it'll deter ad we
don't need legs continue with this
anyway we can um I'll let you guys I
mean you guys can tell it if you I can
fill in the blanks but I mean yeah Greg
was first so um so it all started oh man
maybe like back in I want to say junior
high when we used to go to school
together me will I didn't go to junior
high with you oh that's right high
school yeah high school high school what
we all kind of lived in the same area we
were me we'll Dana
we're from Sacramento California which
is where Dominic d-trix and a few others
are they're all we're all kind of like
from a certain area and we grew up
together we went to the same high school
together
and eventually we started a dance group
called the step boys as a hit was a
hip-hop dance crew shoutout ya know it
originated with uh you know a few guys
and then eventually we picked up will we
all started dancing with us and in
addition to will it was d-trix and that
was when we kind of took dance seriously
and we started training we started doing
competitions and dance was like our main
jam and then Dom got so good at dancing
he actually went on to a few shows he
went on to left us he did leave us and
yeah well we actually sent him away we
were like you're so good we're holding
you back please don't go I mean please
go do this thing and he did he went and
killed it and he did yeah we can't he
was like we were so freakin like proud
of how like cuz we never would thought
like one of the people that we were with
if you don't know he went to America's
no first he went to so you think you can
dance so you think he danced that's what
it was yeah yeah and I don't know he
just like did so well on it and came
back it didn't win but he made a name
for himself first yeah for sure and from
there he went on to America's Best Dance
Crew with quests which should have been
step boys okay he was at that time he
moved to LA and you know he had like his
yeah he had a lot of good dancer friends
out there and yeah they're all amazing
they're all like really good guys so and
they won and they were we would have but
later on down the road like we're like
man if Dietrich's can do it we could do
it that stuff it's easy bro so we
actually did trial and we did guys made
the show I was at that audition - yeah I
think suppose of the you guys beat out
Derek's crew yes it's true so that's
another one it's fallen king yes Derek
was in a he was also a dancer also
actually he is a dancer he's dancing
right now
yeah and he was actually someone that we
all looked up to when we saw dancing in
Sacramento he was like a professional
breakdancer that we were all like when
he
we saw him I was like kind of
intimidated by him and now I hate him I
could already see Derek in China
listen to this when you say no we
actually did like super look up to him
though he was I'm he was super dope he
was a traveling like dancer and they
would go to other countries and they
would win yeah and like we like we would
have never been able to do that kind of
stuff cuz we weren't the best dancers
but we could make good shows yeah we was
our Forte performers you guys are known
as the funny guys we really clowns yeah
like literally circus clowns you made
other dance crews laugh yeah pretty much
it's all about entertainment that's what
you guys were known for then when you
are on America's Best Dance Crew like
your logo was a mustache and like you
were the mascot basically yeah and it
was not about like oh you guys can do
the best flips or you guys have the best
stunts there's a little bit of
everything but the things you guys have
was comedy mm-hmm yeah the producers
actually hated us what yeah you did Dom
Dom was he was the judge at the gym on
the show I'm like the waitress he would
kind of tell us like you know behind the
scenes stuff and he was like yeah you
guys might need to step up your game
because the producers they're like they
really want you guys off the show we
could dance let's show them so yeah we
would you know put on girl costumes and
make a fool of ourselves but at this and
then they kick us off at the same time
we we had a we had as like it was like a
really good learning experience and it
was it was fun and after the show we all
kind of uh you know we needed to figure
it out and at that time DOM and Ryan
were living together cuz you guys met
how did you guys meet again I meant Dom
through Victor actually so same quest
through quest
I met Dom yeah through Victor I don't
know why I met victory through Wong foo
there short that they were doing and
then we just happened to get in touch
and I was like oh you guys are on this
show you guys are like dope anyway me
and Victor kept in touch he introduced
me to Quest
and just naturally I just like got along
with DOM and like his his style of
comedy and stuff like that so we he
ended up coming out a couple of times
and we hung out Steve Terada came out
and then we just kept in touch yeah
pretty much I was going to live in LA
and Vegas at the same time and I ended
up getting an apartment with him in
North Hollywood and then that's where I
guess that goes back to you right not
you yeah I was like maybe here's that
maybe the year before and I think I met
you twelve wasn't tendon okay Dana would
know yeah anyway so yeah it was after a
BDC and like YouTube was a pretty big
upcoming thing for Dom and you know he
wanted to spend more time and effort
into it and I was always like confused
about it because I actually studied
video for school I went to college for
digital media and my plan was to you
know do video and then I saw I hear Dom
getting into this YouTube thing he's
doing good and like yeah and he was like
great what kind of camera should I get
and why do you want why do you want this
expensive camera I was getting a little
salty because you know I was like saving
up all my allowance I didn't get
allowance and I was just like really
excited to get like this you know these
this equipment that Dom was just picking
up like nothing he had like no interest
and no he was just getting it for this
YouTube thing I had no interest in
YouTube at the time so I was like okay
well yeah well if you're just you know
you need this equipment to do this you
need this editing stuff and basically I
was kind of helping Dom in his early
YouTube career and I guess from there he
and or you guys were getting really into
YouTube and you guys formed like rights
yeah and all that yeah and you guys
needed kind of more help getting stuff
out so Dom offered me you know a place
to stay and out in LA to help him
produce some videos
it they'll do some stuff like that so
you know I didn't have anything planned
but to try and dance some more so I was
just gonna you know I finished my I
finished school and then I was like okay
yeah I just made the leap to move out to
LA and hope you guys yeah I think like a
pretty big piece of it as well that we
didn't mention was when we were younger
like when we first started hanging out
right in step boys I was probably like I
don't know 15 or 16 when I first met
them and we really like Greg was he was
like really always into like filming and
editing and essentially he had like this
group of literally clowns right so we
would make these really stupid funny
videos for each other which was what we
did we didn't use YouTube but you would
he would make them on CDs I would make
them into like yeah DVDs we'd give them
to people yeah yeah and that was kind of
like our version like we weren't on
YouTube then but that was like what we
were doing so that was like the
correlation between DOM
knowing Greg's value you know because he
was the one that filmed and edited it
and liked it it was just really stupid
stuff like that we used to do it was
like typical you exactly like early 2005
exactly like this jackass type stuff
yeah like just some stupid skits yeah
and so that was kind of the correlation
between Dom using Greg is like or
wanting to hire him in a sense because
he knew he was that was what he was into
it was really good at it and and then
well I mean you were living with us
spike you were you were literally on our
couch times we didn't we had to it was a
two-bedroom place me and Dom in a room
you were just living on our couch and
the couch was not that big it was I'm
pretty Tom five five and that couch was
like two inches too short for me so I
constantly had to sleep like with a
little kink in my leg and I'm pretty
sure I got some back problems to be fair
yeah it was a really nice place it was
it wasn't that rough it was we were
coming from where we were like stepboys
yeah it was like it's pretty nice
wait so did you both move to LA at the
same time right Gregg moved before me he
was because like this point after a BDC
like I didn't go on the show I was still
in college and we were all like getting
to the point we were really figuring out
we were like kind of becoming adults a
little bit we were figuring out like
what we wanted to do do we want to keep
pursuing dance professionally Gregg was
like finishing college so is he gonna do
dance or film like everyone was kind of
in that phase and so Gregg had like
after the show you know there we work
might have like done professional in you
know moving to LA and stuff like that
trying to do more dance but Gregg got
this opportunity to do film with them
and went ahead and then I remember it
was like pretty like a specific time
where Gregg came back and was like this
is what I'm doing and he hit we had like
this talk with all stepboys about like
you know you know push harder like let's
do some stuff like if you want to do a
dance if you want to be a dancer and
move to LA and dance like we had like
this you know as a serious talk and I
remember thinking like okay I need to
make it change and you know and it
motivated everyone to like lit the fire
and so I just took the leap and I Trant
I was gonna transfer to LA and so I
moved to LA I don't know how many months
after that would have been probably for
three or four months and I just had just
took the leap and I was gonna transfer
school out there and continue my you
know college education and so that's why
I like I came after yeah but I was like
the instigator I was trying move out the
entire dance crew because they were like
my only friends I didn't know anyone out
in LA I didn't have no money yeah I
didn't have like anyone only when I had
was dahm dahm was like you know my
saving grace but he was also the only
one only friend that I knew out there
yeah so it was kind of a risky jump I
mean it was just like something that I
was terrified of you know I was leaving
all my family all my friends and all for
this YouTube thing that there was
nothing involved with it there was like
I didn't know if I was gonna get paid I
didn't know if I was gonna if there's
gonna be a career that I can actually
make money off of or you know be
financially stable from but at the same
time I kind of just knew that it was
something something I don't know I think
it was just the like it was exactly what
I wanted to do I didn't want to work for
a big company but I also wanted to make
some big stuff like I didn't want to be
held back creatively and I felt like
this kind of it checked all the checks
that I needed in life besides the
paycheck so like I was I was like okay
you know I'll figure out the money stuff
later as long as I get to make some dope
stuff on in video and you know this is
gonna be worth it yeah so I was like
yeah we'll come out man like we're gonna
get so much money
we're gonna be alright and I see I
actually we actually got a good portion
of our dance crew - you know like come
out and I mean like jerel he's with uh
you know he's doing this thing out there
with Dom or he was doing this thing with
Dom there's green yeah they're all kind
of from step boys I mean they are from
step boys yeah if you see like you know
a lot of people that's in Dom's videos
you know that they're probably from
Sacramento and it's a it's a pretty cool
family that Sacramento if you don't if
you've never been there it makes sense
because there's nothing to do out there
so I think that's what we kind of like
there's nothing to do but hone your
crafts and like get better at dancing or
video or whatever so it's there's a cool
place it was a boring place to live but
it was also a very like cultured place
so yeah that's the origin of yeah how we
met Ryan basically yeah and then yeah to
continue the story just a little bit
like after Greg had moved I had moved
shortly after and then like Greg said we
didn't really know anyone
so we me and Greg we'd hung out like
every day yeah and then sometimes since
Brian was Dom's roommate sometimes Dom
would be somewhere else like super busy
so we were hanging out with Ryan like
because he was at the house and our
department and and he was obviously
working and doing YouTube stuff and so
it literally just put us in the same
like literally the same room and it just
kind of the same I think the same thing
that connected DOM and
since like the sense of humor like
that's what we shared as well because
it's it's all from the same dancer
essentially we all it's kind of like a
Malcolm Gladwell's outliers in a way
it's it's a book where it basically
talks about how you are at like the
prime age the youngest point you could
have been to learn all that you could
and and be in the right place at the
right time yeah type of thing I think so
yeah yep
I mean I I'm a firm believer of like
there's nothing wrong with hard work I
mean it never really hurt anyone besides
you in your own time and you know yeah I
do agree if we were in the right place
at the right time yeah and it is a very
you know fortunate opportunity for us
you know Ryan DOM especially given us
these opportunities but at the same time
if it wasn't for us putting in the hard
work to get us to be you know have some
type of talent in the first place they
probably wouldn't have even you know
thought of us ago and it just had
perfectly lined up too with you because
you were in a phase of your career where
you you did want to like like create
like a small crew to help you produce
more on a more constant basis right
because if we would have met you like a
year before it would probably been
completely different right um I think
originally I didn't even know Greg could
do what he could do right effects wise I
wanted somebody who could help me shoot
for one yeah and have another you know
bodies around right because it was just
so hard to do everything by yourself and
then when I saw what he could do in
terms of like his filming and now it's
just like how did you make cuz I would
use the camera I would give him my
camera sometimes right and he would get
a shot and I'd be like how did you make
it look so cinematic oh you know you
just do this and this and this and you
know he makes the background blurry and
he's just like I stuff up on my own
camera cause I didn't know how to use it
right you know and then I was like when
he kind of showed me that stuff I was
like damn there's so much things I did
not know what's even possible yeah and
that's the main reason why I wanted to
bring Greg on so I think honestly I
think it would have happened still with
Greg because I was just like so
intrigued with learning like what else
is possible yeah
like if we kept every single video if
you look it's a progression like from
year to year
does huge jumps in terms of what we were
doing and it's not necessary like he
couldn't have done great couldn't have
done it before it's just I was like
literally doing what we do now is like
hey is this possible
how can we do this and you know still
keep it within our brand right but it
that's how it progressed it was a lot of
I think even you like you know like you
couldn't even compare your knowledge now
to that that version of grey because you
learned so much along the way and you
just kept you know if you didn't know
something you never said no you just
looked it up figured it out even if
sometimes it was whack compared to what
you thought I was gonna be or even for
what I thought was gonna be it's like at
least we got it done you know might not
have been exactly how we pictured but
the fact that you figured out how to do
it is I guess I guess in a way it's it's
a good and bad thing to say
yeah always you're gonna you can make
this happen yeah that comes from I think
for sure it comes from step boys and
sense of like we we never it was so
weird because our our performance is
like I said they weren't just dance good
but somehow we made it happen to where
whoever is watching they would either
laugh or understand a story you know and
a big portion of that came from I think
the mentality that we all breeded and
definitely like the older guys for sure
of like take this idea and make it
happen right I think it's just like you
know you can literally make something
out of nothing like you don't need to
have all the skills you don't need to
have talent you know I mean you have
more so just the willingness and the
drive to be able to you know say okay I
got this well back then it was like you
know if take for example we had this
Dance Crew no one knew how to dance but
we all wanted seriously we all wanted to
put on a good show like we knew what
made us smile and what made us like like
a certain dance performance so we're
like okay we'll just tweak our abilities
and you know get that same kind of
moment but with our skill levels yeah so
like you know we knew we had one guy
that I had a that could do a backflip
it's
we utilized that guy a lot because he
was you know it was it gave that idea
that the entire crew could do backflips
exactly but you know we apply that same
kind of idea to video we're not the best
video makers or I mean we're far from it
there's like so many good effects guys
camera people but we try to a man we do
our best to get a really good you know a
professional look but at the same time
we have the time more than half the time
69 percent of the time we don't know
what the heck we're doing 69 percent of
the time exhausting just to go back on
to the origin and finish I'll do the
fast version yeah
just so people understand yes I met Greg
first and it was literally on a per
project basis I was just kind of like
you know it was more Dom's friend and
then eventually like you know it wasn't
consistent enough for you I think to the
point where like I was using you more
than Dom a little white TF slave you
were I was getting tossed around
actually was it white yet before you
started working with who was right
during like right during white TF is
when I moved out like the heart of it
okay so you came on a little after then
I guess so yeah okay you were the white
TF BTS er yeah yeah if someone needed a
video in white TF mm-hmm it's probably
my way and then from there you
introduced me to will I mean already
kind of we already kind of met but like
that's where we started hanging out like
you said we hung out more yeah after
that we I ended up moving back to Vegas
because I really did not like living in
LA and you guys came onto and lived at
the cloth which is the don't the cloth
is you know what the cloth is really
yeah they've heard us say it before so
ok well the club is the first house I
lived in Vegas and it became it the
office essentially I see that coming a
lot like what house is this
yeah anyway I don't think it's ever been
officially addressed as that well the
scenes before they're exposed to us
anyway from there so willing Greg are
there I think the next person might have
been Shaun yeah or was it
Eric was oh yes on visitors no it was
Sean no Sean visited and then he went
back he was still in college yeah I
think it was Sean we were saying you
were like around with Derek a lot
because he already lived in Las Vegas
yeah he was doing his own YouTube stuff
anyway to help him fort after I'm gonna
I'm just gonna say Sean I think it was
Sean okay Sean finished college and he
hit me up well I hit him up to I was
just like I always told him from the
last time he visited like if you ever
want to get back into making some videos
and stuff like that like come come
through you know like we have a place
like because they were seeing at the
house and you know we had some room and
he says yeah I was I'm interested in
that I don't think he he what he at the
time he was very not interested I think
he was just so over college yeah he was
over school that's why he really wanted
to do it and then now obviously he's
back interested in again but so Sean was
there and then eventually you guys moved
out right it was like this weird thing
where everybody except Derek lived at
the club yeah yeah at some point anyway
Sean came in Derek had just finished a
job that he was working with the job
walk he's dancing in a Vegas show but it
was just about to be renewed or the show
was just ending and he had the option to
either go be on the show again or I
don't know what it was a kid the rien or
something or he said hey Isaac like I
want to edit like this is what I went to
school for whatever like do you want to
another editor so I said okay well um
yeah I guess we could bring Derek in too
so he brought in Derek from there was it
Josh Josh yeah you know Dane Oh Dana
moved out we was it that time I think it
was Dana was before Josh no I don't
think so okay well either way Josh
Booher he was a brief period of time but
he was living out here too met him
through internet icon and how was a
thing and it's also where I met also
where I met Paco alumni but yeah I think
Josh was here for a little bit
Dana came in because of Greg essentially
she was coming here
what was the reasoning for coming here I
mean design right yeah it was interior
design but also you know we're doing
like a long term relationship and turn
suit for one well we'll talk about that
next but uh yeah
why'd you say it like that I was like in
agreement oh yeah I mean we might have
to talk about it on a different one sure
yeah yeah okay so Dana and then Josh
ended up leaving to go work with his
parents net in Atlanta or LA and then
Paco the story I don't know have I told
this story about him coming we were
doing I know specifically we were
filming skit so that 30-minute skit so
was it called Halloween one the
Halloween skit so all my fault and it's
okay we'll get to that so Paco comes and
he hits me up you know we kind of know
each other
and then he's like hey man and just want
to let you know anytime you uh you know
I would love to come help just I'll
Drive out and just get some experience
and I was like all right well we're
shooting this really long schizo episode
sure and he drove out like I think
pretty like soon right after I've rented
a car yeah you rented a mom okay so
that's that's one other thing he rented
a car drove all the way out from LA just
to come be on set and help us for free I
wasn't paying him it just came to I was
like Dan this is a really hard-working
cool dude like who does that he kind of
reminded me yeah yeah he just like
giving up some of his this time and and
you know just dedicating it towards
bettering himself yeah and I was like
this is very impressive it was like a
two-day shoot I believe right no you
guys were shooting for four days yeah
but you hit me up on the first day and I
do remember the second day when we're
filming at the time I think you fell
asleep during the shoot or something
like that something like that happened
and we were all like you know whatever
cuz we're free yeah and he drove the
whole time yeah I think it was the end
of that day because I had just a ride
and we went to shoot like right away
yeah he fell asleep in the shoot and
normally I'd be like oh that's if he was
working for us but that's weird but
little did we know inside well anyway
we'll of all people was like I was like
hey do you think it's worth like week
Josh just left we could bring this guy
on board like he we could use the hands
like if he edits I know he did at it
because he was making videos of his own
I guess
jammed and will was the number one
person like fight he was like this is no
help yeah because I was like messaging
him like a good job when coming out like
we really appreciate the topic shocked
yeah you know if you keep coming around
like that's how you know that's how it
always his work like Derek was gone for
a long time and he just helped in
exactly and then that's exactly what I
told him was like you keep coming out
and killing it like of course you know
something's bound to happen you know
it's like and that's what happened
but anyway Paco ended up being a part of
the group yeah
oh well he's in pocket Paco's in and
that's pretty much how he got in but I
think we found because I was always
trying to find out I was like okay so
you don't want to write because what for
me like I mean I was like okay so you
don't want to edit you have such a
specific I do have a very specific are
you write its I know that's why I
writing for Ryan is tough it's it takes
a genius no no it's just big Rhino
genius guys know it's hard because I'm
very particular in what I like might not
always make sense to people but it's
just I'm just very picky even if it's
down to a point one second cut it makes
a difference to me it does I mean once a
I will say the last thing that Greg was
talking about a little bit was like
Greg's value and it was that he was like
super into filming and editing and stuff
like that and people recognize that when
I came on like I didn't do any film I
didn't do any editing like we wrote
something a little bit in the beginning
and I think hopefully like I like to
think that that probably at least put me
on the radar but literally if you want
to
learn something it's aunt like online is
the determination and just wanting to
learn something yeah because I learned
everything from Greg from Ryan from
online like searching and just like
literally just wanting and like pursuing
it so it's it's possible like I didn't
know how to edit I didn't know how to
film and motivational podcasts yeah we
have those now we are this kind of
turned in today just take out the whole
first half just continue from this book
yeah just cause stepboys the movie and
it's just like about inspiration like
about a dance crew that didn't know how
to dance
and they all ended up doing like kind of
big things I don't know everybody but I
mean the one guy sings you know some
guys became somewhat ographers editors
guys a stripper right we have we have
one of our crew mates that is in the
Chippendales so yeah Oh real Vegas show
like it's not a joke
yeah well anyway we could talk a whole
lot more but we've hit about the hour
mark which means we don't have time for
Twitter questions we all let's just do
some rapid fire
I guess one no no just go through it
real quick no with the one we'll do one
and we're gonna pull it from the reddit
page and we're gonna I guess we're gonna
open it up now I don't really I have it
we're gonna start utilizing it things
using shows but what is like do you
watch the old videos still because I
know sometimes you guys do you cringe at
it which one is your favorite one and I
want to go in order of Greg will and in
Ryan honestly I will say something quick
about this oh that's the one thing
that's crazy about like I feel like the
work that I've done with Ryan is a lot
of time if I watch old videos I don't
cringe if it was like something I made
like a long time ago for sure I would
cringe at it but that's why it's like I
know it's not being really special
because I don't know I said they hold up
yeah they really do there's some videos
that I cringe I do add a lot of them
some people are better than obviously
some bears but so which ones are your
favorites then
stole it the good one oh my god
everybody okay we got to say this
because people for whatever reason the
ones we love right especially for me and
Greg when we're editing we're like dying
sometimes and we're like oh no we're
laughing so hard no one's gonna like
this never all the ones we love like so
many of them I know even the ones that
I'm like oh this is so bad and we're
like that means it's gonna do good you
know and for whatever reason being Greg
and that final edit if we're dying we're
like great no one's gonna get this
there's literally like videos that you
guys probably don't know exist that
they're my favorite videos just because
they're so deep yep but I would say my
favorite video would probably be man we
meet some man there was 100 was the
scary one we did with Kyle all the
paranormal writers yeah that's not my
favorite as far as something I was the
most proud of I mean it was probably
yeah it would probably have to be like
one of the big videos I meant like candy
crush that was like a really that was
the one I was gonna say that was like a
transitional video for us I think were
you yeah that's when I was like holy
crap you just created a world
yeah and like we never did anything like
that and I was like if you can do this
and then and then that was your downfall
cuz I'm like great can do this that
means you can do all these other things
and then yeah it just spiraled from
there yeah I was gonna say candy crush
actually god that was the person I was
like yeah super cool
but then that's another one we go back I
don't cringe but I'm like oh this is
compared to some of the stuff he's doing
now in terms of the effects I'm like oh
this is nothing now right but I mean
still it's not nothing
yeah you know even even if you just like
put it during that time where you know
effects we're still pretty new for
YouTube videos yeah it's not anything
good but it was decent for the time for
us it was good yeah yeah there was like
I think at the time Freddie Wong was
doing crazier stuff and was like well
that's his gimmick you know our gimmick
is not even about effects just supposed
to enhance the comedy corridor has
always been some they were wrong before
Freddie right yeah I mean they're low
they were working with yeah yeah yeah
and they've always been like killing the
game yeah some like some YouTube channel
that I always looked up to
can i machine-gun knees no we're out of
time what was your first job um gift
wrapper at the mall they strap gifts
nice time no let's just go quick ones
quick ones how did you meet Dana awesome
dance class when's the next episode of
willing Greg show mm and then I think
one last thing that I wanted to say is
we're out of time sorry I know we're out
of time no I'm just getting go ahead but
uh because the reason why I chose the
question of what was your guys favorite
old videos is that because you recently
announced that you were dating Arden I
just didn't watch this if you know it I
thought it would be kind of cool to see
both you and Arden react to agents of
secret stuff is just you pitch an idea
well we had previously talked about this
but I just I don't think it's a I don't
want to I know you don't
yeah that actually is one I would cringe
at I cringe at agent secret stuff anyway
I'm like yeah he says oh if he skits
it's one of those videos oh it gets so
many legs you guys would do it but I
really don't want to so I'm gonna say
like I don't even know what our podcast
gets normally but double it triple it it
has to be in the first week cause you
can't keep adding up eventually look at
yesterday's one how about that I hate
asking for likes though you don't have
to like it if you don't like it we'll do
it should I do that's really you know
almost difficult like a hundred thousand
okay well yeah I like a lot for a
podcast that's pretty unrealistic
drop it down a little bit all right
50,000 no 100 hundred six thousand the
Gregg special fine second channel though
yeah yeah yeah well I I don't want to do
it and now I feel like it's gonna happen
I don't watch that thing again you guys
heard the deal 69 thousand likes Ryan
does a reaction to a snow Arden does it
and UN Arden see six hundred ninety
thousand likes and we watch Sean and
Ryan's been sleeping that part out don't
even mention this alright we need to end
this thank you guys for watching the
hook the bill podcast I mean you guys
know how we ended so in three two one
Ian oh my gosh that is even deeper why
dude that's deep it all that's not see
you next time