people always ask why did why tfn and I
think the catalyst to that was because
of that tour you ever make love to your
music no that would be super awkward
with the clapper claps right away
everybody okay welcome back to another
half the peel podcast today I thought it
was the I thought the audience come to
me just a kiss you are messing up today
so right before we got started there's
been a lot of technical difficulties on
the part of Paco but we are here with a
very special guest his name is jr. Akeno
this is when the applause was supposed
some of you might know who he is it was
thanks man sorry we've been having
really a lot of issues with getting this
thing started no we're good we're here
about an hour to get this thing started
but we're good and Jerry's here but
before we get started what is lucid
dreaming again lucid dreaming is
basically just you're aware that you're
dreaming so you can control it you can
literally do whatever you want like I've
never done it that's why I want to
actually see that it's not the other
thing no it wasn't the movie into your
thing of insidious insidious Oh what is
Inception no it's not it's not your
projections okay enough astral
projection is I think it's just it's
just seeing yourself sleep I don't know
what it's called just Autobody
experience and you kind of just see
yourself sleep okay
so I think I've done that before or or I
was dreaming that I was doing it
regardless it's very boring oh I know in
that dream or when if I was actually
doing it I was like I thought it was
lucid dreaming because I was awake while
it was happening but I was like okay I
want to fly through this roof and I
couldn't I was just like watching I was
on the ceiling stuck there looking at
myself sleep oh that's lame I know and
it wasn't scary this is before it's like
a livestream yeah and I'm just watching
myself sleep which is already kind of
weird but I'm aware of it I'm like oh
this must be loose
I thought like I felt my body lift up
and I could see myself sleep and it was
just so boring but then lucid dreaming
dreaming is when you can you're aware
whatever part of your dream you don't
even have to be like coming out of your
body or whatever it's like you're just
in the dream and you're aware like
there's certain triggers I guess that
you uh you can you can do like counting
how many fingers you have or looking at
watching your hand or something like
that
oh you have to trick you're not trick
yourself you have to UM need some kind
of way to tell yourself that you're
dreaming gotcha once you realize you're
dreaming you have complete control over
the world you can do whatever you want
you can fly you can have a celebrity
appear is kind of like Inception in
a way then I guess so I'm not I kind of
forget how inception worked well inside
is like it is controlling your dream but
to pick it uh yeah that to its inception
was the whole idea of like planting a
dream yeah right planting an idea inside
of somebody right
yeah lucid dreaming be tight I would
like I would actually probably just uh
be in a zombie apocalypse you would want
that to happen only because then I could
have my you know like you have your
whole load out like I'd have a bunch of
guns oh yeah you know what I mean and I
just go through and like Merc everything
hey would you just lost our monetization
by saying guns you know yo I'm not in
I'm not me I'm not on YouTube yo
straight streets mystery my heart of
smell your Spotify now yeah but I heard
Spotify is actually well going back to
that yeah so so last time that's our
last podcast I think we called it we
talked about the Momo challenge you
heard about that right oh yeah so we had
it in like the title and it wasn't we
weren't like promoting it or anything we
just talked about it like how we're
doing right now
okay but I know better now we had it in
the title and and they freaking flag the
video yeah it had lost monetization is
he tough no it's soft its Placid yes
so jr. is an OG youtuber you've been
around since OH six-six-six on the same
time follow bow so you got started like
I'll let you tell it how you got started
I started I was born and raised from
Anchorage Alaska and shout out nine oh
seven eight nine oh seven was good to
everybody out there Stan woman Nicole is
there yes hood everywhere I'm just super
like offended that he don't ya just grew
up being Filipino I you know just saying
karaoke you know and did a bunch of like
school events banquets and all that
stuff singing at that stuff and it
wasn't until I was like 16 15 16 I did
American Idol and I made it to the top
44 of that year that was Carrie
Underwood season and season is that
season full course and four okay I
thought she was one of those Who am I
thinking of then I don't she blew up
really big but she's not the winner you
might think Clay Aiken cleared out you
know it's a girl I don't know Jennifer
Hudson win which I know she didn't she's
the one but Kenneth underhood Carrie
Underwood season 4 season 4 that's when
you're on yeah Carrie Underwood and yeah
I did that how old are you at the time 6
16 15 16 so I was the youngest actually
in that scene in that in that in the top
44 Wow
it was kind of cool cuz with that one I
kind of didn't know where I stood in the
whole like how good I was I guess they
didn't know how good you were
yeah because it was like okay I knew I
could sing but like am I really gonna do
how do I stand against other people if
no comparison yeah no comparison you're
16 yeah 16 I mean
from Anchorage Alaska being a small
place and this is before the internet -
so it's like oh I really don't know
anything outside of before I was popping
yeah yeah and I yeah I made it to the
top 44 and I was I got a hundred
thousand people sold out at that I was
like okay this actually could be a thing
so I went through high school and then
it was it was like the first semester of
college and I was on that's this this
new site called YouTube and I saw a
video by david choi friend of the show
right yep yes I saw the him playing the
YouTube song yeah he's playing was
featured yes all iPhone exactly yeah and
then I was like oh this looks cool looks
fun like and back then we're not
thinking anything of it we're just like
just gonna throw a video up and I and I
was like oh cool and then so I put up a
video and like I don't even look at it
if it was out of sync it was so bad no
this story yeah I told him I told him
like several times I think a lot of
people would not necessarily inspire
bird like a at Asian dude that
relatability yeah and yeah I just put up
a video and then didn't look at it for
it and then two weeks later looked at it
again it was like 10 comments and 150
views and we're talking about how
Alaska's I mean it's so far that a lot
of people consider it like another yeah
yeah same way to Hawaii a lot of times I
mean I don't correct them Hawaii's
another country that they say like how's
it like moving to the states I was like
yeah we are us yeah I don't correct them
but I just go with or whenever they're
visiting that Hawaii and they're like oh
I got to go back to the States
yeah I'm like you see me now Alaska is a
very I mean Hawaii is very different
last is very different - yeah we're both
different yeah yeah for sure well it's
crazy because some people
don't even know where Alaska is because
they cuz you know in some of the maps
Hawaii and Alaska like some people
really think yeah like I'm all y'all
they're like wait unless you know damn I
wish it was right next to each other you
know find the ones we bomb or it'd be so
worse for us you know you never would
have moved then then you're right anyway
Alaska is so different that they have
like I don't even know how many shows
but I only know that cuz my mom watches
it religiously and she's addicted to
them I mean it's it looks beautiful but
I mean it's not Anchorage they're like
in the middle of nowhere quickly did you
just imply that Anchorage isn't
beautiful no I mean nice is it no it's
wonderful it's a beautiful point where
the show where the shows took place is
not in like the city they make it seem
like it's in the middle of like the
woods oh it is in the middle I think
yeah cuz like literally there's only I
think 500,000 people like half a million
people in the whole state and just to
give you like like comparison like um
Alaska is two times it's like two to
three times bigger than Texas 2 to 3
yeah I mean huge it is but then that's
not a lot of people that's not like you
how well you said Anchorage is like
encourage is about like I'll probably
say like 300,000 people it's still more
than my Island less than his Island
million Oahu whoa like Waipahu Pearl
Harbor area yeah dang they scrap out
there right a little bit a lot of
Filipinos out there yeah what are you
trying to say but I was on the richer's
what does that mean for those you don't
know scrap this is another word for
fighting yeah I just know there's a lot
of wives here I know what you like scrap
brah I think I just know yeah you just
know man have you been in a scrap in
your life once really I mean I can't
even say it was a scrap cause it was one
and done now I'm saying you were the guy
that guy
oh no no but no yeah you knocked the guy
out no I didn't knock him out it was it
felt really bad too
I'd like so um this guy was making fun
of me I was like probably third or
fourth grade for third or fourth grade
nah yeah I don't scratch since but uh
faucets but I remember like he's making
fun of me and also heal yourself
stop stop bla bla bla stop and then I
just punched him in the stomach like
really hard and it was actually really
my timing was really good because we
were all leaving the class to go outside
I punched really hard right before we
got out so no one was looking like it
was already out he was just like crying
and what happened trouble no no he was
using G yo shout out shout out to the
homie I'm not gonna put your name down
yeah similar story oh yeah I think I
already sat in the park can I sit on
this party said it in your book I don't
know about yeah well you just beaten up
people no I mean it's uh so I was in
kindergarten okay right
this is my scrap this is my I actually
have to use the misogynist yes I was
thinking and you know you like everybody
lines up for you know to go to like the
lunch or whatever I don't we used to do
that we would line up and it was always
like the goal to make it to the front of
the line okay where I sat and you can't
run cuz the teacher you just everybody
walks really fast like that but like you
know how kids when they're trying to try
to not run that was me but I could never
get there I could never get to the front
because where I was sitting I was like
towards the back of the class I have to
go around desks so the people on the
other side their backs facing the door
they turn around and they're already
there but this one time I remember I got
to the very front very frontal line
hyped I'm the reason why I remembered
this is cuz it was a big deal back then
I finally got to the front of line and
this girl cut in front of me she did us
she'd literally just saw me there did a
side step and came in front of me and I
didn't say anything
tuchus I stood before her turn around
and sock during her stomach and she just
collapsed and once she did one of those
like where she was on the ground
couldn't breathe and then I got sent to
the principal's office
yeah it was a girl some of my stories
were say just less use she cut dude no
what did yo that's that's not going well
I didn't know what if she liked you
though maybe play she was flirting
that's not how you flirt with
kindergarten Ryan like you know do you
like do you know this girl I remember
her I have it I did not on like a video
I was like sorry Hannah
well I mean I think it's like I was in
kindergarten yes so much trouble for
that already have you so mad you know I
was I was a I was a that was a jerk move
but she shouldn't have cut anyway that
wasn't a proper response didn't
understand the time don't mind that I
got yota for my parents - I feel you
yeah and then the second time I ever got
into a kind of a fight was in fourth or
fifth grade it was an after-school
program and I brought for like a show
and I brought a B and it was in like a
jar oh my god thing and it has like you
know obviously as whole dozen stuff with
it so I caught a B I thought was the
coolest thing I brought it took it to
the after-school program and this kid
tried to take it he tried to take my B
so he called John like he was like just
I guess he was just looking at it but he
took it with him out of my cubby hole
and he had it with him and I caught him
I was like what are you doing I took it
back put it in my cubby hole and the
heat we kind of got into like a scuffle
I don't know he was just like trying to
see it and this is like for the fifth
graders I did like four years of Judo
already so I just grabbed he's just
waiting for this moment and I tossed him
on his head yeah but I mean this is just
natural reaction like we were having
like a little little wrestling thing
going on it's what you were trained for
for years
yeah it was natural I can wait for the I
just it don't take my B and don't cut
that's the key did the B go unscathed
the B was fine it was good yeah but I um
might've been a wasp actually I don't
know oh wow I don't I don't remember um
but yeah I got in trouble for that too
so more no no I haven't yeah those two
times but both times it was a
reactionary response I wasn't pushing
people down and I used to get bullied so
okay
maybe that's doesn't maybe I deserve to
get like punched a girl and then and
this guy anyway that's enough of my
fighting stories fighting story I knew I
would never beat up somebody I know I
couldn't win a fight so I'll just tease
people and run that's why I'm fast oh
man you are pretty fast yeah I always
hear like Hawaiians always be fighting
well my barber my barber was telling me
he hella stressed
no he shiva showed me videos nobody
thing is it's almost like it's almost
like a respect it's not always like yeah
yeah yes are like okay we have problems
that's fine you guys like if we're not
gonna pull a gun stab each other go talk
either we yeah we yeah this talk it's
almost like a kind of like a normal
thing and then after you guys most times
like it's more um no matter who wins
you're supposed to shake hands yeah and
call it yeah like there shouldn't be
nothing else after that
yeah and that and it works that's that's
good though it's better than like you
know someone pulling out a knife and
stabbing someone or and then that person
retaliates know that with their family
and it kind of works I mean it's not
most civilized thing but it's about
respect and I liked it yeah and that's
why youtubers are boxing now they're
trying to respect each other you know
what's funny but they get the bag for it
those that is true you know what's funny
though before that became a real big
thing I always said like man these guys
are at the time they were just doing
dish trash sounds like they should just
like they really hate her that much just
flight display I didn't say bah I mean
before there was an ounce I was like I
mean I talked about this I don't want to
do a show if I was like you guys should
just fight and then make up like just
that's the best way to do it like you're
Hawaii style just just fight it out and
then you know who has no matter who wins
you just hug and then that's it call it
that my super funny that's all
presidents and dictators instead of wars
yeah we just
we'd be electing it on a different I
Donald Trump versus Kim also Kim what
car - I mean he's way younger yeah like
in a fight you had a fight fight oh he
does have like he has like
what is it when you're around his little
teaser god he's small but he's also way
younger than Donald Trump Oh God Trump
from what I hear it's very unhealthy
yeah I can't imagine he has any car do
something about his hair makes me feel
like he he can scrap like you know he
can't fight yeah I don't think so either
I think he's holding on like you see his
hair like he doesn't have you should
just get like he's fighting for his hair
he's so orange to everyone there was
Celebrity Deathmatch I love that show
I know don't know about that don't know
about it yes Larry used to be a
claymation just way too we're way too um
I think TV is way too soft not to do
that no no yeah just like you do damn
YouTube damn they took they don't listen
to this and I mean if we're talking
about YouTube in something like
comparisons from the past all now yeah
YouTube is great and thank you YouTube
for everything you guys but I guess you
guys were in this group called ytf which
was like probably one of the first if
not the first super group on YouTube
well super take that why is it super
well we were one of the mean before this
is before like all the team tens and
like the there was austere because there
are things right now right yeah we were
so we didn't they but they became
businesses like they treated it like
you're literally just friend you just
we're friends and then eventually we
made a business out of it in a way kinda
yeah but we were just friends who were
hanging out and we think it was that
wanted to do more stuff to hang no yeah
it was an excuse for us to hang out we
were just friends
and we came out with this thing whitey
AF yesterday today forever and we had a
message to spread and we basically just
made it because we wanted to hang out
want to tour together and yeah we
weren't we yeah we should like hiding in
videos and bullet yesterday today
forever that's the name that a lot of
you would knew yeah but I guess a more
subtle name that it was which was what
did you guys call we could talk about
that I mean I don't think it matters I
want to know cuz then the way that it
sounded the original name which is I
want you guys to say cuz I don't know
we're just gonna keep it a secret
No so originally originally before when
it was just us talking
it was literally a bunch of guys in a
room right and we were just hanging out
and we were like - we're like well this
is like a YouTube fret and that's what
how it started YF initially started that
way and they started talking about
getting all these letterman jackets and
it was like I was the one thing I was
opposed I know you guys wanted a but I
didn't want to let him in check it
anyway you know oh wow this kind of
popped in my head
what it's kind of misogynistic that you
wanted YouTube fret we didn't know what
I didn't did you choose for you to fret
the name because like you know punching
girls when he was actually I came up
with the alternative to white
because I thought it wasn't gonna
exclude girls from what is she a part of
this you wanted people to have run the
ytf mystery egg but it was just like
well at the time anymore
we had more girl followers and guys know
it's the opposite
oh really um yeah YouTube in general is
just more than okay um but yeah we
switched it to you know yesterday today
forever which essentially it was just
the message that we were trying to get
across right is yesterday is in the past
today you have a choice forever is up to
you same thing is it's kind of the last
two things they're kind of saying the
same thing but essentially just meaning
like the message one to spread was what
we believed in is is just making a
choice to do something yeah
despite your past you know whatever
happened don't let your past
circumstances yeah just do it
that's basically the Nike it's our own
thing who's that it was the same same
idea but in our in our way that's how II
doesn't we told it and then that's what
it became and from there I I guess you
guys went on to do a lot of pretty cool
things Oh
what was your guys personal like
favorite ytf moment favorite day yeah
and then I kind of want to ask them like
dirty questions yeah
our favorite moment you first no I'm
trying to think I'm trying to think yeah
favorite moment
[Laughter]
jokes and nobody gets so long joke long
dude I I mean the first tour was pretty
fun
oh wait the Hawaii one no I was no
Hawaii was awesome other than the fact
that I got my heart broken in Hawaii but
what my girlfriend at the time I found
out in Hawaii yeah
okay thanks remember this Hawaii yes for
sure best time like does I really that
was just a really good like bonding time
yeah it was a great we got our own day
yeah yeah yeah we don't have to go to my
thing why didn't I mean if you don't
want to we don't have to but I do
basically okay remember that day we
actually were doing a photo shoot yes
the first day and then the day before we
actually were celebrating DOM and
Dietrich's and Andrews birthday yes the
dinner so that night I had like a really
bad feeling in my gut and I was like cuz
my girl went out my girlfriend at the
time went out that night
but then just don't see ya and then she
yeah I just felt like you know you got a
just gut feeling yep had a gut feeling
oh but then for most part I'm like just
worried about her well-being cuz I know
she was going now she's drink above abla
long story short
woke up that morning got on the phone
with her found out that she and then we
had to do that photo shoot I kind of
briefly yeah you remember and then I
kind of went downstairs in the lobby and
Nelson house up to everybody and then I
just couldn't hold it in so I went back
upstairs and I started like laughing
hysterically laughing like crying and
like I was like I just like was like
shocked I can't believe this and then
went back down and we did a photo shoot
okay well I don't remember that okay so
Hawaii wasn't that fun no no that was
for sure that was my best time well it
was fun
just wait why despite that yeah oh that
is why I am that is why I
on stage during uh I forgot one of the
songs that I did save this I had a song
called see this yeah and I choked up
during during the performance and a
project man this song is so deep yeah it
was really that moment Wow cuz I
remember writing that song not about a
specific person but then after the
moment after applied it applied and I
was like damn that correct okay so when
you do write songs it's not always
necessarily there is it's always
inspired by love obviously so a lot of a
lot of it is just different aspects but
sometimes it'll be personal and then
other times it'll be I'll know enough
from someone's perspective to write on
it or it intrigues me enough where I'll
be able to be like how would I how would
I react in this situation or right
that's interesting yeah yeah but go away
well I guess that would make sense
though I mean I think some of the best
music for whatever reason maybe it's
just my personality like I really like
really sad Oh tragedy alright great
heart horrible music don't tell them
just like just hurt me it's like damn
yeah I'm just like no but then you get
inspiration yeah you get it I'm like
that too
you just on a writing drought it's just
like I need to get I need to get my
heart broken just dating people just so
he can make good meal yo Taylor Swift
does that I think yeah that's what I
think too
Taylor Swift it loses its allure Swift
conspiracies she dates people only to
get her heart broken so that she can
write good music Wow
now we're on to you yeah we're on to you
t on to I feel like that's goodness with
a common thing that people assume for a
while okay that's good to know now your
favorite moment no Hawaii yeah yeah okay
you know you can't take mine that's true
I mean what else was there all I know is
the last where we did was exhausting it
was super exhausting I got the grant
love yeah
ciao - well we had people who kind of
organized
to save us money essentially were like
how much it was six shows yeah and try
to be the most cost effective
yeah we've been very because we didn't
you know we're trying to save money
there's a lot of us we got to put
everyone up in a hotel we gotta book the
venues we're all doing it on our own we
also needed like Maybachs and like
Mercedes anyway it it was that was a
tough tour cuz we were we didn't sleep I
got like well yeah really but he was
getting sick we didn't we would like
arrived in a city perform you know in
the morning early in the morning we
would you uh leave that night sometime
yeah we would do the rehearsal thing go
to a hotel or something for like two
hours hired thinking of it I know and
then we come back do the show do a
meeting greet it be like almost midnight
if there was an event we have to go to
the event after and the flight was like
a few hours after that so there was no
hotel really it was just like that for
like two weeks straight that's everybody
was mad and grouchy every everyone was
and that was that was the last tour we
did I was thinking I don't want to ever
do a tour again not just with you know
why Jeff just in general I was just like
after that experience is that I wouldn't
say that's when ytf ended but it was it
was a catalyst I think yeah I had to
hurt I feel that yeah I like the jackets
though she was like to try like all the
judges jackets were so expense I never
wore it except for all the black and
Golden's were a little bit better all
the black those red ones though imagine
if we got all of them together and sold
it as a package five bucks for those who
don't know why TF was a group that we
started right like I was saying a bunch
of guys it will consisted of me and
junior d-trix KevJumba Chester C for
dinner Victor Kim said it business Evan
was that seven I don't remember
you know KevJumba keV
Chester d-trix Victor Andrew Andrew
Andrew and later we do
for no we didn't forget Andrew Andrew
Chrissy was also on American Idol yes
what did he make top he's number one in
my heart so is the most successful one
in that season so whatever yeah he is
who even knows who won this I don't even
know actually it's probably someone
who's doing well but we just don't know
who it is
no no hate on that but Andrew Garcia
yeah anyway Andrew was also part of it
and then Tim kind of joined us at the
very end oh yes I remember yeah yeah
Tim delageteau I'm watering out yes
people who don't know and yeah like I
said it was a bunch of guys at the time
not that we didn't allow girls in it was
just at the time when we formed it
that's what who was around it's very
casual this guy's all right I want to
ask one what was like one of the
craziest ytf stories you've never told
but you feel like you know it's been a
while it's been a while I think I can
let another we haven't told any real
stories but we never talked about
anything really
or individually or as a group you see
why TF story yeah like was there ever
like one night where just like 70
strippers came into like a hotel room
thing not from my experience they were
all dudes either boring them oh yeah no
I mean we just were tired but you know
exhausting that was yeah we never really
did anything crazy what well we're lame
honestly the most that we ever did was
when they when everyone lived in North
Hollywood and we just we literally just
hung out I just yeah we're in the rooms
playing video games or watching movies
yeah that's it no we're super boring
nice little pirate bread boy you go to
Panera Bread down the street that looks
like our exciting day like hey don't eat
the Greek food like that one spot oh
yeah
yo yo we're lame down no.not I hear it
back it what's kinda lame we didn't do
what our tours I mean I think most the
time we were literally just doing video
like we really were just having fun
making videos yeah this literally like
it's like how could for the most part
we're literally just doing how what can
we do to be creative and help each other
to make
videos make whatever idea come true and
a lot of stuff we didn't even put on
camera like a lot of freestyle stuff do
like we'd start we'd make each other
laugh so hard too much to date yet too
much laughing we had to stop it no I do
think though why cuz people always ask
why did why tfn and I think the catalyst
to that was because of that tour and at
the same time that's when keV he's
booked that Cartoon Network thing he was
on like doing some Cartoon Network not a
show but he was like hosting or to
network a little bit and so he wasn't on
that tour so already it became six
people from seven yeah and you know not
saying that it's because of cab that's
white anything bud but that is like I
think it's around that tour yeah it was
just too much it's a lot for one I just
didn't I was just a host like I didn't
like I think it I think I think it also
started when you when you start I think
it was the when you start bringing
business and friendship into each other
and not having the clear distinction
between the two we didn't start it as a
business yeah yeah there's no
infrastructure that were like a
communication exactly communication
number one for anything yeah
communication now people know weren't
talking no communication yeah we're just
seeing not talking all right well I mean
that's pretty cool well crazy story I'd
literally don't have one it's fine if
you don't have well the thing is there's
individual drama in the group that
happened at towards the end most of us
were all friends but I don't wanna I
don't know until they come on the show
oh can we thank you a whole ytf like
podcast episode now we don't got enough
cameras Andrew will sit on my lap to do
a reunion no I mean we could a breaking
news we're gonna have a just kidding
anyway yeah we're not gonna do that
yeah anyway I think what do we at we're
not at the 30 minute break already
oh wow that was fast that's quick
alright then I guess it's time for a she
break she she we still need a way to get
into that we haven't figured that out
you guys have a song can you sing it she
she break make it up right
freestyle he goes a shishi break alright
that's hard oh yeah I could have sang a
better sorry guys don't do another and
go here goes a she she break that's
beautiful
[Music]
and we're back back from the CCU break
back from the shi shi break back from
the CC break yeah we're back from the CC
the whole time we were like getting
ready to go again I felt inspired I know
I liked it anyway we're back from the
shi shi break we oh before we go into
that should we just use that as the
jingle no I don't mean we don't feel
[Music]
obligatory get back into the future
version and there's like oh we changed
some notes that's how things work
the main dialect is Tagalog there's
another one though right there's a
lock-on oh that's like a lot of rounds a
lot of ones I think and this is ion yeah
but yeah there's no there's like a lot
my dad speaks six times so but there's
like other one is hundreds really
thousands that's just words no but it's
like different regions they have
different it's almost like yeah it's
like let's say like even in um like in
America we have people from the Midwest
for most like acts those like slangs or
like it's almost like this it's like cuz
like in certain dialects they don't like
pronounce like certain letters and all
that stuff I see it's just stuff like
little things like that and then just
even words like in a hole in Pigeon we
don't pronounce ours at the end yeah
words like like mo yeah mo bettah which
is Obama are better mo Bamba
it's almost like yeah he's a big song
it's a song Bamba has his own song yeah
oh sorry you can't do that song we're
gonna get copyrighted song he's like a
rookie
oh no second year I think that's really
that bill okay so I believe I ran across
a video where the guy was saying that he
name is Jack would ya check was the
rapper was actually knows the guy he's
like yeah and yeah and then mobile was
like oh yeah put me in a song put me in
a song and literally literally name the
whole song about damn and he slaps dude
it is a bad you love it but I think huge
fan I like you the most
there's a Twitter video that I saw they
weren't viral and mobile now they drop
he drop the n-bomb and in a couple of
times but this Twitter video had like
I'd say at least a hundred
oh I kid and it's all about the games no
in well games too but in a jumping like
a large trampoline gymnast area and
they're playing that and all these
little kids are like singing along with
the song and then wow yeah right is the
n-word just like they're all like oh
yeah like seeing like the basketball
games and you see like college like you
know college games get intense and they
are saying it and I'm like people can do
that I mean they're not supposed to what
you're looking and you'd be like I'll be
like damn these guys don't care one of
the college games the red isn't that
part was a bother to come up there's a
black guy filming that he filmed another
black guy in the crowd and the black I
was like I always thought like yeah I
mean you just stay away from it in
general yeah but I mean I guess if it's
not in that context in a negative way
it's they're literally they're not st.
they're not creating the word they're
just repeating yeah like what is it like
ya know I mean I feel like like what if
you got a Kanye West we we are not for
we're for sure not the ones to decide
decide yes
but cuz like at the I just avoided yeah
yeah cuz that end of the day we don't
have the yeah it's not us affecting yeah
it's not our word yeah so like if if you
could avoid it just do it
uh-huh I think that's the thing I mean
every even I was even thought like even
black people not say it - because it's
like demeaning - especially then right
like I mean I I've seen both sides yeah
obviously where it's almost become a
part of the language but those there's
like between the black community are
already fight about that yeah X some
people say you shouldn't say it and then
I see because the argument is like that
the argument is that like they took that
word which was negative and creative
right right at their own which was like
a word of endearment amongst themselves
that's why other cultures feel like they
can say it because it's like oh this is
not a negative thing but it stems from
something like that
so I can see why people would sing yeah
but it's also and I think it's also
coupled with when people say without
education being educated about the world
and I think that's the main problem is
like why you don't even you don't
understand
yeah what comes with that you haven't
earned the right now and why don't we
never will you know what I mean cuz we
don't we don't have that we don't know
the history we don't know we don't know
what that actually means to be that it
also changes over time - yeah like like
even back in in especially in Hawaii for
us like I said the fa G word on a video
and I was like I didn't think anything
of it
yeah it didn't have the same meaning
that it did now granted back then being
gay wasn't as popular I guess or X as
accepted but I didn't associate that
with gay people I just thought like oh
that meant something else like it's like
oh if you're feminine if you're acting
feminine I thought that's what I thought
that's what it was I didn't know you
didn't know that the word itself had a
negative had I known what I know now
back then of course no better yeah but
it's just how in over time and back then
- people didn't think much of it yeah
either like gay people didn't think much
no so for me because I'm from Hoya as
well and then like there are people who
are called ma who's which are kind of
like it's kind of like um
offensive isn't it no supposedly it
isn't least in the comments that from
the other one but it's kind of like a
Hawaiian word for that in a way but not
as offensive and I used to get called
the f-word by them so I was like hmm
what is his word now so I didn't even
think it was like associated so much
like game stuff I just thought it was
like an insult I was like damn dude they
got me they're gonna call me that and I
guess it's not that bad but they got me
yeah so it's just it's weird how it um
things just change everything maybe
there's a word we said today that when
they watch this podcast ten years -
really then they said he went for a
gender joke he's seen as something we
gonna do you see mess of the week we
haven't done it I like that that was
that's when we was it peace eNOS of the
week I thought you almost Sarah penis
you know that's the point
oh that's the thing okay we had issues
earlier with Paco not recording when we
were talking anyway oh you know we you
know what we need to do before we forget
was last time we ran out of time let's
get into the Twitter questions people
had some questions for junior questions
where can they follow through Twitter
what's up oh yeah at off the pill on
Twitter and on Instagram it's at off the
pill podcast alright because someone
took a or it's @jr Aquino aqu Ino or how
else would you say you I like when you
say my name
a queen oh no you does not yeah yeah
that's me I made that up for you you're
welcome to using beef the first question
we have we
a couple okay Kyra Arata
what's one important lesson or thing
Ryan learned from junior and vice versa
one important so yes it something that
you guys have learned from each other
that you feel like you can really credit
the other person oh for sure go ahead
my thing with Ryan it's it's literally
anything you put your mind to you can
you can accomplish that's what I taught
you
yeah I know I think it's not necessarily
teaching but you taught by example but
just doing stuff you have he embedded
into you yeah you already had the
mindset but yeah see someone do it yeah
to see honor on a constant consistent
level and you that's what I mean that's
that whenever I think of people that
have longevity and and someone that puts
their mind to something cuz if people
don't know if you were following Ryan
and you don't already know this anything
Ryan wants to do he will end up doing
and do it fairly well that's not
necessarily right whatever that's right
games whatever you're not allowed to but
yeah I think that I don't think that's
the gotta be be in that one haha well I
mean why don't I think what you're
referring to because we have I mean you
have mentioned this before and what the
thing that you taught me for one is just
a run is no just just in general about
music it's so like literally I knew
nothing like I don't know what a harmony
I didn't know what harmony was you're
the one who taught me that
oh you if you go just like two notes
above mmm the other note or was it two
notes it's something like that I was not
like that's what I would I would take
all of that could I'm just like why does
this sound a certain way and I never
understood why things sound that way and
then when I heard you and Andrew singing
together you would explain to me that
it's just
oh he sings this I sing this and it
sounds like this yeah yeah and it's like
two notes above harmonizes with the
whatever you're singing yeah I learned
all this music stuff and I was so
interested down to like what runs were
obvious like how do you do that with
your voice when you're just singing
annoying it's like going up and down or
whatever do you run I can't do it you're
always doing Dom literally do the same
now I haven't done it in so long
um yeah I mean that's that's because
we're doing it so much that it became
easy to do who does fire huh in any way
I like that what is the run that they do
and then maybe he can I merely remember
I don't remember either singer singer
he's same sings he's trying to sing sing
he sings sings yeah shout of TD jakes
yeah get on the podcast well basically
it just means because we were all around
this goes back to why it's a freegan
we're all around like dancers so people
were trying to learn dance moves we were
on singers so we try to learn that me
and Kev we didn't do anything that was a
lie no but I mean in you guys were
singers right you Andrew Victor Conti
singing and dance Chester the singer Dom
was a dancer Victor was a dancer like
when we did shows me and Kev were just
like garbage we're just hopes like we
just like build time between the good
stuff dances and stuff and sketches yeah
but we weren't dancers or singers like
you had talent in itself yeah no but I
think what he's saying is that what he
does isn't widely accepted as an art
form exactly we could bring people to
the seats but you guys were the
entertainment we filled the time in
between that our performance was
literally just hey nice to meet you it's
so great to meet you good to meet you at
the end for the show but I think it
speaks volumes to how how great you guys
are at what you do because they
literally wanted to see you guys too
most but it's like I mean if you watch
somebody a lot it was just a great it
was a great time to just like get some
fans and be like amen I sing oh wow
a lot of people were shocked I think
like a lot like there's a bunch of
people obviously who heard I already
knew who you guys were
yeah but then there's some people who
would come and be like holy crap this
guy can sing like these guys are real
this is not like YouTube performance
this is like real performers yeah I mean
you're youtubers but now they don't
didn't know that you guys were like I
don't really legit perform mean there's
there's there is that um there is that
mindset of or that perception of like
what a
youtuber is yeah and the the stand I
mean I think across the board even with
just like actors or whatever if you're
on YouTube you're kind of seemed like
below a mainstream yeah yeah and I mean
to a certain degree especially back then
it was justified I mean there was some
shows shows I won't even call them shows
yeah where it's just people it's
basically just a meeting great yeah yeah
but we there was a you guys were
actually performing that's what you guys
did for a living we tried to have
production that I've tried we tried and
even our show I think like we at least
we tried saw effort yeah
but anyway that's something I would say
out the whole music thing which actually
made a big impact on my career cuz I
started doing like music videos and
stuff one of the first ones we did
together was I'm always horrors kill all
the videos yeah hardcore was the first
we did one with David and you
I remember you we were filming that
video and and and you were on a boat we
need this footage like this was that one
of the first things I do with David
actually ever anyway next question we
went we went you have another one see
Loremaster 666 or Johnny X was a devil
yeah asked was there a defining moment
where you said this is it I want to
become a singer Oh hmm cuz I'm sure
during your career there there's
actually been different levels of like
this is what I want to do and it was
like a grand idea and then now you're
like Oh more specifically this is what I
want to do you know whether YouTube
being popped off you're like oh I want
to do this and now when you found out
cuz you talked a little bit off you're
telling him when he wanted to be ya know
I want to hear well might actually know
the it actually happened before all the
auditioning all that YouTube's dug it
was I think I was 12 or 13 mmm and I saw
this I saw the first season of American
Idol and I was like Kelly Clarkson yeah
Kelly Clarkson's season and I would
literally wash it and I was like oh I
want to do that and then I was just a
matter of waiting yeah
and I don't see I didn't teach you that
you already did that before I may know
what it was like but you know um but no
cuz you know seeing it on a level other
than just music and sign right right
and a personal level I think that's yeah
when you see someone that you admire and
respect so it's right yeah but for sure
when I was like 12 or 13 and I saw that
I was like oh man I want to do this and
then I guess moving on then so at what
point are you now where you're like this
is the type of singer that you want to
be you know there's like oh yeah yeah
yeah like genre wise and all that stuff
like what kind of music I want to like
write and all that yeah I think um I you
know I grew up on like R&B I listen to
everything but I'm like majority is like
R&B pop kind of thing so but I also just
love I just like I write from personal
experience so it's a lot about love so
um I think once I picked up like once I
picked up a guitar I was like okay what
what am I gonna write about I don't know
how to write about like things I don't
know yeah so everything's pretty
heartfelt I guess I that's kind of
that's the kind of music I write so
you're mushy [ __ ] love y'all shoutout
Anchorage was good diamond high was good
that's where you went I mean I had Donna
high link Spangler kid Oh use your your
voice in school to be cooler in school
we had kids like that in our school who
could sing American Idol I mean okay no
I sang in school but I wasn't like the
one um I didn't like use it to like you
were more popular than not though I
wouldn't I mean I I was the I was the
kind of kid in in high school where I
was like part of a bunch of groups like
the guy that the floater yeah that's me
do ya I was like one of those one of
those guys I had my core group but then
I was also like just jumping around Hey
jocks and all that I wasn't allowed in
those emotions you beat up girl has
stuck to saying they just remember you
from the
just that group then were you always in
the front of the line forever like I
think kindergarten no I think anybody
just be sure you're not this guy do not
cut traffic same thing like roll your
window down real quick is it okay to
continue a little bit more on this yeah
go ahead I want to do a little deeper
okay so you talked about this outside
before okay how there was a moment about
a year and a half ago yes where you
realized and I think is because of a
breakup yeah oh I I really needed to
decide what I want to do with my life
yeah I mean I'm more or less it was like
um it's not necessarily what I wanted to
do with my life but knowing what I need
to do and assessing like my life at the
moment was like oh I mean yeah falling
off you have a hiatus like you know you
did not do anything and you're in this
position in your career right now
because you have not done the things
that necessary to keep it going hmm
and at that moment I was like okay you
know after the breakup okay I'm I after
a long after a long relationship is like
five and a half years you know you kind
of become codependent at a point right
um so after the breakup I was like okay
I don't know how to function by myself
but then I was like I can either just
quit I remember there was a part of me
was like oh my god
till last night I actually thought about
it for a little bit yeah for like a good
week and I was like no no so um that was
the moment I was okay I could either do
that or I can be here and just start
creating and start making music again
mm-hmm and from that moment on I haven't
looked back and it's been great so
you're like I just saw recently you post
about how you have like I forget what
number it was but like over a million
Spotify was it plays or oh no yeah a
year like yeah because they always do
like a year wrap-up thing I think like
well it's crazy cuz I'm Spotify
specifically it was like when I first
started that first year I think I maybe
only had 40,000 I had the stupid thing
where I didn't upload my music like it
literally has not been on Spotify or
anything for the past 10 years Wow yeah
I was late
you're dumb I missed all that bag I'm
biased Joe all the bags but whatever you
can't
yesterday today the other day but yeah
it was uh yeah I remember when I first
started the first year it's it's tripled
since the since the urine Avco right um
so it's been good I mean yeah and I
actually just recently put out an EP too
so if y'all want to check out shameless
plug got out we started I was gonna ask
you about that actually that's the way
so and not just that EP in general cause
it would name the EP it's your last the
fifth song on that there's five songs
what we started what we started named it
that I really like the one right before
the the fourth one was the fourth one I
think that was either I think a Great
Escape
no this is there that I think it's great
escape it sounds more familiar ah
well regardless you're not sexy I like
that whatever the fourth one was I
remember being like oh this is all great
escape yeah then what we started and
then that's the name of your album and I
always wondered like why don't they just
put the best song name the best song
after the album and put it first so
everybody knows like oh this is the one
everybody knows and now and I always
wondering like how do you decide on what
the name yes and what's the name the
album is for one and then why do you put
it last I guess last makes more sense
but sometimes it's like in the middle of
the album um well I can't well I mean
for me specifically what we started
actually what we started was I wrote
that like five years ago a long time
shout out to Jessie Barrera and Jay bird
they helped me put this project together
and as far as like picking this the name
of the project I was just like if I felt
fitting what we started just seemed like
something that spoke to me where I was
like you know what where where I've been
going where I came from and where I'm
going to go and I
wanted to pay homage to that so what we
started kind of felt like that also this
project is kind of like a bunch of my
influences in one thing so like design
like the first opening track is like
it's very different from yeah it's very
it but it's also very like JT like
Justin Timberlake and sing very pop so
that's something I love the group on
that but then you also have Great Escape
which is very kind of like Latin R&B and
I also that reminds me of like early
2000s R&B which is like um there's an
usher song that called how do I say that
super inspired that and then you have
what we started the title track which is
kind of kind of like a Drake feel the
way the beat the beat is um but yeah
that's how I that's that's why I chose
that as the title but as far as the
order um kind of just seeing how the
flow was oh it's really just a flow
crazy yeah I always wondered that
because a lot of times like every artist
they like name their album something and
it's not necessarily the one that's the
hit yeah yeah you know sometimes they
even name it and it's not even a song
yeah exactly yeah yeah for me yeah I
just did it as a flow thing cuz my thing
I was like okay
how do I want to capture someone's a
year I got it and then I put design in
the front cuz like once that beat hit
you're like okay alright well going get
what do you follow on Spotify oh you can
you can add my song to a playlist you
can follow that's better something yeah
add it on to a playlist yeah and or buy
it on iTunes I'm sure there anything
it's on all all streaming al digital
platform there you go if you haven't
heard jr. before he is one of the best
vocalists that I know personally no but
I mean Ryan I won't say that you you
guys haven't hung out in like a long
time like a couple of years or so and
then the one night you came back and
we're all just chilling and then you
left after Ryan was like damn I missed
Jr's voice I sang for like a little bit
I was like damn I used to get this all
the time used to hang out all the other
place and I would hear him sing I took
it for granted dude as I did took you
for granted singers and stuff like you
like get so used to it and just like oh
when you doing here for a long time when
here at live it's like wow this sounds
like a track hmm so like I mean I think
if you haven't her
jay-ar before go check him out it you
would not I guess you kind of just heard
him singing this you should predicts it
do not base that the perfect
representation here are singing yes I
want to know this real quick though yeah
you ever make love to your own music no
that would be super awkward
what yeah okay okay get it but but
that's okay let's say a like you get in
the mood y'all yes
the moves getting set and then out of
nowhere you just say hi like no and it's
not coming from me that would be crazy
actually be more crazy or crazier you
actually singing Kanye does that
wouldn't be surprised yeah he's like a
service that knew banging Mia and they
came out do it yeah I can see it's just
like him do you like it she's like I
guess now no you know who's wild I bet
you you know it does could get away with
it Chris Brown
like I could see him doing like and then
he like starts krumping like before he
get started yeah yeah I already talked
about the the other part of YouTube
right we talked about it already
YouTube monetize you're gonna see that
is new that's the new that's a new what
do you call it option on YouTube
monetization probably the most they
could what how about they do that they
making YouTube uncut and they'd start
paying for that premium that would be
cool they're a very welcome a target
targeted playlist of just very
disturbing video no it was there was
sites like that like that's kind of like
um like memory bombs world or they
wouldn't really break-ins yeah yeah like
really like damn I can't believe I just
saw that kind of stuff no you could
never see that you'd be gone like
incident yeah yeah you know on that note
dude it's good to see you again man so
well do you have any plugs that you want
to do one more time um new album new
yeah new EP what we saw you have any
shows um if you're in Vegas I'll
probably be sure I'm gonna be throwing a
show on April 5th
just follow me on my Instagram or
Twitter its JR aquino um just right
there and yeah I mean other than that
that's it man
all right well again follow us at off
the pill on Twitter and at off the pill
we gotta make it so it's the same thing
we should message I think we should wait
which which one it doesn't not have the
off the puffs the pill is just Twitter
at off the pill on Twitter at off the
pill podcast on Instagram who has it on
that I don't know we'll try and get it
back anyway follow us on that Oh shirts
we have a shirt too now time for those
that are just listening you won't know
but I'm off the pillow shirts just
shouting that out there's another one
but I don't I don't have the right size
anyway yes
once again thanks for tuning in to the
off the pill podcast I don't know if you
see how we end these but um we just
breathe into the mic no not yet
Oh what are Teaneck next podcast am I
missing anything no yeah we're still
learning
oh they're still they'll come next time
you come back on this will be like pros
I'm done or you guys are so great this
time around anyway
let's close this out and then we can go
eat all right thanks again for tuning
the dollar bill uh guys
your music guy you know this is bad for
the mic right yeah anyway dope