holy crap they're gonna pay me this much
money just to make a video and I just
completely sold out yeah yeah and oh I
support gay marriage or saying like just
saying that you're gonna get heat either
way yeah yeah so you might as well just
make both sides hate you and say you
don't and you do accept that people hate
them love them bring on the hate all
right we we're all good you roll every
cameras good are we doing the claps
claps we only need why why dude it's so
loud in our headsets come on
is that our intro the clap claps that's
the clap claps we got the clap claps we
got beeps well we but we need the clap
claps to sync if people don't know it's
not we're not just applauding ourselves
yeah it's to sync up the audio with the
video yeah anyway welcome to the first
off the pill podcast it's not the it's
not the first one I'm a liar it's not
the first one we've done we've done -
actually we've done three I posted two
on the second channel one was with just
us I think and then we did one with
David David Choi a lot of you guys
really liked it but we stopped doing it
for a very long time oh yeah I'm sorry
there's a third one that we did with
Derek but I don't was unsalvageable
it's Derek you know we went a little
off-topic it was almost like I don't
know what to do with this video we've
been experimenting yeah we've just been
experimenting you know yet inside the
mind of Ryan Higa yep that podcast was
basically inside the mind of Derek it
well it was but I also felt like he was
trying to channel someone else's mind
one day we might I might just post it
one day just because it'll be funny sure
but I feel like we should not be posed
in that kind of pocket yeah it's a long
format yeah no we're getting used to it
anyway we are figuring it out and this
is the first one it's not I already said
this is technically the first one on
this channel yeah but it's not the first
one how did I how did how do we we don't
even have an intro nope
anyway I think we should stick with the
clapping thing I mean we already did it
oh okay off to a good start
I guess you can just say I just want to
give that intro because this is the
first one so you want to intro the
guests so the guests I guess I don't
know if you guys are always gonna be
here we're still figuring out we got to
get I think we already have a bunch of
guests that we have coming up I don't
know if it's smart to say who it is yet
but um you guys already know Paco you
guys already know will and you guys
might know me yeah okay well and also
for people who don't know it's called
off the pill podcast if you don't know
that by now which is a little strange
while you're watching this it's because
that whole thing started when I started
ranting on videos without taking my meds
I have ADHD I don't take my meds
sometimes and when I do that I start
talking in circles and talking about
random things and that's what this
podcast is all about you know just
having fun talking about random things
really is an important and important
issues unstructured no they're
structured bar faris structure what are
you talking about I mean there is
structure within unstructured we all
clapped boom every single time in the
beginning we always clap that structure
and we breathe in
that's our closer yeah we're not we're
still figuring this we have two things
basically that are structured everything
in the middle okay
well it's only our first one technically
fourth one because we're not posting the
Derg one yeah we're not talking about
anything by the way let's get into it
what do we have on the agenda okay we
have so many things to cover because
we've never covered anything yep well
why don't we talk about something that's
you know kind of hot right now
ooh it's a skinning uh what do you wait
what you trying to you made that gate
sound dirty so no I just meant a hot
topic oh you want talk about hot topics
it's very when I was a kid I was
actually scared of hot meat see my mom
wouldn't let me go in there
ya know honestly I know really not
scared but I I couldn't know I was I was
scared yeah it definitely was fright
frightening for unless if we get
sponsored by a hot topic yeah speaking
of which let's thank our sponsors for
today hot topic that's not true I don't
know if that's even legal for me to say
that we're not SWAT not topic is not
sponsoring this
we have no sponsors we have no money but
if you'd like to sponsor this podcast
you could reach this email right here
your commercial could be just like this
have you ever wanted to go and get
something that's kind of scary to kids
but also really cool to some kids that
are outcasts
does that sound bad well then go to
topics are us hot topics this that could
be you this is the essence of off the
pill podcast we tried to start something
I know and we absolutely failed and went
somewhere else with it
people don't know this to it people
don't know this too but we've actually
done more that that we never people
would never see because we were just
experimenting and they're just trash
kind of like this one back to Paco
while we talk a little bit about brand
deals cuz that seems to be something
that a lot of everyone has yeah yeah are
going into it I know except uh you've
kind of been someone that has steered
away from that type of content and my I
personally I'm very interested in that
you told we've talked a little bit about
it but I think a lot of the audience do
would be like how does Ryan make money
on YouTube since the ad pocalypse you
know I mean it's not as good and I
haven't I really don't do that many
sponsorship deals because I always base
the content around I mean you guys know
I've always based it around just if the
ad interferes with the funny or the
story then I'm not gonna do it I get I
get asked to do stuff like probably
every day like multiple inquiries
alright reflex but okay
is that a flex it is that's what
continue continue continue I don't know
what that means I know you're we're
gonna go ADHD right now continue on the
band you're the one who threw me off I
didn't take my fault what are you
talking about you're talking about
brownie like some people ask you
everyday
oh okay yeah people send or that is a
flex it is it's not that weird though
it's normal for youtubers anyway as I
was saying before someone interrupted my
flight ever I was talking about yeah we
get that all the time
I get that sent in random enquiries and
most I would say like ninety-nine out of
a hundred are things that I don't really
care for don't really know or I
find a way to make it funny or it's just
a ridiculous off like it's like nothing
or they just want like sometimes it's
just like hey you mind making a video
for us we don't have any money but you
know this I think we think this you'll
like this product like well I mean if I
really liked it I would use it but that
it felt like I said it comes down to
like can you make it interesting
mm-hmm that's how I choose sponsored it
this that's why there's almost none yeah
and yeah it would be nice to have some
it would be it would we could upgrade
our mics not if you sound horrible right
they're actually pretty good and rolled
shout the road this is not a sponsorship
but they did send this free free stuff
so that's why we have this set up yeah
so thank you very much Road yeah not a
sponsorship nope because it's still
waiting for you one thing too that I've
noticed like brands and will try to
reach out to you the process is very
slow
you know yeah and the way that Ryan
works is is within like a week
he thinks of idea we film it and edit it
and if if that holds back like the brand
or the deal holds it back in any way
it's very hard to commit to it you know
cuz it's like what is it it's time it's
a balance between like you know doing
our own thing and the time that is
involved right with working with them
and going through that process
it's a long process it's really long and
yeah I've also worked with other
youtubers as well and cool
well wasabi and when they were doing
brand deals and stuff a lot of times
yeah those brands would see a completed
project and they'd be like we don't like
this right we want something else that's
also a big thing that I always try and I
wouldn't say negotiate but that's like a
must I always have to say like I want
the creative control and a lot of times
brands don't want to give you that yeah
cuz they want to make sure their brand
if they're paying for it they want to
make sure like it's all about them yeah
exactly
so that's why for me it's just every all
these things have to line up for me to
be able to do it but in a podcast way
easier form this way easier yeah just
talk about it but even with that I would
still want products that I actually like
I don't want to be like I don't want to
name any
I don't want to like talk about X
product and that product I don't even
like yeah you know like oh that's a
crappy thing cuz I like this other one
better but because they're paying me I'm
gonna talk like because it's like you're
signing off on it you're like it
sourcing it in a way exactly and you're
and then it people use it or buy it and
it's bad it's just like your opinion
means nothing yeah if it's a bad product
but you have the luxury of doing that as
well what do you mean where you're in a
comfortable space yeah it's yeah I mean
it so it would be it's comfortable
spaces that is a debatable at the answer
yeah yeah yeah who you're talking about
because I think overall you're in a lot
more of a comfortable spot than most
people of course yeah yeah than most
people so you're you have the ability to
make those decisions and not be like oh
I'll give up a little bit of my morals
or values to do this sponsorship yes
yeah I would say so
yeah but I mean I've done things that
I'm not proud of who she would go into
that I'm not proud of maybe like what is
if you want to talk about what's the
most positive experiences with brands or
ones that you've kind of look back on
and said like that was good and you know
it's fun and I mean there's the thing is
it's tough because I don't know which
ones I've signed contracts with that I
can't talk about there's just a part of
that how about let's talk about the
positive in like which one did you enjoy
the most
I don't know there's a lot of them you
know what a good examples like the
fortnight video right I had the idea and
I went to them actually they didn't come
to me I was like hey I have this idea do
you have some kind of budget so I can
make this you know better yeah and I
went to Epic Games yeah yeah epic games
well I kind of met like a middle person
but we made that deal happen and that
was it's easier that way because I can
present them my idea rather than being
like hey you have to say our name this
many times you got to show this much
gameplay and like that's that's the kind
of stuff that's I could turn off to me
right but I mean I I had yeah I've had
some bad experience it when I'm not bad
it's just like I've had ones in the past
when I started like
in high school yeah I did my first brand
deals I was just like holy crap they're
gonna pay me this much money just to
make a video and I just completely sold
out yeah yeah and people were pissed
back then people kids way different
hated ads you know like how I never
understood that you know how like back
then I don't know if they'd still have
hints but when like skateboarders you
liked got sponsored you big holy crap
he's legit like that's dope Congrats
that's awesome right back when YouTube
first was starting if you got a
sponsorship of any kind people were
pissed at you like I don't know if you
guys remember that time I was like mm
between 5 and I guess 9 and 10 right I
remember we all did this Carl's jr. deal
I remember the Mater made our own
mushroom basically what about portobello
mushroom burger yeah we did this ad
all of us did one in our own way and we
all had to post at the same time and I
thought it was funny I mean I was having
fun with it everybody seemed like they
were doing their own versions but people
were like pissed they were so mad
oh you guys are sellouts and all this
stuff I was like yeah okay it was a lot
of money but I think at the same time
it's because this is at the time there's
a new platform it was like wow these
guys have so much like creative control
and like they're doing what they want to
do that's great and then to see I guess
a corporate that's come in there it's
it's change its new to it yeah you're
just a little too close to Mike that
time Danny got scolded dude the first
scoring of the off the building was
gasps he's a loudest person most also
their closest I think that's even better
sounds more balanced we're talking about
a corporate yeah yeah I see that
perspective but now it's crazy how it's
changed like honestly I even felt back
then I felt like for me I didn't do that
many after that and I kind of learned
but like I wanted people if I was
working with a brand it had to be
somebody my followers would be like
happy about yeah holy crab you gots it
like like the Nintendo and I just did
like I actually love I've always loved
intends and most people do
I think they grew up like our age grew
up with Nintendo games and stuff
like that I feel like that's something I
felt okay this is just cool I've always
wanted to work with them same with like
I would work with I don't know just
things that people like or I guess our
age group I don't know if people are
still what I mean with phonetics over it
like how we were I think this is which
is popularity kind of like a lot of
people are gravitating towards that now
you're kind of far Joe Rogan says just
official Rogan did say that he always is
like swish that is one of the reasons
why I like podcast I love Joe Rogan for
sure I think like was this along like me
two three years ago yeah it's not a long
time but a couple years ago I wrote an
email to his thing to his like media
email really didn't get a response what
did you say I was just like I was
actually pitching to him for to do this
other idea this was like back when the
drama stuff was starting to happen yeah
this is before nobody really knows this
but I even I hit up Joe Rogan and
Julianne from Jenna and Julianne right
because I wanted to do a show that was
kind of based around fighting between
these people these drama channel because
I was so sick of all like the they were
all like district there was no fights at
the time yeah I was like damn imagine if
we had all these people having drama and
they just like really fought like we sit
up at UFC like Celebrity Deathmatch but
not death yeah you know and I had this
idea I sent a very basic version no not
a pitch I just kind of said oh I think
you'd be great for this I would love to
work with you I'm a fan of your podcast
like how you think like I think it's
brilliant
and I sent that over in the email a
couple years ago I don't know when
exactly it was just before there was
actual fights and right like I would say
it within half a year that first fight
was announced it was alright it's been
done great yeah the real question is did
Julian respond Julian did respond yeah
he thought it was a good idea because
Julian's all down he's down for he's
down for us to fight yeah I mean I said
one guy would never do jujitsu it I mean
I would do it but I wouldn't like he's
too big and
grab some sleeves with him what did that
mean yeah what is it it was just like a
term I made up totally grab sleeves head
twitch card I was like Julian grab some
sleeves and he was like what a car like
that grab their sleeves oh you big ears
yeah yeah Oh what were you thinking of I
don't know like the sleeve like yes like
UFC nobody has sleeves yeah well it was
a jujitsu joke yeah I mean that's the
collar yeah trying to grab sleeves
that's the sleeve is over here like okay
well what are you grabbing then you grab
their sleeve you know that you're
talking about the collar no no you can
grab sleeves in jujitsu
yeah of course yeah dude let's grab
sleep stop trying to make that happen
cuz it's gonna happen
all right let's try it's like keep those
move let's grab sleeves let's leave that
alone
alone so that was brands you get another
topic sorry it's just an interesting
thing we don't have to like abruptly
stopped it stop it
you know what's another brand that I
don't know if I should say this as I
feeling it in trouble for it but I don't
care my podcast I can say whatever what
day you get them you know it upsets me a
little bit mines my ears grab someone's
sleeve I'm here and they are Swedish
guess who is it PewDiePie no as I was
fishing you into that it is IKEA so when
I was in LA I went to Ikea I mean
obvious everybody knows the hype right
early IKEA and I wasn't I think I'm one
of the very small majority the minority
not majority one of the minority I'm
part of a minority that is not a big fan
of IKEA what and I've never been meaning
I got all my stuff after the first time
I bought all my stuff for LA from Ikea
and had to build all of it the next like
two days after that I was like I'm never
going here again well that's if they
want to sponsor this part just kidding
nope because let me tell you why later
down the road not only was a lot of the
stuff you know Breaking and some of that
and that's probably my fault for how I'm
eating their product
are bad because they actually have great
a lot of this stuff in here well not all
of it actually not this stuff but
there's other in the other house yeah
it's a lot of IKEA products in there
even the bed that you took for me
remember yeah there was a lot of IKEA
products and they work fine but um a lot
of them would break and I think it's
probably the way I built it yeah that's
exactly my point like I feel like IKEA
is a grocery store for furniture hmm and
like I just want to go to the restaurant
got it you know that's a great analogy
right yeah I thought of all people yeah
yeah I went in there and I instantly saw
the only things I really buy from Ikea
or things like this this is from this I
think this little thing in the
background you see how it's like metal
it's kind of like yeah this cabinet
looking thing yeah the cabinet like
anything like any other wood stuff or
like any of like that kind of stuff I
don't really buy coz it's just it's like
Ryan say it's like kind of falls apart
it's like kind of work too Dom has had
his for how many years well regardless
even if you build it right I'm sure a
lot of people do and it lasts for a long
time and maybe they just treat their
stuff better than I do but regardless I
just I just feel like if you're gonna
pay that much money you should they
should make it for you you shouldn't
like you don't go to a bakery and say
hey could I get some dough and some
sugar and and then oh I'm gonna have to
make this at home now it's been another
half a day no the reason why people go
to AI kids it's actually cheaper yeah
but how much cheaper like a significant
amount is it really it really is that's
where we differ is you don't like it
because you have to build it yeah I
don't like it is because it it's not
like I'd rather just spend more money
for something that's like higher call
like that a craftsman major yeah this
money making barrel I'm like cheap those
much money's I could save well no but I
like so Ione can compare this to another
store out here in Vegas it's like a
local place and they made products that
look just as good as IKEA stuff I think
it called Biggs something I don't know
yeah they made products just as good are
on the same price range I would say I
remember comparing at the time when I
was first getting furniture
they're very similar psyche if not
cheaper and those products are still
held together they're already made and
they do free delivery yeah I knew that I
don't know if it seems pretty big you
know what it is bigs yeah yeah yeah like
it's a big it's a big place big and it's
um good stuff man
yeah they deliver for free like people
come in to us put it where you want in
your house like what that that alone is
worth whatever more you got to pay to
Ikea to me and you save yourself a day a
day you could be working and making
money which is actually why you're
actually losing money by buying products
like that man they're never gonna work
with me huh well that's probably what
prove me wrong
yeah that's probably what that store
does to compete with a store like thank
you because right because like that name
like bomb meatballs they're they do have
good food their meatballs they do have
good fear
dude this sounds weird but I think Ike
is like a dope like second date yeah
that's not weird people already do that
yeah people should have dates there the
wall okay this is something that grabs
my sleeves what's what's going on right
now grab sleeve dude no I done already
is been done I just hate when other
people go to Ikea now and they're
filming pun video oh my dude daddy's
realiza do that and his wife she's like
one of the first people oh she did the
market one right and then someone did
like the IKEA names cuz they're so weird
well I have no idea who did but if
you're doing it now still oh just
weren't still do we know people are wait
didn't he do that no I didn't okay I
think you guys did know I definitely
kind of stuff if we went to Ikea we'd be
doing that but we wouldn't be filming
yeah you don't because we'd also just be
trying to like make each other cringe
yeah which puck is great at but I'm a
Class A yeah in charge I have like he's
been on a Ledge down teeth oh yeah you
are on the pewdiepie buys dude that's
how cringy you are I'm amazing dude dude
that is awesome I'm killing it man I
want to make the pewdiepie any list you
wish you could not good enough man get
on my cringe level
- speaking I should probably get off the
topic of brands because what if burning
bridges just saying though I mean my
opinion could change I'm not gonna take
the deal unless it has changed then
interesting transition from hey we don't
have any brands to you know topic one
really did scare me and IKEA I honest I
still I'm not gonna lie right let's try
how I feel
let's try and salvage is do it so hot
topic did scare you at first but but I
go there but now they're great because
we go there for props we want to have
like a really like you know want to go
for that look and I also think they have
like some good like real nice things
like like they tap into certain I guess
cultures band that's sure or they have
like that like searching like weepings
cartoons yeah happened to that and if I
want to wear like some dumb Sailor Moon
shirt which I love
should we tell people the fun fact that
you like to wear skirts at home for
northerns
oh my I talk to wear skirts there's
nothing wrong with that dude this is
2019 no it's not that it is I live with
you yeah you know like wow what is your
mindset for that like I mean like I'm
not judging yeah it's the same with but
I am a little bit it's the same with
Crocs uh-huh I was like do nobody wears
this so it's just you want your hipster
so I just want to like you know wait I
guess in a way hipster yeah but it's
more like I wanna make people cringe do
you want me to tell the story about what
you're talkin can tell this story
because I think he's trying to defend
himself
no so I woke up so this is we're living
at the old house when you explained the
situation cuz you're living with Paco
I'm lived Paco moved in he's he just
starting to work with us and I was like
okay we got a new guy Park was pretty
cool you know and I walk out to go into
the office and Paco walks out of his
room with no shirt on no socks but he's
wearing a pink skirt I'm not talking
about like a costume like a girl's skirt
yeah schoolgirls yeah he walks by me
he's like hey what's up
like not trying to be funny not trying
to make me laugh he just walks by and
I'm looking at him like waiting for him
to kind of turn around or like maybe
he'd lift his skirt up to try and make
me laugh or like make a joke nothing he
could tell like he slept in it his eyes
he goes I'm a boogers in it
just walk not in sleeping in 100% in it
sleep in it well he just it's almost
stranger because you made a conscious
choice to like hey I'm gonna go out into
the into the world with no shirt on and
just a skirt which is I mean summertime
so it's like really hot and I never
lived in Vegas so I was like no shirt I
need that ventilation on my nips and if
I'm wearing pants you know I have a
skirt I can just open it up and there's
a breeze strumming we already know now
that that's you yeah but like this is
like when you first oh yeah yeah I came
into the group and we were just like
okay so this guy is different not I mean
it's not a bad thing it's interesting if
anything you know don't wear it anymore
no I have been worn in for a long time
see it's not genuine then you don't love
skirts
that's why it's like I just wore it just
to be like huh how we like react I think
you are discovering yourself that's the
kind of person I feel like you are oh
yeah always self-discovery everyday you
know did you like check it off a list
like skirts cross I will wear it once in
a while though for like streams or
something okay well that's just for
entertainment yeah it's funny the weird
thing about it was that you weren't
doing it for any like you just we
weren't filming you just did it it was
behind closed doors yeah that you walked
out of that closed door to me mm-hmm are
you a fan of Jaden Smith I feel like
that's something he did and like maybe
that it was around that time maybe
that's why it might have been but I know
you're inspired by those so the thing is
I had actually bought that two years
before mm-hmm
and then from that point it was kind of
just like hey this is a weird thing to
have so I'm just gonna use it sometimes
okay because like I mean otherwise it's
just sitting around yeah you can't let a
good skirt go to wait yeah you know
guess
if you got it flaunt it yeah watch us
get all these comments like oh my god
will and Ryan are so unaccepting I said
you can wear whatever you want I know
but this is my this is my pocket I think
I think it's a little weird I mean I
have nothing against people who cross
dress that's fine
and who says it's cross-dressing what if
you were Irish is that stereotypical
though there's kilts kilts Scot Scottish
Scottish not Irish when I first saw it
that's what I thought it was I was like
no it's like but it is pink yeah but I
mean they have pink kill today you walk
by night and I was like oh that's a it's
a skirt yeah yeah we're gonna get those
comments for sure well not for you
you're gonna be like oh don't make fun
of Paco he just like skirts let it be
who he is
that's how I think their voices sound
I'll see you in that comments we're
about to get roasted me and will like so
close-minded clothes mind closed minded
bang I don't know that made me think
about like I don't know why we started
talking about that hot topic oh that's
right his weird choices see even the
fact that I even have to quit like I
have to stop myself from saying that's a
weird choice that he made and think
about like all the backlash
yeah like are people gonna it's such a
such a sad thing it was never like this
before we we talked about this all the
time never ought not publicly but yeah
it's my think it's but it's not like
it's not coming from a place of hate no
not at all it's just coming from a place
of like oh this is different to me yeah
I'm the norm yeah like I mean I just I
mean like even like the whole yeah it's
so frustrating to talk because I have to
be careful yeah yeah yeah there's all
these like there's so many rules
landline there's so many rules but like
even like talking about like the like
saying like before it everything changes
saying like oh I support gay marriage or
saying like just saying that you're
gonna get hate either way yeah yeah so
you might as well just make both sides
hate you and say you don't and you do
accept that gay people hate them love
them bring on the hate both sides I want
both
or you get love from both sides you know
are you going to be like I don't care
yeah you know whatever that is try it I
think the old sides will be like oh why
don't you care about our agenda I know
this is like every like podcast has like
PC talk yeah yeah but you know what I
actually never did a video on I never
actually really did a video about gay
people or like kind of like touched on
that one that was like the hot topic
yeah hot topic that was your brands
nobody you know I mean it was like I
mean it was more popular than it is now
like everything happens in trends like
for a while the whole game we're not
that it's done but the whole move the
gay movement and LGBT thing yeah was
solely focused around gay marriage I
forget you remember okay sure
and then now it's kind of like the
transgender thing you know but before it
was more just like you know about gay
marriage and you know gay people and
letting them be there and stuff yeah but
it's funny how things happen in trends
but when that was happening I just never
really touched the subject obviously had
we had gay friends I don't again I was
kind of in that boat of like I don't
care yeah do what you want to do what
makes you happy baby yeah do what you
want to do like I also and if you it's
your religion and you are against it to
me I'm just like okay then be against it
but I'll don't have to go in you and I
come from Hawaii which is a place of
like people are just openly super
flamboyant if they are gay oh yeah well
like they're called marries in a way
indeed life for her memories for us
yeah just heard a different M word oh
yeah oh that one as well but in Hawaii
they say ma hoo yeah but I don't know if
that's insulting
yeah I don't know either
honestly anymore I don't know
everything's changed man but you know
what I always thought the way I really
broke it down and tried to think about
it is like I can't like I really believe
that you can't choose to be gay so how
can you hate on someone exactly yeah for
something they can't control mmm you
know it's like hating on someone like
being Asian yeah but people would really
do believe that you can choose to be gay
yeah like a lot of people still believe
that less but I think a lot of people do
and it's a choice but the funny thing is
I think the people who think like
that are actually the closest to
becoming gay or being gay or they are
gay and they're trying to fight it this
yeah like the only people who are like
if you really think about it like I try
and think it think about it myself like
if it's a choice I can't really right
now think or I think I just can't be
attracted to both of you
I can't choose to want to be attracted
to you guys that hurt you know I mean
like I can't or any guy yeah I can't
choose if you really think it's possible
right now if I were to think like you
know what it's if if it was my choice if
I wanted to do that yeah I could be gay
and I could like you I could be
attracted to you then I'm probably gay
mehar by Turing but I don't think it's
possible to be to choose it like I just
really can't think it's possible I think
you think it's a choice then you're
probably questioning yourself yeah I
thought about it before like am i gay I
know
and then I we thought you were yeah
actually a lot of people think I am it's
well the skirt thing and like you know
there's a bunch of others yeah but and
I'm like very I can be very flamboyant
at times yes but then I was I was just
like hmm okay like I can see guys and be
like oh dude that's an attractive person
but I'm not I mean anything yeah exactly
and for me I don't know this is gonna
get taken out or inappropriate but when
I brush my teeth
not taking out anything dude and I scrub
the back of my tongue and I gag I'm like
I don't like this feeling enough me and
we might have to take it out like hot
topic and I care never gonna appear this
video when they sponsor this well that's
what you're saying about like you don't
think it's a choice to be homosexual I
don't think it can be from the high
point of view imagine like growing up
because from our point of view as a
straight male yeah we we grew up and we
were born into this world and we like
we're attracted to women right so
imagine being like born a man and just
being born attracted to men and having
people say right you know it's got to be
pretty frustrating oh yeah definitely
looking at it from their point of view
is like so and if someone told you like
it's a choice for you to like women it's
like well let's just true I'm attracted
to it's so very easy but that's what I'm
saying the people who are even
questioned like if they even think that
it's a choice yeah it means they can't
they're probably thinking about it for
themselves sure cuz like or they're not
thinking they're just saying like but
anyone who really thinks is a choice
just ask yourself this would you be able
to choose to be attracted to a guy or
girl yeah if you're a guy would you be
choose to be attracted to these same sex
because if you if you can then you
really shouldn't be art making that
argument because you're probably gay
damn here's some freaking hot tea for
you what does that mean if imagine them
saying that that it's a choice because
they are homosexual and they chose to
like women boom Oh explosion you know
I'm saying so they're like it's a choice
yeah yeah damn give me a high-five
yourself to him dude grabbing your own
sleeves that's pretty sweet how do we
get on this topic I need to go down the
PC route oh you know what that's exactly
well we can't talk about current times
and it's really upsetting I think you
know what I don't think it's bad to talk
about it
no yeah and I think honestly the times
are changing right now how you know
everything has become very PC over the
past like five years I would say sure I
mean not just in the past five but
really PC in the past five years old yes
yeah I think like I said everything
happens in trends and this trend is was
is at its peak and it's gonna change and
go the opposite direction I think
there's gonna be a big movement of
anti-peace enos I think it's already
starting to happen and I think it's
gonna become almost like damn you know
we're gonna be like okay maybe we need a
little bit more yeah again so I think
it's gonna go and type in C and we're
gonna be just a bunch of like racists
and meanies yeah but it's gonna be
acceptable and then it's gonna be
through the same thing I really believe
that's how everything works well one
extreme pushes back the other extreme
exactly yeah then and it's always nice
to find the balance but there's never
gonna be balance
just like there's never peace there will
be balance if more people are balanced
boom
that is as not that's it okay that's
I'll work on it yeah yeah but that's
right that's what this kind of sucks
about the world is like it's it really
is kind of through the lens of the
extremes when I think moult like I I
would say the majority of people are
more more of like in the middle yeah but
it's that like that like loud minority
yeah you know which is kind of a shame
mm-hmm well I mean there goes our that's
and that's our PC section of the week
peace eNOS that's gonna be like our
little penis
for this episode of the penis of the
week we talk about gay you can't choose
to be gay if you believe that you're
probably gay all right we're gonna have
a piece eNOS of the week thing I might
bring it back see what people like you
know we're still experimenting I like it
um what else we got on the agenda today
I like it I don't think you meant to say
it but say what bearer menteng you know
like people who are curious about it
it's the about what you know like if
they're about the penises yeah yeah I
mean I mean like you know I didn't mean
to say that but okay
it's just naturally in you to experiment
is um she's she break I kind of do but
like so we were talking about having
this thing in our podcast where we do uh
you know rather than just doing the add
section what if we had what if we had
like this you know how normally they do
mid maybe rose-red a boat instead we do
I mean some people do like sponsorship
stuff but what if we created our own
commercials yeah see this could be you
hot topic or you IKEA Carl's jr. again
so we feel actually worked with in there
great no that's why again yeah film our
own commercial that we run during our
sheshe breaks I think we could make it
but we make it funny that would be
pretty cool I don't think you know
that's a lot of work too that's like
making a whole another video yeah I mean
Oh buddy I mean we could do it super
simple though yeah like like a 20 second
thing take a quick sheshe break yeah
people don't know from Hawaii we call
peeing shishi number one is shishi
number two is do do I guess that same
thing for everyone well I guess if we
take a doodoo break that's if there's a
long ad we do like a minute and a half
add one of those ones where the sidebar
comes up it's like skip ad dude - dude
that's what you can never take a do to
break at a that much taco no need to
Spence no we're bringing it up because
this is how paco avoids work when we're
filming and shoots Paco will go missing
for a clean 45 minutes and we already
know where he is he's in the bathroom
pooping yeah do doing I have a really
tight butthole I don't think that's the
reason I think it's just because you're
on your phone that's okay so a new game
came out what uh so supercell who has
created yes clash royale classic line
right right about with sprawl stars
right like a MOBA game but I mean it
just got released in America because
apparently it's been played in other
countries so what you're saying is the
next time you go to the bathroom I'm
definitely playing longer break yeah so
you're just saying you're not working no
I am well everyone else is like we're
sweat we're try and get things done I'm
writing because I'm thinking on you know
second channel ideas oh yeah because
you're playing girl stuff maybe we could
get a brand deal with brawl stars and
then they'll give me your phone is
probably so filled of poop no cuz it's a
brand new phone I bet you one sitting
food particles yeah there's so many poop
articles but I do like having a shisha
because I actually been drinking a lot
of caffeine yeah should we do a quick
shishi break and come back mini break
two-minute break
and oh wait not claps she break B and
we're back to be off the bill podcast
starring me me and me we didn't plan
that it just happened and I hate it and
I hate it so much
anyway maybe it's a bad idea to do these
she she breaks cuz like I forget what we
were talking about well that's why you
know what it's a refresher because I
don't remember what we were talking
about I show took my meds what if half
the video is off the pill podcast and
the other and happy and I'm just like
really focused I think we should just
like just start like guys actually have
work to do
just talking on your own honesty when I
do take my my adderall yeah I man
adderall such a bad name I guess like
now it's like such a bad rap yep but I
think people get affected from it
differently yeah yeah like for me when I
take it I don't get like height
I'll some other people do mm-hm almost
the opposite and I don't know if that's
normal
but if I had it right now you guys could
be talking and I could be working on
something I could honestly work why you
guys are talking isn't listening isn't
that amazing
it's amazing for me because I get
distracted super easily yeah not like in
the stereotypical like Oh a butterfly
you know yeah yeah but like even just
talking right now I'm thinking of other
things like what things I don't know
just like you've been talking about
words the word talking mm-hmm and then I
started thinking about like and I say
that we're talking a lot I was thinking
about that while I was explaining to you
the other thing damn that's weird it's
not weird it's normal
I think a lot of people do that they
just don't let themselves explore that
part yeah because even when I take my
meds that happens but I can control it
that's the difference for me yeah and
you know when I'm writing like scripts
and stuff like that it's actually easier
to not take it yeah and then after that
but when I'm not taking it basically
what happens is I write all this
nonsense like because the the reason why
it turns out to be nonsense is because
you're literally just going with the
flow and you can't stop because if you
stop you're gonna forget the great idea
you had and but the great idea sometimes
leads to other ideas yeah that are
completely unrelated but you have to
write it down yeah
because you never know when it's gonna
come back yeah yeah and then you take
your meds the next couple days later and
you go and fix all the little things
damn or put it together or put it put it
in to make it make sense
that's the secret right there that is
the old not a secret do it if you have
ADHD do that
I heard it's different for it I've
talked to other people because they are
mean even like like comments and people
writing to me yeah saying like their
experiences are similar some are very
very different yeah I think it's not out
just like you have it or you don't think
I think it's a scale no yeah and I
really get upset when people say like oh
you're it's just like kids I mean a lot
of it is that kids who just want to do
drugs
sure um but it's not fun to me like
adderall is not a fun thing I don't get
that same like hyperness and like yeah
you know I mean it will keep you up but
I don't get that like I don't get how
that's fun yeah you know I don't know
well that's probably because you or
should be taking it to some extent
rather than I don't take it all the time
though yeah but yeah it's not fun to me
at least No thank you way how do we get
on that topic see I should took my meds
we didn't even start with the topic know
what's on the agenda
yeah well for transitioning into
different things
speaking of transitions yeah uh we can
just you know just talk about anything
cuz we we had something trending so why
don't we discuss something that you know
is bothering you guys recently in the
past couple of days yeah let's get
personal because I mean things that this
is something that I learned in a writing
class and what helps you write is name
three things that you really like right
now and three things that you don't like
right now and then that's what they told
you in the class yeah well because
that's how you start writing with the
topic right are you talking about fur
stand up
no just in general Oh in general like
what worth writing stand-up or a joke or
making a video or a story then you just
like right through things so you could
be like I like food I like getting
massages and I like when people say
thank you when I open the door something
I don't like static electricity I don't
like when I pick my nose too hard and I
bleed I love that one do you always
bring that up I do though you always use
it as an example for something it's like
we're playing like I dare you and you're
like oh why don't we doing weird like
you pick your nose who can like pick
your nose until it bleeds no I brought
this up many times this is not the first
time this is like the third time any
I've heard it from you before maybe or
why either no it's - it's been at least
a couple times we're like why do you
always go to that I don't like why do
you want to see someone pick their nose
who they bleed know is that your fetish
No
are you condemning my Kings I I just I'm
curious is that your phone it's not as
we can make that happen but you can pick
our noses till it bleeds but basically
from the six different topics there's
usually like one or two that you really
are like oh this is something that
really annoys me or something I really
like and then that's the one that you go
off on already write about things I hate
yeah so I mean I guess in the past
couple of days what is something that
you really like something has really
been bothering you
hmm something that's been really
bothering you static electricity I don't
know why but even know why it happened
know every time I put my clothes in the
dryer yeah cuz it's dry no but it's just
like it's there's so much build-up it
doesn't matter if I put like one of
those a dryer sheets the dryer sheets do
your laundry oh you didn't know what
that was called huh I thought was a
detergent sheet or something like that
was called yes I mean I never had to use
that in Hawaii that's true yeah and so
now out here like I have to use it
inside used to using Hawaii well even at
the old house the cloth like I never had
to use it and my clothes weren't
staticky uh and so it's so frustrating
cuz that is if I have a staticky shirt
if I put it on and I start driving then
it makes my my seat all staticky hmm and
then when I step out of the car gets
shocked every time it's it's happening
so much maybe you have powers wasn't
there a guy called static shock he's a
black dude why does that matter huh I
thought you don't see clothes oh okay
now I might have been a different day
but yeah I maybe you just have like some
kind of gift I don't know I don't think
that's that's a curse maybe there's some
way you can use it if you can channel
static more than the average person what
is the thing about it like this what is
the ultimate lame superpower that you
can think of for yourself
that's like wow that's you know I mean
like someone who can like remember that
Family Guy episode where like make could
grow her nail is really long that one's
pretty lame yeah but like something like
that like what would be your let's try
think uh I don't know why I had this had
this discussion with someone else before
I was like if you had a realistic par
with having to do with you but like not
unreal I cursed rength or something like
that
okay a realistic lay empowerment
yeah I don't know why for some reason
for me is just like you could hold your
breath for a really long time that's not
lame that's a cool one that's I mean it
is a little lame in that it's like well
would your name be you could swim like
you're going to water for longer than
anyone in the world what are you gonna
do with it hide in the water that's true
so what it's like
oh no they're robbing a bank mister hold
your breath forever man come save us
yeah but if they were like we designed
these walking in the water boots and you
could walk under the water and sneak up
on people boom you're a spy that's where
wheels mine wind
you gotta get trained to go on land and
access a computer or something oh no you
gotta get trained yeah that was pretty
lame mind another lame power mine would
be related to me like growing my hair
instantly long that's lame but it's also
useful I could see how they could be
useful yeah it would just go yeah you
don't want to do like how great magic
with tricks or something with that
there's money and you know how great of
a how great of a business that would be
how many weeks you know what weeks cause
you could help so many cancer patient
that's true but you could also turn into
a business that sponsors this podcast
brought to you by wheels by wigs wigs by
[Laughter]
will or do people who are named will by
the way just make sure you guys check
out was by Wacom I'll be dead if that
has a this is the first time I said I'll
be dead if that is actually real say I'm
not I'm not even gonna be shocked if it
is but I'm gonna go buy it right now
yeah you should something if not someone
listen to this probably will do it how
about you um man I so I had a forget who
was talking about with this but I had
some good ones by the way that use it it
might have been David but but our
premise was a little different it was
like how can you have a really lame
power but make it useful but it's also
like like it has to be like that bounds
of
yeah only reason why I brought it up I
was like it'd be really interesting to
see that's what it was we're trying
thing about tweet cuz I want to see what
other people I never did it I don't see
what other people would come up with
because there's so many but I forget how
to list somewhere of a bunch of them but
it sounds like a fun drinking game where
everyone has to like within 10 seconds
come up with like a lame superpower yeah
and then everyone is kind of like no
butchers it would be cool because you
could do all this this is this and then
right the end whoever has like the best
lame superpower has to like drink or
something I got another lame one what
you could get out you can instantly get
over a cold in 10 minutes so that power
is like like it's good but it's for a
superhero yeah it's pretty lame really
lame what if what if your power was to
just give someone a 10-second cold like
you just feel like sick for 10 seconds
that's it yeah they keep going the other
thing is like the the strength of the
cold is randomized from one to 10 yeah
sometimes it could be like flu for 10
it's not that could be that bird no oh
my god keto flu going through it right
now it's actually not as bad today as it
was the last couple of days yeah it
started about couple days ago so why are
you going back into this though Kido
yeah oh because it's um so yeah I mean
it's a nice diet I like to dye it every
now and then remember this I mean
there's the things I like having fun
doing good I I mean I I eat a lot and I
binge eat it's bad habits for all your
wrestlers out there peak you're gonna
you're gonna get really fat or you have
to learn how to control yourself because
that's where I picked up all my eating
habits I learned binge eating I learned
how to lose weight really quickly it's
so unhealthy
I've been told that but as a kid in high
school I did not care because I just
wanted to win play worse I guess
fighters to stay champion in wrestling
yeah in judo I got second um but I had a
dislocated elbow while you were fighting
in my first match I had a bye because I
was fourth seed and then I dislocated my
elbow they popped it back in or they did
something I don't know if they popped it
like wrapped it up it could barely use
it the next match I had the it was
semifinals ready because I had to buy
and I had to face this guy who was
actually the number one seed and he was
beating me the whole way I ended up
countering him and then pinning him on
the ground because he wasn't a wrestler
hmm but he was like the favorite of the
whole so it was a big upset yeah and
nobody knew that I was like messed up
and then I went to the finals match and
basically at that point after the last
guy it was like because it's all in one
day right so the first injury happened
in the in the morning and then after
noon my arm is like I'm going to that
next one I got kind of lucky being the
the best guy pretty much using one arm
and the last guy who's even like the
guys before me were like oh man do not
lose to this guy we've all beat him
because there are there are 'allahu kids
on the Big Island they were all like
dude do not lose to this kid because
we've all beat like he shouldn't be
there essentially what they were saying
but I mean he earned I mean he got there
yeah you know he wasn't even seated in
the top four out of like the 30 I don't
know how many people with 16 whatever it
is yeah anyway once I laid him I was
just like my arm was done like I
couldn't even like I could grab but it
was like the strength of like me no no
it was feeling like a child like a
strength of a child so I basically had a
longer there so where it got worse and
worse and I didn't know that yeah yeah
so I saw was really like upset because I
don't mind losing to someone who's
better I've always said this even like
if it's like you know if I'm watching
basketball or any sport I don't mind
when my team loses to like okay that
team would just deserve or when we play
basketball
we play every Wednesday and Friday if we
lose to a team that's better than us and
we get blown out I'm like cool with that
but if we lose to a team by like one
point that we should have beat I'm like
really upset because it's like I don't
know why I just get really upset by that
this is how you know it Ryan as
frustrated went after the game usually
like he'll spend maybe two to three
minutes with the guys just talk and
actually let's tip spend a lot more time
to adapt people up oh yeah if we did
really well he'll like hang out for like
maybe five minutes but if he's upset
he'll grab his bags
alright hey guys peace peace yeah shake
everyone's hand just bounce but that's
only if we lose to a good team I don't
it doesn't yeah we deserve like it
doesn't think we could have done yeah
but in the same way in that in that
tournament I was I was very
disappointing because I knew I was like
that was my senior year I was like what
could have been you know and I cut all
this weight people don't realize how
hard that is to do in high school not
just in high school but I mean like well
you know there's so many other things
you got to worry about and you're like
always hungry and you're always grouchy
yeah
and thirsty even so yeah that was a very
disappointing thing when you know I'm
not that I sit I'm gonna say I would
have won but like it you know you didn't
give it your all pretty much so we I
would say you probably did but it's just
things that were out of your control
right stopped you which is I mean I'm
sure everyone can relate to that it's
like super frustrating yeah I still
think you're number one thanks man
yeah but you're number two I am you know
I'm actually numbered out of the number
two in doubles or tennis doubles so
you're actually number four cuz your
other friend was also part of that okay
yeah I didn't know that you were
actually athletic until I saw you like
play basketball and you didn't know how
to play basketball
yeah and you actually could play
basketball I said basketball like four
times okay talking talk now uh so yeah a
very similar situation where my partner
is way better than me I only started
playing tennis in uh in high school
where a lot of people have been playing
it for like their whole lives and then
my senior year my partner and I got
fourth seed and we were playing in the
semi-finals against the first seed and
we beat them and it was just like it was
a huge upset because these guys would
want like this song so because we had
beaten them everyone is like tripping
out of their eyes just like oh my gosh
and like we're a public school too so to
beat a private Punahou oh yeah it was a
explains the people who don't know
that's where Obama went yeah that's
wrong but if you're from Hawaii sorry
for all the Punahou kids I think they
know this too yeah like everyone they're
like the best at everything yeah cuz
they have like
they have like the most pretty girls too
I don't know about that but they have
like the most prestigious cues like the
smartest kids and like all the most
established it's like the top of the
that's like let's take the Harvard of
Hawaii yeah the place everybody you know
if you're not in there you're against
them yeah it's so it's a big deal he's
there the Patriot exactly they're the
warrior they're the yeah the Warriors
so when any other school in Hawaii beats
a Punahou kid usually it's it's pretty
like you're like rooting for them yeah
non Punahou person sorry for all the
underdog from Point yeah but but it's
true I mean that's it comes with the
territory being number one you I mean
people always root for the underdog you
know and so we had beat their number one
seed the number one seed and I was
actually what Dave Shoji's son who Dave
Shoji the you age women's volleyball
coach the okay coach yeah right right
right
ah so we beat them and that night I was
like oh this is dope I got to height I
got to hike because then uh this girl
I've never told this story
Jordan Lum if you're watching this I'm
so sorry but the night before this girl
who is like watching like came up to me
after it's like a good game you're
really cute you know what oh snap
so when we are all supposed to go to
sleep I snuck out and hung out with her
but so like early in the morning and
then went to my match and I was
exhausted and we we lost in straight
sets
in the finals and I I was tired I do I
was tired and then if I was your
teammate but whoever that guy is you
need to apologize if that's once I don't
tell a lot of people it doesn't it
doesn't it's like who cares it's just
states like it's just like a sport who
cares
it's a big deal of dude like you'll
never get that chance again
yeah the same with like college players
like that's why I like a lot of times it
means more for them to win a
championship in college and doesn't an
NBA in basketball because you'll never
get to do it again yeah you only get us
X amount of chances for chances to be
protected
four chances and that's assuming you're
at your best when your freshman
sophomore junior usually your senior
year Dan that I feel bad for that guy
it's big deal I mean you ever know two
events like that can lead to scholarship
three things that happen in your life
you know and you took it away from your
teammates I mean should we have to have
to blanket I don't think so
he's actually a very dude ever since at
a young age he's two years younger than
me but I was always just like how did
you go to know he's three years younger
if he's a freshman what school did you
go to I think um I went to Pearl City
High School parousia
yeah and I was he held himself with such
poise and it's definitely because of his
parents and you could see and I was just
like damn dude this guy's so respectful
and steady trying to say about your
parents
they're cool yeah they're very
respectful and there's a very nice and
very respectful very very different from
you look I'm pretty sure dad don't wear
skirts are on the house now yeah
definitely not or your mom probably
[Laughter]
because so what second place medal did
you get will yeah
none Steve science fair nothing no oh we
did actually we got a dance second place
oh yeah dates no I mean world of dance
that's the world's dude in the world he
second in the world's yeah that's just
the name then there's country on dude
that's then there's continents he did
worlds and you got second in world of
dance yeah it was uh 2018 or 17 or
something right so this past year I mean
excuse me yeah yeah I knew it
yeah we were all pretty young it's me
Greg Dana like we're all in a town yeah
and it was a big deal cuz we were it was
a big deal it was our first like big
bigger competition and dance right
and there was this crew called choreo
cookies oh they're still around and
they're always known as
they're punahou to you they were there
you're bad they're your Puna home yeah
and we were some ragtag nobodies who
were doing like really weird stuff like
we would a lot of them would just wear
like a t-shirt or crew shirt and they
would just dance right and it would be
look really cool
we had like full costumes and like skits
and I did like a play we did like a play
where we were dancing we were not good
at dancing so we had to like to think of
we're good at like making people laugh
and making moments you know in
storytelling you guys a good concept we
did and no one really did that bad and
like no one was really into that like
the dance competitions were all about
the dance just dancing yeah so we would
have like these big wooden sets that we
would have to like lug on and like weird
like props everywhere and we almost won
by we almost beat them by like point
something was a really close really
close yeah I remember seeing that he's
outline I'm sure it is yeah well step
boys yeah the homeless one or no it was
yes I think we call it the bump the bump
show yeah
and that the story of the show was I was
a businessman and I lost my job and then
became like homeless and then there the
story was there was a group of homeless
people that like took me in and showed
me the ways of of their world you know
and then that that's I think this is
this the ending of it was to be like
accepting because then the person who
had delivered me the message lost their
job and then I was like bringing him in
at the end so it's kind of like this
store narrative right yeah yeah and so
people were and we had like really cool
stunts yes that was like and then people
were in a way you guys kind of pioneered
that concept of like storytelling maybe
like like mostly in our area I don't
really know elsewhere no yeah but it
like in the within the dance community
is kind of like a small thing so work
can spread fast sure and then there also
have been like prestigious crews who
have been like yo your idea like we
flipped it a little bit they told you
that yeah
yeah and you know I don't want to say
like any names but there's been like
bigger crews that have bigger shows I
have said like they yeah we've allowed
them yeah some of our stuff say their
names can't no but that was our second
place story my second place story it was
really cool God you know what that means
we're all a bunch of losers yeah losers
yeah we make it we make it there and
then we just do we don't finish yeah you
don't count you had first in wrestling
yeah but not in everything like I said
we almost make it to the perfect level
of championship but we just don't quite
make it so that what that whole story we
talked about was all because Paco said
think of something that you have
problems with you guys gotta stop me
because I don't even remember like
mid-sentence I'll forget what I'm
talking about and I'm moving on to
something else and doesn't matter
ya know that's what this podcast is I
know but at some point if I keep going
really off that's what you guys are here
for someone's guy catch me and be like
hey we're not talking about that no yeah
but the thing is like what you're
talking about there's good substance to
it it's a good story there's no reason
to cut it off sure yeah now if you're
just going off on something just then we
do that right yeah that's that's why
this it's good so but I also don't
realize don't worry
yeah I'll bring it full full circle but
yeah I agree it's always retaining
that's entertaining that's that's why
I'm I've always had well not not always
but whenever we go on dates mm-hmm oh it
would be a real issue
why ill you go on dates now no I like
back in the day if you go on and deal
with a girl yeah or guy I guess the
talking part I would have to always be
conscious about like like I don't I
don't mind like talking to someone and
we'll have a conversation but I have to
like it almost makes me more awkward
because I have to consciously be
thinking okay don't stay on topic
like don't take any meds back then yeah
yeah you know when I was like yeah like
especially like right out of like
college and
that time I was very awkward because I
think I would be consciously trying to
think like stay on top and yeah listen
to what she's saying or sometimes I'm
not even there's not like a disrespect
thing or like I it happens to people I
respect the most I've told people this
before but like it's almost like the the
one time I knew that I had I knew when I
was a kid but like I knew something was
weird
yes I would have like you know like my
um I grew up playing basketball and judo
and they would call you in for Huddle's
right and they would explain the play
let's say basketball they would explain
to our coach would explain the play and
be like I would always get yelled at
because I would never know what the play
was about after we broke the huddle so
like as I got older this is from ages
five to 13 I would keep consciously
trying to tell myself okay pay attention
right pay attention and then I don't
know where break I was like oh my gosh
trying so hard to pay attention that I
didn't hear anything and I would always
get yelled at but I really want I didn't
want to get yeah I don't have to run
suicides or sprints and I would always
have to cuz I never knew what the hell
was going on so like that's how I knew
like okay me how do you like oh I would
always wonder like how do people
remember this stuff it's not that I
couldn't remember the time at the time I
thought it was a memory thing yeah but
it was like I just can't be attention
yeah yeah it is and and it is I didn't
realize until I took meds for the first
time later in life which is in college
and it was actually my prescription it's
not one of those like underground like
buy because everybody was trying to get
adderall back in like in college yeah
it's like a popular thing now mm-hmm but
I didn't think it was it wasn't even
called adderal back then it was
something else Ritalin riddle I don't
know if it was well they might have to
be ritalin and then I think they I don't
I think it's people still use really I
think it's for different things maybe I
don't know right but well regardless I
think I told this story did I tell this
already
I don't think so on the first two hot
gas in the consigui anyway yeah that's
hot that's for people out there if
you're curious if you had kind of have
ADHD that's what it's like cuz I there's
no way I would have known if I didn't
take medicine ah this is what other
people get to experience naturally yeah
I'm guys can read a book and it's not a
big deal yeah
I remember they would do those tests in
school where they would test your
comprehension and like your if you could
read something and then kind of tell it
back to them did they ever do that to
you like in school like with the first
time I got tested it was when I was in
preschool and they thought uh they said
they did say I had ADHD but my mom
refused to put me on meds right probably
would have been school would have been
so much easier yeah but I mean I still
got good grades growing up yeah it's a
weird flex huh I did get good grades but
I kind of cheated a lot weird flex but
certainly that's an odd contraction of
muscles but was that the right time to
use it though tries to keep me up to
date with the little kids
just a little cuz sometimes well I
always use it wrong yeah but the thing
is also I think there's moments where
you do it on purpose like I exactly know
that was right that one was correct yeah
but there's a lot of times you
ironically oh yeah sometimes right yeah
as like a joke on the music what was I
talking about
weird flex but okay but what was the
flexing about how you got grades even
though you oh oh yeah I got diagnosed
when I was today yeah okay the only one
who thinks those kinds of saints have
like an expiration date like two days
before they're like I don't know yeah
like I think it's a matter of how much
people use it yeah mmm but it's also I
think in a way for our group it's almost
been like don't just follow trends you
know and I think it's kind of been what
it's kind of been drilled into can we
follow trends try to I try to keep up
with trends I'm just always late no but
you yeah you're very late and then you
also do it in a way that's like still
didn't eat yet guys
let's eat I'm really hungry time to eat
I don't know if it's necessarily been
drilled into us I think the majority of
us we're it's just in our nature to not
I don't know when I make those if I
ever make like a joke like that
sometimes part of me feels like I copied
a joke uh-huh and it makes no to me it
makes me feel like yeah yeah yeah you
know it's not really a joke right like
what does heat mean again no it's not
that's just something people say no but
if you said like oh yeah I get hit up
all the time for bran deals and I yeah I
said Oh weird flex what okay I'm making
a joke and then we would all look at you
like yeah but but I think that's also
why like you know you know how you just
don't copy trends like if people are
doing challenges and stuff oh I see what
you're saying yeah yeah
so in a way all of us are kind of just
like yeah but you're making you're right
now you're weird flexing but okay to us
right now you're like oh we're too good
for me but no but but we liked I like
them I don't see it really late I do too
I just don't want to do them I don't say
that like yeah yeah I laugh at them but
I don't use them as like in my arsenal
yeah like I know once something gets so
overdone I get upset seeing it honestly
and then it becomes a joke in itself
yeah yeah just why I think it's so like
the dab is really knowing for a while
and then I thought it was so funny every
time I saw like mini mint or do it doing
it like yeah yeah Dan I think that's
like a whole another different level
yeah of comedy not like a different see
right now where we were flexing but okay
that's okay dude dude definitely odd
contraction in our muscles but certainly
anyway um how do we get on this topic
see this is the bad thing I should have
took my pill during the shishi break
honestly I think the last official topic
we talked about was Paco said what
bothers you yeah that didn't even go
anywhere
I wouldn't talk that's why I told you
like so that's what no no it's fine it's
all we're looking for is the seed that
we can plant and then viciously whatever
it better fractures off into okay what
bothers me tell them I don't know dude
grab my sleeve that bothers me as well I
don't know I don't know what bothers me
I was like no way
I don't really I'd have to see here I
think about it because it's not really
something that I can just pull out of my
I have a lot of things so what I do
every day write about things that bother
me
what get them for one let me tell you
about IKEA let's see I mean there's so
many things you know actually one thing
that does kind of bother me but it's
like it shouldn't I don't I didn't I
never understood why people hate
Nickelback so much that's I know it's
super random but I was just thinking
about it the other day yeah cuz I heard
a Nickelback song cuz I was watching was
it Grey's Anatomy I don't know I was
watching some really old show yeah they
had a Nickelback song I don't know what
show it was might have not even been
Nickelback but it reminded me and I was
like dude they're not bad like why does
people like why do people hate them so
much you know trying to think of a
Nickelback song is that the I remember
though there's a music video in there I
don't have the rights to that we might
have to bleep it just kidding out I was
in look at this picture this picture
take a glance at the picture yeah I
still think that one vine is hella funny
was like what no but no but you know
what I mean everybody that's like the I
know it because I go team yeah it's a
go-to but I've always like if you I
guess kids wouldn't get it now cuz
they're not popular but back in the day
they were playing all the time and
nobody had an issue with them I thought
photograph was a great song yeah and
there's voices very like you know like
it's very unique but I don't know
there's things like that and that made
me think of other things that people are
I feel like they just jump on the trend
yeah of like hating Nickelback and we're
like well auto-tune anything auto-tune
sounds awful that's not true there's a
lot of other than that I really like
hearing yeah yeah you know like but that
became a thing right um there's I mean
crocks is something that people like
yeah yeah I mean but yeah yeah but I
mean I understand the crocks one what I
like rocks I I think they're comfortable
yeah I think they're goofy but they have
theirs they you know what I didn't think
about it the real my real reason for not
liking them initially was the holes
the holes made me feel weird I will have
that thing I get like goose bumps just
thinking about the holes is it
trypophobia or something like that I can
get it I just don't wanna I don't want
it to happen so I'm not trying to think
of holes right now my get that pretty
bad that goose that you get creeped out
by holes like just seeing like those
that that thing you know all the bumps
next to each other was it called I tried
before something like that yeah look at
this oh yeah you got bouncy a little bit
you know what that you know what kind of
trigger me like I don't I don't think I
have that but definitely seeing those
patterns is weird at your old house
there were these dead sunflowers in a
vase mm-hmm looking I was like oh why
why do you have that there I don't even
know what you're talking about so I
probably didn't even notice it or look
at it right at your doorway I don't come
through that way oh that's right I don't
go through the front door at my own
house the thing that I didn't like about
crocs enough in the very beginning was
that
Paco's were so like crusty and oh he got
me a new pair and I start wearing kind
of fresh honey I bought him Crocs for
his birthday he just like did not use it
because he went back to using his dirty
ass ones no because it was he body he
didn't buy me the og ones yeah I got
some cool looking what's about what's
cool none of it is cool you didn't get
us og once no I did I'm confused no the
original style yeah I got him some cool
looking like it's like a different one
because he has so many of the other ones
see this is what he had a clothes told a
closed toe one but it had fur on the
inside and that was just weird to me it
was for winter yeah but it was just
weird to have fur on my feet yeah but
for winter it might be nice you know I
figure you got regular crocs I'm gonna
get you this regardless if someone gets
you a gift you should at least use it I
did use it you did not I used I used the
other one I never got him a gift since
and that every time I would see at a
basketball game and you're like nice
yeah
no usually like once yeah Paco actually
got us all Crocs for he did birthdays
mmm he's he converted us yeah
it was you know what it is though it's
like it's just easy to slip on yeah like
so yeah and I wouldn't wear it to like
an event like how he would like call
Paco would but wear it outside go ahead
just like or whatever really yeah yeah
yeah they're awesome
Crocs ah dude I've been trying to get
outta business they closed all of their
American business I think they're still
in this so they could still be a sponsor
yeah I thought I've reached out to the
brand's we gotta get away from brands on
this lake table alone what about post
Malone he did a croc deal yeah I know
I think a shoe with cause I think yeah
that's you know what that matches him
the dice does but he wears them a lot
frustrated why cuz it's dough cuz I want
it I mean you're not post Malone I know
I'll never be post below what I'm like
not with that attitude like you just got
to start working on your music you know
and work on your goatee yeah I'm working
on music and your grill I'm working on
music alright prove it sing something no
no I can't sing though it's like rap Hey
look at this picture picture yeah well
you got some goods coming up some good
ideas I mean well that's a strange flex
but strange contraction of muscles but
okay but certainly yeah but confirmative
man we are lame okay how long has this
been we've been doing this is our first
one and we are just everywhere we're
going for no can can someone check this
is Ben
if not we'll give it a little beat beat
right now and we'll conclude thank you
guys for tuning in to the first episode
official not the first out the first
official episode of off the pill podcast
if you don't know this is how we outro
in 3 2 1
we just um make our mics really smelly
by breathing on it yeah well be you're
the only one using that one so the guest
and so smells okay well I'd like
sugar-free Red Bull why would you
incorporate now we got bleep that brand
no like you we've said so red I would
never you said I would never
shouts IKEA hot topic and sugar free
rebels in South Wales calm Thank You
Ryan
Thank You Paco thank you me you'll
welcome me have a good one guys do this