I am NOT InFocus sorry guys I'm sick I
have to deal with the nays on these
nasal Ness nasal eNOS hey guys so today
I'm gonna be talking about one of my
biggest pet peeves and that pet peeve
just so happens to be you know when
people text message you one word at a
time rather than putting all the texts
into one text message so now you have
like 20 notifications yeah I hate that
oh and also overdramatic oh come on
you gotta be kidding I'm not even gonna
redo this I'm just gonna let it go Oh
drama dick um so as I was mentioning
earlier we probably all know at least
one overdramatic person and if you don't
have anyone like this in your life it's
probably because it's you and you don't
think that you're being overdramatic
because more dramatic situations are
like normal situations too overdramatic
people and it's not necessarily a bad
thing it's just people like myself
warned vonda's drama get a little
annoyed sometimes when you guys know
what kind of people I'm talking about
right these are the people that can
literally make a big deal out of
anything no matter how small it is oh my
god what Dana posted a picture on
Instagram 20 minutes ago so so that
means she's on Instagram and that's bad
yeah she didn't like my post no tiger
not like 3 hours ago yeah that's awful
and by making this a bigger deal these
people actually create drama that was
never there who's something you're not
actually Nicole over there I have to
confront her she's my best friend what
if she just didn't see it okay I tagged
her and I know she keeps her
notifications on so she definitely saw
him chose not to like it so there's
something a hundred thousand percent
wrong I have talked to rich and even
when they come to realize that there was
no drama in the first place hey where's
your problem with me huh oh yeah I know
so why don't you like it I think I know
you posted yeah right I tagged you in at
like three hours ago
see I mean come on we always like each
other's photos and like I don't even
know what why you you tagged the wrong
account me why yeah yeah mine is I'm
over the underscore but being the
overdramatic person that they are they
somehow find a way to create even more
drama out of that because what's life
without drama
I'm so sorry no no don't even worry
about it I would do the same girl I know
like totally overreacted so crazy
oh look Ryan even warned me that you're
on your way oh right that's so funny oh
my god it's so funny you know when
people text messaged you one word at a
time rather than putting all the texts
into one text message so now you have
like 20 notifications yeah as you can
probably see overdramatic people or some
of the most annoying people in the world
but if you want look on the bright side
while being annoying they're actually
some of the most interesting and
entertaining people to be around because
they're never bored bored is an emotion
that overdramatic people will hardly
ever feel because their mind can make
anything and everything seem important
and interesting they have the power to
basically take nothing and turn it into
an incredibly important big deal it's
basically like clickbait she has a
pretty good sing overdramatic people are
basically like limbing click babies come
here rocket come here come here what's
wrong nothing just on my period come on
aren't you being a little overdramatic
excuse me how would you know what do I
feel like if you never had one before
wait a second wait no you're right I've
never had a period before okay obviously
I exaggerated but that's kind of the
whole point that's a textbook example of
an overdramatic person taking a
situation that barely happened and then
making into something that you would see
in a YouTube thumbnail it actually got
me kind of interested in got me thinking
like what makes over demand people want
to do this is it because they love drama
or maybe they just want more attention I
just couldn't figure it out then I
thought maybe I'm wrong you know maybe
it's not for attention or because they
love drama some people are just
different I mean there's two ends of the
spectrum there just like emotional
thinkers and logical thinkers and I
think if you're on the emotional side
that's like the overdramatic people
people like myself are more on the
logical side and just to be clear I'm
not saying either side is wrong we're
just different people emotional people
may see things completely different from
a logical person and it's because they
literally see life in a different way I
mean if that's the case it's actually
pretty amazing because like for over
today people are always exciting their
life is like a movie it's a drama
you see I presented all those skits
earlier from my perspective the you know
the boring perspective the logical one
but imagine what those little situations
would look like from the point of view
of a overdramatic person take a look
I don't know how to tell you this I
don't even know how it happened I'm
pregnant
there's no legality
go
pregnant I have a baby inside how is
that even possible
you know what build what are you talking
about
button nipples rjp who don't even have
don't you ever talk my nipples a kid
anyway the moral of the story here is
that there are just different types of
people in this world yes those overly
emotional overly dramatic people who
might seem incredibly annoying to
someone like me and I'm sure a bunch of
you as well I mean it's not their fault
that's just how they think that's just
how they see life so if you ever get
annoyed or you have to deal with an
overdramatic person in your life don't
even bother trying to be reason that
you're never gonna win in trying to
convince a overdramatic over emotional
thinker to think logically because
that's just not who they are my advice
to you and the only thing that you can
do is to just accept them for who they
are admit defeat let them be there or
there's also one last trick you could
also speak their language be even more
overdramatic than they are so how long
have you guys been sleeping together
what don't you lie to me I was texting
you the whole time on the way back from
our house I know you know what I'm
talking equate a second you were texting
the whole time yeah and you weren't
responding so I know you were talking to
her you were texting and driving yeah my
sister died from a man who was texting
and driving you don't even have a sister
you're gonna bring that up didn't know
you wanted a sister I had no idea I did
and now you know
[Music]