I got one question for it do you want to
look extraordinary you want to get rid
do you want to look big and white with
p90x will be your will build your cap
will build apps on your cat biceps
triceps Tyson no abscess you'll have so
many apps even your car will have abs
push-ups sit-ups push-ups sit-ups SWAT
curls push-up cardio push-up cardio
push-up crunches and she crunches Sanji
crotches benjy with pinnacle axe to go
from this to this this to this this to
this
you'll be widened ripped from size
medium to size media about 10 inches on
my waist nicely being fatty right now
I'm wrong salt I'm an actor and I've
always been - I'm talking me to be on
screen
Thank You p90 flex for changing my life
so what are you waiting for call one
eight hundred five five five five and
get not four not three not two but one
DVD for the price of two so cornell
reports to Michos sold out p90 flesh
does not protect against STD all the
customers in this video are real people
and not paid actors because I didn't pay
them if you experience cramping vomiting
death and were mild leading contact your
local doctor Biscayne yes may not be
right for you know