do you Ryan can you make a horror skit
about how it feels to be a Pokemon
[Music]
please mom I don't know it's gonna be
dark soon but I'm not even gonna go that
far and I'll be back before dinner I
promise what are the rules oh um no
fighting stay away from the city and be
back before it's dark see I got it and
and if you see a human come on there's
never been in and if you see a human if
I see a human I will run away be back
before dinner thanks mom
growing up in the viridian was normal we
were in the deepest part of the forest
so there weren't many other pokemon
around
was quiet peaceful nothing really ever
happened at least that's what I thought
[Music]
back mom wise wise are the things in the
front
[Music]
look at you
ridicule what which is good before
battle I don't want to battle you though
greater choice
[Music]
there we go all better
let me go and get your trainer for you
this is your first time the hell's going
on I was just all beat up and now I'm
that human that just left she healed it
why would a human kind of help us help
us
you got a lot to learn to make us fight
into the brink of death just before one
of us dies to heal us there we go all
better
I just do it all over again and there we
go all better
why don't you guys just not fight you
don't have to obey them and I think
we've tried that it break you I don't
know what it's like to be stuck in that
ball for weeks months even years nothing
to do nothing to see no one to talk to
start to forget yourself
she's moments the very war where you're
from how much rather fight every day for
the rest of my life with these two meter
three minutes and freedom I just stuffed
an eyeball myself
[Music]
[Applause]
no mom
never come out of that fall again
[Music]
sorry