do you write can you do Powerpuff Girls
the city of Townsville poorly drawn and
home to many including your favorite
superhero trio known as the Powerpuff
Girls hey professor hey girls what's up
being that you're really smart and you
created human beings basically out of
nothing uh-huh we were just wondering um
why don't you ain't give us no finger oh
I tried to draw my fingers I tried to
cut my nose Lucky's it's just the way it
happened they didn't try it we got a
blast your finger have an ass right now
girls no please just just let me explain
it difficult it is for me to send an
email I didn't I don't you never tried
typing with your elbows
[Music]
no but I can imagine being pain in the
stuff yeah because we don't got fingers
we ain't got fingernails I mean how do
you expect us to scratch the dirt off
our balls what in PE mr. sacks says we
can't leave class until all of our balls
are clean and we scratch all the dirt
off I put my ponies and they just fall
to the ground you see what we got to go
through because of you know girls please
you have to understand of course I
wanted to know that's the pot line let's
go girls
what is it mare girls the city of
Townsville is under attack by who by him
who is him know him is him I don't know
what this who is so what do you want us
to stop first him or whoa who are you
talking about just stop here we stop
home first then it'll just him who is
him and him his first forget about who
and just get him first wait so who's on
first just go got it let's go girls you
know nobody's gonna get that Abbott and
Costello reference right who him them
them who
[Music]
I've been expecting it's him
Oh him like his name is him that's all
not creative though yes it is me him
that I've come to destroy yeah
any last words yeah yeah actually um
what are you what are you supposed to be
like a crab year like a lobster or
something new related to mr. Krabs and
why is your name him if you look like a
girl here shouldn't it be her what now
why are you doing this him because I'm
tired of people making fun of me how I'm
different oh I'm so red how I have claws
for hands boy can we sure relate to that
we know what it's like being different
at least you have claws look at us we
don't even have anything no hands no
paws no hooves just plain old stuff yeah
you're not the only different one people
make fun of us too you know my ponies
are still in the ground though I guess
we're a little more alike than I thought
yeah I guess we are huh hmm you know
what go ahead and destroy Townsville we
don't like these people anyway
yeah actually people are jerks if you're
the slightest bit different people make
funny well ponies hearing you all talk I
don't feel as angry anymore I don't feel
so long then maybe you don't have to
destroy the town anymore hmm perhaps I
don't yet really good bye girls huh well
that was easy and so once again the day
is saved thanks to hey girls
we just wanted to say that even though
we don't have fingers of our own we know
it's not the end of the world see girls
that's exactly what I was trying cuz
we're taking yours
[Music]
so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
video click the one in the left if you
want to see the last year ryan video
click the one on the right and also
thank you so much to our friends at
tanaka see for helping this animation
come to life well I mean the animation
didn't come to life it's still in
animation but you know like from well
you know what I'm talking about just
click one bye