welcome to pranking a prank er right now
we're gonna pray braggart hey guys so as
some of you might know we went to LA a
couple weeks ago to film some videos
with our friends and one of them was my
dare you video with our good friend use
it from fouseytube I'm sure you guys
already know what that is if you don't
you probably have at least seen one of
his videos
he's basically a prank er who does some
of the funniest pranks that I've seen
like the Mortal Kombat and the elevator
prank or like the yoga pants prank he's
done some of the biggest pranks on
YouTube and in addition to doing the I
dare you video we also decided that this
would be the perfect opportunity to
prank him as well give him a little bit
taste of his own medicine you knows now
we've done pranks before but we've never
actually done like really big well
thought all pranks ain't the kind that
he does and also we've never had to
prank a professional pranker before so
are trying had to be a little bit
smarter than your average prank not just
somebody popping out of a box and
scaring him okay that's exactly what we
did anyway luckily d-trix one of our
other friends let us film at his place
because he just so happened to have this
random stamp of monthly dues that they
sent him for some product placement
thing we decided to take out all of the
middle boxes and hollow it out and hide
somebody in there with a scary mask
that way they could pop out and scare it
the only thing is we were pretty sure he
was going to be a kind of skeptical of
this random Mountain Dew Mountain like
that's one of the first things your eyes
goes to when you enter that room so
instead of doing the scare right in the
beginning which is pretty predictable we
decide to do the scare at the very end
after we finished building I dare you
and I dare use take at least two to
three hours to film that means the
person inside of the Mountain Dew
Mountain had to be able to live in there
for about two to four hours so we also
have to make sure that version have
ventilation water or Wi-Fi of course and
not to mention we even put a bottle in
there in case he has to pee after
filming the Dare video we would then get
used up into position by basically
saying that we want to take a group
picture for the thumbnail once in
position the cameraman would then cue
the scare by saying a key phrase and
since YouTube is pretty tall the key
phrase was damn I'll taller you bro
and as soon as you said let us know that
he was on the way we set everything up
and then it was time to prank a
prankster
I'm so bad at evil laughter so we're
setting up the prank right now for
Yousef Dom has all these modern Jews
that under actually sent to him we're
gonna put shine this mask right here go
ahead
he's gonna be hiding in this little
toilet when we given the signore's unit
just pop up experiment it's pretty legit
scary where's Sean here's my house made
myself a seat down there with a pillow
got some water got a peak of ice pack in
case I get hot and then someone to do
and then we made a lid that's gonna go
on top
check out that hole it's gonna be a hole
for the camera even see it a little bit
yeah what do we have together this lot
you know this camera season and they
will also have these cameras I got one
oh he wants to go Kate with some girls
okay because you like come in together a
little bit yeah yeah Danny freakin super
tall grow taller you broke say I defeat
so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
video click on the left if you want to
see the itthere your video we do with
Yousef click the one on the right and if
you can't click it right now that's
because it's not out yet and it's coming
out sometime this week but let me first
just say that it's one of the most if
not the most disgusting idea we've ever
done so you probably don't even want to
click it
trust me it's disgusting so click it