look up man beautiful look we just got
to do it already
ask him out no we got to grow our beards
out look we always talk about it but we
never do it and what better time the
no-shave November than to grow our
beards why do you want to grow beard so
bad why wouldn't you it makes you manly
or people take you more seriously if
you're driving a car and your other hand
gets itchy you can use your beard and
Scratchy and keep trying and girls don't
like beards actually it's been proven
that girls find guys with beards more
attractive in science what about food
when you eat there's always stuff all of
your face yes you can have something for
later it's proven that there's feces in
beer yeah because of this look I'm
telling you beards make people better
okay and isn't it about time we find out
what all the fuss is about
okay fine but I don't know if I can grow
a beard but just don't shave how hard is
that some guys they just can't grow
beards it grows out patchy doesn't grow
fool I mean how would you know though
like you never we never did it so I mean
there's only one way to find out hey I
mean how hard could it be okay yeah so
not that easy yeah three months in the
works look at our faces
[Music]
barely any girl so many spaces and I
look around there's so much hair facial
scars they're everywhere someday ya
gonna be there can't wait to look more
masculine hijack me yet my double I
wanna stand by a harley-davidson going
through
not quite a beer
disconnected there's potential I wanna
be like Abraham Lincoln
[ __ ] [ __ ] I wanna be like Angelina
Jolie
[Music]
I wanna scrub my beard and look like I
am deep in why thanks Kerry Wood on my
shoulder have a drink with the guy
change a tire got a wired one don't take
on job trouble fire
I wanna get dramatic life's probably
more my eyes can't wait to cover up my
skin like a king majestic in the way I
wanna look like Greg and I like her it
doesn't grow up here
quite a fear
almost
there's potential I wanna
everyone in Game of Thrones I want a
beer just like this guys don't wanna be
like
oh my god do we read it oh yeah oh you
look good our beards are amazing this
looks like a real beer I'm so proud of
us he look like Matt we are men are you
guys kidding me that is pathetic guys
what are you guys like 12 I'm not a
beard at all dudes cut it yes he's a
miracle-gro I consider it a bait it
smells like a beard kinda looks like a
beard look at those patches all over
your face you can see your skin I can
barely see it from here get some
binoculars what are you guys going
through pre beardy but like like puberty
just to clear that up
we don't have to take this from them we
need to be proud of our beards yeah yeah
yeah we do we have beards yeah in fact
oh yeah
let's see who has the pre-beard now wait
what
how did you
well can't believe that actually worked
it totally worked yeah how do you think
everyone else gets their beards so you
listen for Angelina hey guys thank you
guys so much for watching so if you guys
want to buy this song or if you just
want to help out all the sales David and
I are gonna be donating to the Movember
foundation a research a bunch of
testicular cancer prostate cancer a
bunch of men's health issues obviously I
think iTunes takes a little cut of
whatever it is we sell but all the money
that would normally come to David and I
is gonna be all 100% donated a charity
rating is really good so don't worry the
money is being put to good use if you
don't want you this on that's perfectly
fine I will see you guys next week thank
you guys so much for watching I don't
have an outro I already did the teehee
so now what