yeah well always those kids are your
parents wouldn't you play with I just
got my heart broken so bad for so long I
just don't want anything right now
we dropped 130 K in the video and I got
to monetize and stuff good to go welcome
back to another episode of bought the
peel podcast I am Ryan and we have David
in the moderator see we have papa right
here and we have a very special guest
all the way from Australia Danny from
half of raka raka
yeah yeah yeah raka raka raka all right
that's raka raka but everyone says raka
raka I know I thought it was raka raka
but he said raka raka why'd you say that
it's an American thing you know rocket
more like you know that's why I would
spell at least I always thought it was
yeah four yeses pronounce rocker is
Rocco I'll just come up with that name
uh it's like a suburb that we grew up in
was Perico
oh yeah and it was like everyone's like
all going down to Rekha so you know and
then with like my brother and I are
twins raka raka okay yeah that's where
it came from but see you you're from
Adelaide yeah Adelaide South Australia
yeah no one's benefit represent oh yeah
we're just talking about it we both did
chosen Adelaide I didn't I thought it
was a big place but it's not it I guess
it's not popular no that's like Sydney
and Melbourne on the vamp Isis in
Australia I'm sorry
that's so it was pretty children uh it
was we're only there for like one like
almost like 24 hours and it was super
quiet like five town I was like god this
is cool they know me like what it was do
they go with you cuz I went for it not
only for us as well
no no I went with a bunch of other
people with Jase Lee we know they are
singers I was there too
oh yes I do know that yes yes Wayne
dropping twins yeah yeah yeah we just
had this conversation too but about
twins yeah we asked about what but I'm
not the whole twin no have you have you
it because you have a twin brother yeah
have you guys ever dated another twin
another twin combo
no never never whatever is that weird
yeah that's super weird yeah yeah like
if it's so weird I think like my brother
and I are attracted to the same sort of
person I think my god there was a girl
that I was like that was on my Instagram
and I must like this chicks really
really you know really hot and then
Michael texted a girl that I was like
who's that cool she's really really hot
so I think you guys are very similar
obviously I guess so yeah maybe what's
the biggest differences uh he's more of
like an athlete bully sort of dude he's
a bully I've been bullied now by Michael
he picks on you he picks on me and then
I'm I'm the nerd twin well I know that
he did one of those boxing matches right
yeah he fought scarcely come on yeah he
did and you had no interest in that no I
want to go back kicked in
why have you fought a smaller guy yeah
yeah I could go maybe or were you born
first or second no I'll a second oh you
were saying that's always like
apparently that's the thing like the
second twins always a [ __ ] twin wait
really
yeah I didn't know that yeah smarter
though I'm smarter okay I mean he had
his fight and then you had your own
fight in a way like a couple days after
right with kelex oh oh in Soul battle
yeah it had an insult match and I know a
fall what do you mean well like we hear
about this by the way so so wheat like
there's a youtuber called calyx who does
like insult matches and then you know
you bet to come up with these really
brutal disses and it went really like
well I was a Calvin mock was a care of
it but the audience was like whoa
because my dad's got cancer and he was
like pain out my dad's cancer and I was
like dissing his girlfriend his
girlfriend was right there it was really
brutal that's pretty pretty far also
calyx had cancer yeah that's right so
he's yeah he's allowed to say cancerous
oh yes your family so you're allowed to
say that's right yeah yeah it's crazy
yeah what pretty really good you should
watch it it was a great video though
hilarious that's right your guy's Bren
you guys do a lot of pretty crazy things
I mean yeah sometimes I was I'm like
wondering if they're real but like I
mean I'm are they real yeah like there
are certain videos that are rou like we
do a lot of
practical stuff on a dress I like their
stunts and the effects and stuff it's
all practical and then like we've had
injuries before on set like my brother
we do these live like wrestling matches
mm-hmm we're like Marco dresses up as
his character wanna MacDonald on our
Channel and he like like does like a
fool like deathmatch wrestling match
which is like a really full-on wrestling
match with like Bob woth um tax and and
that sort of stuff that's all real box
yeah it's all real yeah yeah so he broke
his nose he cut like he cut like a hole
out of his back like it was yeah it was
Nazi inspired by mankind yeah definitely
inspired by mankind I loved him growing
up Wow
yeah Cactus Jack though that was his
better persona and and I and I saw a
video of you guys you guys did some like
slam someone on a table from like two
stories high yeah yeah that was the rest
thing that she yeah that was crazy yeah
as nuts yeah and so yeah that's what my
co-workers nice well it was on that one
yeah you had to get it read where were
you I was filming it oh no no I like I
like we grew up doing that stuff like I
got parents whenever home so we always
like did like really violent wrestling
matches and as we got older and like the
more stuff we did like everyone wants it
atop each other so it got really out of
hand and really violent
what's the craziest thing you've done
what is it that well you have those
wrestling matches are pretty full-on
yeah like it's like yeah you guys are
like like big jackass basically yeah
Jack Astor's but like a driver rights
groups and stuff like that I love doing
practical stunts I could say you were
saying your your you know lay rate how
long how long have you been here I've
been here for like two and a half months
that's it talk about what you working on
here yeah yeah I wrote a horror film
cool talk to me so I came out to LA to
try and shop it and we got a big bite as
well saying earlier okay and so we've
got like a really amazing producer just
signed on then a bunch of companies have
signed on so like we're gonna announce
it soon are you at this are you at the
stages of like already like it's gonna
happen yeah it's like they're
contracting it right now so I guess if
like the contracting fall through then
it won't happen but apart from that yeah
looks like it's your first script you
sold yes first trick yeah it's the first
time that we like properly finished and
tried to sell yeah it's your first one
in your soda that's amazing yeah you
know but like that's super uncommon
really yeah isn't it to sell your first
script that's pretty absolutely yeah
absolutely
that's so crazy like we sold a TV show
back in Australia and then our um the
network that purchased that just didn't
like do anything with it like we've
finished it we had like the Bible in the
pilot that like yep we're gonna finance
it and then I was like I get one can we
write the second episode and it was just
the thing where we never heard from them
mmm so I think they bought it just to
have it and not do it or something oh
that's weird
yeah it was really trash yeah well I
mean you guys do a lot of like you've
other than the crazy things you guys do
like crazy effects and you do a lot of
like scripted material and yeah are you
the editor or yes I like irons yes me my
brother say I'll like think of what the
idea is usually in a more like
improvised on set or have a script
mm-hmm and then so he'll star on it I'll
shoot it and then I'll do like a rough
cut he'll do a fine cut and he will do a
color grade I'll do it the color grading
you'll do sound effects of music mm-hmm
yeah we split it up and then we've got
like a VFX team if it gets really really
heavy you know how big is your full crew
then well I don't know it like it
depends on the project like sometimes
it'd just be Michael and me and then
other times it could be like 15 people
so just oranges you do then yeah the
core is just us - yeah and then we're
like a stunt coordinator for the biggest
stuff as well so if you want to do wild
work or like car crashes and lots of
stuff we get in like a part that's all
in Adelaide yeah all in Adelaide always
never late yeah we are watching that a
clip of you guys kind of just like nice
and by a cornfield or something you guys
are just kept jumping on to windshields
and just doing all right yeah yeah do
you think the fact that you were raised
in Adelaide and there's like really
nothing to do it's a smaller town
there's so much space that you're kind
of like let's utilize this and it was
like I think what is really aggressive
children like a large city you probably
wouldn't like it we still would have
like done the same sort of thing it was
always like yeah well always those kids
that your parents wouldn't let you play
with you know like yeah you were the
kids we were those kids hang out with
those can you describe your your parents
like what are they like like pretty
laid-back like my dad was just never
home like he was always working so we'd
always entertain ourselves and then like
we had our grandfather that lived with
my dad that was looking after us then he
passed away more 13 and then so like
yeah we saw our mum every now and then
but we provide daddy was just never home
so we always just you know get rapport
stuff yeah
yes report we will board we have to
express ourselves I mean what did they
say when they see these videos though
like they must say something right boy
yeah like originally I doubt I think it
was trying to get us to get a normal job
but then lice is not started picking up
have you guys ever had a normal job
no I'll so like for me to make money
yeah I was like checking into medical
trials and testing drugs that were on
the market oh my gosh yeah and so like
that was my jokes I can't really do
anything else how much do they pay no I
wasn't very good it was like probably
like 180 bucks a day or something and
they wouldn't they they take your blood
or they inject stuff in yeah yeah so it
depends on what the drug is like you
check into the hospital for like a month
at a time or two months and then they're
like alright we're gonna test this out
we've tested on rats but that did that
kind of thing I guess it has to exist
somewhere in real life so you've
actually done it yeah anything like
anything crazy yeah so like at one time
they like it was like a drip though
drifting the drug into my arm and then
it was hurting and I was like oh [ __ ]
this is hurting like you want us to stop
no no it's fine
and then I just kept heard and kept her
and I could feel it [ __ ] you know
going through me and then my entire left
arm just went paralyzed and I couldn't
move it and I was like I can't be mom
but what do you mean I can't be mom like
Tran squeezed my finger like a cod [ __ ]
and then once they sort of took it out
in the drug sort of wore off like I had
yeah they tell you what it was yeah they
tell me about I did so many of them I
said what they'll say is so crazy
yeah that's a very cool first job yeah
it was an awesome job
how about first job that I was in a VFX
house when I was 16 but I got fired like
two weeks in oh yeah I was terrible the
job I don't know I think I'm just
terrible at holding a normal job I just
couldn't do it like I imagine if you
weren't doing the videos are doing these
stuff I'd be like yeah what the thing is
it's hard to go I think it would be hard
to go back to a normal job but maybe if
I never had done it maybe I don't know I
used to be very just like I'm gonna play
by the book and just you know graduate
high school get into a good college get
a normal job in medicine or something
and yeah yeah and then now when I think
about it as like man I don't know how I
would be able to work a specific hours
you know like yeah be hell oh yeah like
what were you gonna do if you weren't
gonna do you film I was gonna
being some kind of x-ray like nuclear
medicine or something alright yeah yeah
no no I mean I I was going to try to hey
I did like a year and a half of college
did you go to college no I didn't go to
college
I am I did like a year of a media course
after school okay and then I was in film
then
yeah like we've been doing us this for
like 926 right now and you guys started
filming all of your wrestling stuff at
the age of nine yeah oh we sound like
making videos whoa nine and we start
arresting a crowned eleven and then we
started really hurting each other like
around 14 15 was it was it because you
guys were like just rough and aggressive
or was it because you guys disagreed on
things
no we're just a bunch of Pharos like
little like like I said our friends were
like it was I can really like sort of
not the best area and like we'll just
have a bunch of feral friends and we're
just a bunch of fools that's pretty
normal in like Adelaide is that like was
that it considered like a I don't know
not a bad area but like a rough just
like in like a not like a higher social
you know area I see yeah it's just that
there's a word called bogan in Australia
like where bogans they're like you know
is that like true blues right now it's
like Australia to hillbillies like feral
is just like you know like yeah see what
bogan
so you guys have close to 6 million
subscribers yeah almost a billion views
you guys have done pretty well for
yourself yeah I think we would have a
billion views but YouTube keeps removing
up yes yeah yeah so you probably already
do but there what on private or there
just what I remove them there to say oh
really yeah it's too dangerous or well I
don't know it depends on the video that
like this is too violent this was to
this this was to that and that started
happening for you oh I'm pretty pretty
early on but once that once the ad
pocalypse thing happened we were just
screwed like yeah adsense is just
nothing you know yeah like I made
nothing of had since and then like yeah
they just started removing and hiding
into monetizing and like it was just it
was hell so where's your form of revenue
coming in then well also like right now
it's like we live off brand it was
pretty much yeah and then say yeah
you're a patron or anything like that a
patron as well yeah yeah but like at the
main income would be produce so these
brand deals
I mean the the ad pocalypse it really
affected obviously the creators but it
was because the brands didn't want to
advertise on certain types of content
yeah
so when you guys are working on these
brand deals do they feel the same way
when they're working with like your you
know your type of content yeah I think
so there's like there are certain brands
that will advertise on our stuff and
there's like two sites the rack rack I
like we have our violence side but we
also have like the PG side as well and
there are lots of brands that want to
work on you know crazier content and
we've spoken to those brands and we've
spoken to like Google about it and like
that we've worked at brands with it like
you can't work with that brand like
we're not letting that brands in our
platform and I'm like you're scaring off
the people that are gonna advertise for
mature content mm-hmm it's it's like
they just shoot themselves what types of
brands would like like advertising yes
so like it I come so a lot of film and
TV stuff you like you know that TV show
the boys that just came out like they're
they're keen to have like edgier content
more like stuff like Adam and Eve would
have edgy or content or you know like
people like that so like incident you
know what does it called VPNs and [ __ ]
like there are there are lots of brands
that will have that is down to do it
yeah if they want to do that the vile
stuff but then we also have the PG stuff
as well which we can do right altimeter
trying to it seems like you're trying to
take your career off YouTube right angle
yeah mainstream movies yeah shows
exactly so doc 2018 were like I decided
I was like I was like I'm not fulfilled
anymore on YouTube I can't feel so
restrictive in like hate it there you
know and that just being really there
are arseholes
yeah was it almost like in a way the
whole des monetizing of your channel
Thicke was it helpful actually to help
you guys a jump because it's like man
this isn't worth it anymore yeah I guess
yeah I guess it's not a great thing yeah
but I could see how like you could you
know I mean it's a scary thing to leave
your bread and butter right yeah exactly
for something else and then so it was
like we had wool riding a film before
that all happened and it was a thing
where we're so caught up with being
youtubers and traveling and doing this
doing that we never focused on it right
was like 2,080 knows I yeah I'm gonna
focus on it like this year and like from
now on you and then yeah so it worked
out apparently the movie could still be
crap it comes out I mean that's still
pretty like I said it's you don't really
hear people writing the first scrip and
then selling it selling that first
script I
you hear a lot of writer friends that
they write out hundreds of scripts and
these stuff and sold one yet so yeah
it's pretty amazing yeah yeah I'm really
proud of it like uh yeah I'm really
really happy with it and you and you
said it was a horror script yeah it's a
horror film you know just I mean I would
have to I don't know why I would have
assumed you done like comedy or
something yeah I don't know like uh yeah
I really do love horror so like this is
a horror film and the other ones were
riding or riding one action one and
another horror one well action as well
yes yeah action really awesome yeah are
you guys gonna I mean if you make the
offer you guys gonna be in the
production side - yeah so we're
directing it okay yeah yeah I say like
uh yeah my brother and I would co-direct
if I decide to let him in because he's
being a bully right now he's doing this
thing this whole distract warn me on
like on our channel yeah but is that
that did that plan no yeah it was like
well he's like I'm doing just check on
you and you better respond I was like
what the heck so he like made me out to
be some like money-hungry villain and he
video and say I was like I thought I had
two hours to wrap mine though yeah I'll
just play I'll play the villain but
you're more of the writer out of the two
right yeah we had five weeks for use
that team at two hours to write mine I
was like so I just sort of slept to give
her something really crafted I was like
I'll just play the villain I was like
rapping about beaches and money like
that's what like the whole thing was
about like as a joke but in my audience
like oh yeah Danny is like to sell out
Marco is the one that's dedicated to the
original stuff but also that [ __ ] so
like everyone's against you right now
but he is a bully it sounds like you
guys have sibling rivalry yeah I guess
so a little bit all right this is the
first time he brought my car of the
video like he like I left the car back
in Australia that I do Drive and he took
it to my cousin's farm and blow it up
and I was like he blocked my car I was
like it's not necessarily done cold for
it makes no sense you seem so happy
about it it's using you're just a happy
person in a happy person yeah he blows
my car's pretty good it's like he blew
it up so I was like okay well I've
already sang to his card and so he's at
a really expensive guys got Jerry
rovol are things I know the Range Rover
service yeah yes oh he is one of those
in that I got a friend to smear [ __ ] on
his windshield and where was the [ __ ]
from my friends also you want to see
this stuff it may or may not be on
YouTube yeah as it may remove it they
didn't remove it and they really say
that they removed it
you can't put shootable windshield well
you brought my car what the [ __ ] is what
my old reaction from a blown-up car yeah
it's so small and then he's like stained
it like smells like [ __ ] permanently
take it to the wash a couple of times I
can't scrape off the char bone like my
car's completely totaled closer you guys
I mean obviously there's like this
rivalry and I'm sure a lot of it is for
YouTube right yeah but how close are you
guys like really are scenes well like we
don't really talk about anything other
than this stuff I mean like yeah yeah so
it's sort of like there's more business
I think it's more business I wouldn't
like have a bad day we should talk about
yeah I've been the case growing up yeah
I think so yeah must be is at some point
where we just sort of stopped being
problems now we'll just like business
partners right yeah geez way as twins
you know you hear stories about twins
feeling certain things or like saying
things at the same time across the world
and you know those types of stories like
have you ever experienced any sort of
strange yes it's so like it's a weird
superpower like I if he needs to piss I
need to piss that's pretty good power so
that that was the one thing and then the
other thing is that yeah we sometimes
would say the same things at the same
time yeah and like saying you know at
the same time just because you're just
so similar yeah I guess so
so like I don't know that they're the
two weird things that apart from that
like I can't talk to him right now
without talking him on the phone like I
can't communicate with him no yeah yeah
but I wonder if like you know they they
used to do those weird experiments back
in the World War like Hitler dude
they're like oh we're gonna take twins
into submarines yeah take one into one
room one of the other and then kill one
and see if there's any reaction to the
other one hmm so like yeah I don't know
like maybe apparently those experiments
worked so I don't know oh I've heard of
that
yeah I know what the results were yeah
yeah should maybe do a video on that
that might be interesting yeah I think
mark would be shot the head just smear
[ __ ] on his face and know what yeah well
yeah he was angry well I guess since the
whole you know you're changing focus
from YouTube into doing your own script
yeah you guys kind of like branched out
and you guys started collabing a lot
more during that year ah no we we
clapping I think from the start like uh
like I think we have uh such as the
different starts what everyone was doing
so we were able to get some pretty big
collapse pretty quickly like like Logan
Pole and like Kay aside and that sort of
stuff like that they're keen to work
with us so like we got into those clubs
pretty quickly like after our first year
on YouTube we started clapping all these
people I actually wrote a script once
for Ryan oh really yeah Ben you remember
Ben Grubbs yeah yeah who sent it we
never heard back from you I don't know I
don't remember ever getting a script to
be honest I really don't I really seen
your stuff before I mean I seen back
when you guys did like the Star Wars and
yeah yeah this is dope and especially
back then like that was like yeah unique
you know it's just like yeah those guys
are dope I don't remember ever getting a
strip really unless what was it supposed
to be like me and not going to
Australian no no it was I could get it
was like extreme tag was the video
well like you will Microverse and Trevor
and tag and it got like you're like now
you're at now you're at than yours that
crash cart we travel now you're
definitely not remember yeah we wrote it
for for Ryan well I mean if you're ever
you know gonna go back to YouTube
if you're tired you're tired of selling
movies you know I mean I'm down first
channel is in need of it
I can't like say you this time you still
post normal videos along with the nut
this year I've actually been like taking
a break this I've been doing the podcast
yeah yeah cuz I was like just I mean you
know I mean you said the same thing
you've kind of felt like unfulfilled
yeah yeah just got tiresome you know I
felt like I was making the same things
and like yeah get it like oh this will
get views cuz it's popular and you make
something cool out of it but it's not
like it's not growth yeah yeah so for me
I mean I don't know if I don't know I'm
just putting words in your mouth but
that's all no no I completely uh yeah it
does feel repetitive and you do feel
like - doing the same thing yeah and
then when you repeat it like if I you've
done this before knowing you stray from
it I coulis
yeah told you you've changed exactly
yeah yeah I mean people for the longest
time because we started doing these
podcasts and so different from is the
first time I'm actually being myself
like on a-- yeah in first channel videos
and people were like alright why are you
so grouchy or like why are you why
you're not happy all the time like you
know like you know people just didn't
know and I just got tired of just I
guess doing the same thing I think a
break figure you know but we're still
making other content yeah yeah but still
trying to figure out what I want to do
it was nuts free it was pretty
exhausting dudes content just like that
though I know but you you were like
doing it weekly yeah for a little bit it
was like you were pretty consistent like
I would go between like two months about
uploading sometimes yeah yeah so props
to you I mean you guys did some like
your dinner uno video and when did that
come out oh that was 2016 I think yeah I
think when do we do ours before me so
yeah so it was a little before that I
was like oh this is pretty like we were
pretty happy with it and then yours came
out I was like okay well now ours is it
relevant like live-action and like ours
is just [ __ ] like what you guys did I
was like okay okay these guys are good
so you guys kept getting better so
there's a sec okay I don't wanna like
Ben's pretty dependable so yeah yeah
there's probably something I missed
yeah yeah but talking about how you guys
are kind of like you know taking a break
and finding that compromise and stuff a
lot of times with artists they'll be
like oh I want to express my true self
but then it's like how do I make money
with that yeah
I think with you because like your
guys's videos are getting blocked or
hidden or sometimes monetized and it's
like why don't you just show less
violence and you guys are just like we
love violence though yeah well I think
that it was sort of like they were
hiding things that weren't even violent
like if it was like certain amount of
swear words I can that channel was just
targeted yeah you know and then I Mikael
of making non violent videos but they
were still striking us alike you know
yeah
changing our channel like like we
started doing vlogs for a beer and then
we started doing I don't know what we
ended up doing like we sort of lost that
way but I just have my oh we won't make
you what I wanted to make anymore so
yeah like that writing has been so
fulfilling it's been the best thing if I
can love a love writing is that it's I
love it so much now right and we're
still doing the big videos like we got
Harry Potter those Star Wars 2 coming
out soon oh that's the one yeah yeah
yeah that's a really like a really big
video and I think back to our old sort
of videos like it's really huge so I'm
really excited to drop that so I'm still
excited to do videos for YouTube but
yeah it just won't be the main focus
yeah yeah how does Michael feel about
the writing and all that well I don't
know I guess that's why he made the dis
tracks he was like I'm still down for
YouTube he's all salty then he must be a
little bit salty and he's like I'm gonna
go back to 2017 with these districts I
know we're gonna have to get him on
later and see his point of view if he
ever comes here you're saying you
screwed up this brand oh I was telling
them earlier for yeah yeah I want to
talk about people know a little bit more
about your twin yeah
Michael is unreliable he's a bit of an
unreal of hood this chick here can vouch
for it hello yeah she's there in that
girlfriend here my future wife
yeah but yeah so like like he was in
together London for this event and then
he's gonna leave today but he messaged
me today he's like I concur my passports
destroyed and I can't go now I was like
yep spoken to the brain for two weeks
how is your passport suddenly damaged
and say I've had to cancel all my plans
to do his plans you know so what's the
saddest place I've to take his place yet
and say like even the friendly he was
going with was like I haven't heard from
Michael what's going on I'm like ah
today said Marcus he's unreliable yeah
we should be good if he was doing other
stuff but he's just making diss tracks
on me and flora what seems like I mean
like this that's like we're really sure
you think that happened so positive like
your car got blown up he's like come to
the event that you're gonna have to take
his place for and they seemed very
positive well it's still like I still
look at it and go how much were a lot
laughs could be so much worse right I'm
just trying to figure like I feel so bad
for my dad like I see my dad getting up
five days a week to go to the scene that
he hates and I'm like am I really gonna
get up silicon you gotta London to be
part of this event and be paid like it's
so stupid to be upset I guess I have a
question did your brother also do the
drug testing thing no no it was just me
saying maybe that's why you're so
positive yeah I've got like a weird drug
lasting effect I had a friend that once
did the drug tests and they did it on
rats and they bought every one in a week
after they done the drugs they're like
we don't want to worry anyone but the
the rats that we tested the drug on some
of them have gone blind so like that was
like a really scary call so crazy yeah
you guys signed a waiver so yeah like
whatever happens happens yeah so crazy
once I turned yellow like a Simpson
because like something to do with my
liver like I was yeah yeah yeah yeah and
then once I was having spasms oh my gosh
yeah but I was still functioning but
thank you for but I did love checking in
there there's always weed people that
are in there it's always like a weird
thing like I do love going to the drugs
but I remember there was a point where I
was still doing YouTube videos when I
was doing the drug trials and I was like
aw crap we don't need to do it anymore
you know but I still feel like I want to
check in and watch something while I'm
in there yeah I'm sad to do some kind of
like non-disclosure right when you're
yeah I was gonna say you could just film
yourself that'd be interesting already
oh you know definitely yeah but I would
be that would be really cool like today
I'm paralyzed
[Laughter]
I got paralyzed for a day or whatever is
it up you just said Michael got like a
like one of the stunts that he did who
will letting off these mortars and this
stick went into his face and it was
sticking out of his face
and his rock facts are just completely
Nollan those like a stick hanging around
space yeah it was really bad
[ __ ] you
on that note we're gonna take a quick
she break and we'll be right back and
we're back but we just found out some
interesting information we have a
question about that because there was a
video right that you posted recently
with Riley Reid yeah yeah who is a porn
star she is indeed an adult entertainer
yeah and yeah and you said you're
staying in LA right now with her yeah
that's correct yeah okay is that the
question
no no I'm trying to confirm things right
now the question we have written here is
are you dating
Riley Reed or are you dating a porn star
all right ah no I'm not dating Riley
read I'm really good friends of Riley
like she's super I've never had a party
and then we went out and we got some
food and some drinks got completely
hammered and woke up somewhere with no
hands and now like I don't know we're
just I don't know we hit it off like
she's really really cool she's super
unique she's really funny she's super
smart I love hanging out with her she's
really cool to be around and I've never
met someone like it actually so keen for
anything and everything like we've gone
a Burning Man comic-con went to Michigan
to film with longneck and you know all
those guys oh she came with you yeah
yeah she's cool yeah it's not she's like
abner I love I love hanging out over but
yeah we are just friends like your BFF
she is my BFF attea yeah yeah
would you I mean I mean would you be
interested in dating her so it's a thing
where it's an awkward thing because you
know I'm like I've got feelings for
someone else right now back in Australia
unless it's like really one side and
unreciprocated say okay I've just had my
heart broken for so long and then came
out to LA and I was like I need to try
and get away from feelings you know I
don't want to feel anything anymore
mmm well staying with the porn stars
awaited
don't entertain oh yeah she's like as a
youtuber do you do you date like you
have a girlfriend have you had like so
this is this is the one thing I just got
my heart broken so bad for so long I
just don't want anything right now well
not even breakup like it was never even
a thing it was like unreciprocated
one-sided Lala it was ages like I lost
count the years Wow oh yeah you've been
in love with this woman for many years
yes man it was just not reciprocated
yeah yeah it was really really one-sided
it was never really a thing and I always
thought well maybe it'll be a thing one
day but it just wasn't si was like yeah
it was really really painful and it was
like it's the point where I'd get
anxiety before I saw them like I was I'd
swear my heart's pounding I'm like oh my
god so I'm so used to getting hurt by
them you know and yeah it was just a
really it's like a close friend kind of
thing because it seems like yeah yeah
like I still saw them and hung out with
them and everything so like I I got
really good friends with them and always
spoke to them but it was just yeah
feelings were never the same so as we
pick at the scab and open up a L boom
yeah yeah I guess what was the turning
point where you're like this is not
gonna work well I was like um well I
started riding when I was upset so
there's a lot of that stuff in my
scripts so maybe that's why I got picked
up picked up because there's a lot of
like I felt really I guess authentic for
like for some area yeah like I said like
I want that stuff is in the script and
all sort of like therapy to ride it
you know and then also I was writing I
was writing songs a bit as well for some
artists like a bit of guys writing stuff
and it got to the point where I was like
picking fights as a person so I could
like get upset to write lyrics it was
just a weird toxic thing artists scripts
yeah but yeah like I'll even now the I
don't know it's just still like a really
weird thing you know well before this
crush that you had lasted X amount of
years
did you like while you tubers still did
you yes you have like a girlfriend later
yeah it was like I don't know playing
the field a bit I guess never never like
a proper girlfriend yeah yeah never
never that like it's always been that
you know messing around or maybe but
like it was never like I never had like
a proper proper relationship for anyone
are you ready for one
ah well no now I'm not now I'm like no
way yeah
good that's to painful it hurts too much
yeah it's like I mean but if the right
one came along yeah possibly like I yeah
ah today I'd rather not right now
it'd be a thing where I'm like maybe in
a couple years down the track or
something it hurts too much and I've
still got feelings for this other person
am I it doesn't feel like they're gonna
go away anytime soon you know you know
what if this movie does really well yeah
it might work maybe definitely at that
point do you still take that you never
know people change they're really
awesome person there but it was just
yeah just sad times guys I need a break
now
it'll be better yeah how's your
brother's love life then you can [ __ ] on
that
yeah let's [ __ ] on that Donna I don't
know like I he's I think he's more of a
sleep round sort of guy right now as
well I guess he's not looking for
something I don't know though I don't
really talk to him about it
mmm that's how much we don't talk about
things but like yeah who knows I know
there's a girl that's interested in here
interested in him here but I don't know
maybe hmm
we'll see I just said that like our
productivity will go down if we're in a
relationship
yeah true you know yeah do you feel that
I feel like you definitely if you're not
in a relationship you don't have to you
can focus on what you're interested in
yeah you have to worry about another
person so yeah I think you can still
make it work but it is time time is like
limited you know yeah yeah and you have
to use some that time so how long how
long have you been in your relationship
for about a little over three years
almost four years yeah yeah that's
awesome see ya love when love loves back
for me affirmed you Ryan
well that's oh I don't know if it was it
to the same degree yeah that you're
describing yeah a lot a lot of the
previous girlfriends that I've had word
ended up premium of yeah that and it
yeah for the most part just didn't work
out yeah it wasn't like same scenario I
guess yeah how many had serious ones
right like maybe like 4 4 3 3 3 yeah
so Yukon high school that's why oh
that's like high school is like a couple
years yeah well that still sounds like
it could be serious yeah yeah maybe but
yeah holy crap for relationships yeah
yeah
you've got your experience then uh I
mean not really like this is the one I'm
in currently the longest relationship
I've been in yeah I'm still learning are
you gonna get married have children well
I mean that's one of the things to it
like I'm still trying to figure out I
mean I think obviously that's always
been the goal yeah you know your kid
like I said I had a plan and then that's
completely changed
ya know so it's hard to say I mean yeah
I mean with you like are you if you're
gonna be working in this area are you
gonna stay in LA uh so yeah I think it
will be like a back-and-forth thing it
it depends on where we're gonna shoot
this film though mm-hmm like I'm if
we're gonna shoot it here then I'll stay
here if we're gonna shoot it in
Australia then I head back to Australia
right but even in being even after this
movie though like you're probably gonna
write more and have to come back out and
pitch yeah yeah so like I think I want
to be out here if I've got a purpose to
be out here even for like it when I
travel I'd rather travel if I've got
something to travel for I hate just
travelling for the sake of traveling you
know like if I'm doing a brand here I'll
go there or for shooting this here I'll
go there right so like if I've got a
purpose to be in LA then like I'll come
out here you think you get over a live
out here I do really miss friends back
home it is like it's really yeah but
like yeah I think so I think I'd love to
have a house here in a house in LA and
go back and forth cuz I'm back and forth
anyway but like yeah like I always spend
heaps of time here then I'm like I
really miss home and then I go back home
and I go I really miss LA so it's like
yeah it's always I think it'll be I
think I'll have a home in both places
what do you what do you miss about it
Adelaide ah having my heart broken
really
[Laughter]
no I think it's like um yeah like the
friends and family like uh you know this
going it's crew yeah I think I think
it's mostly missing friends and family
and also it's a lot easier to shoot
Natalie you know it's hard to shoot in
LA like it oh yeah it's terrible yeah
well you can't blow [ __ ] up here
speaking of blowing stuff what like some
of your videos it has extremely high
production value yeah
what's like the most you guys have ever
spent on a single in a video I mean you
don't have to answer but no I will
answer it it's a it's a pretty stupid
answer so like one time we dropped 130 K
in a video and I got to monetize and
stuff from one hundred and thirty
thousand US dollars so that's Australian
dollars poi like around 90 to 100 K
money and then like it was Dragon Ball Z
versus Avatar hmm I said like we did
like we built these sets we're like
flooding sets we built we're like it was
just like like massive VFX shots and
like it was like a lot you know even
like I'm all sinking the set it was so
expensive
we I love the video but I just got the
wallet I straightaway we made like
harden him what we made off that but no
idea what he's meant yeah it was the
biggest waste of money oh there was a
brat like a brandy oh and there's some
more no no no bro yeah so you guys just
we were like we want to make this we
want to be this money yeah like we
always like there's things that we want
to take off and things that we want to
do like I want to do a flooding set so
he made the video based on the flooding
set alright you know there's stuff like
we're doing in this Harry Potter star
wars video where it's like I want to do
that you know that Harry Potter car that
flies look I want to do that practically
so like we've like that practical flying
car yeah yeah I'm gonna show you there's
not much really cool so like Michael was
dangling off the door and it's like
flying through the air yeah it's really
cool
luckily a brand did this video though
okay yeah so like yeah that's correct
how do you like learn all this cuz
you're like you said you didn't really
care for school or anything yeah you
couldn't hold down a job but when you
find this passion how do you learn that
well I don't know like um I guess stunts
she sort of learns to it your own way
but then we've got a stunt coordinator
as well which we can say I want to do
this this and this and then he can
properly plot it out and planned
and he's really good at that so yeah
shell out Judd Judd wild I say he's
awesome and like for our film we're
definitely gonna get him you know and
then I don't know just like you practice
over the years and you get better at it
you get better at doing whatever you're
rehearsing so each video that we do is
like it's a practice ground you know
just kind of just like combining old
ideas together interesting yeah all the
skills that you learn over those years
and craft yeah so like yeah Ike I'm
really excited for this video to come
out cuz it's really big and like it's
super exciting like so besides the whole
unrequited love situation where else did
you draw I would say I like but where do
you where else did you get your like
inspiration from you know yeah it's a
weird thing I do this thing to my
friends which is pretty cruel if I'm
really fixated on like how would people
react to a certain situation in real
life you know so like I'd act out or
pretend something's happening to certain
people pissy example yeah yeah there was
a big project that we worked on on the
rock record I don't want to say it
because I people still think that it's
rule on our channel but like there was a
project that we did that wasn't real and
then like no one knew that it wasn't
real everyone like we played it out like
it was real and everyone's reactions
were completely like what's going on and
like you got you get to see people's
real reactions because everyone has a
face of how they acting real laughter
then like you know when something
actually happens you know everyone
changes so I'm just I'm so interested in
that sort of thing like with the script
there seems that I wrote it was like I
want to act this out with you know you
know my friends and see how these people
would actually react in situations do
you have characters based off of your
real-life friends and in a way yeah ish
like I based characters unlike is I find
it easier to write if I've got someone
around for me I can fix this person in
my head I can know how this person talk
and I'll hang out with someone a lot to
get their lingo and get how they would
speak and like find out how they would
react to certain things so I do I do
like yeah I do I do definitely based
certain characters off for certain
people and like yeah and then like in
this film as characters at a base to
myself you know elements of that and
then yet a lot from like friends and all
that socially it's so like yeah like
there's like um fight for example
there's like a scene in our script where
his kids offered like a cigarette from
his friend and he really looks up to the
friends and he I come he like I wanted
to see how like our neighbor would react
to that so I offered a cigarette I don't
smoke or anything I'm never gonna give
it to him to see how you react to that
Gyan I mean yeah so like our today is
just looking at that sort of thing fun
people's behaviour interesting that's
really interesting cuz I remember Ryan
saying something similar to me like he
likes seeing the reactions making
somebody feel something when you make
your content oh yeah that was but he's
doing it just to make his never to
people that can't handle its people oh
my god what's happening they're having
fun of it it's never I'm not like
traumatizing anyway like it's people
that can take it like friends that know
me and stuff and so like once they find
out that this is like a prank or this is
whatever like if people are covert it's
fine
so generally these people are cool with
it but like at first was it kind of like
oh do they feel like you're using them
or no really it'd be a thing where i'm
like outside will you mean the someone
walking around outside and like JT like
that sort of stop and then we get out
there's not really anyone walking that
just were to happen right now and then
we just to see how we would react to see
how you do I was just doing a thing like
it's not a prank I'm just trying to
study yeah I was just study it's like ah
yeah and then people know they're like
oh you know okay it's never I would
anyone go like oh man that's too far
you're the boy who cried wolf actually
someone else [ __ ] come out and paper
right there I know it's doing funny but
like yeah it probably is a little bit
mean now that I think of it but yeah our
friends are walking further down bright
heads
so I'm us so we got some some questions
from some fans yeah okay so we got one
here it says so you're friends with both
ksi yeah
they have a fight coming up they do
indeed know your gods
who are you closer to and who are you
rooting for it's a weird thing where
it's like it's even for me because
whatever I'm hanging out of case I might
cast ah so cool he's so amazing yeah
team casa but I hang out with Logan I'm
like yeah Logan so cool too like I
always said they'd be such good friends
you know in real life if they won't be
thing like this and you set up the first
fight too right yeah yeah cuz our Logan
didn't want to do it originally saw flew
out and spoke to Logan about it and I
was like I'd won money on K sighs fight
I was like I'm gonna put money on this
one but I just couldn't bring myself to
bet on either of them I don't want to
root for ya cuca sauce JJ what I'm like
I don't want to see Logan getting his
ass kicked I don't see ya so it was like
um yeah I can't pick a side like it's
impossible like I hated watching that
fight mm-hmm it was so painful to watch
I was like yeah you're watching two
friends beat the [ __ ] out of each other
it's awful I hated it you know it's fine
wait when we had chaos on the podcast we
asked him like could you ever be friends
with Logan and he said he could he
thinks he could he thinks he could yeah
yeah and but then he said he would never
be friends with Jake but I thought it
was so interesting because there Logan
and ki are beefing right yeah what are
they are they are he said he thinks he
could be I might be misquoting but
thinks he could be friends with him
Anderson I said that's a Logan and
Logan's like no not like I think Logan's
like not with it now like I don't know
if I I feel like they could still be
from so interesting you instigated that
you means that it's more studying
running the world from behind the scenes
like I'm curious what did that what did
you say to Logan to convince him I was
just I saw I went there and I was like I
just came back from this fight you know
and like can't cycle drugs like I saw
that what he does even up late like
Logan was sort of like you know JJ
doesn't really upload much but I just
kept like I just kept talking about
every day and bringing up every day and
I was just like it would be the biggest
event in internet history Logan like
it's huge right he's the biggest
youtuber of the UK you're the biggest
youtuber over the US it's a Clash of the
Titans brah like I don't know I was just
yeah that's push for three months he's
like I got
these are for three months spent all of
is that I think I was left like two
weeks trying to convince him like I was
like really trying to convince him like
yeah and he eventually said yeah I'm
gonna do it brah but you know I think he
was great I think the the fact that they
both fought it was super exciting for
the community yeah it was a sport like
it was like not like an actual
aggressive leg like I remember we got
like like we did an interview with BBC
before the fire and they sounded like it
was so this is a while as YouTube's
promoting violence in all this sort of
crap like it's a boxing match what are
you talking about this violence yeah
like they like jumped like yeah like
yeah I don't know they were just trying
to villainize it yeah you can say that
about ESPN there yeah yeah it's a
they've got boxing gloves on yeah I just
I don't know no head guards oh I'm
scared someone's me an octet is a I mean
for sure problem I mean they were taking
hits last time Oh big hits they didn't
have that I mean that's I can't they
can't get knocked out I'm I want them to
both make it's like if you lose my
points it's not that bad but if someone
gets knocked out is gonna be hard to
watch painful to watch they're gonna
mean the [ __ ] out of like like it's
gonna be terrible for the loser if
there's a knock I feel bad for like hope
it doesn't happen you care about both of
them yeah I'd hate to see any of them
get knocked out and there's such big
personalities and like you know they're
all their family and friends are such as
males in their communities and I don't
know it just
I'd feel gonna be painful to see for
sure that's when's that happening
November the 9th yeah so we have another
question from a new burps sorry sorry
about that
apologize Instagram in in Twitter from a
man em7 can you have a fight with
Michael I think what they meant is would
you maybe box all thanks Michael yeah
everyone's like oh this dis track stuff
is just for like a setup for the
undercard fight
I'll be honest right now I'd get my
[ __ ] head kick in if I fault Michael
I've definitely is he stronger than you
oh yeah waste talking to me like he's
like he's easy ease the dominant win for
sure I would get destroyed by Michael
like is because he works out and stuff
and you don't or yeah I think so and
he's just more physically active like I
sit and write and edit and Michael cut
up and he's like yeah yes I like get
destroyed it would be fun though to get
my head keeping my mark
[Laughter]
it'd be cool to see a boxing chess match
like one round boxing one round chess
yeah there you go see there we go
terrible idea yeah alright we got
another question here from Oh daddy Jack
Oh daddy Jack this is a little more
serious question I think okay would you
die for your brother what I'd die for my
brother uh yeah probably if someone on a
gun I don't know what's the situation
spell out a scenario for me there's a
gun and pointed at your brother's head
either you go or you go I'd say like
honest I'd say take him yeah
well this would be a research thing he
doesn't have to set up and see what the
real reaction yeah yes we're gonna prank
him now and actually kill him now yeah I
would die for him to be honest if like
if some of the guns were said I'd
probably really traumatically jump in
front of the bullet and take it for him
what do you do the same maybe see this
is the thing see everyone's got their
answers of what they'd say but how would
someone truly react what's true you have
to set up the scenario and find out
right now that we talked about it I mean
no he doesn't listen to these sort of
things no I mean awesome man I mean
thank you again so much for being here
thank you for having me it's very not
always what's your stuff right honor
thank you for making it happen over
there as well she's beautiful camera
your future wife awesome well you want
to plug in anything where you're gonna
be or where can they find you all right
well I'm moving in with Ryan now so
we're gonna hang out a lot now yeah I've
got nothing to plug thanks for having me
well you're moving I might maybe when it
comes out what's that well it's out
thank you and your social media social
handles
oh yeah just wreck
Rico RAC ka r ACK cool hey and with that
being said you can follow us at off the
pill on Twitter ad off the pill podcast
on Instagram and the way we end this is
we just breathing to the mic so three
two one real find out who this person is
and we're gonna just send it