you know what I don't understand Korean
dramas or all asian dramas they're all
pretty much the same thing and yet
people spend hours and hours watching
them I can pretty much predict what's
gonna happen in every single drama first
they're in love and then they're sad
love comes back and then they're mad and
then somebody dies and for all of you
who don't watch asian dramas this is
pretty much what it looks cheap I do not
know this one man
what
what you know
ba-ba-ba-ba-ba joy will not see you John
oh yeah
he's out dude
let's open it I die
Chico my russian boy and a girl she was
a lot
the
yeah they do
wait no somebody has to die
I'm so beautiful Oh