hey guys as you know I made a bunch of
rants a while back you want to see them
well you can't because of copyrighted
music those videos are no longer
available for you to view so I'm gonna
be recreating those rents and more
starting off with music what happened to
music nowadays people are making songs
that I don't even consider music anymore
it's pretty much like fast repetitive
words with a beat yet artists are making
millions of dollars and I don't get it
it's like they come up with a line and
they're like this sounds pretty good I
think I'll repeat it 20 times in one
song what is the world coming to
imagine if books were like that there
were three things I was absolutely
positive first Edward was a vampire
second there was a part of him that
thirsty for my blood and third Edward
was a vampire see how stupid that sounds
now imagine if music were like that pop
up out pokerface pop pop pokerface ma ma
ma ma wait a second it already is like
that but seriously I thought music was
supposed to have meaning and even if
those repetitive songs do have meaning
it's kind of like okay we get what you
mean now move on anyway another thing I
don't like is when artists make songs
telling you what to do for example you
crank that Soulja Boy I don't want to
crank you I don't even know what that is
and next lean like a cholo come on a
cholo don't even speak Greek and last
one of my favorites the song say my name
by Destiny's Child say my name say my
name first of all I can say whatever I
feel like saying Destiny's Child second
of all I don't even know your name I
know your mother's name destiny
however there is one really really
talented artist my favorite of all
that's right Sean Paul and for those of
you who don't know who Sean Paul is he's
the only guy in the entire world that
can create a whole song using his own
language that nobody can understand I
mean seriously how do you even talk to
somebody like that hey Sean Paul just
give me the light what just give me the
light what Sean a ball Sean a ball yes
that's your name someone give it to
twirl girl just give me the light and
bout to draw
lucky man I gotta know which one I'm
gonna get my blog yes and if you are one
of those people who can actually
understand what he's saying well then
you should be very proud of yourself
because you are only one of the few the
proud the Marines anyway the more of the
story is rap is alive music is dead
that's all I have to say I'm going to
bed peace and that's when I realized the
greatest rapper of all time was dr.
Seuss