so first things first I know I know
before somebody makes a comment I know
my hair is disgustingly long it's
literally never been this long before so
please don't leave the comment here
right can you get your hair it looks
like a dirty mop actually you know what
that's kind of funny go ahead and leave
that comment but it just goes to show
you that I'm so secure with how I look
that I don't even have to hide the fact
that my hair you guys so just because
people have been asking a quick update
from my addiction video I've been doing
good I've literally cut down to about
one Red Bull a day in fact one of the
days I didn't even have a red but that
wasn't today but one of those days but
anyway before I get more off topic like
I said in the addiction video I'm still
gonna be doing a lot of skits and stuff
like I did last year but I'm also gonna
be doing a lot more of these freestyle
vlogs so basically I grabbed a bunch of
deer Ryan's from you guys and we're just
gonna see what happened so let's get
started so gross dear Ryan how many
straws can you stuff in your mouth that
kinda sounds like you just want me to
look stupid so I'm just gonna go ahead
and skip that one and 66 you almost
threw up still gonna use these this I
mean it's my spit dear Ryan can you sing
your ABCs backwards
ABCD efg hijk LMNOP QRS TUV wxy and z
ooh dude he sea horse a hat is so easy
no no he's nails every believer east
arrow he phenomena it is very easy see
the air I spend way too much time on it
look at the Sun went down I guess I'm
just damp what self my dear I do you
pick your nose with your left index
finger or your right huh the way is I
should my left my right he names me
where is that coming from you're right
we sing opera Oh brah
Oh
uh lightheaded honestly when I thought
opera was a nossa little kid last week
you're right you not I cannot
you're right can you even I can even
you're right can you try and call
someone I can not okay yeah that was one
too many puns even for me do you Ryan do
you watch your own videos
I guess serious answer this time I know
I'm not that conceited I don't just sit
and watch my own videos and pat myself
on the back or something you know it's
that would just be weird and conceited
so no I don't do that so no I don't do
that but a good answer to that dear Ryan
do you Ryan how many licks does it take
to get to the tootsie roll center but
since epoch well isn't that crazy cuz I
just so happened to have now I went to
go pick this up real quick a 1 a 2 whoo
a 3 Oh what the that's nothing like the
commercial that's a hundred so far and
it's not even close
600 almost there you can like see the
brown coming out that sounded wrong but
then again this whole deer Ryan is
pretty wrong hey seven eight nine 700
about 700 and now we know how much free
time I have I can't believe I just did
that I thought it was gonna be a lot
quicker I didn't I better not get flight
for this
you're right can you tell us how do you
feel in your read negative comments I
mean what do you really feel seriously
I'll just find a negative comment and
show you what happens from Billy Jones
wow you're a king you piece of 8-inch
your King squinty-eyed in your videos or
go back to doing something like maths
you pathetic Asian fit here you're a
pathetic excuse for a human being go eat
some rice and get the [ __ ] off YouTube
your videos make me wish every Asian was
in the head you're a [ __ ] dick are
you so squinty eyed that you can't even
see can't even see how your videos are
can kill yourself see it's not
um yeah uh you know comments like that
just they make me want to cut you know
more onions because to me you know
negative comments are just so
uninteresting sorry that was so bad but
yes that was a real comment see
basically my real answer is that I don't
really get affected by negative comments
anymore come on guys I've been doing
this for like eight years I'm pretty
sure I've seen everything seriously
your hair looks weird dude Oh am i
that's good I you're I can you rap like
Eminem in my opinion I think that Eminem
is one of if not the best rapper not
that I really know anything about rap
but ever since I was young he was always
my favorite and I guess the answer is
simple no I cannot rap like that I don't
think anyone can just because I can talk
fast it doesn't mean that I can rap it's
two completely different things you're
right he me go grab a ball lamps yeah
sure I'll even do it to an Eminem song
I'm beginning to feel like a left go
left go always think that's one you are
the love squad left squad now who thinks
their father burned up to max one that's
what they said about I'm so bad for more
than rap star but I need a have a
collapse yeah just to keep in my heat I
break your lap toss it a tap sock is my
[ __ ] so high the pop pop he's got that
knot in my back
drop it good a million or a billion
water jettison knows me is the real
Thomas but my name is improper to me
I'll go for a more experiment and I know
that I can rap all that well chipper
evasion this chicken meat leave it leave
it flop you know we're walking into a
land mass with his lamb baby lamb
slapping a Mac on the back with a laptop
that crashed like a pig tax actors night
now back to the lamp router pretend his
lyrical ticking tax Oh Billy Eminem's
our stash to be able to channel Emma
gamoke brightest magical it doesn't
really matter what is here right here
just gotta keep it faster your ear can
hear but you got to make sure that when
you're ending a line its closing off
going off to a row asdf LMNOP one two
three everybody follow me because this
is the part wonderful applause back to
the starting with a third-level what
what a bad answer to that dear Ryan it's
so unrealistic hey thank you guys so
much for watching if you want to see the
previous video click the one on the left
if you want to see the last year Ryan
video click the one on the right if you
want to see a hippopotamus tickling a
giraffe while riding on top of a magical
rainbow on top of a horse picked the one
on the bottom and that's it