got um yep just gotta sit down for this
dear Ryan hey guys yeah I got some new
shirts if you couldn't tell not that I
would plug stuff I don't do that
remember hey guys welcome back to
another episode of dear rise just
because there were so many comments in
the last video reason why there's rings
in my eyes I don't know if you guys can
see it everybody kept saying things like
why is his eyes look so weird I've done
this before I've had it's just a light
guys it's a ring light it's a light in
the shape of a ring a bunch of other
youtubers use the same exact thing if
you ever look in someone's eyes and you
see a ring they're using a ring or we're
all possessed by the devil the devil of
circles rings I don't think that's a
demonic thing or we're all possessed by
ringworms that's gross and itchy I
wrestled I had I don't know why I'm
telling you that it's not attractive all
right guys there's so many deer Ryan's
this let's just get into it here let me
just cut it real quick reach over here
to cut the video right quick cut it
right dere right can you ride a
hoverboard while carrying your friends
why I mean I can carry a friend but if
you're talking about friends it's not
the DVD I so I can carry a friend I'm
pretty sure I can carry one person and
get on a hoverboard but friends as in
plural as in multiple friends I'm not
too sure I wonder what the record is
there's got to be a thing already record
for the most people in a hoverboard I
don't see any record you know what we're
gonna set the world record right now so
we're try and get at least five people
on one hoverboard let go all right there
mister it is so stable 1 2 3 oh my god
oh my god 7 now hi oh yeah oh we're
gonna go get you
Oh God like two seconds oh it happened
dear Ryan please do the rap over from
memory I want to see you try it for
those of you who didn't see that video
that dear Ryan challenged me to turn
Disney's frozen let it go song into a
rap song and people actually thought it
was kind of good some reason even though
I just made it on Garageband in like 10
second not 10 seconds and took me like
couple hours I'm assuming people think I
can do and I haven't listened to the
song since oh I'm gonna listen to it
once and see and if I can still remember
the lyrics but I'll do my best
[ __ ] I'm gonna do it without the Beast
I'll probably do even faster than all
the song was go like a can't hold it
back anymore I got it that's all I
needed that's all I needed let it go cuz
I'm like I can't hold it back anymore
anymore anymore to the waist I'm a door
I don't care what they're gonna say cuz
cold never bothered me anyway wastes no
flows through the air into the down low
miss ruin fractals all around on did you
really think did you get the crown no
sound only Queen up in this town
everytime I blow I hear you're gonna get
it they're gonna snow that I gotta quit
then I let go and think I show that any
little kid wanna get it gotta bring cuz
it doesn't really matter what I see so I
spit it just let it go ah just let it go
yeah conceal don't feel don't I don't
know dear Ryan do it try not to laugh
challenge try not to laugh challenge
here we go
here's cheers big off yeah yep
sorry head off to my nose was bow-legged
Oh cheers Cheers
you spit into my cup Oh farts okay I'm
really threesome I've got the tiebreaker
when it takes all Cheers dear Ryan can
you act out one of those kids who
creates copies of your video this is
like one of my pet peeves you guys know
exactly which people these guys are
these are people who upload other
people's videos specifically happens a
lot on Facebook but YouTube as well
without their permission but they add a
little clip of themselves in the
beginning talking about the clinic even
throw on their logo as if they own that
video to help build their own brand
yeah I'm assuming those are people
you're talking about this is the
Internet okay people don't copy each
other's videos that's wrong you have got
to see how this guy reacts to a deer
Ryan people don't copy each other's
videos that's wrong oh my gosh you have
got to watch this guy's video telling me
to watch a reaction to this deer Ryan
you have got to see how this guy reacts
to a deer right people don't copy each
other's videos guys video telling me to
watch this other guy's video - this way
here's your right - yeah you're right
okay just shut up all of you I get it
you guys steal videos you shouldn't be
doing that in the first place but if
you're gonna steal a video steal the
video you don't have to put your
reaction to the video you just stole we
don't care about that nobody does this
guy gets so yeah dear Ryan can you
please make a reading mean comments
video I'm assuming this comes from like
that Jimmy Fallon Jimmy Kimmel one of
the Jimmy's I'm assuming you mean like
the mean tweets saying oh it's Jimmy
it's Jimmy Kimmel we can try but I'm
pretty sure we're not gonna find
anything like we never get mean comments
efforts all of us here at a rhpc you are
so loved Ryan looks just like
vanossgaming if battles were complete oh
god leave just come true
am I the only one or Derick is not that
funny like everybody else will looks
more and more homeless craig is even
unclear now with praise that means I'll
suddenly are ready to start with the gun
is really a loser
Ryan's lips are so chapped
it looks like my grandma's for China
right looks like you just drink some
milk but the milk
wash your hair looks like deep Shawn's
gold teeth looks like he just hates
someone's and that was the leftovers
I wonder kind of stink yeah I hope
Marley dies okay yeah I'll die I'll die
your face red with your own blood you
get Ryan can you get a trickshot in real
life
do it so close like right there oh my
god the end of this trickshot video
the thing is again so much for watching
we want to see bloopers and behind the
scenes click on the left if you want to
see the previous video click on the
right and remember to keep leaving your
dear Ryan comments in the comment
section below
the Ryan comments in the conversation
below that's kind of a good fun glister
let's go you gotta leave you to your I'm
hopin to the conversation below I don't
know hey I'm still doing it