hey guys so sorry that was in a post
last week I mean other than the podcast
we've actually been pretty on point this
year with the posting and you know
especially with the podcast we haven't
missed a week yet that's a miracle for
us but anyway the reason why there was
no video last week was because I did not
do anything last week I was in LA and
this is something I never thought I
would be admitting on this channel but
the reason for that trip was because of
Valentine's Day that's right I'm not
single
[Music]
Hey what the hell are you guys doing oh
it's seen for you yeah we're just happy
for you man it's a miracle it's not a
miracle stop making it seem like it's so
hard to believe we're not yeah we're
just happy yeah we totally believe okay
you know what can you guys just leave
because this was actually supposed to be
a serious announcement for once and you
guys are turning into some kind of weird
skit joke thing oh is this not weird
joke no and frankly it's a little
insulting that you guys would assume
that we definitely thought it was a skit
yeah or some kind of trolling right
because like that's is you usually do
when it comes to relationships and stuff
yeah like the last time when he was
going to reveal his girlfriend but it
just ended up being Greg you know when I
saw ha because if we didn't see that
predictable those guys I am NOT trolling
and I'm not gonna make some kind of joke
so can you please just let me do my
thing is the longer we prolong this hey
the less serious it becomes and for once
I am trying to be open about this part
of my life so you're actually serious
yes so you really do have a girlfriend
yes how many times do I have to tell you
guys that I have a girl
yeah that was my way of saying that I'm
actually being serious this time Carly
could have just said that but you know
why not add a few more hours to filming
and editing pay for all those costumes
to look guys all jokes aside I am being
serious I am NOT single and I haven't
been for a while now believe it or not
and no it's not the best-kept secret in
the world I mean there's bunch of rumors
I just never publicly came out and said
it people have seen us in public
together we've been in pictures together
we took trips together because we don't
really go out of our way to hide it
we just I've never announced we just
both decided that it'd be best for the
relationship at least in the beginning
to not say anything publicly and then we
just kind of continued to not announce
it because it's just it just became the
norm looking like a huge secret or
anything but since I am trying to be a
little bit more open and honest on this
channel with like you know the podcasts
or videos like this I felt like it'd be
really hard to continue to do that
without you know revealing anything
about this aspect of my life especially
because it's such a big part of and I'm
not trying to make this all overly
dramatic or a bigger deal than it really
is but with that being said I'm just
gonna get straight to the point
so no more theatrics lights I am going
to be revealing for the first time ever
my secret girlfriend of almost two
entire years three entire I will be
revealing my secret girlfriend of three
to five years for the first time ever
by play romantic song that I wrote for
her this belated Valentine's Day about
some of the greatest moments and
memories from our relationship showing
just how great we are together but more
importantly how great I am the
boyfriends another one of those videos
isn't it yep oh and I know you can't see
because of the sheet but there's this
really beautiful slideshow thing that I
made of the two of us since I don't like
to say pictures of us I kinda didn't
have that much to work with so I had to
do some editing
[Music]
to be honest and forgive
guess 2010 because that's when ask him
out and we didn't work out there but the
five years passed and we did a collab
you were a hot song on some MTV cares
he on his side and ear for that show
went to your viewing party for your
episode because I had to let you know I
was into you I wanted to let you know
the truth about how I was a completely
in love even though it's been only a
month with you but think I did in there
was infatuated
the honeymoon stage only lasted a few
months that believe that we can a
reminisce don't remember
first aid let us remember the first kiss
who to say to my precious breathless :
trip than a mr. mountain in truth in my
left eye now to get a nappy I was
needing a little bit but let me get back
to being romantic I remember taking our
first trip across the Atlantic well the
Pacific but that doesn't ride as well
and I she was a business trip so we're
working the whole time in the hotel but
the point is I remembered it and I
remember other things like our
anniversary is probably on the 26 for
23rd I was pretty close this
like a fan
all these years Valentine's Day
don't be late
[Music]
this right over
guess it's time to say your name if the
song needs
[Music]
it's a Chow Arden Arden Cho not Jade
again it didn't rhyme as well so I just
had to kind of change it up a little bit
what's the reveal already oh right um
sorry ladies and gentlemen I'm so proud
to announce my girlfriend Arden Cho
[Music]
I mean technically this is not her but
what we called it another troll video
with another disappointing ending what
no guys this is not a troll video I'm
not trolling the point remains the same
I'm still reviewing the fact that I'm
dating Arden she just couldn't be here
because she's filming the show in
Chicago so I got something stand-in
that's it well yes you did kinda reveal
yeah see but the whole sheet revealed
thing wasn't it I don't like unnecessary
yeah but I mean so are you guys right i
mean ii just spoken to camera where you
are bein a bit like here besides who is
that anyway
wait no I don't think my god who the
hell is RT che