hey guys so I know every year around the
same time when it gets closer and closer
to Valentine's Day I always make the
same type of video where I'm kind of
like not really making fun of romance
but kind of like clowning on the fact
that all exaggerated romance is in like
entertainment and movies and all that
kind of stuff I'm not like really making
fun of romance I'm just kind of dissing
on the whole cliches and old romantic
scenes that happen in movies it's kind
of become a tradition in a way this year
I had a little change of heart get it
because it's like cuz like made of spare
change oh and also I'm gonna keep the
tradition going so let's go chase in
real life breakfast in bed
[Music]
hey hey wake up
what is all this it's breakfast in bed
[Music]
I saw your favorites right thank you
mmm so good anything else you need oh
maybe just a little salt
[Music]
people wake up
baby wake up Hey
look up
[Music]
what are you doing good here you're
awake
what is this it's breakfast in bed
can't we just eat in the flowers okay
that's that's everything so voila
dig in it's all my favorites right yeah
oh you're getting salt everywhere
oh no that's not so remember we ran out
hi what are you doing
oh is that okay this snack seal their
cookies is good perfect
hold on one second I'm on the phone
right now look that so yeah you got to
be kidding me
[Music]
no no no I'm totally free right now
that's why I thought
I I'm on the phone right now so if you
could please come back you know what I'm
gonna have to call you back and so sorry
is just my stupid wife
please come back later I have so much
work to do
yes I have so much to do you just broke
my computer all my clients are on there
I'm gonna get fired now hey I'm sure
we'll be just fine no clearly not okay I
can't see anything what am I getting
what did I do to deserve this kid it's
not my birthday okay
[Music]
in your eyes
no dad I'm good for you dad
[Music]
you go what is this hey ru you pregnant
yeah I know
hold my gut what are we gonna do why we
can't even afford read how did you even
afford this horse or for diapers and
clothes any of it calm down
everything is gonna be just but don't
get on their plane because I haven't
left but it's gonna let in the hoenn I
wouldn't live have never had a moment
[Music]
Gina wait don't get on that plane please
look I know I know I told you to take
that job in Paris where you're gonna be
making a ton of money even though you
have to work for that evil boss that
makes you feel horrible and I know that
straight male coworker that's incredibly
good-looking is gonna be there and he's
been trying to steal you away from me
from the moment you took this job just
roughly 85 minutes ago I can't let you
go because I can't stand the thought of
you waking up alone with no breakfast in
bed I can't stand the fact that there's
no possible way that you're just gonna
randomly show up to my workplace in the
middle of the day more than anything I
can't bear the idea that her son will
only get to know his mother through a
computer screen so I'm Peyton you don't
get on that plane
stay with him
okay I'll stay China we keep telling you
it's Jeana don't get on that plane I'm
not this isn't even my gate I'm going to
the restroom oh don't don't get out
don't get on your foot look riding we've
talked about this I have to go look just
just wait look I know I told you to take
that job in Paris and that I wasn't K
with it but but I'm not because I can't
stand the thought
of you not in the morning timid I was
headed I had it on the way here yeah I
have to go to the restroom no just wait
I can do this I can do this
oh okay okay just you had me at hello
okay what you had me at hello really is
that a movie reference you complete me
oh yeah that's definitely Jerry Maguire
you're a bird I'm a bird so you like the
note but I promised Jack oh never like
go write it hold on your rose and I'm
Jack does this even make sense some
people are worth melting for I wish I
knew how to quit you really Brokeback
coma startup and that really doesn't
work in this scenario I Mullins formally
these aren't even romance movies anymore
you're just saying random quote I'm just
a girl standing in for a little boy I'm
asking him to look okay you know what
seriously stop if I promise to stay will
you just stop this yes yes whatever this
is I promise okay I'll stay um you know
but I'm curious how did you actually get
back here did you buy a ticket well see
I snuck through security and it kind of
ran when they saw me and then I hid from
them and then I tracked you down here
Ryan that's a federal crime you could go
to jail but probably happy you lose your
job you lose everything I know hey does
that mean yep well boys it's not snowing
anymore
what is that so guess again