[Music]
well what is this I don't I don't even
know these people
hey guys this is gonna be a really quick
video just because I'm a little confused
as to what's going on in the world right
now
so I just woke up today at 5:20 p.m. and
I went on YouTube and I saw all these
videos about a royal wedding its trumpet
for are you sick minded people oh pause
the video and press 2 if you want to see
Ryan do some sexual there was even a
wedding cake next to the YouTube logo
and I was like fatty what the heck is
going on if you're anything like me that
sucks you never know what's going on in
the world I don't watch the news I don't
read the news I never caught him you all
I know is the oles but apparently there
was like this Prince and this princess
and they got married and and basically
it was it was a Disney movie I can show
you the world I don't want to see it
okay anyway I wanted to say
congratulations the prince and princess
I guess for getting married and to
anybody else out there who's getting
married
and I have a poem for you that I heard a
long time ago somewhere um it's just
really beautiful I may or may not speak
to you here we go don't let haters keep
you off your grind keep your head up
everything will be fine
keep fighting until you get there when
you're down and feel like giving up
just whip your hair back and forth dude
I don't want to see it
[Music]