aren't you tired of watching those
campaign ads where all they do is brag
about what they've done my policies will
make things better or list an entire
commercial talking crap about another
candidate that's his policy and it's a
bad policy or maybe you're like me and
you just kind of seen those ads but they
don't wrap the numbers and facts at you
they don't even understand over 4.2
million is definitely a big number
hi I'm writing if you vote for me you'll
never watch another campaign ad again
today I say to you that the challenges
we face today or indeed geology and we
will face them today he has a plan to
improve the economy the economy has no
leg room you know it needs to be more
like first class he cares about your
issue access education unemployment
these are all words he knows things no
one else knows starships are indeed
meant to fly not only will we make
healthcare free but it will be forced
he's creating new job opportunities
every day what if we start hiring people
to be your feet for a day he is a master
at the art of debating some even call
him the master debater and put it off
the country steps
why don't you deficit your ass down
he picks up trash off the ground and
almost makes it in he helps old people
cross the street almost look away he
even finishes the narrator's scent this
is sentences
he's a poop scooping hula-hooping
dancing singing good at swinging rock
picking table hitting Diplo to see
babysitting presidential candidate four
years ago you elected the first black
president now you can elect the first
black president that is Asian
I'm right either and I approve this so
then you over coming out today
and God bless