you've seen the videos primitive
technology primitive survival and all
the other primitive building type of
videos that have gone viral over the
past year usually just one or two guys
in the middle of the wilderness building
a house or a pool or a house with a pool
all kinds of structures from scratch
without saying a single word throughout
the entire experience well on this the
very first episode of Ryan tries where I
try to do things that I probably
shouldn't try I'm going to attempt to
create a primitive building video of my
very own but instead of going to the
jungle we're going to the mountains
joining me on this challenge would be
one of my longtime very very good
friends Gregory and what we're gonna be
doing is building an epic gigantic snow
fort entirely from scratch what are you
so we're going on snowboarding trip I
sure did Gregory but I can assure you we
surely are not because what we're gonna
be doing instead is from morning tonight
every single inch of daylight that we
have we're gonna be building and working
and carrying it sweating until there's
no time for snowboarding what do you
mean like that video we did before why
would you want to do anything like that
took us all day yes and I know how
exhausting it was but let me tell you
this one is gonna be so much funner
because not only are we building this
for bigger and better than last time but
we're going primitive which means we
have access to no tools we won't have
seven other people helping us it'll just
be me and you and instead of one long
exhausting day of manual labor
let's multiply that by three welcome to
Ryan's rise
[Music]
[Applause]