it's weird it's like you're missing this
like compassionate bad on this right now
well I wasn't used to girls pretending
like they they liked you a lot and then
the next day they don't and then they
like you again alright and welcome back
to another episode of off the pill
podcast today joining us we have puck
Alito
as usual her huge and a very special
guest miss Arden Cho and I said we
shouldn't bring in but she's been she
doesn't she doesn't bark she's not a
normal dog yeah and she follows me every
was it yeah she's the runt of the litter
[Music]
no I think it's because she grew up on
set with me that is not the reason is
like you trained her to be quiet you
didn't not treat her she was always like
that I don't know if I trained her to be
quiet I definitely didn't but I think
shooting always used to being around a
lot of things happening in production
and I think she got used to it you so
you don't think that the reason why
she's quiet has nothing to do with the
fact that she's the runt of the litter
and yeah well I thought she was deaf for
the first like two years she never
burned she's the best on looks like she
just popped a couple of leather you see
in her frame I think they're like a very
bottom the very bottom the frame looks
like you're you're forcing her to be or
not I'm not
people just listening Chuy's just
sitting on audience lap she is she's
like a chill I did my intros we have
another sponsor for today luckily are
you gonna do that claps oh no okay well
it is Skillshare ooh
I've heard of work basically this
episode is brought to you by Skillshare
which is an online learning community
for creators with more than 25,000
classes in design business and well they
listed a lot of stuff but there's
actually like they
give me I'm not gonna read all of them
like I just read at all I'm supposed to
but I went on it and I think it's better
to just give personal experiences I saw
like all these they have a ton of random
stuff like how do I become a Instagram
actually that's what you do you could
become a teacher on there I don't become
an Instagram inter father I know how to
make your business out of Instagram on
your Instagram your business you kind of
did and what if you take some classes on
Skillshare then maybe I can learn how to
make it a real business there you go
see Skillshare weird we didn't eat we're
not paying her to do that she just said
that
anyway I if you if you join Skillshare
use the link I really hope that oh here
it is go sir calm slash ego if you use
that link you will get two months free
courtesy of Skillshare in US and it will
make us look good
so do it didn't you see oh sure alright
that's all that was so short no I was
wanted to say though when I was on there
I saw the we brought this up when I was
talking to junior yeah they have thick
weird classes like one of them I saw was
how to lucid dream and I was just like
that's something I would be interested
in not so much the Instagram thing I
mean I I know that I'm dreaming and
you're Lucy I can't get out of it no and
then I can't make things happen the way
I want to I'm sure you know I know like
I know it's a dream
I know when I'm in the dream I know
because I always have these dreams that
my teeth are falling out and like I know
that it's a dream cuz something terrible
is happening that I'm like this just
wouldn't happen in real life you can't
change it and I can't change it huh it's
taraf dude I had a weird but I know that
I'm in the dream this is not even this
dream was very like big to me but it
seems so lame basically we were at
Ryan's house all chillin hanging out and
then they're like Paco we got a gift for
you and I was like what and he gives me
a like a small box and I open it and
it's a business card
what does it have your name on it yes it
says CEO like I can finally buy props
and
uh-oh y'all business card we're both
thinking the same thing I was thinking
like a like a card that says like oh
yeah
Paco rhpc a credit card well that's kind
of based on like reality that's like
real life because i everybody never
makes sense
usually mine don't but this one was like
they trust me sorry
maybe maybe in a couple years I don't
want to get back into the dream thing
yeah married we've been talking about
that I feel like we always end up there
even with like David we started talking
about it you guys are weird like that no
I just think dreams are so interesting
anyway what have you been up to people
want to know people have been asking for
you to be on this since the announcement
well they've been asking for Arden Jay
oh I'm sorry I didn't know her
yeah who is she she's like Harry J
they've been asking for you and why
don't we get a like quick introductory
to like for some people maybe I don't
know who you are yeah
so just to start I mean Arden Arden Cho
is a actor slash I guess a lot of things
actor slash singer slash CEO you CEO yes
you should talk about that actually took
over a company go ahead Oh talk about
that I searched so four years ago I
co-founded a company called Leonard in
Church yes we make watches and make dog
collars and it's like a lifestyle brand
that is bringing affordable quality
pieces to you why watches though so I
collected watches since I was in high
school I think everyone should wear
watch and low key judge people and they
don't wear watches because I feel like
they don't value time and that they
don't respect people it's more of a
fashion what's the first thing on but
but that's a thing I feel like let's say
you're in a meeting or let's say we're
in this podcast or you're in class I
think it's really rude to pull out your
phone and check the time true but I
think it's fine to like yeah but if
you're to buy your watch okay nobody
checks their time like this I do
I am wearing it now to support guys go
to Leonard Church is calm it is better
and support she needs people to buy
watches because they do company that she
just over it's not a new company she
just took over as CEO though right so we
we've been going for about four years
and then a couple years into it I mean
it's your it's a typical small start-up
company we were bootstrapping a very
very small team of friends and after a
couple years everyone just sort of got
tired and we kind of it was kind of a
side project yeah everybody was a side
thing it was hard to really like nobody
was full-time and then about I think it
around like 2017 2018 it was pretty much
out of standstill and so around 2018
when basically my partner's were like
hey I think we are all kind of you know
it was fun to try but we're kind of over
it I felt like you know we didn't really
get to do what I wanted to do with a
company I always wanted to make all the
watches that I loved and hopefully other
leather goods as well and so it was a
good start but I felt like there were a
lot of things I didn't get to try yet
and so yeah at the end of last year we
slowly trying to just we slowly
transitioned and I took over the company
yeah top of the year so yeah it's new
and we're going through a lot of changes
I have a new team now but it's very
small very small well just like it but
the watches are actually mad dope like
whenever I go on dates I make sure to
wear it yeah pocket and then the girls
like dang like - you're a pretty
disgusting person but that watch you're
not going to know they do not say that
yeah you're right they're like you know
what these watches are like they look
expensive but that's the thing I like
about that I mean that your whole motto
was trying to get stuff that's not read
it because watches are like so expensive
some of them but that's a thing the
reason when I started making watches was
because since I collected watches since
I was younger you know eventually as I
got older all my dream watches were
getting so so expensive I mean they're
more expensive than cars and houses it's
insane and she still bought them I mean
no not a collector I mean not all of
them that Teen Wolf money huh no she was
on Teen Wolf for people definitely not
enough money
no but damn shame it's other hard worked
money no but I think for me I started
realizing that as I was learning about
the watch business it was just so
inflated the pricing and I realized
you're really paying for the name and I
wanted to make great quality timepieces
that I could sort of interchange and mix
with the nicer pieces I have because you
know it's like if you have a luxury car
wants to say like a Ferrari or a Porsche
you don't always drive that everyday
that might be your weekend car so I
wanted to make a watch that essentially
could mix in with higher-end watches but
never feel like I was going lower in
quality if that makes sense
like our automatic watch I feel like our
manufacturer advised us to sell it
around like fifteen hundred two thousand
dollars and we solved for like right
under $400 so I just wanted to make it
really affordable and that's a watch
that will last you a lifetime it's
automatic you don't need a new battery
and so yeah good I'm really proud of it
so okay that's good yeah
but I want out only hears about the we
talked about you mentioned Teen Wolf a
little bit that kind the watches are
dope and everything but you know I know
people care about team oh yeah a lot of
people want to know about that and do
you kind of like consider that like your
start like that really opened up acting
for you well I I feel like if I look
back at the last 10 years of my career
there's definitely like two moments I
mean one actually is when I met you guys
and we work together good stuff yeah I
think that was a huge yeah for ass that
was a huge turning point because I
learned a lot about sort of that online
world which started music and YouTube
for me and that really kept me afloat
for almost like 6-7 years in LA and if
it wasn't for Ryan and Wang fu
encouraging me to pursue YouTube
platform I don't know if Tim Wolfe would
have happened because I think at the
time when I auditioned for Teen Wolf I
was in a place where I was actually
ready to quit acting I was gonna go on
tour
I just finished recording my album and I
was ready to sort of do shows and have
fun and not do that audition grind so I
went into that audition like I don't
even care talk about that audition
because I yeah you did but talk about
that audition Gregor's a lot of people
don't know and realize I mean you you
tell me all the time when you know
you're
I mean you're nice enough where a lot of
people reach out like random people and
I even I'm like why are you gonna go
meet this random person well if they're
sketch and usually it's like some you
know younger girl who looked up to you
because she watched Teen Wolf where she
watches Chicago man whatever it is and
they hit you up and they want to be an
actress or an actor and you go and meet
with them which is very nice of you I
still think it can be sketch well you
always think he always thinks the worst
he's always like well I and this person
is going to kill you and I'm like it's
like a 23 year old girl might be
actually I have met a crazy girl and she
did the same thing she emailed me like
every month for about a year and then I
met her and she turned out to be psycho
like actually that's what I yeah so that
that has happened it is the nice side of
you that does that and I think people a
lot of times you were telling me that
they a lot of people just kind of assume
you know if you work hard at this thing
it's gonna happen but that's not
necessarily the case so why don't you
talk about that whole actor life yeah I
would say acting wow it really is a
grind I don't think there ever is a
point in your career unless you're sort
of in that top one percentile where it's
not really a grind we're at that point
you're sort of getting offers and you're
really choosing when you say 1% are you
talking like a listers yeah your top top
a listers I mean I still see stars at
auditions and I'm like like who time
like I was like oh you're totally gonna
get it I'm like it's cool though
I would book you to like you're way
funnier sure you're not saying that no
no I would oh no no I'm like thinking it
oh that was a producer and I'm
auditioning like I'd probably that girl
but also to its I'm being realistic but
she's been in a bunch of movies I'm
there's a few people that I'm like yeah
I booked her tell us one no I don't why
no I think it's gonna offend them is it
private auditions are not private are
they sometimes because I think some
people you might be embarrassed if
people knew that the auditions are
certain things I just want to respect
people you never know but yeah basically
back to the audition grind I mean
I think a lot of people think that you
just care about a project you audition
and then you book it but it's definitely
not like that I think there's just a
long process where there are auditions
there's callbacks there is producer
sessions director sessions there's
there's so many sessions until you're in
the mix and then when you're in the mix
for TV they'll then choose a few for
like chemistry tests or screen testing
and then go from there and Teen Wolf was
a really tough process actually I
auditioned for it I think at least three
times before the chem read that I had
with tyler posey and then even after
that I think the network or the producer
somebody wasn't quite sold I think it
might have been like an age thing or the
fact that I wasn't Japanese either way
we ended up having to but you are
Japanese so yeah they actually had me
come all the way to set they had the set
team do my hair and makeup they were
amazing they like put me basically on
set and we ended up shooting our
audition scene with like the actual crew
is amazing like they went above and
beyond to really fight to get me that
opportunity so I'm really thankful for
that and I would definitely say an
epochal asked earlier but I would say
Teen Wolf was at least in my acting
career probably the biggest moment that
sort of set the tone for I guess the
start of my career and what I felt like
I don't know I don't wanna say like it
defines me but I definitely think it's
something that I'll always look back and
say oh I'm really thankful for that
experience and I'm so happy to have been
cure you Kimura especially because 11 12
years ago when I moved out to LA I never
imagined that I'd actually be on not
only a TV show but a hit TV show and to
be a series regular and a cool janna
cool character brightly action-based
like superpower character right and the
thing that's really fun about that is
she actually I don't think was intended
to have a lot of action and stuff but I
think the writers and the creators of
the show they're really good about
incorporating what the actual actor
knows how to do so I remember by like
season four they'd be like hey what
weapons do you know and because I knew
how to use nunchucks they like random
threw that in there and I started season
4 play with nunchucks and so that was a
lot of fun so I feel like Kira sort of
evolved to be like a version of me you
know and a version of her and so I shall
always be like special to me Kira Kira
Kira goes unless you'll come you Kimura
you know you kumuda yeah I can't even
say about speaking about that I know
you're Japanese what did you take no so
you know what man you're stealing this I
was gonna make a video about it okay
it's all good no no but you know what
we're gonna announce it on on off the
pill podcast right now because you know
it's some super top secret information
is it I think you know help you actually
cuz you can more roles now I guess
freshly appropriating something you know
like for that I don't think so right no
I mean I just don't really care I will
say though it's disappointing that as
Asian American actors we are limited to
only play your own ethnicity when
American actors or British actors or
Australian actors really play anything
that can pass as white so I think that's
really unfair I don't think I should
play a role that's let's say Filipino or
Indian cuz obviously I don't think I can
physically pass for that but speaking of
the DNA test I took three and there was
one that was like junk it actually just
said you were a hundred percent Asian
and I was like great I knew that and
then there was one that said I was 60%
Japanese and 30% Chinese Vietnamese like
I think like 10% and like Mongolian
makes random stuff no Korean and then
there was another test that said I was
like 40 percent Korean and then a bunch
of other stuff and Japanese - Japanese
yeah but was the consistent right so the
consistence thing was that I was mostly
Japanese and Chinese so I was like wait
that's so weird so I'm not Korean and
then I asked my mom she was like hmm I
was like what I thought she was gonna be
like woah we're Cory on but she was just
like you know in Asia everybody is just
you know where you live you're Korean
culturally you are Korean you speak
Korean you're I mean you know more
Korean people who would speak fluent
Korean say that you're Koreans like
perfect we can get the homework hotel no
that's the next I can hear it it was
awkward cuz they came out of nowhere
oh but Ryan's big screen no I don't yeah
he does come on xiety okay did I speak
Korean - yeah what do you know beyond a
pope in 30 that means I mean Herbert oh
yeah you probably get that a lot I get
that a lot
no but really though you were saying I
mean in actor life and this is a true
thing you've been turned down roles
because you weren't a certain type oh
yeah
I mean any of you weren't Chinese or
technically if you were to show the DNA
results you could be like I have
Japanese I have cuz your character on
Teen Wolf was Japanese right Korean well
just happen that's the thing she was
supposed to be full Japanese she's
curico muda but because I got casted for
the show they actually made her half
Korean half Japanese which was awesome
but I don't think it was necessary but
it did bring a really cool storyline
talking about Japanese heritage and why
we took my mother's last name versus our
fathers and we had some really great
episodes about that and so I think it
turned out better but I don't think it
was necessary because I think if she was
full Japanese I think I could have still
passed is that right so yeah I think
about when people because there's a huge
community especially Asian community who
get really upset - oh yeah I think
that's part of the reason why people
want to cast exactly what it's said to
be but I mean what do you think about
that I mean there's so many people who
are you know it's hard it's like a it's
it's hard to balance that it's like you
don't want people to appropriate like
you don't want it to be whitewashed but
at the same time where do you draw the
line
you know I think you draw the line when
creatively you will sort of harm the
project for example like there is a part
that I've you know politely turned down
because the role was mandarin-speaking
and they were only going to give me like
two to three months of dialect coaching
and I didn't think that was enough for
me to be able to truly pass
and I knew about three actresses that I
thought were amazing and perfect for the
part and friends and so I just pass it
along and it was great for them but I
think for me I knew that as an actor I
couldn't do that well and so I think I
think for me and I hope other actors it
really just comes down to can you tell
the story well can you tell it without
sort of disturbing yes the same idea
right right right
the authenticity of where that whole
project is coming yeah so I mean I think
if it's a character where yeah I mean
even if it's someone who even though I
speak Korean if the film is about
someone who like comes from Korea to
speak English I don't think that I would
probably be the best for the part he's
going to be other actors that are great
for it but I think if it's a girl from
Hong Kong and she's supposed to be
ethnically Chinese but she's in America
or even if she grew up in Hong Kong but
she went to like International School I
think I could play that because I speak
English and I've been to Hong Kong and
and now when you went to casting you
should bring in your DNA results and be
like look I am actually I think most
people like I mean because our parents
you know a lot especially first gen not
that mines are but a lot of parents of
friends that I know are very proud
obviously they go 8 Asians are just I
mean they fight amongst each other yeah
that's the main problem I think
underlying issue is there's a lot of
racism within the Asian culture there's
so much racism even from Koreans to
Korean Americans and people in China to
Chinese Americans and then not to
mention you know Korea and Japan and you
know etc etc there's so much racism that
is within the Asian cultures that causes
all this animosity so the issue really
isn't casting because I think right now
and what I always tell people is we just
need more stories you don't I mean and I
think for example I just give and a good
friend of mine she is not Korean but she
plays the lead in soul-searching which
is about Koreans going to Korea to find
out about their identity but their
adopted Koreans and she absolutely kills
the film yeah and it makes me so happy
I've seen it like seven times and I'm so
proud of her
as someone who is ethnically Korean I'm
really really happy that she portrayed
that character so well and I don't think
anyone else could have done it as well
as she did and to me if that movie helps
her build her career then she will one
day be at a place where she can then
talk about who she really is
and she speaks Mandarin she does a lot
of things and now we understand more
about Asians you know I'm saying whereas
I think if we don't if we block those
opportunities and if Asians are the ones
complaining about Miss casting then
casting directors are just gonna cast
white and I've heard this a lot like
they'll be like oh it's an anime we need
Japanese and they're like oh we can't
find Japanese actors and you're Korean
and you're Chinese they're like we just
don't want to upset people so we're
gonna upset people anyways we'll just
cast white and so I'm always like so
frustrated when I hear that and so
that's why one of the reasons why like I
love sharing sort of casting information
with a lot of my actor friends is that I
hope it stays ethnic because we have a
smaller pool to choose from yeah I think
that's why when other s like I think
that's why when Caucasians are like oh
well that role was supposed to be white
and it went to a black actor or went to
an Asian actor and they get upset about
it I'm like are you serious right now
we have less opportunities to choose
from to begin with yeah you know I mean
they're seeing it they're seeing it from
a like principle standard there's you
know because there's such a heavy push
behind anything there's always gonna be
a counter action I mean I agree
obviously they've dominated the realm
but I can see what they're trying to say
like based on principles like well
technically you know if that person in
the story is Asian and you cast white
you guys would be upset so why are you
allowing this white person in this story
being cast as something else so I could
I could see what they're trying to say
but I also see what you're trying to say
I think you're never gonna I think
there's gonna be a lot that disagree
with you yeah I've already seen it and I
just like I just sit back just like this
is theirs
to me I think I mean it's it's very
important to your specific job yeah and
so I wanted you to speak about it
because you deal with that all the time
oh of course and and of course there's
always a part of me that's going to try
to be considerate of what people will
feel and you know how it might be
perceived but I always tell people you
have to think about it this way
wouldn't you want a show like
fresh-off-the-boat to exist and to be
great as it is or them to have just not
done it because they couldn't find the
father
cuz Randall Park is great he's so great
but he's not Chinese nice Korean but I
think he's great and so I don't think
that should be an issue you're saying
also shouldn't be because most of those
people know most asian ethnicities are
not a hundred percent anything right
right and so that's why I'm saying I
think the people who are upset are the
ones that are extremely prideful and I'm
sorry to say this racist yeah it's it's
well it's people would take a lot I
think this is where it comes from it's
parents would take so much pride in
their culture which is a great thing but
I mean if you're really breaking it down
I think that's about what it is based on
it's like this is a culturally Korean
thing but like like just like you you're
culturally Korean but technically you
might not be full Korean right
technically unless we find out later
down the road all these DNA tests or all
scans I kind of felt like there's a
possibility I have heard that there's
just not enough data for Asian people
which is why the tests all came out so
different right so I'm I was recommended
to do it again in a couple years once
the data pool has increased the data
pool yeah all right well going on to
back to acting and stuff I guess a lot
something that a lot of people were very
curious about is like what pushed you
into this direction and did you get
support from your friends and family
because that's something that you know
look at that little smirk on your face I
know you got something to say no I mean
it's just I don't know sometimes now
that I'm older I think it's funny when I
look back and think how did I end up
here and how did I start this you know
it seems pretty crazy but yeah I mean
growing up I loved telling stories I
love making people laugh I think I would
always sort of act out the date of my
parents and since I was like three or
four they said I was always singing
around the house I knew I
to be a performer but then when I was in
high school in college I was too shy to
sort of join the drama club and I didn't
think I'd be good enough so I never
really auditioned it was really scared
to audition even also wanted to be with
no Asians right in the Midwest and so I
grew up really confused about my
identity but um I think in college after
graduating I felt like and that's a
really long story but there was someone
who really encouraged me even issues yep
she's ours putting her dog down like put
layers it's really I'm wearing an off
the pill
Oh a shout out shirt and drinking water
in an off the podcast monk Thanks
so until their due upon third bunch get
off the pill no he's not okay sorry so
back to acting yeah it's a really long
story but I was encouraged to pursue
what brought me joy and try to do
something good and radical with it and I
wanted to yeah hopefully make it a
friends not just as a female but as
animation American I grew up really
confused about my identity I thought I
was I think I thought I was white I was
like 20 I know it sounds really weird
but I mean you're I don't know if you
want to talk about it but you told me
that story about your kindergarten
teacher or something oh yeah I have
experienced so much racism my entire
life yeah I think when I was in
kindergarten I had a teacher sort of
split the class up in groups she was
like okay everybody with blue eyes on
this corner everybody with hazel eyes
here and everybody with brown eyes over
here and I was like oh I have brown eye
so I went over in the brown eyes group
and she was like what are you doing I
was like um going in the brown A's game
she's like no your eyes are black you're
all by yourself and I was like
what I'm like fives I'm like crying
inside but also just like to shock to
actually cry but that was sort of like
the beginning of where I was like oh I
am the only one that yeah different but
then I think growing up I really wanted
to fit in and I was born Amarillo
grew up in Dallas so mostly he lived in
Plano but a lot of I might be tripping
but I thought there was a lot of Asians
in Dallas now used in there are like 10
years after me oh okay is that what yeah
we each me up think about this at least
the teacher recognized you did have eyes
she could have said you have no eyes
that's because I'm an Asian with big
eyes they're all natural yeah whatever
don't be hating Paco just I'm stating
I'm saying she could have that's true
that's true I could have gotten even
worse you could have said ching chong
ding dong yeah oh dude you just went
racist again yeah I've gotten some of
those kinds of comments even with my
name they always try to make Arden Cho
somehow Asian Adriene known Chau and I'm
like what where did you get all those
extra letters that was their insults no
it would be actual teachers try to read
my name oh and they would always say
ciao ciao and even this morning I was on
the phone with the bank and they were
like Chu and I'm like it's ch Oh Cho
there's no you but they kept saying miss
Chu miss Chu clothes though grew up not
seeing Asian Americans on TV or media I
felt like I just didn't belong in this
world and I felt like an alien and I
think there are two ways you can go with
life can either sit back and complain
about it or you can get involved and do
something and so I was like I'm gonna
take a leap of faith and try to get
involved and do something and I moved to
LA it's like no money and two suitcases
and didn't know anybody found a roommate
on Craigslist who was crazy and then and
I cried every day for five years yep and
then I filmed a YouTube video yep and
then I started making YouTube videos and
then it works jobs and Here I am today
and now you're on Chicago med oh yeah
wow that was a really good timing on the
applause Paco I'm a comedian all right
it's all about timing baby but yeah I'm
on Chicago med it's crazy somehow I
think I've now done about like 15
episodes and I'm really really thankful
it's a great gig
well that's all we couldn't get you on
earlier because we're in Chicago filming
those that were asking hey and I leave
at 4 a.m. because I actually work
tomorrow in Chicago and it's a four-hour
flight so I gotta leave
well this comes out the following it's
not coming out today well I know but
just saying yeah I'm you'll be in
Chicago for a little bit in the morning
to go film but I'm here for you guys and
you of course and we will be right back
because we need to take a shishi break
wait already but I don't even need to
sushi it's not all about you Arden
Oh why do you have to cheat you know but
maybe the viewers do oh oh okay but then
they could probably just bring their
phones can't they just like sheshe while
they're watching mmm that would be our
British you otherwise don't they know
what do they know what she means some of
them inside everybody it's time for the
shoe break have a good time and we'll
see you back in five yeah no say five
seconds I think yes
oh wait now I have tissues you see so
hello everybody we're back from the
shoes are you hey
hey you get your own podcast Wow
Paco feeling a little aggressive this
morning yes I've only said three
sentences in the first half my anxiety
about am I being loved by strangers it's
flaring up right now yes okay then I'll
let you bring us back you can do that
and we're back what do you mean I did it
okay all right you want to hear you want
to read the Skillshare thing dude eyes
okay probably actually would be good I
don't know if they want my voice do this
have a probably say let's have a
competition you know but then we're
gonna read three times dude that means
let me do this
you could read it three times and I'm
basically doing it for free yeah you are
baby will you read me at least dinner I
read it I have this I just went to cost
going got some actually I should say
guys should I tell them I better super
romantic date last week or this place
let me or I got a read this guy a story
what's take stories I can tell but
before we get that this episode once
again is brought to you by
Skillshare thank you and there's over
25,000 classes I don't think I need to
say this I know they want me to but I'm
just gonna be more straight up and be
like honestly if you guys want to learn
some cool stuff go to Skillshare if you
use our link Skillshare comm / Higa you
get an extra two months free and i'm
talking like you might be wondering oh
why don't I just go to youtube and look
up these random I mean you can learn los
up on YouTube but they basically these
things are very like professionally done
I'm sure they uh I bet you said they
have a very right I think they I think
that you can become a teacher I think
anyone can but I think they screen it
because all the ones that I've seen are
super professional so I'm pretty sure
it's like it's almost like going to like
a higher quality version of like
tutorials mm-hmm so sorry and you get
the first two months free so it's like
yes if you link real shared calm when
you sign a scouser commsta she go so
they know that oh they heard this on the
podcast so I know phone is on the side
at least for two months free I have the
podcast episode 9 is up just kidding
sorry I just got a tweet notification is
separate that's not me oh that's who
runs the off the pill podcast that is a
secret yeah don't need to know who it is
maybe it is me I'm sure I know it's Paco
it's actually multiple view box oh okay
fine guys I lied it's me
but it's new but we're not gonna do that
you know sometimes I'm on it
it's me no and we're back a the second
part listen let's get a spicy yeah
what's Michael
I feel like that just makes me want to
eat a burrito with some extra height huh
I don't know why angry we just ate we
did I didn't eat anyways let's get into
it
alright I just want to know first
impressions of each other
and then second impressions of each
other after reconnecting through
Facebook okay
first impressions were Facebook yeah the
first time when I ate you up she has a
better memory so last time we talked
about we talked when we first met that
you you said I talked about this how we
have different and I said I was gonna
let you talk tell your side how we think
we met at different times I think we met
well I I know I think I know that we did
not meet do you know add a casting thing
because Wong foo was casting for agents
of secret stuff yeah we did Emily
together I auditioned and we read
together I don't and I was like I do not
recall I think my first impression of
you was just like oh he's just like this
guy and I don't know what the hell think
I'm sorry but I'm there for like an
audition and so yeah I don't think I was
thinking much of it I just want to do my
part well and I just thought didn't go
home and cry again i know ii swore that
I saw your audition via tape and not in
person that's why I think our stories
vary I think we should ask one of the
guys I was there like I know it must
have been Kristen was there and I think
Phil was there so we'll talk to one of
those guys yeah films I mean first
impression of Ryan was he's just some
guy yeah that's what she just said
that's what you so bad I mean no I mean
I just was like oh but you know what I
can't even remember so yeah he doesn't
even remember me so obviously he
obviously I was not memorable and Wow oh
wow this is a real actor cuz I haven't
even worked with actors and I wasn't an
actor I was just like oh man I better
like really I was intimidated not just
by her but like all the other actors I
feel like you were scared of me a little
I was scared of the whole situation
because even like getting a sound
and I wasn't used to that stuff I was
just like oh I better actually learn my
lines Paco knows how and I'm new in
videos I'll have stuff to that right but
I'll just go off-script he'll go like
line after line and he'll mess it up so
much and I'll go like sometimes it'll
change the story yeah let's do this now
yeah and then it messes everything up so
uh yeah all right I was more worried
about that I think at the time all right
and then uh so you guys are dating and
then there's a steak story which steak
are you talking about the first time
around the first time oh I think that's
funny I mean we'd even say that we've
dated the first time around that's
always like well we kind of dated yeah
no I mean it wasn't even like it was
just like we were getting to know each
other but I was only considered dating
yeah and I think we wanted different
things and honestly we didn't really
know what we wanted I mean I knew what I
wanted back then back then I wanted to
get married and have like 500 kids and
like it was just five really five it's
point you had your team you had your not
that I knew but you had a very strict
plan for your future and you send
reminders you had reminders for it I
don't know if you want to bring that up
or not yeah no I was a little weird um I
basically thought that I'd be married
with kids by the time I was 23 and I met
Ryan when I was I think about weight 94
yeah about that age and so I think at
that point I was really feeling rushed
where I was just like whoever I date
next like we're gonna get married and so
unless we're gonna get married I don't
want to waste my time and so I think I
was a little bit kind of mean to you
because I kind of was like don't waste
my time cuz you young I wasn't mean then
again I wasn't mean back you were gonna
meet at the end though I was because I
was a little annoyed I was just like not
you I wasn't I was very like oh you were
not used to girls saying no to you
you're not used to their know-how
Shannon no I wasn't used to girls
pretending like they they liked you a
lot and then the next day they don't and
then they like you again okay in his can
you can my defense yes it's
not that I was pretending to like you
and we've talked about this it was that
there was a part of me that didn't like
you you made me laugh and you were so
fun and I thought you were really
intelligent and charming and awesome but
then there was this other part of me
that was like no you have to think with
your head scheduled he's too young he's
not ready for anything serious like
don't waste your time you're only
getting older time is ticking tick tick
tick you know so I think there was just
I was really torn and so that was why I
definitely wasn't gonna give I was nine
twenty maybe at the time and like I so
liked it the weird thing that was like a
lot of awkward things were like we'd go
not like we were dating but we'd go on
like dates
I guess that's dating yeah like because
I'm underage and like to her she would
make me feel like like I mean I was like
I would feel embarrassed cuz we do like
some of her friends and they would all
be like a little older I mean not like
24 25 they're older than you that's why
yeah a lot of my friends are older and
so then we were in situations where they
were much older than you yeah like like
seven eight years and then I'm just like
oh I can't get wine I'm sorry and I
think at that time like I was really not
okay with that either so that bothered
me a lot
I would bother me too though it's a
little different when the guys older I
think oh no that's sexist
no no but I think it's true right like
it's a little it's not as as weird for
the girl I guess but even then if you
were a 25 year old guy or 20 40 or
whatever and you were doing somebody who
was 20 and you went to a restaurant with
all your friends who are like 28 29 and
you guys all got wine and this person
gets carded and you can't even be there
that would be a pretty awkward for you
yeah wouldn't it yeah I mean if that was
a girl mhm
yeah but I think as girls it just feels
less weird I think it just maybe it's
sexist but I think I just really had one
she with you being younger I was young
yeah but obviously all right and I
caught her and now yeah right grandpa
was so old and boring like I think I'm
Way more fun but I'm also old and boring
so now we're both old
Sassie baby okay well roast you so hard
does fun things I do a lot of fun things
yeah I'm trying to do more fun things
you already do I don't know why you're
suddenly mean I want to do more fun
things well because I didn't live my 20
is very fun I think I was so ready to
like grow up and be an adult but I
didn't get to have a lot of fun so now
in my 30s I'm trying to enjoy life more
and have fun like I made Ryan to a
staycation yesterday yep
and he's really happy about it obviously
no I mean it's not but it was great we
had a nice dinner we went to get
massages made a couples massage it was
really romantic yeah we I just always
thought that such a weird concept
staycation where you get a hotel in the
same city that you live in yeah and the
part of me I mean I got used to because
she likes doing that but apart me and
first was just like it doesn't make
sense we have a regular bed like a
cleaner one probably I don't need I
think about those kind of things when
I'm walking around hotel when you do
barefoot I'm like man I know there's
probably spit and like all kind of who
knows what's on that floor there's no
way they cleaned it very well in between
the hour that we had they definitely big
they don't they don't clean the remotes
that stuff bothers me they don't know
any [ __ ] in the curtains but it looks
okay to make it i yeah i don't know i
just love hotels and i love room service
and so like making a mess and not
cleaning yeah I mean I think it's
because okay a little bit is that I
don't have to clean it because I'm the
type that once it's messy like I need to
clean it right away that's why I like
even when I'm hosting people I feel like
I'm always cleaning the whole time yeah
because I want to stay clean but then
when I'm in a hotel I feel like it's
okay because it's not my house but I
don't really make it I get it I mean I
get the whole staycation thing for all
you couples out there if you can't get
away for a long time well I don't know
and I think you like it I don't know if
everybody would like that well I think
it's about making time to spend time
together I mean for those of you guys
who don't know we've been long-distance
for a really long time and Ryan works
365 days out of the year he worked on
his birthday he works on holidays he
walks every single day this is work
bears work so he works
and so if I'm like let's take a trip and
let's go on a vacation I've done it
really hard for him to take more than
you know a couple days off and so
staycations are better because then he
only loses one workday or he can like
today part of the staycation and then we
work in the afternoon and so yeah but I
also admire that about Ryan so I know
this is not a full roasting session Ryan
is very hardworking and that's one of
the things that makes me like him so ya
know because all of a sudden I felt
really shy let's talk about Paco now
part of what Arden does for you is
whenever you get into like a
relationship of some sort let's not talk
about don't listen he drops everything
for a girl because when he is so in love
but I'm telling you people that's the
way to do it see yep you need balance
let me defend myself no this is now
roasting Paco time yep but I mean talk
about it because I think that's very
relatable for a lot of people especially
people who I mean people don't date as
much I feel like right dating is like
happening less and less like I guess
exclusive Rio date yeah real yeah not
like tinder hookups yeah well I think
the generation has just changed a lot
and it's really weird because there's
just too many options and everybody is
sort of always like one foot in one foot
out or like always kind of look in that
way in though does everybody I want to
go mow they have fun right you don't
want to commit and it's sort of like you
go on a couple days but it's just like
dinner or whatever and then you're like
oh but let me see if I can meet somebody
better yeah but I think that's why I
like we work because we're both like old
school and we're just kind of like you
can take out school you're both old
things but also like we're too lazy to
like meet new people like we never did
I've never had tinder coffee meets bagel
any of those I don't even know which way
to swipe and I don't think you've ever
had that either mm-hmm oh I missed that
you phase of no tinder weed that was a
combination
yeah yeah we missed it and honestly
there's like a small part of me that's
like oh they could kind of be fun but
also it's very overwhelming and scary to
think that you're just out there and
people can like just sway wait yeah you
yes or no and it's just so like I know
feels really unauthentic I'm sorry I'm
sorry no but I mean I have a lot of
friends who found their soul mates on
those sites and so I think it's great if
you match with the right type of person
but back to Paco Paco just he just has a
big heart and I know you guys all think
he's like nasty and that he's just cool
you guys audience they just probably
think Paco is a mess but he's actually
actually pretty sweet he's really sweet
and he anything he goes above and beyond
and maybe a little too much so I always
tell people like if you like someone or
if you love someone your instinct it's
like sort of give everything and do
everything but I always tell people like
Paco you just kind of like reel it back
a little bit oh no definitely like you
give too much too early no okay then
it's like okay bye let me defend myself
then so about a year ago it was real bad
oh yeah I know yeah like I would ask
heart in like all types of stuff and
everything and I would be like going out
to LA all the time like for this girl
and everything and I would just give way
too much and Arden was like like why are
you doing that you don't even know what
this person likes you or anything like
make them want to work for you type of
thing and it totally made sense and as
of recent like I I'm focusing on myself
a lot more and when you start working on
yourself and this is all things that I'm
kind of like learning from you you know
so just to show you that I listen and I
do know I'm so when you work on yourself
you make yourself the prize you make
yourself important and other people will
see that and value that in you and
they're like oh I do want to like you
know get to know this person like you
know how are they so focused and passion
is something that a lot of people
respect and admire and find attractive
and you know I got a lot of passion good
I like that you do listen sometimes see
and that's why I'm a lot better
now I'm proud of you Paco and that is
the basic relationship that you guys
have had
Paco coming to you you telling him the
same thing him not listening and then a
year later now you've kind of listened
yeah I'm a lot better now okay and for
those of you guys out there yeah I feel
like if you are you know wanting to date
and get into a relationship I always say
the best advice is love yourself know
what you want and who you are and if you
respect yourself somebody else will as
well yeah but you also really have to
love yourself I know it sounds silly a
lot of people are searching for love
what does that mean love yourself I
think it just means you have to be at
least semi happy with who you are like
if you don't even like who you are how
can you expect someone else to like you
let alone love you so I think a lot of
people jump into relationships to feel
like they are loved and to fill this
void but then what happens is you then
put so much pressure on the other person
to love you to this extent that isn't
really capable for them to do on their
own but I think when two people are you
know adults and they kind of know who
they are and they're balanced and they
have this healthy view on themselves and
life and they come together and they can
hopefully have a balanced relationship
that makes sense yep what I've heard is
like it's complimentary exactly instead
of having somebody complete you where
they're filling voids right you already
you're like very secure and who you are
and somebody makes your life better
exactly but without them you're okay
with them it's better so I want to know
how you guys kind of compliment each
other you know like you guys are you
guys are similar but different and so
similar it was so different yeah no but
you're similar in the fact that you're
both boring
we are both boring I don't think I am I
think I'm super interesting you're them
are you serious you are the most
predictable person I ever met get a hold
of Ryan I know he's either pooping or
playing video games sleeping or playing
basketball it makes sense that's a lot
of things like you just named that's a
lot of things anyway I don't think I'm
that boring but yeah we're very
different she does a lot of things she
has a tiny group of friend she has a
huge group of friends that I she has so
many friends that I have
such a hard time I mean I don't want to
sound racist but a lot of them are Asian
and and very like hard for me to
remember like three different Jenn
friends well that's that I think in your
defense
I understand I actually do have like
seven friends named Jen so that's a
little hard and two of them are Jenn
married to Ben so that's really
confusing too well they're both Yujin
right so Jenn in and they're both
married to guys named Ben yeah so I get
them mixed up a bit and they get
offended yeah Jim and then gentry but
you know it's fine I know so funny I
didn't know that her last name was Jay
yeah all right well thanks yeah so you
hey you've even answer the question what
do you like about her what do you like
about her what do I like that was a
question no he looks so upset about that
question took what do I like there's so
many things he's like how dare you make
me pick one know what didn't know what
it was the that was the original
question
yeah Paco is asking how we complement
each other how we make things work and
what you like I think you get me to do a
lot of things that I don't want to
initially initially but then it but then
it helps I think it helps because you're
right I mean I think if you weren't
around I wouldn't do a lot of these
things that inspire me essentially even
if even if it's not a good thing like
something I don't want to do it'll still
inspire me to create something yeah you
know I think that there's a there's a
lot of that and learning to be more
openly compassionate I think I think
blacc naturally I always go logic I
think you myself but I feel like yeah
and she's a feeling so we're so
obviously so I've learned to be more but
that's like a kind of normal
relationship that isn't normally no it's
not the girly feely I know you're saying
but we're not like feely
but then that's a thing like we're
different in the sense of like I'm not
like the type of girlfriend that's like
we have to like talk every single day
move to be together all the time I feel
like always hold hands and be like we're
not like that we're fine on our own
we're fine like with Ryan here working
and me back home working or whatever we
you know we balance that out but
definitely yeah Ryan
is much more logical well love languages
that that helped us understanding how
many is there by five love languages I
love languages are very different yes
Brian is just time and touch and then
mine is probably gifts and acts of
service and words of affirmation so
we're literally the opposite yeah yeah
so I think a first couple years was
tough especially with the distance
because we were always a little bit like
missing each other like do we like each
other do we not and so I think once we
kind of figured that out and realized
okay we're just - people right right I
think Ryan is your happy even if we just
spend time together if we're not doing
anything yep
but I'm the type that's like we do
things and you have to like see I think
that's common in a lot of relationships
I think a lot of couples can relate to
but what helped us is talking about what
we're talking about right now right I
think that will help any relationship to
know that because I didn't know that
people I was just like white I don't
understand how you don't understand me
it was a lot of that before whereas I
think what I learned from her is like
people are just different like very
different and it helps and it's
interesting too because the thing that
you guys probably don't know about Ryan
is he has all these plans and he has all
these ideas but he's not the type to
sort of say it and he never says
anything unless he's actually going to
do it so if I was like let's say maybe
year two in I'd be like hey let's go do
this
and he'd be like I don't know or I don't
know if I can and in my mind I'm like
dude just say like maybe you'll try or
maybe we will butt in but later on I
realized it's because he didn't want to
say it and not do it because in his mind
that's worse whereas I think for me I
would be like no I just want to know
that you're making the effort if that
makes sense
yeah but yeah I mean and then to answer
Paco's question with Ryan I like that
he's so logical and he sort of like
helps me during your break together yeah
yeah I think for me like I take on a lot
of things I'm doing a lot of things all
the time but in like the most simplest
way he's really good about being like
hey it's okay you have all these things
you have to do today and then you got
five new things to do but everything's
gonna be okay
let's take it one at a time and so he's
really good about like helping me sort
of do that and like we play clash
together and a lot of times I start
freaking out and I'm like oh my gosh
we're gonna lose we're gonna lose and it
just I start putting cards down and then
you'll be like normal people who don't
know it's a game you can play with two
people he'll be like no we're okay we
still got this and then you like calm
down and then we win and it's awesome
yeah it's just I think another big one
it's a perfect example I think you being
like this
hey I think it'll help other people it's
helping me but at the same time that's
what I'm thinking that's why I think
about you all the time was okay no it's
even no anyway I think another good one
is like something that I think I never
understood how people couldn't get over
is if something bad would happen to you
that day how you would linger on
something and I always thought like what
there's nothing you can do about that it
happened like how can you improve it and
versus like a lot of times she'll bring
me something like something bad will
happen to her she'll tell me all about
it and instead of comforting her which
my natural thing is I'm gonna solve the
problem how do I stop this from
happening in the future
that doesn't work guys and girls out
there who are illogical that's mostly
guys though mostly but it's mostly guys
were factors so don't I had to learn the
hard way like they just want a lot a lot
of people just want compassion and not a
solution
yeah even though I think the thing is
and that's actually something that I do
appreciate about you too is that he
helps me get out of that like lingering
faster but I think you have to first
approach it with compassion and then fix
it like for example let's say like I
trip a lot when I walk up the stairs but
sometimes like I would fall really hard
and they might be bleeding and then Ryan
would be like why did you do that okay
there is definitely times and you're
like why would you do well you know I'd
be like what were you running because
I'm sorry thing like maybe you should
stop running
yes so like for the longest time I was
like he's so mean but then later I
realize
in his mind he's logically trying to fix
me so that I no longer stop tripping
because he's like why do you always trip
he trips so much I mean I know it's not
it's because my mind is faster than my
climate like my life you know others and
I'm thinking of other things and my legs
just can't keep up I'm just like boy I'm
a lot realized sorry and a lot who's
what I'm trying not to laugh he always
laughs see that's why he cares about you
yeah no no it's fine because I
understand where it comes from but also
I mean I'm just this is like the most
like basic example where now though he's
really good about being like oh are you
okay and then let's not do that anymore
I don't say okay me but he doesn't say
like that but he you know this well
that's a very specific example that's
just one example and I'm obviously this
happens in like a lot of other things
where like let's say something bad
happens at work and I'm my days ruined
but then he'll you know let me sort of
vent through it and he'll be there but
then very short after he'll point out
things that are still positives and
instead of me spending the rest of the
day lingering on that and being upset
I'll kind of be over it because he'll
have helped me logically realize that
hey there's really nothing I can do to
control that moment in situation so
let's not be sad forever so in a way it
kind of helps that you guys have
different perspectives because you
really need to each other and you can
see it in another way and because if not
I would have never like if that happens
to other people I would just give the
logic like the solution versus like
compassion like yeah you wouldn't have
compassion robot I just think it's weird
it's like you're missing this like
compassionate DNA I'm super feely dude
but you know Ryan's really sweet he's
really sweet he's really sweet and
what's crazy is that they're so sweet
and he has such a big heart which is one
of the things I love about him but he
would never really let you know and
he'll never take credit for it and does
a lot of things for people you don't
know
yeah yeah so he's a type that would
really
ever want anyone to know yeah definitely
not one of those like youtubers that
would go and like film the nice deed
done that before but we've also done
that though I'm telling it now we've
done I mean just growing up it was just
like for fun yeah like it's not because
I care okay alright so I guess are
really not so sweet considering
everything it's so it's selfish I'm
doing it cuz it makes me feel good
whether people know or not it's like you
know I have extra bucks I'm gonna go to
Walmart get a blankie or whatever and
nothing to do in Hilo so we drive around
and give homeless people blankets and
stuff it's not because I'm like hey
let's film this it's because I'm bored
yeah and it's something to do and it's
not a bad thing in my mind and I feel
good about it
so it's selfish yeah but it's different
the unselfish byproduct a lot of things
that we do that are everything for me
like you know you mentioned earlier that
I love you know meeting young people and
helping people I love connecting people
but it's because I want to help people
but at the same time it makes me feel
good right yeah people need to
understand that everything we do is
first I have nothing it's it's fine
yes anything wrong with that yeah like I
give Paco romance advice because I want
to one day when he gets married be like
hey yeah cuz of me I know and I'll do my
girl or whatever or boy or boy whatever
happens girl I support it all yeah yeah
I love you either way mm-hmm but I want
to go into something a little bit deeper
now
Brian is so exposed right now he's never
been this honestly not that deep maybe
not that he just more I want to know
because you guys do have a long-distance
relationship and we talked a little bit
of about dating online and stuff and a
lot of times online dating is a lot of
long-distance at times so what made you
know it worked for you guys like where
did you guys compromise it you
compromise out clearly you did but you
know talk about it like what where in
your mind what did you have to give up
in order to make this work I did
I guess I'll start I had to change
I live by habit and I follow the same
thing I normally do so you're boring and
it's mean to some people but people who
live like me understand this is what
works and this is what I'm gonna stick
to so I have to disrupt my schedule and
to me that's a big thing it might not be
a big deal to other people but if you've
done a thing a certain way for a long
time and it works for you to change that
is is see it sounds bad but it's a big
deal to me it was a bishop like you're
laughing it's true that's I mean I was
dying because I just remember like year
one there is this time when like I was
like we never do anything and you were
like we went to the grocery store
yesterday and he was really proud of
that yeah we left the house I would have
normally just order things to come to me
right Ryan didn't leave his house for
like eight months guys before we start
that is not true yeah I do things you do
more things now I do more things now
what people hit me out like hey do you
think Ryan would do this I'm like dude
if you can get him out of the house
that's amazing are you talking [ __ ] to
people you know what though I've gotten
pretty good at getting him out of the
house yeah well me because he cares
about you he L words you I came out for
your birthday party he did I surprised
me for my birthday no oh sorry no
because you say go cuz I care about you
but I went to his birthday party oh and
you left the house for Jenna's birthday
party you surprised her in LA - that was
a long time ago
mmm I just like being home yeah he does
he likes being home but yeah I would say
compromise is probably the biggest thing
and I think it works for us because
we're both really busy with what we're
doing and because would she have
something going on I think long-distance
relationship is really hard when one
person is always waiting if that makes
sense yeah if there's less that that
person because it's hard to if you're
just waiting around it's hard to like
like oh why aren't you texting me like
every morning because you know if you're
working you probably don't have the
energy sometimes or you don't have the
time and I think it's also understanding
like there's definitely times when we'll
talk a lot more
maybe we'll FaceTime more maybe we'll
you know hop on the phone a lot more but
then there'll be weeks where we won't
talk much at all either because his work
schedule is crazy or because mine is
crazy but we have a mutual understanding
knowing that that's okay and I think
that's something I really appreciate
about Ryan because you know maybe five
six years ago there was someone I was
dating that when I'd be done filming and
I might have a 17-hour day on set
18-hour day on set where I literally am
leaving set washing my face and hitting
the bed so fast that don't even have
time to text goodnight and it sounds
kind of selfish but just really tired
and sometimes you don't want to talk but
then that person would get really
irritated and upset not understand and
not understand filming schedule or long
hours but Ryan gets that and so I think
you know whenever something is busy like
that I don't have to worry that oh no
he's gonna be upset like because he's
not he gets it you know and if we make
plans and it changes he's like alright
that's cool I get it and I'm for sure
filming in general I think it's it's
really tough for the other person who's
not in that industry if you're not in
the entertainment industry to date
somebody that is I think is it takes a
long time to get used to it I mean just
the fact that like in me I had to even
get used to you just kissing another guy
on a show even though it's acting you
know oh my hey you kissed somebody else
too
no I'm not saying I'm just yeah but I'm
just saying you have to get used to it
you have to understand like if you're
very open about it like that's there's
there's other obstacles that most
couples don't have to go through right
right and that is a big one and I'm sure
like it's not we're not the only ones
that I mean if you had it's true you
know but I will say for those of you
guys out there if you run into that
situation I think kissing on camera is
really the most unintuitive ever felt
intimacy kissing on camera which is
really kind of sad to say when people
are like wow you guys have so much
chemistry I'm always like well thank God
we're good actors I literally I think
I've always felt nothing and so and I
think it's because you have 150 people
staring at you you've got cameras in
your face you got what people think
right and then it's always funny when
you see the most romantic shots and it's
beautiful those are the ones that are
the most awkward because it's everything
slow and they're like move your hand
higher or lower turn your cheek turn
your face this way that way and it's so
awkward but then you know with sound and
editing in lights they make it look good
and so one of the least romantic things
and we I mean you know more than anyone
it's kissing in the rain oh yeah we've
done a small version of that Oh a lot in
Teen Wolf yeah because people think it's
so romantic is in the notebook oh yeah I
would assume it is we had this scene
where just so you guys know when you
film with rain it's not like normal rain
it's like pouring pouring water because
for it to catch on camera Oh Maureen you
can't see you can't see it so if you
guys ever see like raining outside you
just try to film it you really can't see
anything so then to replicate rain for
fit for camera and for film they just
just go crazy and I remember when we
would do these things running through
rain by the time we even get to each
other we just can't see and then we're
kissing and then holding it for however
long till they call cut I remember after
every take we would just release and
both be spitting water on the ground and
it was just like it was a gross but it
looks romantic and awesome yeah that's
for was that Teen Wolf
yeah Teen Wolf we did that we kissed in
the rain a lot I feel like yeah there's
a lot of rain rain that show is very
much like it's more of a romance than
it's like yeah I would say it's like a
lot of romance a lot of action it's
really fun it's very dark but yeah
there's definitely a lot of romance and
they make it look good we had some
really great a great crew the great DP
made it look really nice that was um I
sent the video I said it wasn't my
favorite show
oh really they're like oh Ryan just
didn't like it because it like me
kissing another guy well but we weren't
even dating like that no no that wasn't
the research oh that's not no I think
the show you're on now is great yeah
it's like well it's well-written not
that Teen Wolf wasn't guys okay but I
just I think it's not meant for me
I think that's meant for more
I mean I don't know if it is but I
thought it was meant for more for girls
or guys constantly have these beautiful
body shots and body shots yeah we have a
lot of guy fans too and a lot of
middle-aged women there's a lot of moms
really the only people that like run
after me like at the Grove in LA are
like forties fifties women really yeah
well that is uh I did not know that was
I thought it was like 13 to 17 year old
female girls yeah I think they more
excited for the boys yeah they're
they're more excited for like dylan
o'brien Tyler and like Cody you know
those guys yeah well I didn't realize
how long we're going but we should go
into some questions actually some of
those questions were so the biggest
similarity was from CM see my Janice on
Twitter yeah the question about long
distance relationships from Andrew Tran
on reddit which one's did we do a little
bit compromise know what do you think is
the number one advice and what would you
say to make it work long-distance
relationships it's hard to say because
ours is such a weird thing you know so
different from other people but I think
that's something important that every
relationship needs to understand is that
your relationship Wow a relationship is
unique in its own way and you need to be
able to compromise and not be selfish
something that works for you won't
necessarily work for me or are you yes
became a weekly yeah I mean yeah I know
it makes sense yeah but also well not
soft was super soft guys don't listen to
him I don't know what that was like
people I just gotta keep my brand oh
that's all you know is that your brand I
don't know why is your brand like that
what made you think that that was his
defense mechanism mm-hmm I feel like
that's what allows he's so emotional it
doesn't matter who very emotional it's
are they're more Twitter questions
Twitter questions there were more but I
mean we don't have to state we don't
have to do it I just I think we need
still hear what's good what you got I
guess you know uh Vanessa Mendes asks
Arden what are some actors you would
like to work with mm oh you know I want
to work with these days Gemma Chan
super big fan she's crazy yeah like to
work with her she's covered a lot lately
tough she's been doing like what it why
her specific just cuz she's pretty not
just cuz she's pretty someone clip that
and send it to her so that Arden and her
can collab in some way oh my gosh no I
just think I don't know I just really
like her yeah she's just a very
sophisticated nice elegance to her even
in her style of acting I think it's
really right really really great I mean
because I really like like Natalie
Portman I like Nicole Kidman I like your
like classic beauties mm-hmm and I think
it's really exciting to feel like now
there's an Asian American woman that I'm
like yes that's like that mm-hmm
okay yeah another Twitter question from
yellow Paco so do you but really are you
serious did you guys kiss yet we're
waiting till marriage
yeah we're not inappropriate so you guys
have kissed other people but not each
other yeah but it's just acting can you
guys at right now and kiss each other oh
that's so awesome
hmm I mean it's so if you're reading out
yourself then I guess that's it huh yeah
that's not it okay you should tell
people how really bad you are with
trends oh yeah you're like oh my gosh
I'll be like wow babe have you seen this
and he's like um that was a trend like
two and a half years ago hey why do you
always when you do my voice like um well
I text I see it like that no I don't I
don't put enough emojis that's oh that's
a good tip for those of you who are
dating especially you guys out there an
emoji will go a long way yeah a little
smiley face would turn okay - okay just
add the colon and parentheses and it
changes everything
are you mad no exclamation point happy
face everything it's like are you mad
and it just no they are it's because
before that if
or that if you are you mad will happen
if you don't put the emoji we have the
emojis shows everything's fine I don't
know if that's just us but I think a lot
if you date a guy that you think is
always mad don't ask him if he's mad
because he's probably never mad I
learned that too later the hard way I'm
not always appearing mad is that you're
more see when you're smiling and you're
happy it's great but it's a lousy social
you're so serious like too bad yeah good
luck good luck editing this yeah for a
part - you guys would like to see art
and show on this podcast again she's
always taking over I don't know but
she's pretty good at it so we will soon
be having an LA version of this podcast
and I'd like to nominate myself to be a
host for the LA podcast should be a
moderator please leave it in the comment
section below subscribe replacing them I
would like to replace Paco your buddy
it's okay she'll probably in Chicago
doing bigger things
oh stop it I only have two more episodes
good yes can you say that you only have
two more well I mean I see no no I mean
I could maybe come back for Season five
writers if you guys tweet to Chicago man
that you love me that is true you
actually do have to I mean those things
matter
Oh shows will keep you on if they know
that the audience likes you Wow and that
was on I think I think that was one of
the reasons why your left Teen Wolf -
well I mean you stayed on oh yeah cuz
they wanted you out earlier right yeah I
think she was only supposed to be on for
a few episodes we are sorry you're gonna
cuz initially you weren't so it was a
guess like my parents like a couple
episodes and then they extended it and
then kept you went on to the next season
Chicago med that's really lucky with
Kyra - it was only supposed to be your
write a couple episodes but what they
kept her going and I think it's cuz the
fans yeah they really like this all
right well good lays the end we are
wrapping it up
yeah first you put down her dog and then
it's putting yourself down
yeah what you don't do oh my gosh stop
it
and I
sorry I didn't mean to roast you so much
I wasn't really roast to know what's in
i'm just can we I'm not Park on a
sensitive oh my gosh are we gonna fight
let's not fight here you guys say the l
word to each other anyway I'll live
juice thank you so much for tuning it to
the off the pill pot yes waiting to plug
oh yeah I am oh come on dude I'm just
worried cuz sometimes you just end this
thank you so much for turning off the
pot gas I'm not gonna say I was gonna
say remember to check out her letter in
church watches she just became CEO small
businesses support EE all oh I thought
you messed up at first but Yoshi yes and
again thank you just go share we don't
have to do another plug but just shout
out to them and do you have anything
that you want to wow that was chewy yeah
Chuy's like coffee or something but yeah
um I guess follow Chewie Jo that was a
good plug know the good Segway it's
funny cuz she she was living here I know
watch Parker's twitch gross yes follow
me um I might post YouTube videos again
I'm not sure when but I feel like I keep
thinking about it yeah it was a good
series though the one were you eating
with different people I thought yeah I
liked that the one where you did with
the rhyme yeah that was fun that was fun
and then I just got busy and actually
started filming Chicago med and I was
going back and forth so much I got hard
she's doing real things no I love
YouTube it's just for those who don't
know YouTube is a lot of work you have
to wear every hat and so I think YouTube
is so tough but it's definitely
something that I always want to do and
so yeah hopefully I'll be back and then
definitely thank you I appreciate it if
you support Leonard in church please
follow us and if you have graduation
gifts or birthday gifts or whatever I
think it's a great present there you go
that's the plug yeah so while we end
this thing we always end up waiting
where do they follow
you're right I forgot Oh
you're right you're ready follow us off
the pill on Twitter and off the pill
podcast on Instagram and read it and I
don't know what the read it is ready
calm slash are slash nigahiga there Wow
follow us there and we'll see you guys
next time and three two one just breathe
into the light that's a winner Wow
you don't even watch the podcast it's
very long I shout out to all the people
who are still here because if you stay
past when you know we're gonna end the
podcast you're a real one type will give
them a secret code so that we know if
you guys stayed or not and the only
explain what the code is just if you're
still here type in purple elephants
alright I'm coming for you that's the
fun I mean it's not the funniest thing
we can come up well offense or purple
elephants are good no no I was thinking
about purple I don't know either
alright type in purple elephants and we
know you're real bye