hey you guys don't know I'm in college
now and Shawn he's still in Hawaii but I
found someone who looks exactly like him
meet the new sean fujiyoshi co-op pause
myth rookie [ __ ] Feeny cook up so Wong
Chairman Mao kung pao chicken for Chi
Minh Trail way ding dong ding dang dong
- yeah sorry about that he has a disease
known as destroyed uranium mistake Euler
by acetone systolic [ __ ] but on the
bright side it's time for the trailer
when a down-on-his-luck movie producer
needed a miracle we don't see something
from you in 30 days you're gone he
turned to the Internet have three
million views other video matches one
video every video I want them in my next
products and found Ryan and Sean what
we're going to Hollywood Hollywood yeah
yeah
now Ryan and Jones set out on an
adventure of a lifetime
hood I never hurt a bit yeah it didn't
hurt at all
coming this November
we