I tried to make him cry too you know his
parents abusive so when I was like I
don't remember this but when I was a kid
apparently I stabbed him with a weed
digger did you punch girls in the
stomach no but you know what I did hit a
boy all right
clap claps you never get it right whoo
oh I don't know how you trying to go
laughs are you trying to go at the same
time no I never try to go at the same
time Oh cuz then when I edit it I never
asked you I just always wondered why you
thought you guys try to go together and
you guys never make it this is a rare
case word like one of our guests
actually watch all right welcome back to
another episode of auth appeal podcast
today is a special Mother's Day edition
that's why we have Paco it's not that
funny Fargo and we have my mother as
well yeah so today is a special actually
is it gonna be on Mother's Day it is yes
Mother's Day Sunday see we did this
specifically we did a release scheduled
for Sunday's so that it would line up
with this oh yeah for this very episode
yeah and fathers days and Easter's
they're not our Father
father season on Sundays Father's Day
Sunday as well is it I'm not sure yeah I
thought I don't know uh I hate holidays
that always like land on a day of the
week no I mean well I actually like
qualities that stay the same like I
don't like holidays that aren't on the
same day you know Halloween's always on
yeah Thanksgiving is always on Thursday
yeah and you know Easter Sunday like I
like when it's like always on the same
day yeah then I don't know yeah it does
confuse things yeah I don't know why I
went into that no idea what a great
start to the pollak know I didn't come
prepare today because normally I like if
there's a guest in mind I'm like okay
I'm gonna start
thinking about what to ask like what
kind of questions do I have but um this
is different for me this was your idea
it was it was good I thought that this
would be a pretty fun episode for
Mother's Day not a lot of people
actually ever get to see auntie Lucy on
camera she's on the camera a bit no ugly
every time I feel her she's all like
what do you say IDs what do I say I say
Paco you know that this is not gonna be
in the video yeah
and you a lot of you cut it out though
right I'd be like I told you but I I
guess this would be cool to like you
know kind of see the person that you
know created and gave a lot of guidance
to Ryan you know so creator yeah well
first of all happy Mother's Day to all
the other mothers I since today it's not
technically Mother's Day for us today
but it will be for people watching this
so happy Mother's Day
but sorry quit no no that's cool I do
just want to wish her you know I'm not
selfish
happy Mother's Day thank you Paco yeah
[Laughter]
but uh yeah how about how about we just
go into a little bit of it you know
introduce yourself you know you're
Ryan's mom but what else do you do for
the company cuz a lot of people actually
the superfans kind of know a little bit
but there's a lot of stuff that you do
behind the scenes that you don't you
know ever show on camera oh it's really
Cullen boring but I didn't want to know
still so it's not your choice if it's
boring or not we want to know the boring
stuff I just like to think of myself as
I'm just helping behind the scenes I
don't like to be in front of the camera
so I'll just be like behind the scenes
whatever you guys yes and trust me I
tried many times you know I mean like
heavy used to use his dad Kevin B's uses
his dad all the time and that every
video that he did with him worked really
well and then you know and your parents
kind of the opposite no they don't they
would not she would not well actually my
dad is worse he refuses to be you know
to trick him to be into some stuff but
she does she really doesn't like it
either
why is that what's your issue I don't I
don't like the way I look on camera you
know I don't like pictures and then I
don't think I sound good you know I
don't think like how about nice for you
I don't like the way I sound
most people are like that yeah except
for Paco
he's like so actually I didn't like the
way I sounded either when I was first
like editing my own videos I was like
this sound what I learned is that the
reason why we're not used to hearing how
we actually sound is because in our
heads our skulls act as like tuning
devices though yep
so John's different yeah we sound
different yep so that's why when we hear
something how we actually sound like
whoa I know it's not how I imagined yeah
exactly
so yes I don't like that and then I
don't like to act so like I don't mind
this cuz I feel like you're just talking
I'm just talking yeah or like that rap
video like I thought it was just playing
a game or sometimes yeah so I mean it
was okay I was just being a good sport
yeah you're a great sport it was making
my mom rap like Eminem yeah for those at
and that video was so funny when the
vacuum cleaner turns into the guy
Larry's but uh how about let's let's go
and I think this is kind of gonna be
almost like a long Twitter type of
question yeah I mean there was a lot of
good questions yeah there and I just you
know we're gonna find out a little bit
more about Ryan's childhood really yes
yeah and your parenting tactics Wow
and you know we got to go kind of edgy
at first though did you spank him as a
kid
I must have because Charlie talking only
goes so far but I wasn't like a wooden
spoon or I mean was I even like a ruler
I think you did use a wooden spoon no
you were more of a like pull your ear
like hey yeah and so my erection you do
that because you can't see there's no
like
you know like if you hide you might get
a bruise just pinched it here just a
little redness it'll go away he's
abusive now in today's day and age
that's considered child abuse know who
is worse though you are uncle Wendell I
think it was equal except that I think
his level like you know he's a little
bit more tolerant maybe like I'll go
from like here to there I'd be like talk
talk and then okay and then it's like
that's it zero two hundred is black and
white for you yeah yeah and then also
what I guess in Ryan like growing up
because you guys are kind of similar in
the aspect that you both have ADHD right
yeah and so you saw yourself a lot of
yourself in him actually though I think
only when he got diagnosed then it was
like oh wow that's how I was you know
like when people talk after like really
focus otherwise I'm not listening and so
it's bad when he and I go to a meeting
because I know he's not listening
listening I just don't know how much I
retain right I'm like I have to be like
like really he might not be listening
you know but it's just interesting I'll
remember it but I think it's it's it's
good to know that you are because when
you recognize it then you know what you
need to how you have to adjust herself
yeah like him I hate to read hmm I mean
I just I just can't read through a whole
book mm-hm yeah you're not much of a
reader Ryan's not much of a listener as
soon as Ryan has his phone out I know I
should just stop talking because he's
not paying attention what yeah so going
into that going into a meeting together
I think a lot of people don't know this
not so behind the scenes cuz you didn't
really go specifically into what you do
but you are like an acting manager for
him right yeah but I don't like to say
am i I'm isn't manage I don't like you
saying what's your job because I don't
manage him I mean I I do things that
make his job easier or gives him time to
do what he needs to do which is like
create right yeah so I do all of the
other things all you know
business side of it and then like when
you guys come I know he's not gonna cook
so I'll cook threefold yeah make the
snacks clean up you know he doesn't have
time for that so aunty is kind of like a
manager caterer accountant what hust
actually an accountant retired now right
and when you retired were you still uh I
guess was Ryan
when did you start kind of like helping
him out on the business aspect so I
think um it was good because we kind of
grew together right like we both knew
nothing of YouTube and so we kind of
like learn together so I think it it was
kind of helpful for the relationship
because it wasn't like I knew more than
him he didn't know more than me and so
we kind of just help each other along
the way so it was it was pretty good and
a lot of mistakes were made but learning
experience exactly
and with that you know because a lot a
lot of especially Asian parents would
not allow their child to go in something
in like a creative aspect but because
you guys were growing together do you
think that helped or what helped you be
more understanding and leaning of
letting your son go into this when your
other better son Kyle is a an x-ray
technician right right and he like
completed he graduated and you know he
is about to get married and he has a
career I mean he caused I don't know
Kyle I think caused a better child well
first of all you're not supposed to
compare Paco
when you become a parent you should not
appear your children that's funny no I
got better grades than him in school
yeah but he was the better dude over
he was Tamagotchi an underachiever yep
he could have been like like so much so
much better at you know he could have
like even even two so he got his extra
Tech and then he's debating or sure to
get his nuke man and I'm like oh you
should get your new command you know
because I mean what's two more years
and he's like nuclear medicine degrees
right for those that don't know what
nuke med is basically it's an extra two
years of schooling right yeah so you
know he'd be the type like and I just
say it was 5050 because he's a type two
like I'm satisfied yeah you know but in
fact that's what Ryan was gonna go into
first and then yes so when he dropped
out I guess what was making you so like
understanding and accepting of that cuz
your first kid was like went through the
usual you know school career all that
stuff
oh no you still you still want I still
want it we still wanted him to go to
school you know it's not like we said
like oh yeah go for it you know but I
think it's a parent's well the way we
think is that you want your kid to do
something that they enjoy right and so
you force your kid to do something and
what if they hate it but you but you
also as a parent want to tell them the
downside of what it is you know so I
remember I told him well you know if you
do this and it ends and you go back to
college or your friends are all
graduated they'd be working and he's
like yeah it's like okay well you know
you know you just give them the downside
cuz that's all you can do as long as you
make them aware and it's a part of your
job is to just give them guidance you
know but really you just want them to do
what they want to do and then support
them how about for you Ryan like at what
point were you like no I think this can
really be a thing for me like did you
have to do a lot of persuading for her
or was it more just like I'm gonna show
no I mean I I it took me cuz I doubt I'm
like very conservative with like I don't
take a lot of risk you know and I knew
the safe path was to just go and get my
degree like Kyle and I was gonna get
into nuclear medicine I just thought it
was so boring and like I just didn't
like it but it wasn't a lot of her like
it was more me coming to that point I
wasn't like I wouldn't I'm not the kind
of person to take that risk without
something to fall back on you know and I
think I think in his situation he was so
like frustrated and he was so stressed
because he was still doing YouTube
and then trying to study and then they
were like brands coming to us and you
know like calling and you know people
like calling contacting him and so it
was really stressful so I kind of like
he had to do one or the other you know
you had to make a choice yeah and at
what point I guess were you completely
okay with all right you know I he is
financially stable you know that I'll
have to worry or you don't want do you
want him to go back to college still no
no I mean like in the beginning it was
actually there was no earnings in the
beginning yeah yeah cuz that was like
2009 before Adsense right kind of well
there was ad since but it was hardly any
advertising I'd even know about it like
the partnership program was like not
things people knew about like only
certain youtubers got access to that in
the beginning I would say like 99% of
people did not know about it like did
not know that you could even make money
off of you off of you know posting
YouTube videos so at the time it was a
bigger risk but you could still like
still there were some ads and stuff
coming in like in terms of like product
placement and stuff so it was a it was a
risk but it's not quite like hey you
know let's go and just do this thing and
there's no money in it like follow your
dreams kind of think there was some
money in it but we didn't know yeah it
was gonna get so big you know I mean it
got big like maybe after 2010 yeah and
so in the beginning they were it's
really no money but you could just see
how stress he was so it was kind of like
he couldn't go like do both he had to
make a choice plus I was here like in
the dorms at UNLV where like you have no
privacy and make for one that's already
stressful like to even make videos was
like not common people like I mean it
was embarrassing you know and to be like
oh you're with living with someone so
you I have to literally wait until he's
gone to make my videos for one and then
we have suite mates so it's like two
rooms and there's two people in each
room and you guys share a bathroom
that's between the two rooms and yeah
essentially
like there's like no time where there
was like silence and so I would have to
go you know off campus and I was to film
some stuff if it was in my room then I'd
have to wait you know you're not just
working on your own schedule plus their
school you know so it was a very uh not
an ideal situation for either for both
it was like either one is gonna suffer
so it was to me it was an easier
decision um and then when I brought
brought it up to them I was like
surprised because I thought there was
gonna be more pushback it wasn't like
the stories that you hear from a lot of
other like a so-called Asian parents I
think a lot of parents would feel the
same but it wasn't it wasn't like
dramatic but I also think because we
come from Hawaii it's a little bit
different from us because we do have
Asian parents but I guess the whole way
culture you guys are more like lenient
and understanding of different things
you know you're not necessarily you're
talking like first-generation Asian pear
yeah yeah it's like this is the model
you follow yeah she's like she has I
mean you can just other than a Hawaiian
like pidgin accent she doesn't have an
accent and she's like what do you third
generation third because you're your
grandfather I can write to Hawaii so
even my grandparents don't have accents
right well pidgin well they were born in
Hawaii yeah yeah and I guess because so
you were born in Hawaii right big on
right and uh and you have kind of a
bigger family right when you were
growing up what parallels do you see
similar to Ryan growing up so you know
we could get to know a little bit more
about you get to know a little bit more
about Ryan because we touched on it a
little bit you said that you as well
have ADHD right mm-hmm so like when you
were growing up and you saw Ryan growing
up like what did you see similarities a
lot of for you did you punch girls in
the stomach no but you know what I did
hit a boy I was older I wasn't like
kindergarten what my dad tells me I
don't quite remember but you know that's
what he told me is the boy's father came
to our house like I think he was Asian
also
understand okay no because the culture
yeah I mean it's not like I was doing it
because I hated him or anything I think
I think he either like he must have
harassed me or something I don't know
what it was it had to be like around I'd
say second grade but I remember that
where did you punch him no I did I don't
even know like how I hit him but I
vaguely remember or yet a dad came to
our house I mean I know who the boy is
and he still is in Hilo that's a small
town no I didn't know sheep I see they
can't this back when I was a kid a kid
ago you know parents can't tell they're
bad so there's so much stuff no no the
thing is there's so many stars right
like like you have so many stories we
have so many stories but it doesn't just
come out yes someone has to dig it out
right you know there has to be like a
situation that and the time that the
teacher called the house that Ryan punch
the role in the stomach we are bright
with everyone it's like Uncle window
yeah I've got the car dad yeah but maybe
if I got the call maybe I would I had a
flashback
[Laughter]
but I know that the boy he either like
chased me or he did something to me and
I'd four brothers so it's kinda like I
was tomboy then oh yeah I was I was in
fact my dad was kind of worried that I
would be like totally like tomboy mmm
yeah I'm four brothers you know yeah you
have a really big family at people have
less like families have shrunk our main
other than like Mormon families I guess
but like in general like oh yeah it was
common to have like five brothers right
and we're like a bunch of siblings yeah
because back then that's all they had
you know there was no entertainment will
you do when you're bored you know I
don't know if that's what it is I think
like they came from big families so it
was okay you know what I mean but now
when you have when you have children
it's kind of like you think that economy
yes and what a college costs and you
know so just different like I mean even
like our generation most of us like we
worked to pay for college you know but
now we pay for parents pay for college
but that's because also you could work
and pay for college and not be in like
huge amounts of debt how could you guys
[Music]
but you know a lot of times like we yeah
I think we did spoil our kids you know
our generation but it's because we
didn't have have it easy so you know we
want to do whatever it can give them
whatever we can because we didn't get it
yeah I know but speaking on that uh I
just reminded me when you're talking
about I guess who was the more
disciplinary one yeah I think it was her
because I do remember like and I only
know this this story because I don't
remember it specifically but I do know
that though anytime I can really think
of that my dad really yelled a really
disciplined was that time when I
supposedly I guess he yelled at me and
said they told me that I don't really
remember too much by I punched the girl
right for cutting me in line so I push
her in the stomach she dropped a lot of
power behind this you know I was in
kindergarten and then I guess I got sent
to the principal's office they called
home when I went home my dad was the one
to you know normally she would be the
one yelling or spanking or whatever it
is but apparently he was the one who had
to deal with me and I don't really
remember I have no real unless I blocked
it out I have no real memories of him
really you know disciplining me but
supposedly he gave me a big I don't know
what he did yelling he's gonna make me
cry why didn't you cry but you wouldn't
cry yeah yeah yes prior I thought I was
right but you're never you're not really
a crier cuz my I tried to make him cry
too
you know his parents you should try to
make your kids because you kind of want
to get a reaction right you know either
like yell back and and Kyle and Ryan I
used to hate it because when I used to
lecture them they'd never contest like
they'd always be like okay I'll be like
you know okay and I'd be like you know
you kind of worth it but that's that's
the
you know how male and female yeah
females we like to like keep going
because you want to see that they're
engaged in the conversation not only
that but I guess you want to get the
last word and they say okay shuts you
down
it does it does so you kind of want him
yeah I remember the time that you didn't
remember like he told my dad used to
take pick him after school my dad used
to pick him up and then take him to
basketball
doesn't the taste you know he hated
basketball and judo and so he would give
my father like all these excuses have a
stomachache headache whatever and then I
find out later that oh he didn't go
because or he had stomachache
it's just like fueling so we went home
and I told him you know if you think
that you're like smart enough like you
can make your own decisions then I'm
gonna pack your bags and you go to
grandpa's and you make all your
decisions and you're thinking oh he's
gonna cry just like it's just like sits
there he doesn't cry you know so I pack
up this little bag and I and I leave it
and I'm waiting for him to like tell me
something you know or come back with
something he doesn't go back into his
room so what you understand you know
he's like okay and so then I tell him
because I have to get the last word
right cuz he said okay
something okay why I'm leaving this bag
right here so it's a reminder you're not
old enough to make your own decision if
you're supposed to go basketball you're
going to basketball well I don't
remember that one but make sense sounds
like me I guess uh I guess we're talking
about a lot about the bad things but how
about you know each other dad I think I
was justified she cut me in line he was
challenging but that in a way was that
something that you saw positive in your
son oh for sure like where were some
other traits about him that you
recognize like oh no there's like a lot
of good things about it did you ever
recognize oh he he's gonna do great
things or did
noticed like oh he's a good kid did you
ever think he would have the influence
that he has you know on a lot of
people's lives oh no definitely I mean
we didn't even see this whole YouTube
thing yeah I mean that was like total
shock because and I think the first time
we realized it is you and Shawn made
rivo mm-hmm there was this like
nonprofit organization in Hilo and they
know I guess it's part of like a bigger
organization but they were called Revo
and there was a myspace contest that if
they got so many I don't know what it
was like sore throats or something and
then they could win like $20,000 or
$10,000
yeah and so um he did a video he and
Shawn did a video and they Juan and then
I was like and you know these are people
all over the world
voting for him for these people in Hilo
so I was like I told him why Ryan you
you actually make a difference in the
world you know and folks were like high
school
yeah right like 15 probably yeah that
was quite a surprise that he's able to
like was able to reach people and people
like you know yeah when it came to like
you actually saw that it made money for
someone and it was a good organization
like it was it promoting art and um they
had like art shows and stuff and it was
a good nonprofit I think so yeah that
was like pretty cool but at the time we
didn't think I mean we didn't think much
Shana I didn't think much of anything oh
they're asking for something I guess
yeah and it was a funny video - yeah it
was just like oh yeah I guess back then
and people just threw up whatever they
wanted yeah no but it was funny to be
honest what did you guys do with that
money
no we so people had to go on MySpace and
vote for them oh yeah and then they won
yeah so that was like impressive and
they actually made a difference you know
so that uh that's when you kind of saw
like oh yeah yeah she's not a normal kid
I just think that he had like kid look
at my beard I just think yes he has an
effect on people you know
that that was quite a surprise and then
I think the next in a couple years after
that there was a boy he's like haha like
half Japanese half Dutch and he lived in
Curacao
and he actually asked his parents to
bring him to Hilo so he could meet Ryan
so he was bullied in school because you
know I guess like there's hardly any
Asians and so he was instructed she was
too far from the mic just so people are
wondering so he he watched Ryan's videos
yeah he seems to be like really like I
don't know how bad he felt but he was
bullied right he was pretty amazed like
this how old was he he must've been like
a little like nine year old or something
as this young kid and he looked very
depressed and yeah I just remember we
had to I get no idea you were talking to
the mom I guess she contacted the paper
what she contact the newspaper Oh what
yes so in order to get to to contact you
oh she wrote into the newspaper asking
if she probably told her story about her
son and how he was bullied and he goes
no and he the only time she heard him
laugh was when he was watching his
videos and so you know she wanted to say
that they were making a trip to Hawaii
and he really wants to meet Ryan and so
the newspaper contacted us the local you
know paper yeah so he actually came to
Hilo and then we got together met him at
Starbucks I think yeah yeah so that was
kind of like wow and here he was in
Curacao you know yeah this super shy
like it almost didn't say anything yeah
just like looking down the whole time
but the real cool thing is that like I
don't know how many years later when we
first went to Japan me Sean and will was
it will and Greg yeah we had a meet and
greet and he was there and he was like
an adult
and it was just like one of the coolest
things ever is like I remember meeting
this kid and now he's like this lead
it means hot boy he's half white half
Japanese hella good looking good looking
kid tall taller than all of us and I was
just like man this guy's all confident
shaking her hand his hands bigger than
ours
was like man I remember when you were
little depressed kid good-looking dude
that was cool that was amazing you know
to have somebody travel so far just
because like helped him through like a
really hard time yeah yeah see that
depressed kids out there and sad people
gets better exactly as long as you make
was very you meet your idols that's the
only way oh it wasn't a very weird
situation though cuz it wasn't like
wasn't you some I in some islands or
something like yeah so Chris always like
I guess a small island amongst like so
many islands right I don't know I don't
know where that is
hey you look that up but he basically
was saying like even when he went to
Japan I think like he doesn't look like
yeah doesn't look like cuz he's mixed he
doesn't really look like wherever he was
and then when he was watching your
YouTube videos he was like see that's
that's like me he's like me but little
did he know he's a lot better-looking
kids man
looking really good okay well I mean we
didn't really get too much into we got
some Twitter questions in but we didn't
really get into it but a quick she she
break and we'll be right back and we're
back
[Music]
and we're back
yeah we're back
how's the song go she should break song
I don't know
wills the one whose condition I mean you
you could I mean I let's just talk about
the actual song that they just never
mind
and we're back I'll fight that's what
we're coming back and we're back I'm
gonna fight you why one day I'm gonna
get strong enough to beat you I mean
it's not I don't really think it's a
strength thing one day I'm gonna break
your legs
you could probably hey you're as big as
you are you cut a week you know there's
some people like I mean actually you
wouldn't know you never Russell but when
you look at them they're like they're
kind of like big so you would assume
they have a certain strength you're kind
of weak for they called kind of beat
your arms aren't stuff and like you're
kind of athletic I mean you're
athletically you're pretty athletic in
everything you do yeah but you're kind
of weak how come like you're good I mean
I'm not gonna diss you like you're
you're good at other things like you're
gonna you know other sports and like you
play tennis soccer basketball but you
put your weak how come I'm all about it
like my arms could fit in your arms but
I think my arms are stronger than you oh
you're way stronger that's weird
I don't know it might be a I was
wonderful Jess ask a doctor actually
talking about fighting did a - we should
get Kyle at some point I don't think
people understand the dynamic know him
you speak so Pitt or so PJ no I I think
with people he'll speak good English
it's like among English well yeah
amongst like friends yeah yeah I think
it's good subtitle
for him wait I edit that never mind and
you know what though he doesn't he
doesn't like he's like them he doesn't
like being in videos like he always like
even when I lived with him and I needed
somebody he would be like you wouldn't
want me wouldn't want to do it
most people would like jump it's a lot
of people jump at the chance oh yeah and
so I was always kind of like a challenge
like yeah wow it is embarrassed cuz I
was like man you know you mount family
likes to be in this I don't want to like
inconvenience other people and then I
found out later after I left Hawaii Oh
people actually like being in videos
like they want to be seen these weird no
I didn't at first I was just like oh
they're embarrassed like to be a part of
this but yeah I took you away from the
topic sorry yeah Kyle and I we fought a
lot a lot so so but I think you know
what it's normal I mean I just think cuz
my brothers fought you know and I keep
hearing it you know like how like when
you say like well how's your kids and
it's like do they fight it's like oh
yeah they fight like I think everybody
does you know it's part of growing up
was uh one of your bigger fights if you
were home I need over the computer
fought a lot over the computer yeah
those are you on computer yeah and also
our best our favorite activities played
computers and stuff and Kyle was bigger
you know he was older and he was a bully
poor thing no cuz he was so little
Ryan was so little so I didn't know like
how long it was going on but I remember
one day I came home from work and then
Ryan said you know Kyle he punched me or
something that eyes like ran into Kyle I
was like so mad I was like don't you
ever touch him I know he did later but
you know he probably did it again and
again but I was like don't you ever
touch him yeah we we fought physically a
lot so when I was like I don't remember
this but when I was a kid apparently I
stabbed him with a weed digger my rabbi
is or something you know I go we do I
like three years or two years old or
something like that so I it has like a
little you know you know what we figure
is right dad he's like a little scholar
and then I also heard I don't remember
this but I don't know how or what I was
but I had to go to hospital ones cuz he
was the he put your arm out of my sake
yeah ell boy or something like that yeah
dislocated my arm as a good kid swinging
I know I never liked like I wouldn't
back down to him like if he hit me or
like did something that hurt me I was
like I'm gonna return tenfold like
whatever you do if it's a pinch I'm
giving you like a punch if it's a punch
I'm gonna stab you in the eye because it
was just like it was just like you're
not gonna get the best of me yeah yeah
you're not gonna get the okay because he
was always like like she said he was
naturally good he's well as people that
you just hate because they're always
good at stuff that you have to work hard
for you know yeah like for like judo and
stuff like he got we both play second in
the state but like he did not train
there's I mean he trained we went to
practice but he didn't train like all I
trained yeah you know for like
everything I worked really hard compared
to him but he was just naturally good
and that was the most irritating thing
in the world to me people who like and
there's you know people like that I'm
sure yeah that's me yeah you were yeah
you're a good example you're someone
who's naturally good at a lot of things
which makes you lazy super I'm pretty
much Kyle
so mom kinda was the firstborn thing no
I think it's your your personality like
he was so laid back yeah but if I was
laid back I would be so bad at
everything
he was just mastering everything nobody
think like as a second child though it
makes you more competitive yeah you see
the second child is more competitive
because they see what the older child
did want to be better
you and your sister were like are like
best friends yeah but we didn't get
along a couple of times too she took a
lot of things for granted like she would
take for granted me driving her around
and stuff
and like she wouldn't like care about me
or anything I remember as a young kid
one time I don't know if I told this
story here I tell this story a lot
because it's probably my favorite one
but we were in the backseat of a car
after a soccer game and she was sleeping
and just had her mouth open and she was
like sleeping look like that and I was
eating eating an egg salad sandwich and
I saw her and I just put a big
egg egg on her tongue as she's sleeping
and then the car hit a bump at you oh my
goodness well no the best thing was when
Kyle went away to college I think then
it got better hmm
is that when you feel like you started
really connecting well that's we never I
mean we didn't become like close like oh
you guys are we just didn't fight so
naturally we started getting like we
could be in the same room before like we
couldn't really even but I think even up
until then you guys didn't really hardly
talk and then I left then it was like at
least they could like talk or play games
together
before I was like don't play with each
other don't even talk to each other I
was like yeah but now you guys are like
pretty close yeah yeah I guess I mean
yeah yeah much better
that's real convincing it's not like I
go to you know I like some siblings
they're like best friends and yeah tell
each other everything
like I don't know what he did for the
past month like I'm sure you went to
work but like I don't know I don't call
him lived in the same house he didn't
even talk to [ __ ] yeah I'd be like
where's Kyle it's like I don't know and
then I find out like Kyle is in his
bedroom like it's like just a different
floor you know like and I think more so
boys and just a personality's like
they're not stalkers you know yeah so
texts now is the best thing hmm do you
guys have a family group text no no
remember my dad he's gonna listen to
this he still says if you have an issue
just text me really he really can't text
but he knows how to make outgoing calls
now I will say that do you want to get
into some Twitter cues because there's
we actually answered a lot of the
Twitter questions will you
you use some a lot of those as your own
questions no giving them credit these
are things that I had take all these
people's questions because I study my
guests
okay this is a interesting one because I
don't even know it from Jordan the anime
dude what is Ryan's first word oh my
gosh I don't know
see I don't that's why I don't know how
come parents you know you know I bet you
remember Kyle's first World No so
usually you keep like baby albums you
know you just biome at a stationary
store or whatever and then you fill in
all these blanks like you know first
first word they walked you know this
kind of thing and I know Kyle's one is
pretty filled out the second child you
really get um I think you're so busy
with the wit like you having two kids
that the second child I know you have
less house probably more exciting cuz
you're first and you have time yeah like
your first car you take probably take a
lot of pictures of your first car your
second cars like I already had it the
first significant and I know that baby
all album is not fully complete okay
well I Janna Kim asks what's your
favorite embarrassing thing that Ryan
did as a kid favorite embarrassing
favorite embarrassing yeah you know if
it was embarrassing I don't see it was
my favorite we have a favorite story
nobody it what was embarrassing is but
we have it in your book you know where
he taught the kindergarten teacher like
he would actually like contest what she
would tell them to do you know and so
that was like so embarrassing I mean I
think I don't know how many parents go
through this but normally you have like
a 10-15 minutes is a long parent-teacher
conference mine was like almost 50
minutes and I live zero-five-zero yeah
kindergarten trouble
so much to talk about oh my gosh
oh I don't recall I wasn't in that
meeting even if I was I was a big
kitchen yeah I don't know how many
parents got to go through that
kindergarten button and was like almost
50 minutes embarrassing but I do
appreciate that teacher because she
really was patient with him like whoo
yeah oh yeah she's still alive I think
so I'm not sure but she's like listen to
the podcasts excuse me yes I am well at
least I care to ask but yeah she like
really tried to understand him and
wasn't like the kind of person that
would be like you know you go talk to
the vice-principal you know what I mean
yeah like push it off to someone else
yeah exactly like just like you know my
my my son is was like that you know
she'd be like no you know we just have
to treat him like he's an old man in a
little boy's body because we would like
contest her like if she would say
something like if it was to sit on the
floor and then somebody else is not
setting up floor he'd be like well how
come they're not sitting on the floor
you know he'd be like contester and so
um you know it almost sounds like a lot
like a lot of people look up to Ryan and
they see him as an idol but as a kid
growing up until now like super
troublemaker super ADHD not paying
attention almost like if you saw him
growing up you'd be like this kid is not
gonna make it you know they're gonna end
up selling drugs and like not having
anything no but you know so I kind of
look at it as you saw he was so strong
minded that whatever he decided to do he
was gonna like do it you know so he
decided like he was gonna do well at
wrestling he was gonna do well if he was
gonna do judo he was gonna do do it do
it well I'm not so sure about basketball
though cuz you really hated and he
really was not good well the thing is
with judo I was awful at it right my
whole like pretty much until like I
would say high school yeah high school
eighth grade cuz I hated it but I did my
whole life I should be good at it but I
was like pretty awful and then in high
school I had fun so I was like oh this
is
and then I just became good I just tried
actually try but then but and then all
the techniques came back right yeah that
knowledge kicked in and then yeah so it
was good a nice I do remember like
growing up and stuff like going because
we'd have to go to tournaments being in
a club yeah and I would like just not
even try but that's a strong magnet part
like if he was like I'm not gonna care
he didn't care but if he was like I'm
gonna do it good he's gonna do it good
you know so he could be he was like his
worst enemy to me yeah you did judo for
a little bit I did as a kid and I my par
you week I actually got second in States
Oh like you know not like high school
club clubs and then um I remember I did
not like it cuz I would have a lot of
headaches as a kid so getting thrown
around my brain would rattle in my skull
so I'd always get like headaches after
practice and I told my mom I didn't want
to do it and she was like it's not once
you get your blue belt you can quit so
then that's that's when I tried super
hard yeah well we had the same agreement
but mine was black so the agreement was
you had to do a martial art this is like
from like young time you have to do a
martial art and you have to do a team
sport so it was like okay if you don't
want to do basketball then you go to
soccer it was like no I don't want to
soccer okay then you don't want to do
basketball you do baseball no I know
into baseball okay then you gotta go
basketball you know and so then it was
like okay you don't want to go judo then
you gotta go cut a tape but you start
from wiped out oh okay no it in yeah no
so it's kind of like that was kind of
like kind of the rule dang I kind of
want to go into one thing but we should
stick to the Twitter questions well just
go we can always come back to alright
okay cuz I guess talking about that you
know in the parenting aspect and you
know it seemed like you had kind of like
a set goals that he had to accomplish
and you know he was completing these
goals and stuff
earlier you also talked about how as a
parent you know sometimes you want your
kid you want your kid to be happy doing
with what they're doing right so I think
for a lot of kids especially who watch
YouTube and you know maybe they want to
go into a creative field or they want to
go into a field that isn't necessarily
approved by their parents what
suggestions do both of you have to these
kids where they can prove like oh you
know this is how I can convince my
parents to go into this field that I
want to go into you're saying you're
talking about you're asking what do you
as a kid do you tell your parents to
convince you to let you do YouTube as a
career not no not YouTube a creative
field
so cuz you know a lot of people be like
oh I wanna do YouTube those kids are
dumb but like some people want to do you
know like maybe they want to have a plan
you have to have a plan like and then
like she said give them the warnings
like okay well you know most she would
tell me all the time because I from a
young kid age before YouTube I'll be
like oh I want to be an actor and you
know what she said she said oh she's
like she didn't say oh follow your
dreams she was like you know there's a
lot of starving actors in LA I was like
okay I'll do the singing
what you want you sang a lot I didn't
want to be a singer though I just used
to sing a lot and she's like you're not
a singer to a certain degree and this is
just being around singers like junior
and David and you know it helps to be
our own singers they teach I mean I'll
never have a singer's voice but I can do
enough to like I understand it more it's
more of a science I mean not it's not a
science but like there is some science
yeah yeah that I didn't most people
don't really know about but besides the
point yeah I would say have a plan give
them give them all I'm saying for my you
can give your perspective but I think it
helps for her too that the fact that she
told me like okay this is what you're up
against you might not if you make it
great most people don't there's like a
point something percent chance in the
entertainment field at least for me
going to be a actor or a entertainer or
some sort it's very rare to really blow
up right to know that
get that information from her it it
helped me because I'm like okay if I'm
gonna do this I gotta be like committed
to it and like I already know like if I
don't want her to tell me oh I told you
so you know so you got to commit to it
and I think knowing the if she's like I
mean no offense to other people who are
like this but if she would if she were
just like yeah you know what you could
be an actor if you work hard and you
just do it right like which is true but
be I think it's just being realistic
like a lot of people work hard it
doesn't mean you're gonna be successful
in entertainment you might even be good
at it but it doesn't mean you're gonna
make money yeah you know so if you're
willing to live poor or if you're
willing to live all these like mega
negative things that come with it then
yeah by all means but if not you could
just don't don't go in thinking you know
be yeah be realistic that's all I would
say and you know a lot of times I think
it's like opportunity but opportunity
zone you're like it's timing and it's
like being ready right and so I mean I
related back to Ryan it's kind of like
you know he was like doing YouTube and
then opportunity came to make money and
so he was like fortunate you know what I
mean so there's that one quote that's
like luck equals like preparation plus
opportunity right for sure you know so
it's all timing so I remember a father I
was like oh what's your son studying you
know he's in college and he said oh I
forget he was studying like music you
know and he was like yeah you know he's
studying music I don't know where that's
gonna take him and he's in California
and I was like you know you never know
it's like if that's what he loves I mean
who knows right if he has that
opportunity and he's ready
I mean doors might just open you just
never know so you just gotta encourage
them to be successful in whatever
whichever way they go of course you want
them to be a little focused you know you
want to jump from like okay singing
acting okay you know what I mean so at
least you want them to be a little
focused and then so that guy is
definitely selling knives right I mean
you never know
so well I haven't talked to the father
but I remember his name is Bruno
definitely silly
Bruno actually aside from when he was
young yeah he was like ready you know
and then opportunity it sounds like the
opposite of inspiring like podcasts but
it's you know you need a sense of really
like I mean I'm we're not saying hey
there's no chance the odds might be slim
but like again you work hard enough even
sometimes people who work their ass off
right it pays off in different ways it
doesn't always mean it's gonna be the
end result you expect like you if you
work your ass off it's gonna pay off in
some way it might just not be the exact
way you think it is because if just
statistically it's not realistic
no but if everybody that worked hard
made it in that industry then nobody
would have made it because it's all the
same everybody's you know yeah yeah
because like if I'm completely honest I
didn't work hard most of my life and
I've found myself in a very fortunate
situation and I'm like along with you
guys and stuff and I forced you to work
hard yeah forced me to work hard now
yeah but you know you're ready right I
mean like you you have like skills and
then they would then there was this
opportunity a little bit but if you
didn't have like that experience you
wouldn't be here yeah that's true too
cuz you did do things before that I hate
that even for me to like a look at it
and be like okay yeah he understands
like you've had you not made any videos
and just came like and asked to be a
part of this I would be like who the
hell is this guy yeah you know so there
is something there and even with your
personality and stuff like that's you
that comes with you'd like doing some
hosting things that you weren't always a
great speaker I don't think without
having to build that up it's a skill now
I was always a great speaker like my
first word was actually a paragraph by
William Shakespeare but in all religion
as a kid I was a I did theatre and stuff
really yeah that's right like you put in
some work right yeah I'm sure that
helped you did a lot did a lot I never
did theatre I hated I actually don't
like public speaking at all I hate
speaking in front of people you just
hate the public that's not wrong that's
not I don't like being in public likes
being in private yeah I mean I like that
segment because that's actually
something that you know a lot of people
are curious about and I think a lot of
listeners especially younger or people
who are trying to find themselves and
don't really know how to appease their
parents you know it'll help them I think
well you know parents worry right of
course because they want the best yeah
they weren't the best they want them to
be successful they want them to be able
to earn enough money to make a living
you know what I mean so parents have a
lot of fear for their kids but something
you just have to look like if they have
the talent or the passion you know you
never know I mean who knows right like
we didn't know Ryan was gonna be this
far I mean we didn't plan for this
not at all I think I'm just I think a
lot of people need to understand you
from the parents perspective is their
kids are considered like an investment
is that because you know I put so much
money into this bird into my offspring
this person I care about that I want
them to succeed in the way that I see
because maybe they don't have the
perspective or the openness to
understand that they're oh there's
different ways that you can make money
especially with the internet nowadays
and so if you were to explain that and
like you said like have a plan show them
how you can do it how you can actually
have a revenue and be a financially
stable and like what your 3 5-year plan
is yep it helps oh yeah so that's still
the guidance part yeah you know what I
mean yeah and I still think a lot of
people once they see a lot of people
don't realize they don't see the work
that goes in like you look at basketball
players and say I want to be a
basketball player they get millions of
dollars they you know live have like the
nicest clothes nicest cars everything
they see all the things you know that
basically they see the rewards and they
think that you know they know it's hard
work they might be good at basketball
but you don't really see you know if you
really should have map out what your
plan is then you kind of it becomes more
real let me do it from a from a youtuber
perspective a lot of people what they
what they tell me especially like kids
that
I've encouraged like oh yeah do what you
love do if you want make youtube videos
make them a lot of them will make I
would say videos for about a month maybe
two months and they realize holy crap
this isn't easy like along with other
stuff I have going on in my life like I
just don't have time but that's like if
you want to be committed youtuber you
got to dedicate your life to it at this
point you know and people don't don't
realize that so when you say like put
together a plan like how are you gonna
be successful you got to do your
research like ask a youtuber what do you
do every day like a the one that you
want to be like and most of them will
tell you like oh they're either filming
everyday editing or they had to build up
like how did you get to where you were
it's never the story that people think
it is it's a lot more work than people
think it is and until you try it for
yourself that's when they realize like
okay this is not what I want to do or
this is too much and I think those
people are the people that actually like
respect they find a newfound respect for
people who are doing it yeah even if you
don't like what they're creating you can
still be like you know they're working
hard yeah it's a lot of work I mean like
I when I mean like when people first
started doing daily videos I mean there
was one guy even when I started we did
daily videos and I was like this isn't
not content like this is just I mean at
the time it was new it was like I don't
want to see you walk to the mall like I
don't care obviously there was an
audience for that and there still is
more now than ever
but you don't realize even for me as a
youtuber was like oh yeah I could do
that every day until you do it and you
realize holy crap no you can't even take
a day if you're a daily vlogger you
can't take a day off even even like you
know I don't know how often pewdiepie
posts pretty much every day I know he
shoots a lot in one at all at once so it
kind of spreads it out but just the fact
and now he has a lot of help but in the
beginning he didn't have the team that
he had you know he had to work on that
and put in all that time and effort and
you don't you don't really see it
because you don't see all you don't see
that side yeah people think are videos
but if they're five minutes long took 10
minutes to make you know you don't
realize how long it takes to film and
edit and write and everything that goes
into it but I mean smart people know but
a
you do it it's really hard to just say I
think you know if I as a parent if I saw
like a child like you know your child
working so hard and just like improving
and I mean I mean that comes with talent
too right so then you recognize that and
of course you want to support it you
know so I think that's what you got to
do if that's what you want to do like
prove it then exactly prove it yeah less
about talking yeah and it's not as easy
as you think and so naturally your
parents are not just gonna jump on it
because you you that's what you wanna do
because it looks nice or you know looks
like fun yeah yeah
alright anyway thank you for joining us
on this special Mother's Day edition
thank you to Paco for being a good
moderator and I cuz I didn't know how to
yeah thank you for being a good mother
Paco and um yeah I didn't think do and
do you Lucy thanks your mom I did I just
did
no you didn't okay thanks mom tell her
you love her I love you mom I love you
mom
[Laughter]
yeah with that being said where can they
follow us you can I was just going to
see you're 5050 with that yeah that is
that is my fall was forget off the pill
on Twitter and Instagram special
Mother's Day edition yeah wasn't we
weren't expecting to do this one but I
guess with that being said you know
actually know what to do because you
actually wait when you said if you don't
like what I don't like it what I think
you know when you guys asked like oh who
doesn't like the breathing in the mic
yeah yeah I don't like it a lot of
people don't like what answer you put on
the headset for me please this whole
thing because my mom did this whole
thing cuz she didn't want to hear
herself and let alone the breathing into
the mic alright with that being said
tune in next time for the next podcast
talk to you next podcast
well we can't end it if you don't do it
so why we're just talking then are you
kidding me no ready why but I don't get
it that's just what it is until we come
up with a new thing this really isn't
good for the my Steven said yeah that's
why I think you guys shouldn't do it at
its dirty yeah well this turn ahead on
the mics nah let's just end it