hey guys so you know that I don't
normally do challenges and that's not
all this video is gonna be so just watch
it to the end I keep getting comments
that say this dear Ryan can you do it
try not to cry challenge and I know a
lot of other people who have already
done this challenge watch the whole
video or watch a bunch of videos and
show the entire thing but the sake of
keeping this video quick I'm just gonna
show the highlight from each video that
I watch and I'm gonna put in some
subtitles just in case you guys can't
understand me I don't even know what
videos you're supposed to watch I'm just
gonna watch videos that other people
watch so I guess let's try it out I used
to think that pork chops and karate
chops were the same thing hahaha we
found ourselves up numbers a day average
raising two kids who's definitely ever
always been a Miss is so boring how come
the little girl grows up but he does an
age does he Benjamin Button so unhealthy
for him probably she never even sent me
a damn card you don't want me man
probably cuz you're so loud why why
Adele why are you guys talking during
the songs why are people still memeing
this we're screwed this one's pretty
happy let's see that's why I love Pixar
they're not sad like all these other
stupid sad videos so you know this is
cute but why did she fall oh my no no no
she can't hide pics it Pixar's not to be
happy oh my how did he teleport
like that I miss Minnesota too me too
I miss when the Lakers were there did
you know that's that's where they came
from the Lakers came from Minnesota cuz
there's a lot of lakes there she's so
blue she has blue hair and yeah blue
balls
they're blue w2 padai and I'm craving
sushi you never have another woody this
is so bad you didn't even try for this
one pic Sarge I used too much big sur
footage okay fine I'm not a crier
obviously and I'm not saying that
because I'm afraid to cry I mean I'm
perfectly fine with guys crying I just
crying for things that are real not like
movies and whatnot so I decided rather
than just doing this challenge for real
like everybody else I decided to make
for you after watching a bunch of these
challenges and doing research are the
most tear-jerking movies and clips I
linked to my incredible research team
and we scientifically broke down the
saddest things ever take a look there's
got to be more than death Pixar I'm
looking outside of a window all that
rains that makes people cry right dose
we got oh what about saying goodbye to
someone you love yeah okay sing goodbye
okay good what else anytime a soldier
returns home those videos always make
people cry right now
that's pretty sad yeah that's good
that's good okay what else we got a
really sad looking puppy well I mean
wouldn't fly it's circling around it yes
that is sad that is super sad Ella flies
oh what about like a kite what about a
kite that can make someone's head how
cuz you're like flies and stuff you
don't have to raise your hand buckle oh
well
picture this alright imagine a little
nerdy loser looking kid eating lunch by
himself while the rest of the kids eat
together on another table huh that's sad
right I mean I guess it's understand all
right what else anything dereck nothing
so how about not being in the video
because you're always filming it what I
got it what if the kite was blue better
see we clearly did all of our research
and with all that information we finally
did it we created the saddest video of
all times rather than just watching me
do it I've created a video for you guys
to watch I'm challenging all of you guys
to do the try not to cry challenge right
here right now so if you guys want to go
and do the challenge and record your
reactions to this I would say pause the
video right now go get your camera get
your popcorn oh and while you're at you
better get some tissues as well cuz let
me tell you you are gonna need it you
want to get popcorn butter all over your
camera and stuff with that being said
this is a SCI's video ever and your try
not to cry challenge
where'd it go
[Music]
it's time to say goodbye
oh my god
hey if I was in here no go ahead go
ahead yeah
[Music]
hey Greg I want you to do this next
scene what won't you be the star of this
next video really yeah I'll film it this
time cuz I want you in it oh my god do
you know how much this means to me thank
you all even worry bro you'll be great
ready okay yeah ready when you are hi
and action
[Music]
where'd it go
Oh where'd it go oh no I'm gonna have
ant dogs you're gonna have a feast how
did I just disappear did it go in my
mouth did I drop one did it fall back in
the ball
[Music]