what the hell is this hey you guys don't
know I'm in college now and Sean he's
still in Hawaii but I found someone who
looks exactly like him
meet the new sean fujiyoshi and the
bunny went hop hop hop all the way home
I love happy endings ha ha ha hey man
what's up
how could you do this to me how could
you replace me with that thing you know
I would never do such a thing in fact I
just made a video of us and we're in
California filming the movie really yeah
dude check it out
ah
Oh
so what do you think what the hell I
wasn't even in that thing but I thought
it was pretty good
and never in any videos anymore and the
reason for that is because we have too
much Asian in our videos you know we
have a bad yellow to white ratio what
that that doesn't make any sense at all
think of it like a Twinkie if you bite
into the yellow cake of a Twinkie and
there is no white cream filling it sucks
you get it
oh I get it I see what you mean huh so
I'm still the one and only Sean the
fluffy bunny fujiyoshi right yeah of
course
okay bye don't worry you'll never know
you
and don't forget if you want are moving
to come to your city go to i love indie
films comm and boat contest ends on
october 31st so hurry up please
ah