hey guys so recently I've been noticing
another trend a lot of people have been
posting videos titled women say or men
say and I'm sure you are too by now
that's why I made a whole bunch
here's how you move your line at 9:00 in
the morning good idea baby I love
talking to you on the phone for hours
especially when they're silent pauses
who's Justin Bieber I love dieting oh my
god yes I love traffic oh my god yes
traffic aah blackberries can do way more
than iPhone
god I love waiting for the bus another
red light love it don't you love
construction in the morning oh I can
talk Twilight movies way better than the
books so take your time crossing the
street it's cool
I'm so happy unicorns don't exist TV see
you later tonight who's that does
someone have a flat tire I love when the
toilet seat is cold in the morning
non-alcoholic beer genius Kidz Bop
genius
t-pain sounds way better without a door
to go Siri you're always right so math
is so bill didn't get passed you know
where I really want to go this summer
where are South Dakota you know where I
really want to go to somewhere where the
DMV you know what I really want to go to
somewhere where the hood
I think Jersey Shore's education it was
better than Kobe Bryant who Walton Bron
James
you