like you speed wrong
[Music]
so did you like it no dear Ryan can you
squeeze a girl's chest what are you
doing what I'm just squeezing your chest
why hot because it's mine and it's
Primus then maybe you shouldn't show it
off so much top fine you had a small
chest anyway do you know that is a chest
I play with dear wife no bleach trailer
[Music]
I don't know I heard a lot of crazy
things about these bad boys but here we
go don't know what the big deal is
they're not that your life you shave
your armpits so everybody has been
telling me to do this for the longest
time now one of the most popular D
Ryan's I get every single time I guess I
finally got to do it before I do I just
want to say goodbye and thank you guys
you guys have been around since I was
like 13 or 12 I thought you guys have
never come but then you did you stuck by
me through all the hard times and just
want to thank you thank you for all the
memories
[Music]
that being said goodbye my friends we're
just moving on to a better place
[Music]
hi I'm Ryan Higa and right now millions
of armpit hairs are being murdered at
the Western Hemisphere known as the left
armpit just because they weren't born in
the right neighborhood not the head not
the lip or chin not even here in the
right armpit left
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
so will you be an angel here and help us
put an end to her murder from all of us
here in the right armpit we just wanted
to say to all of our brothers and
sisters in the left to keep fighting
hold on and know that our follicles go
out to all of you better yeah I don't
know if I like this too much so leave
your questions in the comments below and
you could be responsible for the next
video this is never seen Ellen visit
this ever through this is hell sore okay
so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see more
bloopers and behind the scenes from this
video click on the left if you want to
see the previous video click the one on
the right and make sure you guys always
remember to shave your armpits because
not only is it sanitary but it's also
feminine tear feminine as a feminine
then men M&MS