[Music]
hey guys thank you all for coming today
I brought you here for a reason but
first let's introduce ourselves my name
is Ryan and then it's going with you
[Music]
what why don't you introduce yourself
why don't you I just did weren't you
listening
no you what's up guys my name is art
dizzle okay thank you I do she's on my
nizzle alright Rd so for up the hizzle
thank trizol but y'all can call me
r-dizzle
are you done what you trying to rush me
doll no no these some kind of radio
racist dog you racist no I swear I was
just trying to I'm just playing go ahead
anyway let's move on to you hi guys my
name is Regina but you can call me
Regina and I like rainbows and sunshine
and puppies but I don't like my puppies
noses are wet because when it's wet what
is that is that boogers or is that water
what is that
okay let's move on oh yo yo I don't have
a body what my name is
boob but you can call me Hana they walk
who so she's able to not shake area
teacher Suki Honda Civic okay okay wait
your name is boob no he means Bob yes
that's what I said boob no Bob Bob Bob
boob question yes Regina if his name is
boob can I be Regina gas-tight no no you
let's just change your name why not yeah
I don't understand why I feel like it
isn't that right that's right isn't that
right my name boob so I don't know why
you okay that's enough
I didn't gather all of you here so you
can come and change your names you are
gonna be our diesel you are gonna be
Regina and you were gonna be haunted
it's settled but the real reason why I
brought you all here is because I want
to start a series with all of you you
know bring a little gangster into the
picture
maybe a little ninja a little I said you
ain't in under this under what under my
umbrella that's a lamp so what you think
you're some kind of umbrella expert now
stupid and combine it all into one to
make one awesome show what do you guys
think my name Bo
[Applause]