hey guys so I know it's been a while
since we all hung out it's a little
awkward because it's been like two years
now but um any of you wanna and you guys
all had the same no scars me did you
guys also make an accident with your
curling iron
yeah actually hi what no I know for a
fact that we got that from a sword you
know when we were filming the fruit
ninja video maybe you did I got mine
from a cutting ah yeah me too well no I
know for a fact that we got it you want
dad you don't even know I mean I do know
because I created you so I kind of would
what didn't you're not God you're not my
mom you're not a carpenter you don't
make things look you know what forget I
said that you're right we got that from
curling Hoda what are you trying to say
that we're not real no I mean I don't
get it are we not real people or not
yeah what are we you have a right to
know I really don't think we should go
down that road right now
well is this a real road or a fake road
or railroad rocky road rocky road ice
cream yeah how come I'm the only one
with Canadian accent yeah why is that
Indian look guys there's not complicate
things okay then just tell us how we
fake or real
we like versions of you but like cool
wrong guys we really shimmy we're out
weird this is all a dream like in down
one more I really don't think that
Titanic thing got from Canada up guys
please I'm begging you let's not but
maybe we're just clones of you but
better oh my god they're gonna tackle
the clock in the Jedi happening to this
college they hated Star Trek wow do you
seriously bro that's messed up you think
I'm from Canada stop okay just stop I
don't know what you guys are okay I
don't even know what I am in all this I
started this like four years ago and I
wasn't thinking about that okay look the
only reason why I started doing this
series again is because people kept
asking for it why don't they stop oh
sorry
look if this is how it's gonna be
whenever we hang out then I don't want
to continue doing this okay so can we
please just drop it and just start over
so are we the Jedi's then ah
[Music]
all right so now that we finally cleared
things up let's start talking about
clear anything up but you said to drop
it we didn't really clear what you said
right
I just think you're doing it wrong look
whether you guys are making it up or not
why don't we go back to talking about
your stories what story your notes cars
I mean you guys should already know my
story you know the fruit enjoy filming I
got hit by a watermelon the watermelon
hit a sword which hit my face I posted a
video about it
come on the video fruit ninja fail oh
yeah didn't know it's so boring
Canada anyway yeah that story what
happened to you guys I told you my
curling iron did this okay and what
about you two curling iron carding I am
look if you guys are gonna make up
stories at least make them different
from each other how do you keep saying
we're making things up cause you are me
you're the one that's making things I
have video proof of what happened it's
uploaded us so do we did you do hi yeah
so there I was I was doing my norm
hunter oh sorry
so there are one
[Music]
that's when the curling iron lightsaber
cutting my nose whoa I can't believe
that actually happened so I guess you
finally watched Star Wars huh what is
that
let's just move on art is all what
happened to you and please do not say
that it was curling iron you don't even
have hair to curl how could you possibly
have gone up okay so there I was like
every 15 minutes of my day curling iron
such an easy warm-up for me you did
three curls what I mean you started
counting at 98 so you technically only
did three curls trying to make me angry
what No
you're clearly the toughest guy I know I
know better than to do that do you like
me when I'm an old blues artists oh
you're too cool and strong and you can
read good than me
[Music]
nately Oh seriously what that is just as
unrealistic as Regina story I know that
didn't happen you even put me in the
story if you don't want to be in it next
time they'll throw a way to my face yeah
why would you even do that right
Prante please tell me your story is even
somewhat believable oh that was it was
the year 2010 okay I need you to focus
okay we need you to get a perfect score
another person to take home the Camaro's
what you trained for that this is what
you worked for your whole right I
believe in you hard to do this so don't
worry coaches have got this
a buncha now jutsu
y'all ready let's do this and at that
very moment It was as if time Stood
Still and I suddenly understood every
little thing he was trying to tell me it
wasn't about the maple syrup or the free
health care it's not even about all the
Moose mooses or me it was about being
proud and proud to be where I am proud
to be what I stand for
proud to be Who I am who is that you
might ask my name is hunter Waku so she
sailed to dodge day teriyaki Suzuki
Honda Civic and I will always and
forever be curling for Canada
[Music]
[Applause]
what the hell are you talking about
I don't know see this is exactly why I
stopped making these videos why they
make no sense I'll do all your other
videos at least I didn't lie about how I
got my nose score not lie yes you over
knows you're yes you are Wow um I'm
sorry guys I guess you I guess you guys
were telling the truth I just never
thought that it would wait don't flick
away yet to see the behind the scenes
video on Higa TV click here and to see
the last Getzel from two years ago click
here late now they both take you to the
behind the scenes video if you want to
subscribe to my channel click here no
this also takes you to behind the scenes
video this one if you want to subscribe
this one if you want to go to my Twitter
this one is for my facebook this one is
for the Canadian curling Association
website just kidding they all take you
to the Canadian curling Association
website sorry