hey guys so I know too many years since
we all ass got together but uh what what
have you guys been up to
[Music]
guys guys you guys all look a lot fatter
hey guys so I was always saying earlier
how I'm upset okay with you okay why I
don't know why don't you tell me what
that's what she said she who are you
talking about
well Saloth you alright can can one of
you guys please explain this I don't
know if she saw you haven't made a skit
so in over a year
yeah you're too busy making those stupid
off the pill videos I mean it's been
really hard to get all you guys got
those stupid wack songs nobody wants to
hear you sing man oh come on you're
barely even a comedian let alone a
musician nice guys did pretty well but
not good enough if Miriam Johnson passed
you and subscriber alright alright you
guys think it's so easy huh you don't
know what it's like to have so many
people to please you know what go go
make a video I want to see you guys make
a video see what a time but how did you
guys when did you like how did you just
shut up and play
[Music]
lesson one talk to your camera in a room
by yourself really fast music I thought
I had movies and movie your eye drops a
lot you guys I'm ready to go I'm gonna
be talking about about two things I
don't like I don't care if you guys
really I don't care if you do I don't
care if the quality is bad on came to
the dock my bed all I care about is be a
might be bad and the videos done this is
to make thick advertisements that people
don't even want
oh look at me I'm right I'm selling a
product like like this box with paper in
it and I just take one whip but it
doesn't stop huh
this is a it's like a magical box it
doesn't is unfitted i want it lesson
three be Haitian lesson 4 make veer
right videos dear Ryan
lesson five create stupid videos about
dams because you have no friends
[Music]
yeah sounds
[Applause]
I am never watching a room or a tepache
you can turn me on oh my girl and I'll
never behave and if you follow me
burning out
I'll never expect it cuz I'll be
plugging in your roses on the table
table fit the batter's take the side of
my table I only use you and I take your
phone I'll call it but then until I hit
you up I'll put you back in the closet
huh you're not a lamp well to be quite
honest I'm not even a girl seriously
what is it is it like pick on Ryan date
today or something well we wouldn't have
to team up on you if you bet us be on
your team what we would like to play
right holiday exactly what must be shout
why must we fight this is how it start
it starts from a little pebble and it
grows into a big problem it doesn't
matter if your skin is white or black or
green it doesn't matter all that matter
is that we work together because United
you might be the air I know we stand
amen what the hell are you talking about
I don't know