yo dog how long are we gonna have to
wait I told you we have to wait for
Regina I mean I'm sure she's like see
she's calling right now I'm sure she's
just like on her way hello hello Regina
speaking where are you who is this what
okay I don't know how you got my number
but stop calling me Regina you called me
this is Ryan oh hi Ryan and to what do I
owe this pleasure
where are you we're all waiting for you
right now I'm in my car great so you're
on your way
no I already is here even better then
come on in see that's the problem I'm
locked inside of my car and I need help
because I can't ruin the windows because
the car won't start because I don't have
the keys because the keys fell down and
I can't find it because it's dark
wait so you're inside of the car duh how
else do you get locked inside of a car
did you try unlocking the door oh okay
I'll be right up
all right thank you all for coming again
despite the minor delay
so how was all of your Halloween's yo
dawg it was tight I scored so much candy
wow you of all people in
trick-or-treating that that's great
trick a treat no that's embarrassing Dom
well you're never too old you beat up a
little girl and took hers silly sir Gina
how was your Halloween I had the worst
time ever not one kid came to my door
and that's partially the reason why I
came late tonight because I was waiting
for people to come would you know
Halloween was yesterday uh-huh
that explains it explains what well I
was getting a lot of complaints from
parents because a bunch of monsters and
Miley Cyrus's were showing up at my door
so I would shoot them with a water hose
oh my god did anybody get hurt no well
at first but then these three Jonas
Brothers showed up at my door and I
should have known they weren't real
because they were all Nick but I was
just so happy because I love the Jonas
Brothers okay and then they took off
their faces and I realized it wasn't
them so I got really mad and grabbed my
shotgun and shot them dead
wait what I shot them dead you shot that
and Larry you shot somebody your
murderer you killed some actually it was
three kids that's almost just as bad but
it was consensual and that's all that
matters what no no like seriously you
have to get out of here you stay here
we're all gonna get in trouble okay the
house should think oh my god what get
out of here I can't why it's locked
wait that's not fair I never get to tell
my Halloween story I'm sorry honey how
was your Halloween I stay home cook rice