tonight on channel 6 get some news live
how you should dress for the upcoming
week
once again the World Cup takes over
television ratings is ensured really
doing jail time for a failed DUI test
and stick around for a sit-down
interview with an ex member of one of
the deadliest gangs in gangs ville
coming to you tonight on channel 6
good evening I'm Ryan Higa and this is
channel 6
schizo news live we did not realize that
by naming our program schizo News live
it would have the abbreviation SNL which
some of you may know stands for another
television program known as supernova
lockness a sci-fi original and also
secret ninja lizards on nickelodeon and
of course the ever-popular salmon never
lies only on Alaska TV we also didn't
realize that by naming our station
channel 6 that we'd have a 666 in our
set which some people believe to be a
demonic number also related to the
Illuminati well what we say to those
people that's a bunch of illumine on
sense and also because we're not going
to change the entire set because I'm a
bunch of numbers like that's gonna be a
lot of work for nothing tonight we have
many exciting stories for you but first
let's go to one of those angry and
confusing four-way split screen debates
about something probably political angry
guys all very good points summer is
right around the corner summer and once
again it's that time of the year when
temperatures start to rise how should
you dress for this upcoming week here's
Regina with the forecast thanks Ryan
as you can see here we're gonna have
lots of green all week showing that
summer is finally here
so make sure you drink lots of water
because it looks like it's we have no
other colors so it's 100% all green
meaning it's gonna be a hundred to
greens fear of heights all week back to
school Ryan what and now let's see
what's happening in the athletic world
here's Hana tee with sports in sport
news the World Cup is finally started
first Bastille beat the Croatia then the
United States that they are gonna win
and then the spur win the NBA world cup
when all of a sudden LeBron crowd the
nega fall down from the heat but now the
question remain on everybody mind who
take home the World Cup or feat does
things start to get messy in Argentina
does Portugal down once they run out the
ideas and finally does LeBron James
still cramp the leg and fall down or no
around the lake
far down nobody know looks like we'll
just have to wait and see thanks on the
day is famous singer ed Sheeran really
doing jail time for failing a DUI test
we have actual footage from the scene
take a look
late night drive sir it's late leave you
know why I pulled you over
I don't want to know sir you've been
doing any drinking tonight you know I'm
gonna do step out of the car and walk
this line please sir step out of the car
and walk this line please walk the line
please sir walk Oh big fan huge fan
that'll do and now let's go to our
dizzle with you know what really pisses
me off
our dizzle you know what really pisses
me off Japanese television gameshows why
do you always got to have that little
box in the corner with somebody reacting
through the show I'm not trying to watch
somebody react to the show I just want
to watch the show I don't need somebody
telling me how I should react when I
watch the show I know is it the word
show like way too many times in the same
paragraph and I'm trying to put emphasis
on this Japanese television game show
you know what I mean go Fah show and
finally for our main story of the
evening I have a sit-down interview with
a man once a part of a very violent and
dangerous gang and what life is like
after escaping that horrific group let's
take a look first of all I just want to
say thank you for doing this I know it's
not easy to speak out about something so
private course of course let's start
with the basics tell us your name what
you do where you live or don't you
prefer not to give that information or
you know no no no that's fine we'll
probably just put at the bottom the
screen anyway we're more Awards so tell
me Steven what has life been like as an
ex-convict come on that's cause I ex
murder we won a model word relax rapist
no I'm never expand we're talking about
Exorcist or x-men what so then you are
still part of the gang then
no I'm literally in hiding right now I
didn't think I'd ever get out of their
life I don't even know what they'll do
to me if they ever fall sorry can you
pull that thought hey can we fix Stevens
audio his voices come in all deep and
weird maybe like blues or wants to be
heard on Oh God and hotel did lighting
today I can't even see his face turn up
the lights no no please if they find out
where I am I'm steep Steven where you go
the interviews not Steven Johnson Steven
Johnson those interviews not over truly
inspirational best of luck to you Steven
Johnson of 42 third Street downtown LA
apartment 6b so that's all we have for
you tonight from all of us at Channel
six schizo News live thank you for
tuning in and have a wonderful night
breaking news this just in it seems to
wait it seems that we have it seems to
cut it it seems that Steven Johnson the
man I just interviewed is in a live foot
chase with a bunch of gang members we're
not sure who or why yet but oh no oh I'm
now being told that the chase is over
steven has collapsed from dehydration
and now the gang is beating him to death
that's awful but I suppose is a moral to
every story and something you kids can
learn from Steven summer is hot so make
sure you stay cool and always be sure to
drink lots of water or else you're going
to let the leg fall down show so once
again from all of us at channel 6 get
some news live thank you for watching
be safe stay hydrated we're not the
Illuminati goodnight
hey hey leave my Silhouette
he looks kinda like an eyeball what does
that mean weird Hey look it looks like
an eyeball I look with a moving pupil no
it's a asian eyeball
now it's mad Seattle Seahawks the bird's
eye I have Sauron Sauron remember that
look he's like you see how it's looking
around Japanese eye of Sauron oh man
we're probably gonna get killed don't
kill us huh