it's at the awkward stage again jail no
jail no GL no wax no wax wax off what
hey guys so if you guys haven't already
noticed switch I don't think you have
because it's only been like five seconds
into the video I got a new chair I got
it for free but I don't worry this is
not a product placement I just they sent
me an rhpc a bunch of free chairs so
just give them a shout out thank you
guys so much thank you to the whole
means that DX DX Racer I just butchered
their name don't take the chairs back
please I like it if you guys didn't
notice my chair was always squeaking and
ruining takes and all my other vlogs I
don't know why it took me this long to
get a new chair especially since I used
this problem into every video it's not
perfect - it's like art it's like the
channel colors in fact I technically
didn't even get permission from them to
use their brand in this video so
technically I think they can get it
removed
I should probably cover that up with
some funny pun joke you guys haven't
noticed we always trying to cover brands
up in case they get mad which they have
in the past for some reason I don't know
why free promotion you know cover up
other brands these super clever puns
such as and of course now
hey clever right I couldn't think of a
good one I don't know why I always
ramble in the beginning of your Ryan
let's just jump into it dear Ryan New
Balance 10 Oreo cookies on your face
we're doing snow angels on the floor
really 10 Oreos I mean or Jo's I've
never done that before but I'm pretty
sure that's not that hard to do in fact
I'm confident I could probably do the
whole bag but what's a snow angel
alright here we go
what do you make the best part of the
face probably right here this is a lot
harder than I thought it was gonna be -
this is easy to get ten I'm gonna go way
past tape oh this feels like it's shaky
dude this is not gonna stay but I can
try again I can do it I can do ten all
right here this is a better piece oh my
gosh I'm mad alright I'm cheating no
stack for me and then once I get ten I'm
gonna snow angel for this ten I did one
right I did one angel
let's just see how much we can stack
13:14 I'm on Oreos watch was Ryan smiles
I don't know how much that was do you
Ryan how many types of laughs do you
know do them the courtesy laugh the kind
of funny left the funny laugh the really
funny laugh the I'm dying laughs that's
it con laughs the silent laugh the
weaves are left the old man laughs
machine gun laugh the lol through text
laugh the sarcastic laugh haha the rich
person laugh they're trying to be mad at
someone but they made you laugh laugh
the evil laugh ha ha ha ha the sloth
from Zootopia laugh
well the singer laughs the pee-wee
Herman laughs spongebob Patrick
oh sweet word seth rogen Freeza the
joker the watching nigahiga videos
laughs I don't get it and last but not
least the most annoying laugh of all
time dear Ryan how long can you do a
wall sit pour I've done a lot of wall
sits in my life if you've ever done
sports you know what wall sits arts when
you have to like bend your knees like
you're sitting like on a chair basically
but against the wall I'd like burned
your legs it's extremely tiring I can
hold it for a long time all right timer
starts no see I've done so many lawsuits
in my time that this to hood this
doesn't even faze me anymore I don't
even feel like a burn
like in fact I could probably hold this
all day oh dear Ryan make a sentence
consisting of just puns I don't know
when this start happening but I've
become known for puns like yes I think
puns are funny sometimes but they're
cheap comedy it's really not that funny
it's just silly and dumb and I'm already
trying to stray away from doing all fun
jokes because they're not good jokes
guys plus a whole sentence of just puns
like is that even possible I don't know
how I would do that but I will try and
go look for some words that make me oh
so funny and silly and just a fire pun
spitting galapagos animal with no chill
Ben there you go I just did it that
entire sentence we're all puns if you
didn't catch it I'll do it a little
slower for you guys I do not knows how I
would do that but I will try and go look
for some words that Meek me oh so funny
and silly and justify or pun spitting
Galapagos an email with no chill beach
yeah even I thought that was too much
that was a bit of a stretch you see guys
this is what I'm talking about bit puns
are not funny I'm completely over puns
but not anymore dear Ryan can you do a
soccer trick shot I mean last time you
guys saw when we did it with basketball
shots and that was already really
difficult okay ever since we did that
basketball trick shot every dear Ryan's
like trick shot trick shot do more trick
shot guys we're not doing perfect okay
we're not even dude good no no we're not
even good we're like decent or do decent
we actually like doing trick shots but
the catch here is that none of us here
and do decent play soccer or football
sorry for the rest of the world the
basketball fun was Hardy nothing we
actually play basketball so we're gonna
do a soccer one I don't know if that's a
good idea that might take days but I
guess we can't let our fans down right
dude decent we do it decent oh my god
see easy and we don't even break
anything this time so leave your
question in the comments below and you
could be responsible for the next video