hey guys as many of you already know I
made a myspace like a few months ago and
it's doing great I have like 30,000
friends and growing but sometimes it
does get a little stressful
I get like 600 friend requests a day on
average do you have any idea how long it
takes to approve all of those not to
mention I get tons of comments and
messages saying stuff like why don't you
ever comment me back I mean I watch all
your videos why won't you accept my
friend request I sent it like an hour
ago you never respond to my messages
I'll suck it up I got stuff to do you
know I I clean my keyboard okay I read
the dictionary apparently you know I do
stuff so anyways all joking aside I'd
like to say that I'm sorry that I can't
reply to all of you guys I really do
feel bad sometimes so I wrote you guys a
song that I hope you'll like despite the
fact that my I'm losing my voice right
now and yeah here it is
as time goes by I learned that my space
is a great responsibility and I realize
that all things I haven't done affect
all the people around me so I want to
take this time out and apologize for the
things I haven't done and for things
that didn't occur yet and things I don't
want to take responsibility for I'm
sorry that my friend requests have grown
things about an hour tour group omalo
sorry for the times that I had to bow to
you were online and I did not know that
you were at home just waiting for me for
longer every message and come and I see
sorry for the times I would neglect
sorry for the times that it did not
check I'm sorry for the things I haven't
done
I'm a ninja gangsta game alert agent
sorry that I'm busy I'm always away I
got a lot to do what more can I say
cuz I'm doing homework like every day
free charge that I had to write the
freaking essay no I didn't take all your
requests ricotta's be hey or how to be a
prayer understand that
you get pissed off this that it's not
your fault I know all the hate mail I
get from you just because I respond to
Sloane I should apologize for singing
this song is it sucks and makes a fool
out of me I will respond to you right
now but I forget cuz my a DD you blame
my a DD for me being so busy it's not
that I am lazy it's just cuz my a DD did
you blame my a DD for me being so busy
it's not that I am lazy it's just cuz my
a DD