I've decided to retire from the game of
basketball to pursue my true passions
and what would that be baseball golf I
heard you're good at ping pong actually
watching anime and playing video games
he's gonna see hey look some of the guys
don't believe me but we tell them thumb
that you're Michael Michael yeah tell
them who you are tell them you're
Michael Jordan what I'm not Michael
Jordan grab the wrong guy
what's going on here we needed a
basketball player but we got you instead
well I still play basketball you do yeah
you don't look like a basketball player
yeah you look more like one of us
well I might not look it but I am a
basketball player I'm Jeremy Lin
who changes for yo you get the
superheroes why do you need my help well
I mean if this were a fight it would
already be over but since it's a
basketball game if we fight we get in
food before food though how old and they
spell it that way got a lot of work to
do there's two sides to basketball
offense and defense on offense jump
shots
free throws
layoffs
even more important than offense is
defense most important thing is to
always keep your man in front of you
it's time
they got nothing how sure they look
awful boss they don't even know what
they're doing
a new guy doesn't even seem all that
great either huh what well they got this
NBA player what it's another travel Goku
remember you need to dribble the ball
but every time I do the ball bounces
through the roof
I want l1 him me me I want to know every
shot he's ever made the bus he's a
nobody at boss he's not even like em
dear Brian
in fact he kind of looks like one of us
except well Wow what he's got some weird
hair I told you it's cuz you're using so
much chakra
you mean key [ __ ] around you all you to
do is stop using it that's it what if
instead of holding back your guy's
powers we let them loose we can use that
to our advantage
yeah
what all right guys this is everything
we trained for remember all your trains
got to let's do this boys hey and girls
thank you all right put them in I kind
of made a change to our name we're not
too squad anymore well then what are we
toast you guys actually showed up I'm
surprised we're not afraid of you you
actually think your little toon squad
should be to us the animals no toon
squad can
we're not the toon squad anymore we are
we are the we are the Animaniacs squad
that got me to know what kind of name is
Anna maniac screw you guys okay order
your own Jersey's next time
my trap still binding circle