hey guys today's video is going to be
about all those inspirational sayings
and inspirational quotes that we've all
come to know and love and I'm not
talking about all of them I'm just
talking about the really overdone ones
or the ones that are just kinda stupid
and just to be clear I have no problem
with people who will try to inspire
others I think that's great that's one
of the many reasons why I still do
YouTube I'm all for deeper meanings like
I love when things actually make you
have to think then there's the ones that
are just trying way too hard to be
inspirational it's those quotes that are
just so cheesy and just not real and
they're constantly posting about them
whether it's to remind themselves or to
try and inspire the rest of us we've all
seen the polls you know you're scrolling
down your Instagram feed it's not only
some girl pulls this picture with a
caption of nice-looking pet I did I just
caught myself sorry young girls and guys
I got to be a little PC here I know guys
that post those things as well you know
I'm just trying to be real here usually
more girls that I've seen personally
that I don't presume say that either
there's a 50/50 exactly equal amount of
guys and girls that post these things
all right it's not the point I don't
know why I'm making that point the point
is I am a horrible person okay and I
have a horrible mind it doesn't let me
get inspired by these things when I know
how hard someone is trying to make an
inspirational pole or trying to be
serious and inspiring I can't help but
be realistic and make them a little less
serious sorry in advance if every day
meaning of life is to give life a
meaning if the meaning of life is to
give life a meaning you kind of just did
that for us now didn't you you already
gave life a meaning so I guess life is
meaningless because you already defined
it you miss 100% of the shots and you
don't take how is this one even
inspirational you can't make a shot if
you don't take it as extending the
obvious think about that did you ask her
out nah man I chickened out you know you
missed a hundred percent of the shots
you don't take no I didn't miss the shot
I just didn't take it no what it means
is you can't make the shot if you don't
take the shot well that's like pointing
out the obvious that's like saying if
you don't take the bus you can't take
the bus or how you would put it you miss
a hundred percent of the buses you don't
take wow that is G it's like mind
blowing so whether you think you can or
you think you can
you're right I think I can fly and I
think I can't die unless you're right
which is not the number of breaths we
take the number of moments that take our
breath away okay I get today's a gift
that's why we call it the present so
we're just making puns now well in that
case tomorrow is going to be a chore
that's why they call it the future
yesterday was so awful you wish you
could have just skipped it that's why
they call it the past next seven days
are just going to suck all the energy
out of you that's why they call it a
week you cannot save people you can only
love them well I guess but don't tell
that to a firefighter or a lifeguard
love you shoot for the moon even if you
miss you'll land among the stars this
one is not even inspiring if you think
about it the beginning part is good it's
like shoot for the moon go for it and I
agree the next part is is actually if
you think about it really stupid it's
not inspiring it hard saying shoot for
the moon even if you miss you know at
least you got the stars that's like
telling a kid hey go for your goals even
if you don't make it well you know good
enough what with my job I'm going to
quit my job move to Hollywood and pursue
my true passion it becomes an Oscar
award-winning actor even if I miss still
let among stars
well it still got my oscar nope we have
to look through the rain and see the
rainbow
I've grew up in Hawaii you don't need to
look to rain to see a ring you can go to
Yosemite and see a double rainbow
without any rains I think you're even
encouraging people to see the rain
you're putting a negative that you're
putting rain there and rain is great
who says rain is a bad thing rain helped
create the rain box you have to kiss a
lot of frogs before you find your prince
this one is so dumb
I disagree so you dumped another one huh
yeah gotta kiss a lot of frogs gross
afraid your friends nope even if you do
find your prints you think he's gonna
want to be with a serial frog kisser how
do you thing about real frogs you had a
kiss a bunch of gross guys first and
that's better how life gives you lemons
make lemonade I forgot the sugar
lemonade is not just made of lemon it's
barely lemons it's mostly water and
sugar life's gonna give us that that's
Ike telling somebody hey you have this
crappy situation lemons now make it
better lemonade without offering them
any water or sugar the help is aku just
got fired
oh and make lemonade and get an even
better job there's no jobs available and
even if there were I mean let's be real
you just got fired no one's gonna hire
you you know what that sound desperation
no one wants to hire the guy that just
got fired or girl that just got fired
takes more muscles to frown than it does
to smile hey you know it takes more
muscles to frown than it does to smile
right okay and well maybe you should
smile more because you know it's easier
well I thought you were supposed to be
inspirational you want me to take the
easy way out
no I was just kind of I'm just trying to
say that you'll find love you stop
looking like somebody saying hey I've
been looking for Waddle my whole life
can't find him I guess I'll put the book
away and not look maybe that way I'll
find him I just can't figure it out I
stopped looking years ago and I still
can't find love hey I'm sorry I couldn't
help but overhear but I was thinking
maybe one day you and I could grab I'm
sorry I'm just gonna stop you right
there I'm not looking right now oh okay
then she's just don't get in man every
day like it's your last
this is the worst thing you can preach
to kids and I heard this as a kid
growing up all the time is just so
irresponsible the reason why people take
care of themselves and they behave and
they fall in love is is for their future
it's not for that day
what's on that dude what the hell
happened well with referred to all of
this yesterday I was on my way to spend
all my life savings at the mall and when
I got there other than just parking in
the hot side I just grabbed my cards at
the front doors ran over a few people
went that's when the cops showed up and
get this I recognized one without one
faster than give me a piggy come one
wants to go so I've swapped up to him
and just punched him in the face got
tackled ed no what are you crazy you
just ruined your life dinner it's fine
because yes here was my last day and so
as today you know I'm just going to a
drop of soap I don't even care of scared
I love what you do do what you love how
profound Oh a brilliant
it's literally saying the same thing
twice the only way that this quote is
remotely useful isn't that the transit
property you can also say eat what makes
you full be full from what you eat enjoy
where you live live where you enjoy
living one plus two equals three three
equals two plus one
hashtag transitive property always look
on the bright side this one's not that
stupid it's just they shouldn't have put
the word always in they can't always
look on the bright side I mean you can
but that's delusion something it's fun
on my girls pregnant why are we gonna do
like it's gonna ruin us hey come on
don't think like that I mean I love her
and I think she's the one but I still
think we're ready to be parents yet hey
look on the bright side you're right do
the get you don't even know if it's
yours yet I think she did kiss a lot of
frogs before you you know looks money
doesn't buy happiness last but not least
this one is actually one of my favorite
and the perfect example to use because
it's the one that everybody usually
agrees with everybody grew up with this
this quote being told to them we know
one way or another whether it's
literally a teacher or parents saying
that to you or an inspirational video or
you saw the lesson on some Disney show
or the show's horns everybody else money
is the root of all evil and although
again I agree with this one to a certain
degree I know it sounds bad but does it
make you that bad of a person to be
realistic for a change what's wrong just
found out my prom is dead what what you
saw yesterday she passed away last night
no she's still alive but she's in the
hospital right now she requires a very
very expensive surgery and I can't
afford it can barely afford rent let
alone the food on the table you know
what have you took out a loan or
something we're already paying off a
bunch of loans i guy I don't know what
to do all my life is over her life is
over
maybe not what you're not gonna believe
this but I magically found this at the
end of a rainbow and it's filled with
one and I really feel like you needed a
lot more than me there
are you serious take it I'm sure it's
enough to like pay for the surgery food
for a year rent your loans whatever
you're serious you're going to give this
yeah like whatever will make you happy
man Wow
I don't know what to say other than what
the hell is your problem
what how is this supposed to make me
happier okay money does not buy
happiness no that's supposed to be for
your grandma's build it just told you
how horrible my life is right now and
you're going to go bring me this the
root of all evil No yeah like I said I'm
a horrible person couldn't get that by
now anyway obviously I exaggerated these
examples a little bit you know for the
video my point remains the same
hopefully you picked up on it's great to
be inspired every once in a while we all
need that you can't live by these cheesy
quotes that sound perfect or expect to
follow them all the time and maybe I
could be wrong maybe there are people
that actually do live by them all the
time but I personally think that if you
really think you're living your life
perfectly you're lying to yourself
because as nice as these things might
sound nobody can live perfectly and
everybody goes through highs and low you
just have to be realistic it's fine if
you don't live every single day like
it's your last or to the fullest because
you're not wasting your time sometimes
people like to chill my last day would
still be probably staying at home
watching Netflix and it might be a waste
of time but I enjoy it and no money does
not buy true happiness but must be
realistic here and I'll use this one as
the example cuz it's the last one that
you seen and it's you know that you just
understand I actually find the realistic
quotes you know in response the cheesy
ones to be more inspiring there's that
realistic name that says you know money
does not buy happiness but I'd rather be
crying in a Ferrari with a million
dollar home rather than living on the
street yeah it doesn't sound nice or
inspirational but at least it's true and
to be honest that actually inspired me
more because it makes me appreciate what
I'm fortunate enough to have if you
actually have money and you live by the
others saying money does not buy
happiness you're taking for granted what
you're fortunate enough to have like
something that would actually bring a
lot of happiness to other people who
really need it right now and I know this
all might sound horrible and the
opposite of what you want to say is
trying to inspire someone but you know
I'm not trying to sound like a douche or
a dick I'm just being realistic I'm
being real this dick sorry I really I'm
starting to sound a dick but you know
what no I think I'm just being honest in
fact I am going to be the inspiring one
right now but in the honest way I've
been thinking for a while on that in
order to be truly happy you do have to
be a Zig
got upset other people's I know from
personal experience that if you're
always trying to please others that
defeats the whole purpose of life this
is your life
so not just okay to be a dick and be a
little selfish in fact some of the
happiest people or dick repotting
there's literally the best cake I've
ever had seriously that was awesome
there's one last slice left slope and
you guys go ahead no no no I already had
a place where should a minute to the
birthday I mean I had the biggest slice
I could impossible ticket we all move up
this wears off good we've got four
flights you get the point to see
sometimes you got to be a dick that
could be the start of my realistic
inspirational quote line thing right
next to the money can buy you happiness
mean in fact those two can go together
money can't buy you happiness money is
happiness because if you have money
money makes you rich and rich a sharp
for Richard and as we all know the
nickname for Richard is dick proving
that in order to have happiness
sometimes you got to be a dick and piss
people off because like I always quote
starting today they can't have happiness
without the penis hey okay okay I know I
already have to add this party into all
the people that I might have offended by
saying the word dick or penis too much
at the end there and also now let me
just go ahead and make things right and
just say vagina yeah gender equality