hey guys so this is not gonna be one of
my typical videos on this channel and
the reason for that is because a good
friend of mine in general Marley's
actually not her but her boyfriend
Julian gave me a call and told me that
he's gonna throw a surprise birthday
party for her and then we got all
excited and said hey let's throw a
performance for her not thinking how
long that would take to create and and
learn and then also we'd have to perform
it being that I'm not a dancer or a
performer of any kind but here's the
twist it actually became a much more
difficult challenge than this was
supposed to be a little over 24 hours we
have to create a performance create the
music for the performance learn the
performance get the props get the
costumes drive ourselves to LA get Gemma
out of the house start setting up
rehearse get more fingers so I can count
more things that we have to do that
we're not even ready for yet sorry
stressed but anyway sorry this is not my
usual type of video on this channel but
rather than posting nothing this week I
thought here's something weird sorry in
advance Jenna birthday cookies nope that
idea Oh beautifully orchestrated song do
it hate it next uh dumbest idea I've
heard so far
birthday pop-tarts love it let's go you
should be really related to Jenna so
what are Jenna's favorite things dogs
drinking games if you think Jenna what
do you think oh yeah the squeaky toy
yeah oh yeah basically the song we're
trying to make is this right here no
it's I heard it's like Santa's Bell yeah
I like the good kids here I should know
she fell into like she jumped into like
a river something cut her nose I cut my
nose from a sword at least Navidad
oh yes okay well there's some dancing in
me that makes me well great you know
apart step boys there are actually
dancers on TV America's Best Dance Crew
Derek was actually in the Jabbawockeez
show in Las Vegas so we have three
dancers so we could do something dancing
but Shawn and I never danced not in our
lives wrestling skylight 24 hours now
make a performance make a song which I
will put together a really whack British
in some way I don't stare okay we should
use figured that one song birthday
parties so figure I'm a big fan please
do not remove this your song it's only
gonna I'm gonna use a little bit that we
can use oh we can use district district
78 that is a what that's Tom's friend to
something they only bless you she keeps
on checks out in this oh yeah we have
all right call them write the music
we're gonna use a comb right now you
pick up it's a district 78 hopefully
they don't remove this video for
copyright issues there's some picture no
marbles inside no something else we
wrote an inside joke now probably make
her legs
well that one where we made up
Valentine's ruin there's a dog poop
rotamer messy something it was like a
combination I'm like does she bunch up
yeah alright so it was an inside joke
but basically we said deshi
and basically that means like a bunch of
when things are a bunch of crappy things
basically means crap but the S word but
we don't say that on my channel cuz
working Richards it basically it means
do this right now like me is this
probably you should get started
Marty Tea Party crew why not enthusiasm
if you don't feel like you I don't I
don't feel like doing a party team right
now we're making the stage jessica Lee
is some of these verses we're gonna
check out Ryan
it's been a struggle to try cut up some
beats I recorded a bunch of sounds here
listen to this I'll let you hear this
first part this is her squeaky toy you
know yeah yeah this is all I got so far
[Laughter]
wait hold on whoa you spend two hours
making music we spent four hours making
Authority Oh teen something hey Shan
Shan what we got shoulder that's it it's
a working idea it's in the works
a lot of 20 hours left we need two guys
come up with stuff I think we could do
it you got ready team party party Kony
okay party crew or a cave party boys
we're bringing the party but we need the
party on three one two three
[Applause]
we're not even bad we've got some things
that black backdrop
we've got some sweet moves sweet songs
I've got a sweet crew I think it's gonna
be pretty sweet
[Music]
honestly I don't know what's going on
hey is my tongue blue it's like 12 a.m.
we're exhausted the song is done but we
have not even half the performance and I
would say even that half that we do have
that me and Shawn barely even knowing
you have to drive to LA tomorrow morning
so we have to wake up early so we can
get there on time of to be there setup
and everything are on four we have to
leave at least by 9:00 so we have
literally nine hours until we have to
leave Vegas might not get any sleep
performance is not even close so yeah I
mean you know I guess you could say
things pretty serious exhausted right
now day two it is almost 10:00 now we're
a little late we should be going instead
of filming this part but it's today the
performances the performances today so
we have to go to LA right now
we'll see you in LA and right about yep
the door we just got here so we never
found a log for 30 so we have about an
hour and a half done
Randy they're gonna be doing the only
cool part of the boat whatever like
what's on track umbrella get this light
so we could see the light okay how you
feel today bro at all I'm not ready at
all what do you mean dude we've been
practicing all night I know it's done
already
I'm tired so Jenna Kosar here Risa's
sign see here Oh squeeze me already get
a break everyone ah
that's a Julie on three we were not just
kidding our Nelson you're being sneaky
wait what is this sit what is happening
squeeze the toy
[Music]
Wow you really just do that one you just
messed up our whole routine will do god
this was supposed to be serious and
you've just made it look like like well
like what can't see curse words in front
of jenna Marbles everybody knows that
she keeps it PG fine then what's another
word that we can say instead what about
dude okay and that's a night or we can
put it together and have Missy dude or
like do the messy Oh guys I think I got
it it's not messy to do or do the messy
it's just it's just
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
yo it's over bro good job old dance and
you know no idea we were just in the
neighborhood we're like chair nails now
he's make something real quick let's get
a suit that was kindly