and I just what obviously wasn't
expecting it so I just fell to the
ground and I was like wearing a dress I
don't know what it is about dance but
women just love it it is attractive it
is just a cow like right there at the
window cuz they just broke free are we
good we're good to go alright welcome
back to another episode off uh oh I
didn't I messed up sorry welcome back to
another episode of off the pill podcast
oh it's the wrong song I guess we'll go
with that we're struggling today we have
a special guest miss bethany mota in the
house and of course as always we have
david the moderator seat baby the
moderator see he's about to get replaced
as we have all the Leto right next to us
[Applause]
so we are like I said we were here with
Beth and thank you for being here we
didn't know were so close yeah we were
what were you just talking about before
we started rolling we were doing time Oh
something we're talking about the room
that Dietrich's made for him all right
so just to preface that how did you
bring that up well let's let's have a
little bit of a introduction you know
something for some of the audience that
doesn't know who you are me true so who
are you I
Wow introduction here we go um I am
bethany mota i am a youtuber I've been
making videos for gosh like sometimes
annoying yeah like ten years now Wow and
I do other things like music and
designing and just a lot of different
things and mainly I just do social media
stuff so you brought in over ten million
subscribers yeah no so that's very early
news almost a billion views yeah
are you um still working you were
working with not Abercrombie just arrow
pasto are you are you still working with
them or no no ended
and I think like 2015 okay but it was
like a few years and really really cool
it just I felt very out of place because
I was suddenly thrown in with all of
these like legit fashion designers to
like help me put this collection
together and I did well though it did
really well it did better than I could
have ever expected but yeah it was
definitely like crazy that I was like 18
at the time 2050 that's when I met you I
think right in Japan we met in Japan
yeah I was around that time I think even
later no I think it was way before that
oh really I think it was like it was a
while ago twelve or something mm-hmm oh
wow yeah how old were you at the time at
sixteen okay that would mean sense yeah
we got you to eat squid ink remember we
heard you're really picky I still
remember that yeah terrified I know it
wasn't that bad though you didn't like
it
it was pretty bad how did the Arab
hostel like think umm about him kind of
interested in how that kind of came
about did they just reach out to you
randomly or I well it started with just
like a casual meeting like I didn't
think anything was really gonna come of
it and we basically just did a few meet
and greets like in New York and they
were like whoa we want to work with you
more so I basically like picked a few
items from their existing line and like
put that out as like these are my top
picks and then those kind of all sold
out and then they decided they want to
do like a full on like partnership so I
launched the bethany mota clothing brand
under them and so i was in all of their
stores and online and it was really
successful it was just really fun also
to like actually design and have
something out there that everybody was
like could actually have and wear and
yeah it was a crazy experience
you're 16 I think I've never been 17 or
18 when that happened that's crazy
that's still pretty young good you're
working with a bunch of adults yeah
that's what's crazy too is like because
I'm older now I mean I'm still young but
it's like I'm more aware of what was
actually happening I feel like because
it all happened so
and because I got into it so young I
didn't really know what was going on
almost like not to say I didn't
appreciate it but kind of kind of like I
just was so unaware of like how like
one-of-a-kind that was because it was
deal that was right that was a pretty
big deal right especially at the time
for youtubers that wasn't like you
really one of the first to get a major
that's a major brand like it's a I think
right yeah no absolutely not no we don't
have that in Hawaii though I think in a
while but when I heard about I was like
oh I've heard of that before and then
like that's a major Brannen for
youtubers back then we weren't getting
those kind of deals now maybe yeah back
then it was a big deal but are you still
so you're not working with them anymore
but are you still doing you're still
doing fashions related things right uh
not like developing clothing I mean it's
something that I definitely want to do
more in the future but I think it'd just
be much different than it was back then
because I was also obviously a lot
younger so I think anything I put out
now is just gonna be like a little older
but I haven't been designing I've just
been like like I still do fashion
related content but just not like
designing clothes that's your main focus
to look back to making more videos
because you did take a look a break for
a bit right yeah I took like I feel like
I took a lot of little breaks and then I
took a pretty big break most recently
and I think it's just like it started
probably end of 2014 when I was kinda
just like I am so burnt out on this
thing because I was going hard for years
and I honestly had no social life like I
didn't have any friends I was also
homeschooled when I started making
videos so getting into it when I first
started first couple years it was like
three videos a week Wow and no one on my
team so it's just me filming editing
everything and I didn't socialize so my
question is if you're a homeschooled how
did you like come across YouTube and
knowing that you could make videos and
stuff like that
it was actually because I was
home-schooled that I feel like I was
more aware of it because I was home all
the time and so it was like always
online and then I stumbled across it I
feel like actually if I was in public
school at the time I probably wouldn't
have cared as much about it and
definitely wouldn't have made videos I
think was just because I was just bored
and so I started watching them and then
decide to make them also being so shy
growing up I think if I was in public
school there's no way I would have even
started a channel but it was because I
felt like I was kind of like hiding in a
way and then this is like me being able
to talk to the world from like my own
room that's true I feel like back in the
day especially like I don't know if this
is true or not but I feel like a lot of
the older youtubers people who start a
long time ago or more like shy and
introverted people who fall in the space
to express themselves and it's kind of
changed to like the opposite yeah I
noticed that I think there back then
there was a lot of it was mostly I think
introverted right people that felt like
this was kind of their only outlet to
actually express themselves in ways that
they would never do in front of people
right and then now it's uh I mean I
don't want to say it but it sounds like
it was like like the losers the loser
kids who are kind of on it and it kind
of made it big and then now the cool
kids are here you know like the Logan
Paul is like tall buff looking
good-looking dudes and like you know we
weren't that back so we found a space
where we were like safe but now the cool
kids took over do you feel like it kind
of helped your person like help develop
your personality oh absolutely
like even comparing Ben to now my first
video I was so awkward I mean I'm still
awkward but back then it was so bad like
I was whispering in the video because I
didn't want anyone to hear me talk like
in my house and then I also was wearing
glasses back then because I was too
afraid to wear contacts so every video
I'd have to like take my glasses off and
just be like school win team just so I
could look in the viewfinder and like
see what was going on so awkward and so
scared but don't you think that's what
made you loveable though like to the
people who really like loved you they're
like oh my god I relate she saw quick I
think that's like why we watch people
like we watched certain people that we
kind of
yourselves in so I feel like a lot of
girls that were my age could relate to
so much of what was going on with me
back then cuz I was just really trying
to figure it out kind of all over the
place
well what's getting back to the just
because I brought it up earlier but
didn't continue about the story that you
were telling us about oh yeah that Dom
so you're dating d-trix it's not a
secret right it's very public I lived
with d-trix for a long time and now he's
actually the reason why I moved out to
LA for like a few years but uh yeah so
Dom Dietrich's is currently what she was
he on So You Think You Can Dance
they think you dance so he was gonna be
here but he will be here another time he
said well I don't know how that story
came basically the night that you had
your ninja milk release party Dom held a
small little get-together like a
barbecue at his house and so like a lot
of the rhpc guys went and we kind of
like hanging out he showed us around and
then he was like hey you guys want to
see this this room I made for Beth and
we made a room he made a room yeah yeah
what was the occasion well let you take
it away cuz you know this best
so basically Dom made a room for me it
was for Christmas because we have this
rule with like any gifts that we give
whether it's like birthday or Christmas
that we have to make them and it can't
be like store-bought so I made him like
this light-up sign and I like used power
tools for the first time I was really
proud of myself but he made me this room
that was basically he recreated my
childhood room and so he did all this
research apparently like looking at what
my room looked like and like watched all
my old videos when I had like hot pink
walls so he painted this wall hot pink
and then created this like stitch mural
cuz lilo and stitch is like my favorite
Disney movie and then he had these
pictures of me I like walk in and the
first thing I see are these letters at
the top of the window that just say
little Beth and then there's like all of
these pictures of me as a baby but he
photoshopped himself into them so it's
like a little
babies together agreed that it is creepy
like it is I thought is there though
totally I was honestly in tears cuz I
was like this is the most thoughtful
thing anyone has ever done is it creepy
a little bit but yeah so and then he
like screenshotted like a picture or
like a screenshot from my draw my life
video and framed it which was really
cute they're just like pictures of my
family everywhere and then my two
childhood crushes which were dylan and
Cole Sprouse were like okay they're
funny now I still don't want one
otherwise none but they're twee hazard
bunny yeah yeah one of them like works
in a brewery has like like Disney are
they from Disney yeah you know exactly
Cody Brenda song what's it I don't
remember
suite suite life of zack & cody oh yes i
heard of that those guys grew up and
they're like yeah well I mean that's
like yeah it was super thoughtful and
yeah it's a really really cute room that
he got like this old TV with like eh v8
why can't I speak VHS tapes so it was
really really sweet
I was crying how long have you guys been
dating uh we basically two years we met
three years ago and then we dated for
like almost a year and then broke up for
like six months and then got back
together now it's been like a little
over a year since we got back together
yeah you guys are super in love thing to
say Oh life I mean I grew up from a
family that's not really touchy-feely
but good but when I see you guys
together
yes a very loving person he is he's such
a passionate lover I could tell well you
guys have met before because I mean like
we're just talking about this earlier
but you actually sing and I didn't know
that at first but you you guys came here
I don't know if you guys work together
or not but I know Dom came here as well
to work with David oh yeah we did one
song you guys made a song yeah Dom Dom I
think you guys both wrote it or dumb
dawn wrote that one okay it's very sweet
song mhm and I mean I was I've always
told Beth this but I think you know
she's one of the most underrated singers
on YouTube I think she could have done
music if she didn't do Beauty but you're
doing that right now right yeah a little
bit I think it's just one of those
things that I've dabbled in so much and
I really want to do but it's like I'll
do it I'll like I put out a song like
five years ago or something and then I
was like I don't know it's
I'm just so unsure and also I just want
to like I know it's one it's one of
those things or it's like almost waiting
for the right time but I also kind of
just wanted to perfect it more before I
start putting it out because I just
always want to give people something
that I feel is of substance and that I'm
proud of and if I feel like it's not
really there for me then I don't really
want to share it that's kind of like you
you do you should sort of like that too
like I was I was more like that and then
now it's just I make podcasts oh no I
mean I mean we still we still have
projects like that but I yeah I wanted
to be able to just do things that are
like I don't know free not having like
so much thought into every single thing
I still want to do those things as well
and I feel like you're the same way but
like what is your main focus right now
because you you do so many things that
you're doing your videos you know like
you said you were doing the the clothing
the fashion thing and then
you sing when she trying to dance to for
a little bit obviously you learning
dance if you're living well you're not
living with Dom but since you guys are
dating cuz all he does is dance and
every moment if he will be in the car
and he'll just start like yeah he does I
started doing a lot of freestyle dance
you it's really bad uh no I haven't
really been dancing you would think like
we don't really dance together he's
actually taught me a few things and he's
like choreographed little things for us
that we never like finished but dancing
is something that I kinda really only
went for with Dancing with the Stars
like that was the most I've ever really
pursued that I kind of wanted to pursue
it a little more after the fact but yeah
I don't know I think it was fun but it's
definitely not something that I see
myself doing like it being amazing fun
you were like I thought you were a
dancer from that I mean you're pretty
good I mean I took dance classes growing
up and then once I got the offer for
Dancing with the Stars I was like I
really want to do it cuz dance is always
something that I really enjoyed but just
never really went for and yeah I think I
definitely surprised myself maybe was
also just like having such a good
teacher but I definitely found myself
doing things that I didn't know I could
do especially because it's so many
different styles it's like every week
it's like you'll have salsa then you'll
have like jive then you'll have like
contemporary and so I just became more
aware of my body which was really cool
but yeah I think I kind of fell in love
with dance a little bit during that show
it's just something that is kind of cool
to have like I think I could incorporate
it into certain things in the future but
definitely wouldn't be like my main
thing how long ago was that when you
were on that show
that was 2014 I think would you say that
you're your excitement about dance got
you more interested in dawn it was about
the time right yeah I thought about that
I don't think so
maybe she maybe it was like a
subconscious like wow I'm really loving
dance good this guy is a dancing that's
actually attractive that's actually what
made us like hang come together yeah
because it wasn't like a YouTube
YouTube creator summit like one of the
after parties and I was just really into
like anytime I would be at an
after-party or anything I'd always be
salsa dancing I don't really know how to
do it but I enjoy it and so I just
remember there was like this crowd of
people and I was like who here is gonna
salsa dance with me tonight and I kind
of knew you said that no I just thought
it I thought that every time I would
like go to a party I was like who here
looks like they would salsa dance with
me and so I knew he was a dancer
obviously and so we just started salsa
dancing and then we just like dancing
with my instant the attraction that was
actually the first time that I was like
oh he's cute because I met him before
that at the Tony Robbins conference and
I just he was like cool as I go cool
cool but isn't really intuitive see the
skills yeah I didn't see those moves I
was like see the advantage of being a
dancer because I don't know what it is
about dance but women just love it it is
attractive it is and yeah it's
attractive when someone knows how to
move their body mm-hmm well Paco can
dance is how's that working not any more
I used to as a breakdancer b-boy oh
really
Dom did but he got more into like uh it
was a go choreo I guess Dom's well
versed in in dance
David and I was variants at all I'm the
worst dancer I'm too stiff like I look
like a would going back to what David
was saying like you're actually a good
singer and David doesn't just give out
compliments he's very blunt actually
borderline mean to people that don't
know how David is like talented people
yeah like they will be straight up and
he won't say you're good unless you all
unless you really are but he does tell
I've asked David before I was like can
everyone sing and what was your answer
to that all honesty you want me to be
honest or happy off be completely honest
can anyone sing or learn to sing yes yes
they can learn to sing but
but I do believe some people are born
with natural talent and some people will
never have that will never sound good
even if even if they learn they won't
have that I think weird that but with
dance David and our that will with dance
that's what I'm saying like I you look
like a dancer when you dance even he
looks like a dancer when he dances but
when David and I dance where that where
those people who just can't wait I think
I can no what I'm saying is you can
learn but you'll never be you never look
I'll never be a d-trix yeah that's for
sure
wait so you're saying so like I said
some people that are really great
singers that it's natural someone who
worked really hard could never like
attain that sort of I'm gonna disappoint
a lot of people no but to a certain
level it's true right I think that they
come down to just their natural speaking
voice that sounds better I don't think
it's about the speaking voice for me I
think it's more about like so the way
that I would explain is you know you
find young kids who are amazing singers
right you guys agree with that you'll
see like turn on on those TV shows
they're naturally gifted they did not
learn how to do that because they were
taught they were just born that way and
I think there are a lot of people like
that in many different fields like
including dance singing or intelligence
right I think like there are people who
are born with it but then I do think
that you could work on anything you can
get good to a certain point but I don't
know if you could achieve greatness that
makes sense I think it's true it's just
like being good at basketball right like
I could be the like I could work my ass
off and I'll still be five eight and
never in the NBA and even there are five
eight players shorter people who can
dunk I think no matter how much I would
have work like that I could come haha I
can done there's a basketball game that
Ryan and I are playing and those right
after the game we're kind of sitting
down just like relaxing and then this
one Asian kid just like Palm the ball
ran up and dunked and he was like a
little bit shorter and the first thing
me and Ryan did was we stood up
really he's shorter than us but like
possible so I mean why did I bring that
up
Oh about Island musical time yeah and
then in for dance like you could dance
because it's kind of natural for you I
was saying like no matter how much David
and I train we'll never
we could get good to let the point our
cap I think I get it yeah but like you
have like this high cap for like dance
and singing mm-hmm and I don't know
things that you I mean I would never do
that show let's put it that way
Dancing with the Stars you'd never do it
never there's got to be some great
incentive for me to embarrass myself
that way but also I think taking this
and in another route is like you are a
very kind of introverted kid it sounds
like but you have all these natural
talents within you that what did you
kind of always just know what's there or
was it just like oh this seems
interesting and you pick it up very
easily I like with the singing I feel
like I was always singing when I was
younger and I just remember remember
like getting mad when people in the car
would sing with me and they were like
off-key eight-year-old me so mad about
that that means you have really good so
we're saying is a pitch and like I think
I mean this is a question I like to ask
a lot of musicians and singers is who
and your family is musically gifted so
usually when I ask my musician friends
it's either their mom dad both grandpa
grandma it's always like that so I was
wondering if if that applies to you as
well maybe an uncle or not it's like
gifted and actually a lot my mom is and
my grandpa and then a lot of my cousins
is a mom so my mom sign gotcha yeah so
it's it's true my theory is still
correct see it so it is something you're
kind of born with and it is to I mean to
a certain degree it's gotta be genetic
right mikage in your genes because I
mean I it's gonna sound bad but like
there's certain ethnicities that ever
like my majority of that ethnicity can
sing you know I mean like I think the
majority Filipinos but a lot of
Filipinos can sing a lot like black
most of them I know can at least sound
better than your average person yeah I
don't know if that's true or not I might
be making stuff up but how by people I
know yeah are all at least somewhat
decent like have nice either it's a nice
deep voice or like they came to actually
sing or something
as a musician I will verify that okay so
I'm not being the truth I find the
african-americans Filipinos generally
speaking the darker you I don't know
what it is I don't know what it is I
think it's maybe the the their vocal
cords their structure darker - yeah well
pretty I don't know now we're just
basing it on racist on it but it's it's
a great root of thing it's a positive
stereotype yeah even I've heard some
like even you know African Americans are
not greats they say that I'm so bad and
they sing and I'm like they're so good
you're such a liar like you're just all
really good at singing or they have a
high cap for that right they could learn
to sing right yeah and it sucks being
Filipino and not being able to sing well
you're only part you know what I've
never heard you sing because I can
that's what they all say have you tried
yeah yeah let's hear something no next
question that was a nice tone you next
question okay
well now we know so you're gonna be a
singer dancer you're basically made to
be a pop star
you got the fashion a little bit of
everything what is in like not joking
around what is your next thing you want
to do uh I mean honestly the music is
one thing that I've just recently
started taking more seriously and I
think it's because I've been so scared
with it for so long that I just kind of
have been diving deeper into it recently
and yeah so definitely music stuff and
then just kind of getting back into
YouTube again I think that I needed to
take a break to kind of just reset and I
think I felt this almost this pressure
of also who people kind of perceived me
to be for so long especially getting
into it so young that was
kind of one of the biggest challenges I
faced was as I got older was kind of
breaking from these ideas of how people
saw me which definitely I was never fake
like that was 100% me at the time but
then as I started getting older and then
I did start having more of a social life
and did start like kind of exploring
myself more it didn't necessarily add up
with what people were used to seeing so
yeah I just kind of needed time to take
a break from all of that and it's kind
of like what you said is like I want
that kind of freedom back of not feeling
so much pressure of everything that I
post has to be like the most perfect
thing in the world right and just the
fact that I could actually just post is
enough and as long as I actually enjoyed
it that's more than enough because I
definitely got to a point where I wasn't
enjoying it and it was just a big stress
ball I can relate to that 100% like I
definitely have seen your vlogs this is
like a wall aback but just like knowing
you outside of YouTube because I met you
before I seen your videos and then I
want to go check out your videos I was
like oh that's interesting you're a lot
more you know like like myself a lot
more like energetic than you would be
like talking here and it is hiring and
especially for getting older since you
started at what age was that 13 yeah 13
you're basically one of those you're
like one of those Disney kids right who
was trapped in the same like hey guys
you know like one of those things and
then not that you were like that I'm
just saying the Disney no but when
you're trapped into this thing you just
it's it's exhausting because you grow up
everybody grows up and to a certain
degree you just you need to have that
switch and people aren't gonna like it
but it has to happen look at Miley Cyrus
and it works yeah okay
well oh we are at the sheshe brake part
of our show so I guess we'll be right
back
[Music]
and we're back and before we get back
actually I forgot in the beginning of
the episode but thank you and child to
road for these mics because they gave it
to us for free and the road cast and the
road caster so again thank you to Road
for all your needs for things that are
audio actually don't know is it
it's just audio Road there's a lot of
audio yeah for your audio needs it's
like a their slogan oh I'm reading it
like an ad for your audio needs Road
take the high road they could use that
they don't have to use that alright and
now we're really back okay do we want to
start with likes we have a we don't
always get a lot of questions from
people but when we put out your name and
saying you're gonna be in the podcast we
got a lot of questions so you want to go
through some of those yeah we have
people haven't hurt a lot of people
don't even know that you started up
again yeah yeah so I think they're kind
of curious about what you're doing cool
yeah we got one here what have you been
doing since not posting videos we talked
about that but I mean that's that's what
they're interested in we where we can
take that too is a lot of youtubers or
even content creators have been taking
breaks lately they've been saying like
you know I need to I've been getting
burnt out or I need to take care of my
mental health and stuff and maybe this
is something that you vibe with and
that's something that you felt at the
time or maybe you feel a little
differently so maybe we can get an idea
and like pick your brain about that so
kind of y-you know you took a break and
what do you been doing yeah I mean I
feel like the YouTuber break thing has
definitely become like a thing for a lot
of people especially in the past like
two years I it's almost like when I
first saw that other people were doing
it it was kind of comforting I was like
okay I'm not the only one that's like
experiencing this and having these same
feelings coz when it happened to me I
feel like no one had ever talked about
that at that point or at least I had
never heard anyone talk about that and
so I felt like it's something going
with me that that like I'm suddenly
feeling all of this stuff like mentally
with my craft and yeah cuz when it first
happened to me it was I think I didn't
realize that maybe I needed to take a
break but it's been incredibly helpful
for me I think just to kind of distance
myself a little bit and work on myself
because for me at least I feel like I
was so in it that I completely a little
bit like kind of lost a part of me and I
wasn't keeping up with myself so I
wasn't like my full self for my audience
and I feel like they definitely saw that
and yeah so I think when I first noticed
it was like 2014-2015 when I was just
like I need to like step away and even
doing that was so hard because people
want things like all the time and it was
really hard to kind of step away from
that and I feel like a lot of people
were confused because I never really
liked old people why I took a break but
it was kind of just what I needed to do
for my own mental health and just kind
of checking in with myself and and just
kind of like reconnecting with the world
a little bit and appreciating things
outside of social media that helped so
much because I used to find myself
almost like getting anxious if I was
like if I was somewhere really cool and
experiencing something if feeling this
need to have to post about it and if I
didn't I felt like dang it I didn't do
that and I'd be upset about it and like
Who am I getting upset that I didn't
show this to everybody yeah and I I
could have had an amazing time but I
didn't because I was so worried about
posting and I think everyone can relate
to that even you know people like girls
who were worried about impressing a guy
it's like oh I didn't post this thing
that I went to this party so I'm so mad
about that instead of just literally
enjoying it and not worrying about
having to post it because it just kind
of takes you out of the moment so that
was one of the most valuable things I've
learned is to actually just kind of
enjoy life and now it's easier to kind
of get back into it because I feel much
more myself than I was what are some
other ways that you can
said you were working on yourself
outside of you know creating creating
YouTube videos like what what were some
other things that you did for yourself
besides not posting on social media some
activities or like what does that mean
to you like to that you're working on
yourself is something taking a break
even like what does that mean yeah some
people may go out to a meditation
retreat or see you they know yeah it's
huge right now some people may just
focus on a relationship or some people
may go traveling like what or maybe do
nothing right like what what are some
things that you you did to kind of get
to that place where you feel free uh I
definitely didn't go on any retreats
yeah I feel like I didn't do any of that
like meditation which meditation is
great and I've tried it and it's cool I
just didn't really do any of that stuff
I feel like I just more so dove into
myself and asked myself questions about
like kind of where I was at with myself
and how I felt about myself and then I
started to realize that also because I
started making video so young I think I
I know at one point I felt this pressure
of like my appearance in my body at one
point because like everything that I do
is so like it's always been so like
fashion and that kind of focused so
obviously like my appearance was a part
of that and I think that I let that
stuff kind of tarnish my view of my like
self if that makes sense so I kind of
did a lot of like almost just like kind
of doing like I don't know how to
explain it more so just like thinking
about it and in understanding myself and
what made me kind of get farther away
from myself and it kind of had to love
myself again and love myself more than I
ever had before which then I think it
comes into like a whole other thing it's
not even about youtube as much that's
just kind of like life stuff that I
think everybody on some level at some
point in life experiences it's like I
feel like I didn't fully love myself at
that point and then kind of feeling like
I had to please everybody at that point
in my life wasn't helping the fact that
I wasn't really loving myself and so I
needed to step away from
everything to figure out how to get that
love back for myself and it just came
down to honestly what helped me is like
being a kid again and like just being
curious about life in a way that I feel
like I kind of got jaded to a lot of
things in life kind of what I was saying
earlier were when I was younger I didn't
realize what was going on to the point
that it was happening so much that I
think I failed to even be as grateful as
I could have been and that was one of
the most valuable things that I've
learned in like the past few years and
during taking a break is just how to be
amazed by life again and be excited
about living that was that's beautiful
it's great no I think a lot of people
need to hear that yeah and I think
because you're in the beauty space in
particular you know beauty is all about
kind of like an outward parent your
outward appearance right now if you
write down beauty in the superficial
form but like you know it's going back
to what you said about rediscovering
yourself and figuring out like Who am I
first before I can start putting on the
makeup and the outfits right I think
it's it's pretty interesting that you
brought that up because never thought of
it that way yeah and I think that's good
for other creators to hear like you said
at the time I guess 2015 you said you
kind of took your break it wasn't the
same thing as like this past year right
wherever you hear everybody is like oh
I'm burnt out I need to take a break it
definitely must have been hard to have
to like you had so much success and so
much momentum that it's not an easy
thing like even even now for me this is
like my version of a break but I'm still
doing stuff it's I can't even imagine
like I just just getting myself to this
point was so difficult like how did you
how did you convince yourself to be like
okay this is the best decision for my
life to take a break when you have all
this momentum going for you you have a
successful channel that's bringing in
revenue and you know at any point if you
do stop you'll still have your hardcore
fans but you do know if you do stop
there's a most youtubers know that
that's like deadly to your career right
yeah so how did you get to the point
where you convinced yourself or where
you add a breaking
point where you just said I have to do
it it was kind of both because I think
that I was continuing to try to put
stuff out when I was already feeling
that way and I just felt like it wasn't
as good as it could have been if I was
like in a better place so I knew for
that reason that I probably needed to
like take a break and it was really hard
to step away but I think it was a bit of
a feeling of just like I know that I
could be happier and I know that I could
be in a better place so maybe I just
need to to listen to how I feel right
now and take the action that I need to
and also it's like I feel like at the
end of the day I don't really have
anything to lose because as long it's so
cheesy your truth you know like I'm so
happy like I'm so happy with life in a
way that I'm like wasn't back then and
so I wouldn't change any of that and and
I knew that obviously it was gonna
change things if I wasn't uploading as
consistently especially if like there
are people girls my same age that are
posting exactly what I'm posting that
are more consistent than me obviously if
I'm not keeping up with that then people
would prefer to watch them but I think
was just learning to be okay with that
and not letting that it was almost more
of an ego thing and I feel like once I
let once I kind of understood my ego and
I was able to control that it helped so
much because I was like I would I had
these fears that didn't even really
exist but it was only because of my ego
mm-hmm fears of like other people
surpassing you like the girls your age
and stuff like that yeah talking about
yeah okay that makes sense that is a
tough thing to do I don't think
necessarily if you haven't really been a
creator it's hard to explain that fear
yeah a lot of people when you tell them
oh I'm burnt out or like recently like
Lilly as mentioned and other youtubers
have came on and said oh you know what
they're burnt out they gotta take a
break I see all these comments are like
oh wow must be tough being a millionaire
who's famous and they don't really
understand you know or they think it's a
lot easier to do what we do to a certain
degree where even if it wasn't easy
though it's like everybody knows
themselves better
and anyone else right so I think that
part of it for other creators I think
they understand now like that's
everybody can burn out yeah for people
who don't have these kind of who aren't
in these lucky fortunate situations
where some people just can't take those
breaks
what would you say that those people I
mean I mean it's hard I know it I'm not
putting you on the spot cuz I I try and
think about that too
because I understand what you're saying
but I feel like it's hard for me to
preach that to people who can't afford
to like you know that my job is too much
right I'm burnt out I need this job but
I have to do it how would we I'm just
trying to see for myself how do you
reach out to those people and give them
the same advice absolutely yeah I think
that there are ways that everyone can do
it to be completely honest I think that
if I don't think I really what I did in
my situation is I completely stepped
away but I don't think that I really had
to do that I think that there definitely
was ways for me to continue what I was
doing while being smart in accomplishing
what I did in the past few years as far
as like myself personal growth I think I
could have done that simultaneously
while staying consistent but I didn't do
that I think it's because I was just so
in fear I was so afraid and so confused
that I just wanted to completely shut it
all off but I don't think that was
really necessary I think that's just
what I felt that I needed to do because
I look back on it and and yes I did take
that break but part of me is like you
know maybe I should have just at least
stayed a little more consistent and and
worked on myself so I think there's a
lot that you can do even if you can't
just completely stutter away yeah I
think it's what I found to be the most
valuable is literally just being able to
be honest with myself and be just
transparent about where I am personally
and just really diving into yourself and
that's kind of the part that can be hard
for people too is you know it's it's
being open with yourself about like what
your fears are what you're afraid of
what it is because I think also the
biggest problem is that I didn't want to
admit that it was my ego and I think I
could have figured all that out while
still being consistent I just kind of
chose to step away okay with
it's good advice I'm wondering did you
have like what is your circle look like
your circle of friends I know you worked
with you work with your dad he's been
pretty integral in your career like did
you have friends to kind of like help
you get through this I know you're
dating DOM but was there anybody else in
your circle or was it your family that
kind of helped you come to this
realization and kind of eliminating your
ego yeah I mean I definitely surrounding
myself with friends is helpful and I've
done that it's also nice just to like
like I said just be more in the moment
with people because I feel like I wasn't
always the best at doing that so yeah
definitely
just making more time for friends and my
family has always been really supportive
my dad has been there since the first
video so I always like go to him for
that kind of stuff as well because he's
always very encouraging and also kind of
helps me remember like why I started
doing it all in the first place and it
wasn't for obviously like we didn't know
that any of the success was even
possible at that point like back then
it's like we didn't even know that you
could make a career out of it and so he
always kind of reminds me of that like
the little me that started it so yeah
and when you started you were you're
pretty young so like like how do you
balance like your dad like the
relationship between your dad as someone
who's integrating your business and then
also your dad like it's kind of it can
get a little weird right I mean yeah I
think it was definitely it was
definitely more challenging when we
lived together because it was hard to
separate the two but once I kind of
moved out and like had my own place and
all of that it honestly got way easier I
think there's something about it's like
I don't really want to talk about
business over dinner you know it's like
you want to separate the two so I think
that's the only time that it was really
challenging but everything else it's
like he's always just down for whatever
I want to do and just backing me up and
whatever my decision is for whatever it
may be but yeah he's definitely I got to
I got to know him
better than you actually on the a couple
of tours that we've done like a lot of
times you'd be like you and your dad and
your mom yeah and basically be with your
mom and we just be hanging out with your
dad and I guess that's kind of speaks to
like what you were saying like you were
kind of like to yourself kind of thing
but he would constantly be like he has
good ideas he's constantly like pitching
he's like he's always coming to music
not even for you he's like hey what if
we did this what if you did this and he
keep pitching ideas so I think I know
what you mean when you say like once you
weren't in the household because if he's
constantly I don't know if he did the
same thing to you but to me I was like
these are good but if I had that every
single day like morning and night I
think that would be pretty yeah it could
be a lot I mean it's all great intention
like oh he's right he's great yeah he
definitely yeah I think kind of tying it
back to what David said in the first
half where music can be tied to like
your parents and stuff so in the aspect
of like how hard you were grinding and
like possibly like you know you burnt
yourself out and stuff like it sounds
like maybe you got that from your dad
just that that work ethic and yeah I'm
just curious as to what like what does
he do
besides you know before like you were
doing YouTube instead of farmer yeah he
worked on dairy farms cuz we grew up
like central California so it's like
only dairy farms like no shopping malls
los Manos our from Fresno cuz like
basically if we wanted to go to any
shopping mall we'd have to either go to
Modesto at Fresno cuz there's like
there's nothing in the town we got a
target and everybody was like really
stoked about I was like my where I'm
from Hilo small small town yeah yeah
super small town so he would just work
on like electricity and like building
dairies and he owned his own dairy
business so he was like knew how to be a
business owner but yeah I was all like
dairy farms up until I asked him to be
my manager do you know to milk a cow I
don't I've been around a lot of cows but
I never never tried to milk when I had a
lot of pet cows too because we lived
though isn't it
you have to you know hey what do you
mean I mean I was a farmer
I guess dairy everyone talked about
their pets in there also if you're no
they just they went to another farm they
just went through the other I mean I I
don't know I'm family members who had
college but they had them for different
reasons
yeah we we had cuz we lived literally on
a dairy farm one of the farms that he
worked on and so we just had like a
bunch of cows I remember one night like
two o'clock in the morning there was a
bunch of noise outside of the house and
I woke up and there was just like cows
like I opened the window and just a cow
like right there at the window cuz they
just broke free and so your sleep
surrounding our honey I grew up with
cows too all around me so it's like that
constant I know I can I can just smell
it
I can smell where you live manure yeah
do you have any siblings
everyone's sister younger older she is
older she's five years older and she has
two beautiful daughters what does she
think about your YouTube career and she
actually started a channel like shortly
after I did and she was going with it
for a while I don't know if she's still
posting on it but yeah she got into it
for a second - it's funny cuz I think
she might have made fun of me right in
the beginning when I started and then
she was like I'm gonna get on this - in
what way like what are you doing yeah do
you think you are
yeah I feel like everybody yeah I got
about so much flesh in the beginning
yeah she was probably had public school
like my sister makes YouTube videos
public school yeah okay and then you
were saying on the break that you you
chose to go do private schooling yeah
and your sister chose the public route
why did you choose private school
instead of public I just was I just
never really liked public school and my
parents just gave us a choice or like if
you want to be homeschooled you can so I
was like okay I'm
doing that I just felt like I just felt
like I was wasting time like in between
like if I cuz if I had it my way I was
like I just want to go to school do all
the work no recess no lunch just like
let me do all the work and then go home
and that's what homeschooling was is it
still like five hours a day or well well
how long at school yeah how does that
work how does the homeschooling system I
never asked this to someone before but
I'm does it yeah what do you wake up at
a certain time do you just do York when
you want um your yeah you basically do
whenever you want
that was a problem though is I feel like
it definitely taught me a lot about like
managing my own stuff and like having a
schedule a little bit though because
actually not maybe not because I started
to get in this habit where I would do
all my work for the week like the night
before I had to go in because basically
I still had a teacher so I'd meet with a
teacher once a week and I would give her
all of my work for that week and then if
there were any tests then I would do
those tests and so basically it's like
if I had to meet with her every Tuesday
I would literally leave all my work for
like Monday you'd procrastinate which is
the same thing as every other student in
public school really I would do my work
as soon like in class if I could like
homework and stuff like that just so I
could like have fun at home it was just
so I don't have to worry about it
I was opposite well anyway that's in
know you had a I thought it was your
parents that I you know I don't know
much yeah well I mean I would like
supervise I guess or like held me here
and there but yeah it's like I had an
actual teacher technically got it so
with a teacher like go to your home or
you me now at this place and there's
other homeschooled kids or is it just
like one thing she's you would like go
in and there were like all the teachers
and their cubicles really interesting so
did you have any friends then any we
kind of talked about it but yeah I did I
had friends from public school and then
also once I became homeschooled for a
couple years that's when I was in dance
class and then I took theatre for a
little bit too so I made new friends
through that well do you still keep in
touch with them or
um not so much I mean a few like when I
go back home but yeah not not as much as
I should
well that was one long Twitter question
do you have any scary fan encounters oh
it's a pretty consistent question yeah
yeah hurry
scary or just like interesting less
interesting creepy yeah okay a really
good pitch that was a good pitch the way
that she said yeah you got some okay hmm
well I have one that's like weird to
talk about now a curious no um this guy
a while back this was probably I don't
even remember May 2013 2014 this guy
that watched my videos he was a lot
older than me maybe by like twenty or
thirty years he came to a couple
meet-and-greets and it was just like
strange scenarios but then the weirdest
one was I got a like a package or like a
letter to my house
this is when I was still living with my
family and we opened it up in there was
like this USB thing and so we put it in
the computer and it was the video of
this guy and he just started saying like
all this stuff and he was just like so I
have your address and like I'm going to
tell you how I found it and he like
pulled up the listing of like my house
and it was like clicking through the
photos for some reason I'm like yes I
know what my house looks like photos of
your house well like has he found the
listing of the house mine and so just
like started clicking through it and
just like was like you should like just
basically he was telling me like I
should be more careful with my personal
information cuz like it could really for
him he was like it could affect your
well-being and I was like you're so
right
and just like said some like honestly
weird stuff and it really freaked me out
and from that point I was like I can't
live here anymore is that why you moved
um yeah that was one of the reasons oh
so this is a little more recent then not
like when you first started no well yeah
this was like probably four or five
years ago yeah what about your your
parents are not there anymore in that at
that location at the gun oh no we all
moved from there yeah so that was
probably the most like creepy weird
situation yeah
and then I've just other than that it's
just been like little mishaps here and
there mm-hmm well what about like weird
interactions because you do a lot of
meeting greets and stuff
what's the weirdest thing somebody said
to you uh I got proposed to a lot but I
don't like seriously though very weird
no not I mean with candy not like
legitimate I mean has has anyone ever
gone
oh you're Wow you're you don't look like
how you look in your videos all the time
I get that all the time yeah
but shorter that too yeah it's
interesting because people see and I'm
sure it's even worse for you because
you're in the beauty space right well I
don't know I don't know is it worse oh
do they come up to you and be like oh
you look good and you're in your videos
they say they say I've not seen that
before it's just like they don't mean it
as insulting they're like oh you're a
lot taller or oh yeah you look a lot
skinnier in your videos or something
like I've gotten all of those I've
gotten that too I don't know if it's the
same for like you cuz you're a girl
no I the only one I've gotten is height
is like a lot Oh really like oh wow
you're a lot shorter in person you take
that as a dis or I mean I yeah not so
much anymore but back then it was like I
was really I really hated being so sore
I hated being five three and so when
people would say that I'm like thank you
for reminding me
but that was probably the only thing
there was one time at a meet-and-greet
this wasn't like she didn't say anything
maybe it was the lack of her saying
something that made it happen is like
she basically wanted me to give a
piggyback ride but I didn't know that
she like maybe she told me but I didn't
hear it cuz I was like really loud so I
was like this girl she comes up she just
jumps on my back and
what that's that's assault she jumped on
my back and I just what obviously wasn't
expecting it so I just fell to the
ground and I was like wearing a dress
fall to the floor and she immediately
just like gets back up and runs away and
that was yeah so embarrassed
I felt so bad press charges against her
that's why she ran she was so happy like
she doesn't she just wanted like a cute
picture how could you I know that's
funny if she's listening you're
remembered now have you ever gotten any
crazy gifts cuz I know I know from what
I've heard females tend to get like more
extravagant gifts from fans than males
like I have a friend she got like an
iPhone Oh
have you ever gotten anything like that
no any jewelry appeal box I used to yeah
I did I mostly got like stitch stuffed
animals because she loves one stitch
yeah and a lot of handmade stuff mostly
but never anything really drives me a
lot of food yeah we got another Twitter
question here from Selena what's what's
the thing that you're most proud of
honestly today I was really proud that I
got your like super early
I was really yeah you're one of those I
got here ten for LA that's like being an
hour early it really la people are
always late so much that I literally was
like should I not go in it's like 10
minutes early maybe I should wait yeah
that's very proud of us but other than
that other than that uh most proud of
like that's a tough yeah like in what
genre of life like whatever you want it
to be yeah let's say career do you feel
like um do you feel like you're
successful now I do
you didn't when you were actually making
videos um you had to yeah yeah
definitely
I think I also feel it like in a
different way now where I just feel like
I I mean I feel like I know a little
more like I still have obviously so much
to learn but I feel like I I feel
success in a way of like I guess what I
understand and what I'm aware of now and
like just kind of how I define success
too because I think like how I defined
success in the past was maybe a little
different than I define it now but as
far as like my like biggest
accomplishment or like things I'm most
proud of I think we I think your answer
is great like yeah yeah like I think I'm
definitely proud of everything that I've
done career-wise like obviously I'm like
whoa that was that's really cool I did
all that especially starting so young
and not knowing that any of that was
possible and like building something at
this age and also just doing something
that I never thought I would do cuz I
just never saw myself as that person and
even the people around me never saw me
as that person so I'm definitely really
proud of that and I definitely felt that
success but I'm also really proud of how
much I've evolved as a person and how I
also define success now because I feel
like it's just a lot healthier and more
fulfilling that's a good answer to a
very broad question yeah and if you
didn't if you didn't feel successful I
was gonna say you should because you're
on this podcast no Ryan Oh successful
this is a big accomplishment way to ruin
a real moment all right well we're
pretty much at the end of our show so I
guess thank you again for being so real
with us and for being here yeah of
course it's the opposite way around it's
it's our honor that you're here is there
anything you want to plug right well
she's getting back in well yeah what are
you so you are getting back into YouTube
yeah okay
YouTube stuff so like stuff check out
Beth's channel what's your channel
bethenny must hurt it used to be more
embarrassing yeah what was it before it
wasn't your name
it was Mack Barbie o7 Mack Barbie
[Laughter]
alright check out bethany mota she
changed her name our channel name and
you can follow us at off the pill on
twitter and at off the pill podcast on
instagram i remembered this time and
once again shout out to rode thank you
very much yes thank you rode for the
fries things that being said having said
we'll see you guys next episode and this
is how we always end it we just breathe
into the mic and ruin our road mics in
three two one
a harmonized call see you singers
[Music]
there this is really nice
[Laughter]