hey guys so Father's Day is coming up in
a couple days or it's tomorrow or today
I don't know when I'm posting this
Father's Day is coming up or just Pat
damn it take two hey guys
so it's Father's week and I'm gonna be
completely honest I actually wasn't
gonna make a Father's Day video because
I just did a Mother's Day video and I
didn't want to be too similar but then
all the comments on that Mother's Day
video was kind of like well now you got
to make a Father's Day video because if
you don't that sexist I don't have a mom
so if you don't make a Father's Day
video that's not fair to me Wow Ryan you
actually cried in this video but a
little yes I got a little emotional
talking about my mom a Mother's Day I'm
sorry I just have so many feelings but
basically for this video I wanted to do
something a little different when you
tell your mom I love you for no reason
at all it's a completely normal thing
and in fact it's a very nice moment most
times she'll just say I love you too but
for dads on the other hand and I don't
know if this is just a guy thing but
it's not something you'd say to your dad
randomly at least not for me and
honestly I know this sounds absolutely
terrible but I don't even remember the
last time I told my dad I loved it and
don't get me wrong I love my dad and I
know he loves me it's just not something
that we say to each other it's just
unknown fat but then I wondered what if
I told my dad I love you randomly out of
nowhere what would he say what do you
say it back to me would it be awkward
would it be funny I don't know ergo yeah
I love you dad experiment was born I
told everybody in the TV app to film
their dad told him I love you and to
record the reaction I gotta say I had no
idea what to expect but I was not let
down at all before we get started I just
wanna say thank you to everybody send in
a video on to all the wonderful dads out
there happy Father's Day you know we
love you we just don't know how to say
it and apparently neither do you
I love you that I love you that I love
you
I love you why I love you
hi I love you dad love you too
I love you dad what do you think hey dad
I love now oh thank you I love you love
you too
why are you videotaping dad I love you
well I'd say that dad I love you baby I
love you daddy
okay I know love your dub guru Tata I
love you dad I love you
anyone what you do okay would you want
nothing you get nothing
hey dad I love you are you doing dad yes
sir I love you
dad I love you I'm playing my game thank
you
today I love you okay I love you okay
what's up nothing hey Dad I love you
trying to picture no it's not a pretty I
love you I love you what do you want dad
I love you
he wanted to that WI you said hmm hey
say that spiritually uncomfortable hello
hello dad
hey what you say what a scoop wanna oh I
am this is Ryan
this is your other son oh right yeah
yeah what Oh
just calling to say I love you oh thank
you never make a video for me I am
making a video for you right now
haha you're being recorded oh really
yeah what is your call oh no that's not
good
the joke was gonna be like telling a
bunch of kids to tell their dads I love
you cuz you don't normally say that to
your dad that's something you say to
your mom you know it's not something you
you say to your son right oh no not at
all
you