two guys walk into a bar but the third
one is a duck joke
what it was a knock-knock joke get it
knock-knock joke that was terrible
oh you think you could do better yeah
okay go ahead
want to hear two short jokes in the long
joke sure joke joke joke that's a pretty
deep joke almost as deep as this one Joe
Joe oh I'm sorry I was only half joking
joke lunch
Asian joke this is really getting
serious now
are you serious black jokes that's the
one type of joke I can't stand why I
can't handle it oh I can well then stop
your whining and suck it up I know your
type you walk around with a chip on your
shoulder thinking you're punny than
everyone else well guess what
I Got News for You buddy you're not you
shut up you think this is gonna be a PC
camp don't like a walk in the park well
I got a few aces up my sleeves so do I
well then let's stop beating around the
bush and cut to the chase
[Music]
wait stop this is pointless you're right
this is pointless wait why are we doing
this again I don't know I'm still
drawing a blank I know it got so person
seriously you want to just call a truce
shake on it
fine
[Applause]
oh thank god that's all seriously I'm so
tired of doing that wasn't even funny
anymore never what you wanted to go grab
a drink or something sure there's like a
bar five minutes away all right I got it
got what the best joke ever
it's a knock-knock joke oh my gosh
seriously again Ryan
boy hey just just hear me out just hear
me out all right these two guys walk
into a bar and you get it
knock knock cuz we both walked into the
I get it