hey guys so as many of you already know
I am NOT the most musically gifted
person but I do love music and recently
I've been trying to teach myself how to
play the piano not with real lessons or
like with a teacher or anything I've
been just like youtubing people playing
the piano and I just like copy their
hands pretty sure that's how people
learn right honestly I don't even know
how to read notes but anyway whenever I
try to practice playing the piano my
dogs for whatever is it it doesn't
matter where they are in the house they
come and they just they just go crazy
they just start barking so loud that I
can't even hear the piano I mean that
literally like scares me sometimes it
makes me not want to play it see I don't
know if you can tell how loud those
barks are from the video but trust me it
is loud and the thing is if I ignore
them and I keep playing Roku for
whatever reason it gets even louder by
doing this like you just like turned
into this really high pitch like cat see
I don't know if it's because I play the
piano so well that they want to sing
along or because I'm so bad that they
they want me to stop probably probably
that but regardless they will not let me
practice so one day I decided if they're
not gonna let me practice the piano then
I'm just gonna turn them into one so
everything you're about to hear is 100%
Marlee and Roku barking and doing that
high-pitched cat scream thing I'm not
sure why I did this but it's um it's
done this is the dog piano
[Music]
[Applause]
- there - it - it
[Laughter]
[Music]