and this ever happened to you and Bohr I
have as a Wii Xbox and internet connect
I wish I could place my time in a better
and more Japanese way no fur that's the
kid that looks like you'll never not not
have to waste your time unless he's
wearing something some kind of martial
art fusion match well let me tell you
retain the whole world my star everyone
loves to get down hungry kids two older
kids two kids riding kites and kids
flying bikes all kids love to gaze up in
fact you know that can topple these kids
Japanese all night into the Japanese but
can top up each kid most toys are lame
and boring like this Xbox I can't even
catch the pool not for long kids thanks
weekend that's what you say when they
can come with you can take the ball and
catch it on it's not catch it on the
other side and all that bad boy all the
way to the top by the way
did you know that you can even catch it
on the bottom but that's not all kids
they can't AMA many other fun juices as
well gentle face Bowl by yourself
a giant wrecking ball friends cheering
telling your friends you have an apple
with you really don't making yourself
look like you have a great big I get on
your head okay
or even just shutting up your irritating
friends and because I can college way is
a really hard one sharp point not only
is it safe for kids but it'll keep your
kids safe as if you order now we'll also
throw in this free salad self-defense
DVD for just $19.99 for we've all been
there
gulps and someone pulls a gun to your
head but when you've never not not
enough people to defend yourself again
that means you need to know to stay safe
all you have to do is get this kendama
cell festivity and I will personally
teach you how to hold the kendama that
has a DVD when you really know they are
option damaging so order now you're not
only today but the candy free that's a
whopping seven thousand three hundred
and ten yeah now we're giving it to you
for not twenty eight not twenty dollars
but twenty easy payments of $79.99
British pounds so what are you waiting
for order your time you'll be saying
every time