okay so this video is something I should
have done a very long time ago but what
can I say I'm a procrastinator I'm sure
you've noticed but almost every single
youtuber other than me has like really
good branding on their channels you know
like they all have those really nice
channel banners and updated playlists
and logos and tuka but most importantly
they all have this channel trailer that
when someone new comes to their channel
they can see this really cool epic
trailer of what their channel is all
about so that people get excited to
subscribe to them yeah after nine years
of being on YouTube I still don't have
one of those I think for the longest
time I had my draw my life video as the
trailer I'm just terrible at branding in
fact my banner is still one of the
default banners that YouTube offers you
when you first make a channel I mean to
be fair it is a nice banner I mean those
autofocus colorful light ball things are
actually really nice that's why I picked
it because it's a new year I'm gonna
start the year off right after 9 years
of YouTube procrastination no more I
finally have a channel trailer confetti
I mean it is two weeks into the year so
I guess I kind of procrastinated on this
video and actually I still don't have a
logo yet I haven't been updating my
playlist and as for my channel banner I
know you know what my channel banner is
fine who cares if it's a default banner
it's nice I love those autofocus
colorful ball things
thanks Ryan we love you too what the I
started making videos in O six didn't
think much of it just did some lip sings
random skits you know it was just me and
my friends having fun
I had no idea other people will be
watching I still don't know why people
watch but I'm thankful for it you know
it changed my life you know I went from
being this depressed bullied kid who
just wanted to be someone else to being
confident just happy to be me and that's
what this channel is all about you know
being yourself being different being
weird if you want to put on a wig and
lip-sync to the song barbie girl you'd
do it if you want to go and share
command me out of your hands but it's
always been your childhood dream then
make it happen if you want to be a
singer even though you've been told
countless times that you can't sing it
doesn't matter because the only person
that can stop you it's you because it's
never too late to be yourself are you
done because I mean nobody really asked
you for your whole life store what do
you mean I thought this whole thing was
a clip from an old interview or
something nope just part of the trailer
and you're still talking over all the
best parts well I mean I was just trying
to make it a little more inspirational
and didn't even make sense it just means
that it's not too late to do what you
want to it's also not too late for you
to leave because I mean I'm the one
doing the things so you know if you
don't mind hey you want to press it
surely tell me I don't know instead tell
me why don't know why God that nipple
you want the truth
you'll get handle the through okay okay
fine dare I'll do a dare the hood son
this is your dream Oh dad this is your
dream
I just want to tell look I can't see you
anymore
hey just because it made out no because
of the wall
okay I get up dude I'll tap out
you
son
I'm just gonna be completely honest with
you all those random scenes you saw at
the end are not for 2015 those are all
deleted jokes that I wrote last year
that never made it and I only put them
in because well we only have one video
done so far this year actually should be
coming out next week and just to get you
guys excited here's an epic trailer for
that video so yeah all jokes aside I'm
really looking forward to spending
another year with all of you and like I
always say whether you've been there
from the start like nine years ago or if
you just follow this channel today thank
you guys so much for watching your
comments and support literally inspire
me and allow me to keep doing this doing
something that I love so really from the
bottom of my left boom which is kind of
sweaty cuz it's hot in here at the top
of my still the left boob which you know
what I'm saying the heart area thank you
guys so much you have no idea how much I
appreciate it
yep this got cheesy really fast and if
you know me I never in the video with
cheese yeah that works I don't think I
have so I'll leave you with this one
last joke and it just so happens to be
the best most epic joke I've ever wrote
that rhymed and it goes like this what
do you call hey what are you doing what
I was just about to in this video with a
really good joke and you interrupted me
oh yeah so if you don't mind could I do
it no go ahead
sorry thank you okay what do you call
alright so thank you guys again so much
for watching if you want to see bloopers
and behind the scenes people on the
right if you want to see the previous
video click the one the left I don't
know why I switch the order this time
and also if you're wondering why my
voice is weird right now it's because I
have the flu