yeah and what are you doing nothing what
do you want you just crap again it's not
crap okay I'm learning gonna be a ninja
I will show you how to be a ninja huh
you're gonna teach me how to be a ninja
please watch this I'll show you how it's
done
my dreams in the air don't change their
lair bear but you don't even care here I
go there I go this is my song where's my
automobile Niles lost everything with my
chopstick make it off my wrist every hit
the gun team so fast so quick
I bet you have my ninja tricks oMG did
you like me just watch GG you can't see
me
I'm living in just like a pine tree tree
Monte see you can see me cuz I'm a ninja
ninja in just like a pine tree tree -
Ichi you can see because I'm a ninja
ninja ninja just like you was except for
the fact we don't sell peace out your
back it's just a way to sweet see you
coming but we have more
don't come near so we'll give you stop
and though this is my clothes yet over
time
here comes slow motion I'd like me don't
forget your fatality draw Bonita in the
club they look just like us from this
visit something rare rare this move
looks like a square square and the air
air GG you can see
CGT you can see me cuz I'm a ninja GG
you can see me
just like a pine tree CG you can see
because I'm a ninja ninja