first there was the Nintendo followed by
the game-changing Super Nintendo
involving two for player technology with
the n64 and GameCube advancing into 3d
and held human detection of the Wii and
the groundbreaking hybrid console
Nintendo sweat cheated us all the way to
our most recent cutting-edge
state-of-the-art glorified origami
cardboard technology known as the
Nintendo now wait are you serious
cardboard yeah that's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard Lee $70 a cake and
the people who brought you none of the
things mentioned earlier me now present
the Nintendo paper my name is Ryan Higa
and I am the CEO of Nintendo with a name
when I first heard of a Nintendo lab I
thought wow this is brilliant this is
genius but it's just kind of missing
something it wasn't quite there I mean
it was cool it was it was dope it just
wasn't Nintendo it was literally like an
in-out of Tendo and not a 10 out of 10
dough like a 10-10 dough you know
cardboard is something to be really
focused on years ago and now that
Nintendo is doing it it just goes to
show you that we're leading the pack and
we're headed in the right direction
backwards people don't want to invent
technology anymore they're sick of all
these newer smarter more advanced
products to give fidgets spinners
kendamas slime humble wrappers people
don't want better they want to go
backwards that's why the Nintendo paper
is perfect for this generation with an
8.5 x 11 inch paper screen and with of
less than 0.1 mm it weighs only five
making it not only one of the largest
screens out of any handheld console
today but also one of the lightest and
most portable thanks to its multi
bendable size and complete wireless
technology and even with a screen that
gigantic it's one
durable products on the market we've
performed countless stress tests from
drops to scratches to running it over
with a truck the screen just does not
crack however it isn't quite 100%
waterproof yet but our incredible team
of scientists are currently working on a
waterproof case and that's not going to
be an issue for long now I know a lot of
people think that this is just some kind
of money grab because on the outside it
might look like a normal average useless
piece of paper but that's just because
technology has just sucked the
creativity out of people and just like
the lab with a Nintendo paper - to bring
back that creativity and imagination
because when you use your imagination
wait no what why am I talking like this
because like I went back like 10 years
or something
you see the Nintendo paper takes you all
the way back to your most creative days
when you were a kid and you didn't have
the technology to create a world better
than your own imagination that's our
true mission here at Nintendo with the
need to avoid copyright issues to bring
back the most valuable asset in the
world chose imagination so order the
Nintendo paper now for the same exact
prices the labo $69.99 no joke that's
how much it actually cost and before you
know it get it all back the brain of a
child
[Music]
wonderful
are you doing - this Nintendo paper is
freakin awesome man oh you like that
you're gonna love Microsoft's new system
what's that Xbox