the fact that we're talking about
technically we shouldn't be talking
about it is what the messes are trying
to say yeah in this conspiracy but so if
we die don't say that Vancouver and
Toronto gossip
hot girls I know you guys are taking but
they got huh I mean doesn't mean we
can't acknowledge that Japan was by far
our favorite trip bullet Oh pop it
kick it twist it no you just drop it and
you break it all right claps claps claps
oh no I turned it in welcome back to
another episode of off the peel podcast
we got our usual okay that's enough of
that
I was trying to be a house trying to be
a producer dude we have our usual cast
back cast back
hi did you introduce them yeah will and
will not a lot of people know my name is
Willy surprised you know down that's
gonna be your guys group name I used to
go by Willy you didn't really sauce well
that was just an inappropriate gamer
name that had but when I was a little
kid oh really you didn't know that yeah
I wasn't trying to make you almost like
a twelve-year-old I didn't know that I
didn't know that's why you named
yourself that good start I was funny
not anymore I was oh man
okay well we can't say that but this is
will why can't we say that we could I
guess we could yeah it's your podcast
I'm will I'm Paco no you so say and I'm
will I know I'm will and I'm will
and I'm Ryan together we're Ryan and the
Willie sauce all right what song is that
I don't know where that came from
looks like Paramore um we do not have a
sponsor today but you know what cool huh
doing way way oh nice too late yeah but
I guess what could be a fake sponsor is
your foundation yep I'm going right in
today yes I do have a nonprofit that I
don't remember when that video came out
it was on second Channel something
usable two years ago cuz I'll still it
wasn't anyway a lot of people don't know
about it but the idea kind of came from
it's kind of like a make-a-wish
Foundation but instead of sick kids it's
going towards the caregivers so it's
almost like without them knowing so it's
instead of making a wish it's like
giving somebody an unexpected surprise
yeah like someone who's selfless yeah so
the first one we did was this girl that
we heard about through a well my mom
heard about through a newspaper back in
Hilo and she was like this she just does
everything she's part of the Peace Corps
and she uh just like right out of high
school she went to like Africa to help
spread like AIDS awareness and stuff
like that she was a beast basically she
did so many things it seems unrealistic
it's like this is too good of a person
so she was our first person that we you
know did something for and then we
talked to her mom secretly this is
basically how it works we reach out to
you know a friend or a family member who
wants to nominate this person obviously
they didn't know about the foundation so
we didn't wait for someone to nominate
we had to like basically just go and
find the mom and we secretly talked to
her and said is there anything we want
to do this best day ever
that's what the foundation is called so
that's not what it's called that's what
the show was called the foundation is
the Ryan Higa foundation org and
essentially we reached out and we found
out that she needed a car she didn't ask
for it she didn't even the mom didn't
even ask for it but she said is theirs
we said is there something that your
daughter is gonna need cuz she's going
off to college and really what she
needed was a car so we ended up getting
our car but that's just one example not
saying we're gonna go and help cars to
everybody but if you're out there and
you know somebody who's like done a lot
of good things or you just really want
them to have their best day ever go to
Ryan Higa
foundation org yeah nominate them and
there's a video don't remember what it's
called or older huh what's the video
called on Technol it's well the show's
best day ever
cuz your idea is to give somebody who
deserves it their best day ever
not that getting a car is her best day
ever but it's just the show know what uh
like what would qualify someone this is
somebody who like you know work hard or
make edits podcasts and you know yeah I
mean if they're a good person
sure they've done beyond he's a good
person I'm out you if they go above and
beyond like like a like a teacher you
know you hear those stories like the
teachers always they're broke but they
spend all their money to their salary on
it it's kind of kind of like those
typical shows you see on like the news
you know how they do like those segments
where they surprised people yeah but I'm
trying to turning into a show at the
same time
yeah that's cool that's cool so I mean
we just need nominations to find good
people you have to be 13 at least or
older than obviously to nominate legal
reasons and then right as of now I think
it's only in the US the the nominee
nominate from wherever you are but the
nominee should be in the US just for now
okay we're not big enough yet very cool
super cool yeah anyway off from the
foundation since we got right to it I'm
gonna bring it up at the end I mean he
just felt like later you know do it
after this you break if you want yeah
[Laughter]
what uh what's on the agenda today dude
life is on the agenda
Dana's sick she was yes or Dana and
you're leaving you're going to Japan
wanna Japan you're so lucky I'm not what
are you talking about what do you mean
okay then stay then oh you're not lucky
okay stay then no don't leave Tamara
worked hard for this one okay oh did you
uh no but I mean it's just an expression
taco yeah you guys remember the game
fatal frame Xbox game
that sounds really I never had the
scariest games it's meant to be scared
you take you go around basically and you
take pictures I do see like it's not
it's not meant for kids I don't think I
do remember that was really scary yeah
it was a fun group game to play with
people mm-hmm I like I don't know maybe
that's where my my enjoyment of seeing
other people scream it scary movies
comes from were you the one playing it
or just wanting to do as a group huh did
you play it or watch it like when both
yeah I was trying to watch it I couldn't
play it's too scary you're kind of like
a weird sicko like why is that weird
no no cuz you like my people like that
how much you like seeing other people be
scared not necessarily but I mean I
don't a lot of people like those
compilations of people getting scared
you don't watch those videos and think
it's funny no I don't it depends on the
reaction yeah they could be pretty funny
I don't I don't usually watch those it's
like something Ellen does she scares
people yeah it's like yeah those are
like nice gears like ah yours is like
dude let's go watch this movie like the
conjuring it's good okay that's a good
movie yeah but you just always like
anytime you go and see a scary movie you
always invite the whole group you like
anybody wanted to watch this movie
Greg's always like just doesn't respond
or something yeah but I mean it's it's
just the kind of movies I like oh yeah
sure do you uh anything wrong with that
or weird about it dude a lot of people
like scary movies I like scary movies I
do want to figure out why I get that
enjoyment though I go into scary movies
and I base how good it is based on like
man I actually felt something I like to
feel something when I watch movie
whether it's happiness sadness or if a
movie makes you feel something it's a
good movie yeah and it's really hard for
you especially according to the last
podcast yeah you're a robot that is not
true
but it is but if something makes if a
movie makes me feel anything I think
it's a good movie
that means I got sucked into it yeah
it's probably also with scary movies is
if you actually feel scared when you'd
like don't expect it or ever because
it's easy for like like you were saying
or I remember we talked about this a
long time ago we're like jump scares are
kind of like the easy way out
yeah but when the movies use all their
like tricks to make you feel scared yeah
that's when you're like whoa it's the
building of the anxiety yeah it's not
really the actual jump scare
at I mean that's just like the that's
like a fart joke in comedy it's like the
easiest way to get a laugh or do the
screech that makes both you guys laugh
no but like jump scares you you told me
this and this is how he kind of
convinced me to go watch more scary
movies Ryan was like horror and comedy
have a lot in common because those are
the only two genres that rely heavily on
timing heavily yeah yeah it they're all
about timing and that's why kind of
Jordan peels movies have like exactly
done so well I mean he's like he's a
comedic genius yeah
and he's able to translate that into
like horror so maybe you want to talk
about a little bit cuz that's actually
something that you're interested in yeah
I mean I from even before get out you
know it inspired me but B even before
that I was like I've alway mean you guys
know I've always like people ask me all
you want to make a movie
my natural gut is to go and make a
horror movie that's what I would have
want to create more so than like a
comedy movie because the only reason is
because I feel like it's so similar in
terms of timing and it's something new
yeah and I feel like it's it's fun to do
I don't know maybe something is wrong
with me Alex just carefully I like to
give people
I don't know increase their heart rates
I don't know what it is mmm something's
wrong with me dude you should make human
centipede for is there a third one there
is a third one oh my man if people who
have not seen it don't not one of the
ones that I think is considered a great
horror movie but it's great shock value
do you remember playing scary games
growing up
scary games what yeah like like you were
saying with the fatal friend do you
remember that that was the only one man
it wasn't like your genre you play games
oh there wasn't many I mean Resident
Evil did you get scared of Diablo first
time you play oh no did you remember the
first boss the butcher yeah I had to
have my brother come to kill him cuz I
was scared
yeah he was scary I guess I don't know
something about I don't know I wasn't in
film at the time or wasn't into making
videos yeah but like it's easier now
because when
watch those horror movies or like it
not just horror movies anything that
takes you out of the film like a horror
movie or something that you're really
into it's hard for me to not picture how
they're filming it if that makes sense
yeah yeah like if there's a shot where
it's just like in the music's building
I'm picturing like the editor damn why
are they turning up their volumes so
high right here obviously something's
gonna happen if not they're gonna cut to
something else and then like I'm already
pre-planning so many steps ahead because
I'm trying to picture how their timeline
looks like yeah and it's so not fun but
if there's a really good movie that
sucks me in that I don't think about
that stuff yeah
that's on you I don't know that makes
sense I that's the only way I can try to
get out of movies cuz I get sucked in
very easily that's why I don't like
watching scary movies cuz even though I
know it's not real mm-hmm like I'll just
be like oh it immersed yeah I get super
like just I'm in it that's why that's
that's why I like when we talked about
it last time when I had to go oh dude
that's the only way I can get out at
them verbally say something to be like
I'm in a movie I'm in a movie
get me out of here like after the
conjuring when I went to the cloud yeah
I turned all the lights on yeah wasted
your electricity dude I turned like Ryan
you made me see this movie after I
didn't make you it's fun no I don't you
you don't regret it no I don't because
there's a good story really good yeah it
was it was funny though even like when I
watch dude you and Arden are probably
like the worst people or or best
depending on which to see horror movies
with because that's what scares me is
you guys person who next to you that
grabs you on a not so scary part will
scare the [ __ ] out of me I've never
grabbed no but you'll yell I will you'll
yell and it's I like kind of get a
little bit mad cuz I'm like that's not
part of the scare but like it scares me
and I'm like that's not that shouldn't
happen that's a jump scare you know how
to get you you do you do
people like scare you more it's more
scary than the movie yeah and it's a
little upsetting cuz you're like man
they just jump scared they fart joke
damn we did go off top let's go listen
let's go through some of the interesting
stuff we have here so I mean it's not
interested is interesting to me but um I
didn't know who he was until like today
uh-huh not that's not necessary sure I
didn't really know much about and how do
you
Nipsey Hussle Nipsey Hussle so he just
died
yes very young but by the time this
comes out that's true a few days this
week yeah he just died he just passed
away this week cuz he was shot in a in
front of his store own store and you
know a little bit more about it so well
yeah he's a rapper he's a rapper but
he's also like a huge community activist
yeah he did a lot for his communities
just just bringing awareness and
everything like that and was trying to
build people up in terms of like
employment in his stores I saw a couple
of videos talking about how he employed
artists who were trying to make it but
also needed money so this is how this is
how they would hustle this is how they
would grind and his mindset was just
about like bringing like positivity and
stuff and a quote actually I mean he had
such an impact on the community that
mark ride Lee Thomas hope it's how I
said his name is a member of the Los
Angeles County Board of Supervisors who
represents the southern part of the city
released a statement Sunday night saying
his district mourn the loss of hustle oh
dude I'm gonna butcher his name I know I
just saw that it was like oh I can't
wait to part mice - I don't know known
to us as the hip-hop artists Nipsey
Hussle was a father businessman
entertainer and an inspiration to many
with really Tommy so this is a common I
mean this is like a common thing that is
this is why I heard of him because every
celebrity not every majore him his
celebrities came out and they they were
showing like such respect and like such
I mean you know they do that a lot times
when people pass away but yeah it was
like a consensus like this is such a
good guy he you know naturally I'm gonna
look him up I looked him up I saw all
the great things he did but there was
also something that just
right before the podcast I wasn't even
searching conspiracy or anything but
this thing popped up on my Facebook
Timeline and it was a conspiracy about
his death and I'm like oh here we go
again just cuz someone dies and gets
shot it doesn't mean there's a
conspiracy mm-hmm but then I looked into
it you know I love my conspiracies you
love them and there's you know what
there is I mean I I haven't done enough
research of something I'm gonna say how
do I give a disclaimer like don't take
everything I say as a fact but take you
know a grain of salt
take it with a grain of sugar I don't
know why I changed it anyway if you look
at the conspiracy in super inch I only
looked it up for like an hour so I don't
don't um don't knock me if I get it
wrong yeah our own research essentially
yeah do your own research but from what
I've read and I've only checked it sites
obviously they could be wrong and they
could be saying the same thing yeah the
conspiracy was that he was releasing a
documentary or making a documentary
about this doctor doctor said dr. Seuss
Abbey who claims that he got a or he
created a cure for AIDS I don't think
it's claimed he actually proved it in a
95 yeah okay well he proved it that he
has a cure for AIDS and HIV right you
know in a court I don't know about HIV I
think just AIDS isn't that the same age
any leads to AIDS no well we just doing
okay I think it was oh it could be eight
well regardless it's everybody knows we
we know aids as being incurable right
but he has proven that it was C I don't
even know if I can say that it was
proven I don't know the article said
that okay so it's not us we're reporting
what we saw yes cured AIDS essentially
and everybody knows I mean in the whole
especially the conspiracy world people
know that if you if you just like curing
cancer or hearing aids like selling the
treatment is a lot more profitable than
selling a cure because then you get to
build them every step of the way yeah
you know there's always that conspiracy
and basically there's there's I'm gonna
give that really yeah that's crazy yeah
there I mean like people talk about oh
there's been a cure for cancer it's just
that it makes so much money treating
walls than it does curing them they're
the pharmaceutical companies make more
money off of a country being sick than a
country being wealthy or a healthy
healthy arm it's all the pharmaceutical
side
could be maybe you know I mean they
could have investment you and me on the
conspiracy I'm telling you you do you
should look into it you don't have to
necessarily believe everything with a
grain of sugar and just like you know
look it up and but basically there's
there's more to it but you told me some
stuff that was interesting you brought
up about I was just talking to you
before this went live there is another
artist by so essentially um in the
article that I had read dr. stubby and
this is up that I've heard even before
this event right but doctor said we had
found a cure and he got stopped like at
an airport or something I think in
Honduras and basically he got stopped
for having too much money on him right
and then he got detained and while in
custody he died three days later due to
fighting a battle with pneumonia but the
the big conspiracy is how could one of
the world's most healthy men suddenly
died to pneumonia within three days so a
lot of people are draw up the idea of he
was executed you know possibly
conspiracy yeah there's there's no
actual evidence right and then I believe
there's an artist by the name of left
eye or something yeah it's a woman yeah
what did she do she she was talking
basically talking talking about it and
trying to bring awareness turnabout from
TLC but she essentially from what I read
again that much I probably look more
into it but she was murdered as well
right oh well she wasn't murdered she
was in a car crash a car crash but
people again suspect because she was
talking about and bringing awareness to
it and then this whole thing happened
because you know named she also was
making a documentary that's yeah yeah oh
Lisa left eye Lopes hmm good for you you
know you're so hip I know some things
about the culture but yet so that this
whole thing came up and it's very
regardless it's a little suspicious yeah
and he also has a quote I believe that
people have been tweeting and stuff
saying that uh what was the exact quote
I have it somewhere
it's basically he said if I if they kill
me for
documentary or he says here it is if
they kill me for this documentary y'all
better ride for me not that I really
know one ride for me means what is right
for me me and Barry down for me like
they know what I was about you better
ride for me maybe she's like maybe like
put keep pushing it so I saw that Nick
Cannon actually instagrammed it or
something that he's saying he's gonna
finish the documentary yeah and I'm like
dude mmm that's date like and Twitter
was like protect me again yeah and all
this stuff like but if you have to go
about it though I mean like you would
say publicly you're gonna finish the
documentary people know if something
happens to him we know it it is like
there's still no way to prove it though
so I wonder this is kind of like not a
side thing but has there ever been a
conspiracy that was like pretty big that
actually got proven in it transferred
from conspiracy theory to fact and then
action was taken has that ever happened
I'm sure I'm sure there has been maybe
when everybody thought the world was
flat in nineteen of 1492 yeah everything
was a conspiracy at some point right
mm-hmm
yeah I mean like more like in modern
modern times where maybe someone was
like it became it was a known conspiracy
and then either something came out or
someone proved it well this is what
happened just see small it right it was
a conspiracy at first a lot of people
were saying what that doesn't sound
realistic that sounds like he staged it
mmm even before he the facts came out
right true people were saying that and
then you know a couple weeks later he
gets caught or they find like his I
don't know I don't know I don't know how
it went down exactly but all these other
facts came out yeah and but it's like
those are like a small like a small
example of that I think you're talking
about like a grand scale like worldwide
yeah or even something that is like what
government you know so they've been it's
like okay if it if it is like let's say
let's even say like God forbid I hope
not you know Nick Cannon whatever yeah
they get they get him they get off on
that would real quick they get him right
and maybe even has like a note it says
like they came in Bob I was a government
like then what do you do
did someone else call the police someone
else carries on
cuz they I think when Nick Cannon said
it was like I'll take the baton from
here so it's almost as this like it's a
relay you know one person like you know
I don't know I don't even know what I'm
trying to ask but it's like I know what
you're saying what's the next like how
do you how do you find you'll see people
yeah pursue and make sure you know those
people are you got it somebody you got
to get somebody with in power yeah to be
a conspiracy there is to be like to
pursue it yeah but also what person
morality yeah but the thing is it's like
a you're basically in like a loophole
because that person loophole what is it
called where's the word I'm thinking oh
not conundrum either but basically that
person who makes it that way into power
your isn't gonna make it there without
playing ball yeah you know yeah so
that's why I think those things never
come out yeah is even if somebody who if
I all of a sudden I believe in
conspiracy theory is certain ones on all
of them if I were to somehow magically
make it into a position of power a
president right I'm not gonna make it
there by saying hey I wonder if the
Clintons murdered something something
they're not gonna let me rise into power
with that kind of thinking I say so I
think it's there's no way really to
expose those kind of like no completely
innocent person can rise to that I'm
right amount of power and then they make
a non in the way on the on the journey
there they make you seem like a crazy
person already when you say conspiracy
theorist you're thinking all this guy
believes in Flat Earth or has nothing to
do yeah exactly
but like aliens are we're not gonna get
into that but yeah aliens are not a
conspiracy alright are we going just
talk for Derek I'm so excited I can't
wait to talk about all his alien stories
that's pretty crazy how like you
literally it was like overnight that all
these conspiracies like just exploded no
no no it's been around for a while but
the fact that he was pursuing this
documentary more people were like
exactly this is adding on to it oh yeah
I think even more like suspect mostly I
think he could have easily just been
another shooting but like where normally
when those happen like especially to
celebrities yeah if you find out oh they
caught the killer or they killed the kid
yeah I didn't
anything I think supposedly also it was
like on his turf in his area yeah you
know and how could people have done that
and just gotten out you know that
quickly the turf was healing he he was
in like I believe something something
you know some I don't I don't know what
it is it's I don't want to say anything
I'm wrong but it was something
gang-related and then he also was
meeting with someone I think whoever
that police officer whatever it is not
the officer the guy you were talking
about using the rolling sixties
neighborhood Crips yeah well that is but
he was supposed to meet with someone the
next day talk about preventing gang
violence yeah yeah so he was in a gang
right mmm that's it that's right right
yeah but yet he's trying to stop can be
trying to prevent people from going on
the same yeah yeah yeah but I think a
lot of the times to uh originally gangs
were a way for like people who were in
like broken families and stuff and they
would have like like brother brotherly
ties or someone a father to look up to
and everything like that it wasn't it
wasn't originally supposed to be about
like fighting and all that everything
he's like right you know talking about
late in the 40s or the 50s
we're like the the original purpose of
the gang yeah I was supposed to be like
that before
yeah and then it kind of just like
turned into something else
mmm right well I mean that that yeah
like I said I don't know enough about
this like whole conspiracy I literally
just spent an hour before you guys came
over yeah I'm looking up stuff so I
don't want to spread misinformation and
also don't talk more because you might
die what oh yeah this oh that there's
that too and like there's the fear of I
mean like people shedding light on the
fact that yeah even Nick Cannon the fact
that we're talking about technically we
shouldn't be talking about it is what
the messes are trying to say yeah in
this conspiracy but so if we die
[Laughter]
mysteriously yes I'm an idea of how do
you think you're gonna die though right
yeah yeah like maybe you're gonna like
some people think like I'll do I just
know I'm gonna die in a car crash no I
don't I don't have one but some people
would think that they have a feeling no
Walker
to a forest put my hands up above my
head and dissolve and become a plant all
right that's how I'm gonna do it if
you're gonna let me choose you know I'm
not letting you choose I just think how
do you think you're gonna die I think
that's probably how would we ever never
want to be a plant no I mean I'm gonna
like into like the trees Oh like ashes I
don't know either
I've never sounds like a psychic how do
you think you're going to die is
actually in this is in this 36 questions
to love thing that I saw okay and it is
like it has a lot of different questions
that eventually like get you and this
other person you get to know each other
a little bit more one of the questions
was how do you think you're gonna do you
have an idea how you think you're gonna
die do you know I don't I said it how
would you want to fast very painless Pam
I would want to die in my sleep I think
that's probably I would assume the most
people like and I'll be sure to remember
that when I plan on killing you both in
my sleep are you gonna make me dissolve
our plants huh yeah that's true
seriously tell me how dark this went
dark but I like it because I like damn
we are evil we're going into evil
territory death and conspiracy and some
people think you swore on the law the
last pie no I said [ __ ] fu TT ing is
that pigeon
that's pigeon I think messing around
like cutting around yeah yeah people
thought I'd swore yeah I'll swear for
real right now
yeah then do it I'm [ __ ] around
flattened around yeah it's not a bad
word guys I didn't swear in the last
podcast oh sorry
did you I mean you say [ __ ] it's not
even bad though they say that on TV you
know really yeah and [ __ ] they say
bitchin i knows it yeah yeah they can oh
she doesn't mean we should be just like
you know she didn't she didn't ever
force the issue wait before we go to our
see she break I think we should start
off with some Twitter questions Oh what
we she see you then Twitter questions
after one because
let's do it before will loves to Twitter
questions hey where are they underneath
the Nick Cannon Bart um not lamp Higa
says favorite memory from childhood go
well actually the at is what Reina erase
her favorite memory from childhood it's
a very basic one well it kind of ties
into do we have memories from our
children oh no I don't know do you have
one immediately that you can think of
but favorite weird it's a but I don't
know if I said this on the bias but one
of my favorite memories is when I got
spanked by my dad what because I passed
another kid and I passed him and
remember like like I went to a private
school I was like a Christian school and
my dad was a was a pastor what true
right so it was like oh why why am i
messing up so everything is like it
didn't look well mm-hmm and so my dad
spanked me but he used a racket paddle
and not a normal racket paddle a wooden
racket Palace know what racket paddles
are wooden know there's the string ones
although old school ones were wooden I
think you know I was like you know it's
about three so why do you like what that
you liked it no yes what you got you
into it's because oh he said after he
like spanked me so hard the first time
they don't even pull the paddle back
that my whole butt was red except for
the little air holes so it is like
there's little white spots on my butt
from the rag and I just it's a funny
image I just think it's funny you saw it
no but the way he said it is very like
you can see it in your own head you know
huh like your whole blood is just red
except it looks like you have a reverse
chickenpox oh I thought you liked that
for a different reason oh no it makes
sense where you're going to Japan pretty
sure if I if after you got spanked I
went up to you and ask you like hey did
you like that you perfect oh that's
definitely not definitely at the time
but now it's kind of funny I've got so
the conclusion that you're a masochist
that's the one that likes pain right I
don't know I think a little bit but not
I think a lot of it because for one
verbally you like to get abused and you
amuse yourself I do
and
and when it comes to comes to like the
shoots that we do like the other day we
did the the pulling the sheet thing
right yeah and then you're like out of
nowhere you just like hey what if I were
to like ride into this table and fly off
the bike and land like I like dude
that's super dangerous so we're not
gonna do that but you really want to do
it so you did I thought it'd be on your
own for your own video yeah and I
thought I thought I think oh and that's
just one of the fairies
I don't you're a masochist the inside of
my thigh mm-hmm yeah that's your fetish
huh I don't know maybe mmm you have a
favorite childhood memory no but I want
to figure out more about Paco favorite
childhood memory I don't know if I can I
mean it would take me a long time to
think of one specific one but probably
like sports like I did some baseball
when I was really young I had like some
pretty good memories from and martial
arts doing martial arts growing up and
like going to tournaments and getting
first place in those and it was just
really good memories I think from like
you know feeling accomplished as a young
boy I was a very unhappy kid so I didn't
have a lot of good memories yeah at a
very it wasn't a rough childhood it was
just a very I was a very unhappy person
naturally you still are no I'm happy all
the time for simple things you just
don't smile I guess not what about like
extracurricular stuff that made you made
you happy like when I hated like most of
my time was spent either studying doing
basketball judo which I hated both at
the time I didn't like basketball back
then I never hit like a sweet little
jumper and never I never had many any
shots really I was like block I wasn't
the worst guy on the team but I was
probably the second or third worse
mm-hmm yeah so it wasn't very happy
you'd be like yeah that's not really
want to go to the next one though
because I got some sleeves to pull okay
not grab it's questionable thank you
Raina next we got Joe Joe dick key Dicky
thoughts and reusable straws oh do you
want to pull the sleeve sir so do you
want me you can go ahead
reusable straws I love reusable straws
oh really mr. using the straw right now
that's not reusable
that is reusable honestly yes it again
um the when I use some at home I'll
actually like clean these but I'm
talking like the metal ones yeah I
thought they were talking about like the
ones you recycle like the like the paper
ones you can talk about that those ones
I do not agree I don't I know it's all
about the environment and stuff like
straws can't do straws really make that
big of a difference like I know there's
a lot of straws in the world yeah
there's got to be other ways because
those straws are awful I think with the
straws thing supposedly it doesn't have
that huge of an impact but it still has
a little bit of an impact and also the
thing that it gets is the visual aid
because there is this one picture where
this turtle had a huge like just a straw
so yeah yeah I saw that and they're
trying to pull it out and there's like
in his brain and all that stuff and
first of all that drug should emit
snorting drugs that drug turtle [ __ ]
it's a starting drug and your own joke
ruin my joke I'm not funny well I mean
so that seems more like an emotional
reaction
yeah like a logical one because there's
other things you can like before straws
I'm sure mmm I haven't done the research
but I'm sure there's other things more
you know yeah feasible or whatever it is
to fix then straw straws can be like the
worst thing like why that and yet every
place in LA is starting to do these
paper straws yeah and I hate him like I
get paid you get paper in your mouth I
think I thought okay thoughts on
reusable straws reusable straws are good
yes yes yeah agree agree I think you
should be using a reusable a lot of
things like I bring I don't use plastic
bags anymore like I bring my own bags
how hard is it I reuse plastic bags yeah
how hard is it to just use the same like
just get a bag and bring it same thing
with straws how hard is it just to clean
a straw and reuse it sort of you save
your plastic bags for the market I don't
even get plastic bags
I bring I breathe you see I do know I
saw I go I think it's a Asian thing yeah
I say yeah yeah you guys do that growing
up make senior plastic bags from the
market and stuff because we do remember
to layer our trash bag or our trash cans
and stuff like that and just for a
random stuff I got scolded for using
straws from someone really recently
mm-hmm
and it weird thing is a
girl that it was into and so I was like
just being like just trying to catch
conversation as soon as I use a straw
she just got mad at me and I was like
well it's over good job
that's all it takes huh yeah but even
these straws you can clean these I mean
I know it sounds kind of wack but you
can actually wash these and clean it no
it's super easy this is actually a topic
that I was gonna bring up for notes was
recycling and apparently you're gonna
bring up recycling yeah because the
thing is a lot of people think that it
could be too late for recycling that you
know we're killing the earth and it's
it's too late for the stuff like that
because before China actually we
exported a lot of our recycling and our
waste to China because they're such
their cheap labor laws they were able to
take these things recycle the trillions
of products but China I think within the
past couple years something banned
importing of like loathsome waste so now
cities that used to make like I think
like sixty something million dollars a a
per ton for recycling mm-hmm
now have to pay like to get their
recycling done a lot of these places are
burning their recycling their waste for
energy but it's just like so what does
our I guess country do now in terms of
recycling because it takes so much for
them to sort through all these like
small things right so what we could do
individually is to separate them but I
feel like it's because America feels so
entitled a lot of us are just gonna be
like why do I need to do that you know
I'm already helping by recycling why do
I need to take these other steps no
one's going to yeah I mean some people
were obviously but the majority is not
going unless it becomes a cool thing to
do or gonna make it cool yeah or it has
to become a I mean like high five
yeah well California already has that
though what's worthy yeah you get paid
to recycle you get five cents back I
think California has ten cents right we
had I don't remember what it's not that
you know no we still I mean I still
collect all bottles and stuff like that
but yeah we do get we'd get no rewards
here so I don't see why people are
incentivized here to do it mm-hmm most
people don't I see a lot I drove around
the neighborhood and stuff I don't see
many her cycle like recycling things I
see
of trash cans it's more work for people
one of the things that ladies in my own
personal opinion is like it's it's it's
good to recycle but it's also like a
good thing to be conscious of like how
much trash you're actually using like in
general like that's why I think we
started trying to like use a lot of
reusable stuff you know and like I know
it sounds kind of hipster but you like
put something like instead of using
things you know bring a jar and like
fill whatever you're getting like rice
like when we go get rice like we put it
in like a reasonable bag or a jar so
we're not very good about the boxes and
then you use it any throw away the box
wherever you know what I mean like just
like a thing in the back of my mind I
think that yeah that wasn't always like
that it was only like as I became an
adult so yeah but that's my two cents on
it well overall recycling is good more
people should do it what's unreasonable
straw is good yeah
shishi break I'm not a fan of still not
found a paper straws still not a fan you
know they used to be made of corn I well
you told me that yeah why don't they do
that sounds like it's probably a
conspiracy a conspiracy crosstalk
warning idea she should break already
[Music]
classy and tried to take it and we're
back in our pack okay and we're back
welcome back to the second half of the
box take it out of the [ __ ] oh my gosh
it's so loud whoa what am i drinking out
of it's my brand-new off-the-field
podcast mug get it at weekend they know
I think so I think people ask if they
can get it uncle look get it somewhere
well I thought wearing off the pill
shirt too but yeah no sponsorship plug
and you snap and then put CGI over yeah
yeah CGI right hit the mugs good see we
already knocked out all the Twitter
questions now we have them are yeah well
okay what is this one I won't skip it's
my favorite
Tata says out of the videos you guys
created which one of them took the most
time in Hawaii oh that's just a question
for everyone the most I don't recall
I don't recall a most time time and why
like everything start to finish start
you writing to when it's posted yes I
don't know you would know that yeah I
know I think I mean some videos it's
something I wrote like the year before
does that count sound like I'm actively
working on it though yeah be like from
when he pulled it up finalized it and
then got it into our hands and then you
know gets edit it didn't post it
honestly probably one of the BGA videos
those take the longest oh yeah I didn't
think of that because because your
prosthetics pardon it that's why it I
mean people will ask for anything I want
you guys make another one it something
like just like 10 minutes it's not ten
minutes because the videos ten minutes
does not mean it takes ten minutes to
six ten months so those are what I don't
know about that but I'll usually write a
concept first I need to have a good idea
for a song and I don't have to think can
this song fit into where the storyline
is where all the guys you know but it's
but then there's another step which is
even harder which is from there if I
have a concept I work with David to be
like hey can you translate this to
Korean because you need to have Korean
in it right yeah okay pop so there's
that step which is painful because we
have to find words that I can't even
contribute I don't know how to make
something sound good
syllable wise I'm wise cuz I don't know
you know green yeah so there's that step
and then after that we have to make the
song and I have to learn and the other
guys if they're in it have to learn how
to say these words and not even words
we're saying sounds basically imitating
what we're being told it's really hard
yeah it's it's just like a and just make
a song the subtitles take over at that
point that's to make this song and then
we had to go through all the other stuff
to make the video it's ridiculous and
the music video is more of like a
traditional sense of filming a video
like oh there's a budget involved it's a
budget there's a crew like out here we
do it very like YouTube style right we
have like quick quick fast out there
it's like setup to the scene you have a
call sign shot that the proper film yeah
yeah and it's it takes way longer it's
way more expensive
and so you know what if you guys want a
BGA video patreon right here I'm
thirteen million dollars if you don't
raise thirteen million dollars by 24
hours of when this podcast released just
can't have it honestly though like
that's part of the reason why I don't do
it it's like financially not like those
videos do well but I don't really like
really benefit from it that much in
terms of like financial I like to lose
money I think I'm the first one you know
it's you don't because they're not
sponsored if they were sponsored then
you could get you know it would be worth
doing but timewise and like money-wise
it's expensive yeah out of my pocket -
I'm not like yeah and the guys are not
I'm not paying them they're just doing
me a favor yeah I being in it dude
you're paying them an exposure sure but
I don't really count that I would love
to pay them I just don't have the budget
yeah it all goes towards making the
music video yep one of those those are
the ones that take the longest and
that's why I don't know but with you
guys I don't know I mean what what's it
your turn
what do I say I don't know I mean I mean
that's that's the one but for you
personally like your experience what is
the longest one for you I guess the one
that I made out of the videos I created
like which one took the longest for you
to like partake in is actually probably
might've been this the ghost-hunting one
cuz you were the only editor really no
I'd switched over to Greg oh a large
chunk of it yeah I mean that took a long
time but that wouldn't be one that I
look back you're like wow that was just
took us such a long time I mean we had
like a an unfortunate loss of progress
during the process but that that's I
don't really I mean yeah I don't know I
can't really think I mean that has to be
pretty much the one that is answered
because mine is my experience is
different in terms of like I can't think
of like a first channel one I can't I
guess I mean I guess the obvious one
will be Dragonball I mean that was a
long time ago it took a long time or any
of those big effects for yes you know
those want to take a long time cuz I
mean yeah people don't know we don't
know how long it takes
yeah it's okay it doesn't matter all we
do is make podcast now anyway I think
one comment that annoys me the most is
like just Ryan can't you make more
videos I could I definitely could I
could post three times a day but it
I bet you I could I would shoot I'll
steal them right now in two hours but to
where you watch it if you watch it sure
I'll make I'll make ten videos a day
yeah that's easy but we'll watch it but
that's not the type of content you come
to him for as well it's well I mean some
people like that stuff but like it's
just not what I am I like doing for one
yeah yeah to the super employee board
you know thank you
Tata nine nine three zero nine one nine
shouting yeah thanks for the question
anyway that was yeah we got some
Twitter's out of the way we don't
anymore about whatever we know enough
Twitter question okay we can do more
next time it's just that we can all have
very similar ones you know yeah but yeah
be original damn dude I mean you know
what we should do which is fun we should
just pull like what we do for you - why
don't we just pull from the comments
section dear Ryan there's so many yes
good I saw good questions every time I
walk back to podcast there's way better
questions in the in the comments section
I like what a bunch just go look it up
so right now there's we change it for
the next one if you guys leave if you
guys have interesting stuff that's you
know I think the thing I like about it
is people can upload it yeah you have
good questions that people care about
versus like not no offense to be with
left those twitter questions is just a
lot of times are very like stuff we've
already answered also we only had two
hours for this one cuz we didn't really
give time yeah yeah so was leaving you
were questions you were questions yeah
because uh I mean I think I like the
YouTube system I think it's in terms of
like the uploading system at least it
shows like what people care about yeah
so leave some interesting stuff up both
the ones you like just like a dear Ryan
I like that yeah dude okay this is weird
but Vancouver and Toronto got some hot
girls I know you guys are taking but
they got I mean doesn't mean we can't
acknowledge that I mean your type though
I don't can I talk about your type real
this I do why no because it's really
interesting to me and maybe other people
share the same thing it's not a bad
thing it's just like roasting well how
does that mean roaster are you beat cuz
see
means you think think of it as an insult
then well no cuz every time you you find
one way to because it's so interesting
you're an interesting person cific she
looks like Paco SAP and punk goes yeah
or you'll be like what well you so you
Paco I don't know if this is a common
thing but you said that you really like
girls with skinny arms yeah
specifically arms I like the stomach not
like the legs or skinny arms you said
like haven't heard that finish you said
breakable I've been with the girls who
weren't break but I mean that that just
gives you a picture in your arm yeah
that looks very brief in your head now
your arm
I just find it so interesting it's just
very interesting to it is I've never
I've never heard of that like that's
your interest what that is so specific
that's why cuz I say a lot of things
that other guys would say but then that
we different like nobody can it can also
display like you can imagine a whole
person just based off of that one thing
off their arm yeah I accept this
challenge we got to find those pictures
and we're gonna test him okay you know
we're like oh do you think she looks
like well what are you trying to picture
oh you like those really tiny girls not
necessarily tiny I actually wanted to
date somebody who's taller than me for a
long time I know are a lot of I still
would but I personally would prefer and
I know I'm not tall but I don't really
like when the girls taller no most guys
are like that most guys don't want to do
it like a whole like oh you want to feel
effeminate like is it it must be
something to have something to do you
don't mind Oman is shorter than you only
by a little bit yeah but she's tall
she's I think she's my height may be
taller possibly it was like five eight
yeah yeah no I'm fine not knowing I win
it's not the only way yeah yeah but you
do have a specific type I do that's why
I just know things a negative thing I
don't know why you gotta be like so
defensive I'm always defensive when Ryan
brings something up I'm like
has lost it hasn't been bad whatever I
said that was bad there's a lot of
things I can't say on this podcast make
you look bad dude don't make you look
bad I'm here to guess you have Paco you
asked me a fan your preferences in girls
they're great
dude yours to Monica is like she's
awesome like not just like physically
looking she's like a really nice
down-to-earth like genuine person thank
you but how's your arms look she has she
has good arms not breakable not break it
wasn't like very tone very toned I just
thought it was funny because it was like
the first time I've ever heard that yeah
somebody they've even heard collarbones
I didn't know that was her that when I
used to wear more what do you call those
not tank tops eunuch Phoenix
oh maybe v-neck yeah yeah like it was a
tropical arts oh my god I like his
collarbones and there was like I
remember when that first started
happening was like this is a trend wow
people actually like that isn't bones I
think it's a feature it's a physical you
can see it looks yeah they're surgeon
things like that I just like some people
have very sharp jaw lines you know
people start collar I don't even know
what that looks like some people have
outlines in their sweatpants you know I
don't like a wallet yeah I mean the
bigger the wallet you know then you like
that man's got a little receding there
that is true he does well under taxes
don't I'd have no idea I didn't take my
pills today oh you didn't know I'm off
birth control better be careful
dude it's so you guys let's talk about
that a little bit you guys have been to
Japan oh yeah yeah yeah and I was I'm
jealous because I haven't been on any
trips we went on the book to her but
that was just me and Ryan and that was
yeah that was really fun for me
Japan was by far our favorite trip for
sure he got super hooked up yeah shout
out to Ben Grubbs was working at YouTube
so there is this thing called geek week
right and essentially I do I just didn't
want to go because I was like I need to
make videos and like what if we what if
we give you a budget fly all your all
your team
you know essentially we'll make you a
video so you not to worry about that but
you basically had a one week vacation in
Japan yeah and then you promote it on
geek week and promote on geek week so it
was like a win-win you know you get a
vacation and you get a video usually
what stops me from going places I need
to work on something yeah so we did that
and YouTube Google they have so much
money they put us in the Ritz like the
nice one of the nicest hotels in Tokyo
Ritz Carlton in in Tokyo in Roppongi
it's like the business district very
fancy super nice I think that's a gaijin
hunter and there was um what does that
mean it's like we're the Japanese girls
look for a white guy foreigners type of
thing I didn't know it looked like super
like it looked like businessmen area
yeah yeah super nice and definitely
expensive not that we'd had to pay for
it yeah but they gave me will Sean and
Greg just four of us yes we all had our
own suite about the size of like so
pointless suite had two beds yeah
it was so pointless but it was like the
best like it's hard to beat when you're
four you guys even said that you ended
up sleeping in each other's really I
don't think I slept in mind maybe yeah I
think we gave was that the we gave like
it let someone sleep in ours or
something but yeah I don't think it was
too big there's too much room and and it
was together anyway and had chocolates
where you guys every night every morning
we had you chocolate spray but to be
fair on the trip there was a lot of work
yeah like we were working the majority
of the time we're filming we're like
going to locations yeah and you guys are
doing the NADA to a video I don't know
yeah yeah official fake no to video and
then the we did some meeting read stuff
like that yeah but um yeah that was
interesting I was it was for sure a good
trip best trip and you guys did an onsen
yeah that's what I was saying we're
jealous I wasn't being sarcastic we're
jealous that you're going to Japan I
love Japan yeah cuz we had such a but
it's such a um such an interesting place
it's the only time I went on a trip
somewhere where I felt like this is
actually like a completely different
country because no one understands you
yeah like in Singapore people still
speak English
Hong Kong actually no I take that back
we went that mean changing that wasn't a
good experience I had a horrible thing
that felt the same more like no one
really yeah
taxi drivers trying to scam me and
Derrick the whole time they're trying to
overcharge us like double and we
couldn't get anywhere and the people who
brought us out kind of weird like
stranded they just rotting like you know
we had no idea children working we
couldn't find a hotel like it was fun so
in Japan I would say go to an onsen
preferably one that you actually have to
take your clothes off and sit and tell
people what I wants it is it's like a
bath house or like a spa break it's like
a spa place yeah yeah and now dude I
honestly want to go to one where it's
like old ladies yeah that's what we went
that's what I want to do and also go to
ski G fish market
no that clothes I thought they had they
moved locations or something yeah well
go to wherever like wake up super early
or stay up all the way to like 4 or 5
and come and try and do that I'm gonna
try to do the the mati carts which is
the Mario oh yeah I'm gonna try and do
that there's like he's a Kaia they have
a so we didn't go in there yeah but they
have some weird stuff in jet in Japan oh
yeah for sure these people and I think
what I can say because I haven't you out
there they're weird dude they're weird
they do some weird stuff mm-hmm but it's
at the same time they're like the nicest
people like go never meet any more
polite have better service and in Japan
to me I don't know just my opinion but
they do some weird stuff like his
process Club that we went to remember
there was this place called Black Rose
yep and it's a S&M bar you know what
that is yeah yeah like would be nice
they do that and they do like whatnot
that we did it was closed so I don't
know if you did you ever tell this story
I don't know but we were with like the
person who was taking us around I like
you were just trying to show us like
weird stuff weird stuff fun time and we
went up to this bar and just you and him
just me and him and we was elevator the
elevator opens up and you step right
into the bar and it was red velvet all
over the walls and can't melted candles
everywhere I was like black furniture
and we
walking was completely empty and I was
like do you think we should go in here
like what's gonna happen we walked to
the end of the bar he just like like
walks in dude to do like American guy
hey everybody here and I was just like
um I think they're close and he's like
yeah I guess their clothes and they just
laugh but I came down I was like kind of
scared like that terrifying it creeped
me out
yeah but I'm pretty sure if that bar
would have been open we would have had a
different experience oh for sure that's
what I mean though I think that's the
kind of stuff that you would do yeah I
probably do some ways though like that
yeah yeah I think there's a good amount
of them they're pretty excited for you
mr. Ainge better bring back some good
stories for this podcast and then film
it yeah I actually wanna try and do like
uh I was really inspired cuz I just saw
the Conan yeah it out Without Borders
something that dude he's hilarious man
so funny like I'm inspired I want to do
something like this right things don't
you feel like only he can get over sure
he says some things and he like the way
he's so charismatic that he's able to
act a certain way when people will laugh
yeah you did it
you'd be like your comments would just
be the opposite you know I mean maybe
well that's why you being a comedian is
about being self-aware you know and just
like understanding how people perceive
you yeah so I I mean like it shouldn't
change but he what's being said is still
the same thing like he says some things
and he does some things that I feel like
if Logan Paul did it oh for sure exactly
the same as sure he would receive the
exact opposite response
hmm but it's just based on likability
how are we going in on this part about
what is it is time what I mean just
extending that conversation because
that's a conversation in itself is it
how like people's actions yeah aren't
the same just because of who they are
yeah of course you know I mean it's not
necessarily fair but I think it is is it
fair I do think it is so you think it's
fair like Jesse Smollett is famous so
he's able to get out of a crime that he
committed no I don't really no no no
there's no way I thought of it because
that's I just saw a video today yeah
that he's not getting talked about that
what a Chicago Police Department was
basically saying like it's the reason
why
he's getting away with this it shows
that yeah if you're famous we have money
you can get away with things yeah and
that's what I mean in like not people
aren't treated the same you see who they
are and I I mean I don't think that's
fair yeah
well what I'm talking about is like the
whole likability thing if you've built a
foundation and a character behind you
sure that shows that you know I you have
a positive attitude and you're trying to
do things for the better that you know
certain things that you do he would
should have an understanding of okay
there's a reason behind this it's not
purely for what he's just saying I think
it's very important to yeah build a
foundation and context just like the
Ryan Higa foundation giving back to the
community with the one best day ever at
a time yeah going nominate somebody if
you have somebody and then obviously
we're gonna fact-check we're not just
gonna you know you didn't give yourself
up best day ever and then you know
there's there's rules and stuff you can
follow there just go to writing a
foundation org anyway nice plug thank
know solid with that yeah don't worry
it's non profit nonprofit very cool
there's people who've donated and if you
donate it's not going to me it's all
going back into creating this show yes
day ever
it's very cool just so you know cool
alright yep thank you guys for tuning
into the appeal podcast again sorry this
one was incredibly random follow us at
off the pill Twitter uh-huh this bothers
me so he'll pop guys gonna write it down
on the wall over there do that off the
pill on Twitter at off the pill podcast
on Instagram and this time we're gonna
be taking questions from your comments
as well yeah we won't normally take them
from Instagram why don't we plug that we
should take some from Instagram we
should do an Instagram question a
Twitter question YouTube question I like
that
okay just viewer questions yep we're
gonna get questions from everything so
follow us there leave a comment and
we'll hopefully get to it oh no I made
that a question if we don't your voice
is garbage what's the what's the word
today ooh
not purple elephants believe him another
one to see who's loyal mm-hmm although
people I saw people skip I know for a
fact they skip to the end so next time
we'll do one now but next time
do I know the work that the one right
now is I didn't skip to the end okay
I didn't skip T type that if you're
you're a real one I've never said that
before
if you if you stay to the end you're
real a ride with me I learned what that
meant today yep RIPD r.i.p yeah baby oh
babe
alright see you guys next time I just
realized I didn't dude three two one
no what change it up curveball
I didn't skip to the end you guys next
time