you know that you have a really big
pimple when you're like autofocus and
you can still see it
gross hey guys sorry I haven't posted a
video in the past couple weeks we were
on such a good spree and then you know
we're posting every single week for like
a month and a half and then I um did
what I always do
and I ruined it because I wrote
something that I knew was gonna take a
long time to make it's been about three
weeks and it's getting pretty close but
it's still not done hopefully it'll be
worth all that time probably not and I
don't want to spoil it or I don't want
to give away too much but just to get
you guys excited and because I made you
guys wait so long here is a tiny preview
of what's to come next week pretty
exciting right fine I'll give you guys a
real preview at the end of the video but
we'll get to that later back to this
video as most of you probably already
know I tend to make a lot of puns
I know I know most people don't like
puns they say it's like the easiest joke
to make and it's the lowest form of
comedy and honestly sometimes I feel
like I don't even have a choice I didn't
train myself this way I've always been
like this seriously I can't help it like
literally see like this is a perfect
example of a bad one because that's not
even a good pun for literally it's not
even lit Oh guess it just needed to be
lit orally that's the face you were just
making right yeah I get that a lot but
hey it could have been worse you know at
least I'm not one of those people who
makes puns out of the word pie I mean
those by far are the least funny puns
funny ones funny fun what hate when that
happens that's the other face that I get
a lot but in all seriousness guys I'm
not even joking when I say I can't help
but think of funds I think of a lot of
people are very similar to me like think
we can't help it it just it just happens
and that's not a good thing gets very
distracting actually like I'll be
talking to someone and they'll say
something that triggers me to think
about a pun of what they just said and
then I don't hear what they said because
I was trying to think of the fun and a
lot of people like to call it a DD or
attention deficit disorder but I think
that is inaccurate because it's not a
lack of attention a so called
a DV or ADHD people we are paying
attention but to everything that's all
it is I'm paying attention to everything
specifically to puns we're just people
paying attention to puns PPAP yep I
think that's the only thing that's more
upsetting than a bad pun old overused
memes that aren't relevant anymore how
about that
this videos like a test to see how long
you can endure
horrible things that are being done to
you sure half the people clicked away by
now but for those of you that are still
here I thought of a fun little challenge
that well to me it's fun because I like
punch or call me immature I don't care
what people say I personally still
believe that puns are comic coal I mean
obviously I don't love all of them some
are better than others send me for
example to me I find liza Koshi to be
well is that Hillary Clinton yep
why did you photoshop Liza's face on her
blood cuz I think she's Hillary yes
I hate we are never gonna get to the
actual challenge unless that challenge
has already begun no it hasn't the
challenge is as simple as the name
sounds the pun challenge it's all about
making pie the twist is that instead of
just hand picking easy convenient words
to make your puns work you have to use a
random word generator and try your best
to make any of those work in any way
possible
I know that sounds really simple and
easy but trust me you can make this as
difficult or as easy as you want it to
be so this is the random word generator
which if all you have to do is Google
random word generator and one of them
will pop up there's like a bunch of them
right now it's set to one word so it'll
make one word at a time but you can
change that if you want to make it more
difficult for yourself I said it's easy
or difficult as you want to make it what
is the wheelchair superhero do to get
places key roles do you think Derek
doesn't put on sunscreen in the Sun why
it's just how he rolls
[Laughter]
[Music]
Oh with me I knew that was coming to you
Jimmy a note
[Music]
Harmonie night he's laughing who said
this uh lens cap pal looks like what
reaches peanut butter cup
what who lights and camera setup for
what for action
yeah that's a lot of fur action what
major are graffiti artists really good
at what market eggs how do you make a
lonely woman happier more kitties like
morgue or kitties what is a priest with
a lot of saliva VA's favorite pastime so
descriptive sprayer
I think it's brand say fiction one two
words yep I just decline that buting we
call it the bad pun challenge instead
because that's what these are three
words I mean it was funnier for shown
dip poor thing had to pay define but I
only had to pay sense when the train
comes why it will go you're just doing
just from Hawaii people and nobody else
is gonna get it act like one Rick Riley
can just go to the scary so what do you
think about my new place I don't know
it's kind of cherry oh it's actually
really good thanks man I mean I have
been a musician my whole life so
[Music]
you I know have a problem with what I'm
addicted to kitchenware
hope to Chrome doesn't matter if it's a
can or Bowl like I'm chromatic I'm
gettin chubby I'm getting like a double
chin and when I lean back turn to do a
quadruple chin like no that's like one
and a half tops
now that you see that over there now
that's a fortune what are you drinking
tea with a straw yeah it's a straw a
drink hey did you know that humans
breathe in oxygen and it turns into
carbon monoxide so it turns into carbon
dioxide yes sometimes it does I cannot
believe lit everyone's just gonna like
my photo no one's gonna comment for real
and all over the furniture damn bro you
skipping leg day again you know me man
you know son two things you want to
always look for in a girl number one her
fragrance and number two the white ship
puts carrots up her nose
why you're probably not the best
examples but um you guys get the point
and like most challenges I'm supposed to
call out a bunch of people to do this
but I actually thought it'd be better to
ask you guys I tweeted it out and said
who are some of the best people when
making puns and these are the common
names that popped up but like I said
everyone's invited not just big
youtubers I just want to see more puns
it's a dying art and I want to bring it
back and it's easy to do you don't have
to make it into a skit like oh I did
there's no rules just have fun with it
and that's what this challenge is really
all about celebrating puns and getting
rid of the negative stigma around them
because like I'm
and earlier some people we can't help if
PPAP is a real serious disorder that I
made up it affects everyone in the world
that's the real reason why we're all
here not just to bring BiPAP awareness
but to finally bring an end to punch Amy
just because most people happen to hate
puns doesn't mean that you need to
accompany them in punishing those who
make them beep understanding have an
open mind don't be late to the movement
be punctual every single part of you can
make a difference it doesn't matter
where you are whether you're famous like
Stefan curry on elevate Cruz Kim
Kardashian lil pun or just a normal
person riding in your average suburban
being driven by a man in a turban to the
local 7-eleven every pun is encouraged
to join the fight to end this epidemic
once and for all because we all know
it's better to fight with word puns and
web pounce and that all depends
[Music]
guys message brought to you and pay for
better Hillary as one nation I'm pretty
sure everyone's gone by now I promise
you guys I was gonna play you a preview
to the big video that we're working on
right now so I will do that right no it
was crazy right anyway thank you guys so
much for making it this far into the
video be sure to go and tweet and
comment and go harass the person that
you want to see try this challenge they
have no choice and so that they're
forced to do it I can make sure you guys
come back next week for that crazy video
I just played I promise you guys and you
know I don't promise things off in here
but I promise you guys this next video
is gonna be real lit
it's just gonna be a real letdown
[Music]