I am one haircut away and getting rid of
all this decaying dead hair but you
still need to live with it for now hey
guys if you didn't catch the last video
I'm currently in the middle of a move
right now I apologize this room is
incredibly at least temporary I swear I
should be moving soon but anyway over
the past few years I've always gotten a
bunch of comments asking me how are HPC
or the Ryan Higa production company came
to be you know these guys
[Music]
wait we're doing mine now what where's
my fries you have to let me know so I
can at least look and get a free spring
and I guess what I really think about it
I never did introduce who rhpc was or
when they join it kind of just started
showing up in videos now and then and
then eventually all the time you guys
kind of just figured out who was who
what today it's all gonna change because
for the very first time in our HPC
history for the very first time I
already said that I be telling you guys
all of you viewers out there for the
very first time the story of all the
rhpc squad came to be I don't know why I
did it
so like that it's not the story isn't
that epic it's pretty boring actually or
is it no it's it's actually not that
interesting at all or epic look I'm just
gonna be honest and tell you guys the
honest story so I apologize if it's a
little boring I'm just gonna do the best
that I can do relaying the story to you
guys without exaggerating too much from
my own memory even though I can't
remember things that well it was the
year 2009 when I escaped the unlove
training academy
get back here chops on about Liars
tuition
[Music]
thank you I never thought you would
actually ever help once I got my tuition
back I had all the money to travel to
another city
the infamous city known as no sandy
lease which is Japanese for if you want
to make it here
don't be Japanese the city was beautiful
when I first arrived everyone seemed
nice and pleasant and all of them were
beautiful little did I know these were
some of the best actors and imposters in
the world luckily for me I had found my
first allies you gotta be a little more
careful around here who are you I'm
d-trix these are my friends will howdy
and Gregg County wait what gaudí yeah I
have gout ate too much oysters as a kid
that's why I had to replace most of my
body oh okay
and that's when I started to ease off on
the sea
after a couple years battling off the
imposters I knew we couldn't keep up
this pace it was time to go back to
Vegas
they got us completely surrounded great
to the drop of smoke after that and we
all head northeast for the desert smoke
they don't cover us that fall guys go on
I'll hold them already talking about it
alone out here don't worry about me
I got reinforcements
my god
[Music]
all right Shawn the hell are you doing
out here I just got done with the
Academy so I came to hang out
crazy come on Shawn wasn't a lie early
on before we went to different academies
like myself he finished his training at
the academy in the city of roses he
easily became the brains of the group
[Music]
hello there hello greetings sir Tom shot
him down open up shop Oh No and that's
how we met Derek he was a mystery
unpredictable a wild card I believe the
first time we met we asked him to take
us to a shop for some food and beverage
he brought us here we still don't know
why Derek brought us here but we're sure
glad he did but that's what we came
across one of our most valuable members
Dana
[Music]
there was final piece to the puzzle now
knew we had everything
the ultimate team known as the rhpc
squad
hello what you're just gonna give
everyone else epic intros and leave me
out well I was getting to that if you
would let me finish it's on the next
page oh well it better be epic like
everyone else is it not a stupid joke
it will okay so may i whatever and there
was final piece to the puzzle now knew
we had everything we needed to create
the ultimate team known as the rhpc
squad oh and then we added the stripper
to the end yeah I was pretty accurate
stuff go yeah that's good