[Applause]
welcome back to the right TV show 2006
when we first started but got cancelled
after two shows due to all views and
ratings No
you know what they say though what do
you do when you fall off the horse you
make lemonade we have a very special
guest coming on tonight a lot of you new
to the show might not recognize him
right away
but he has been in my videos since the
very beginning from how to be ninja to
bromance
please welcome seen boo boo Jai Oh shiny
Sifu Jo shine you already know me why
are you acting this is East Tennessee so
see tell me a little bit about how you
really got started why'd you keep
calling me that
what see you keep saying scene well what
do you want me to call you guys so Tom
you've seen a lot of people have been
commenting my videos they have these
same things like where's scene I haven't
seen seen in a long time
has anybody seen scene where have you
been why haven't you been in videos
lately do you really want me to answer
that huh
but you already know where I've been
uh-huh and you could just tell everybody
we're all right well I'm Wow see this is
the Ryan Higa show not the scene boards
everyone to death with his life story
show right
so tell me seems Shawn Stan you said
you're actually in college in Oregon
studying engineering correct I didn't
actually get to say that but yes that's
correct
tell me then what is a Liopleurodon
that's not really an engineering
question so I wouldn't know Lana this is
starting to get ready yeah we'll be
right back after a few words from our
sponsors stay tuned my gosh you startled
me don't be afraid because I'm here and
I'll always be here that wasn't a real
commercial you're not a real commercial
el Rebecca just joining us right here
with stem fiji water brand tell me Stan
John Dean Sean Sean yes
so tell me Jason other any new products
you're working on are you actually gonna
let me say it this time or are you just
gonna cut me off again
uh-huh oh you mean you're gonna let me
speak or uh-huh you're just cuz I'm
seeing is actually working on starting
up his own YouTube channel of course
after he graduates from college that's
actually correct for once and he has a
little clip that he wants to show you
guys as a preview to what his channels
gonna look like so take a look I kinda
edit your clip I hope you don't mind
wait what what's up everybody sean
fujiyoshi here I just wanted to let you
all know that I will be starting a new
YouTube channel and it's gonna be
awesome
because if you subscribe to see you'll
be seeing things similar to this that's
drama comedy legit parkour weight
physical turns to the camera beautiful
turns to the camera with wiggle turns on
the camera with wigs and parkour yeah
big bouncing inflatable green ball land
is like realistic but not real goddamn
and of course lots of scenes with scene
in it that you've never seen before see
so stay tuned and keep an eye out
because my channel should become
very soon but my channels already here
you know what Wow look dude tomorrow my
show is this funny to you making fun of
me how many one am you see you know I
can't believe after everything we've
been through you still choose me like
this you can on your own show I mean
we've known each other for so long not
just the videos we've done together
not even all the blood sweat and tears
we shared in high school sports but
we've known each other since we were
little kids and yet I come here all the
way from Oregon and you can't even see
my name right so really all you want
just say my name say your name say my
name truth is I don't even know your
name I know your mother's name destiny
what everybody give it up for our guest
tonight Destiny's Child
[Applause]
[Music]
why is that see Shawn sorry five six
seven eight
[Music]
that's something good