these happen to you I spilled liquids
all over my table I spilled liquid all
over the floor I feel liquids in my
dad's hi I'm Ryan Higa and I'm gonna be
showing you a great new product it's
called the chef like that it's a grits
and that's been in tall shabby and rank
technology don't believe me watch this
if you have a spill on your table and
ordered every rag or towel would just
soak it up oh so boring me but thanks to
this shampoo I love you will you not
soak up the liquid but you just push it
off the table still not impressed if you
aren't enough look around a second chef
free that's right you're getting duchamp
look reservoir that's a $5 value for
just $19.99 so what are you waiting for
or did your shower and you'll be saying
WOW every time