hi I'm Ryan Higa and i'm sean fujiyoshi
and boy we had something really special
to tell you we have exclusive SuperDuper
outrageous go off the mysterious unknown
super secret secret nobody knows the
secret except for the
supercalifragilistic see people's secret
Tom nobody knows the secret not even the
newspapers or the radio or the
television or my dog my dad or my rat or
my pandas or my Jackson but my fish
not even my big green ball moves a
secret you guys are the first one to
know the super duper outrageous casas
mysterious unknown super secret wait if
we tell them our super duper outrageous
cool also mysterious unknown super
secret it won't be much of a super duper
great school also mysterious I'm not
super secret that's right
now I where I'll tell you
ha just kidding without you right now
here it is
drum roll please we hurry up my face is
getting sore we are gonna be a movie
yeah we just wanted to thank all of you
guys who are watching and supporting us
without you guys you probably wouldn't
have gotten this opportunity and please
don't ask us if this is our last video
because it is ha just kidding but
seriously