could you just do something else it's
been like a month since to be amazing no
one cares about Miley Cyrus anymore
two months what it's been roughly two
months I don't get it do you not read
the text at the beginning of the video I
don't think we're supposed to see the
tape look it's been one month since the
VMAs we need to put on a Miley Cyrus
video no we done yes we do will you get
that through your head will you huh oh I
got it what is on it this is another
pitch about me twerking I don't even
know who working Sean wait a second what
if we've been looking at this the wrong
way
what if there's a deeper meaning by wait
a second hold that thought well what
have we been looking at this the wrong
way what if there's a deeper meaning
behind all of this
behind what hi Miley behind why she's
different why she's changing why she's
been twerking so much I got it what is
Miley really isn't changing what if
she's purposely trying to ruin her image
so that she can intentionally lose fans
because some secret organisation is
trying to use her popularity to take
over the world it all makes sense now
[Music]
what the hell are you talking about how
do you even come up with these
ridiculous conclusions will it's so
simple how do you not see it seriously
well shut up Sean you don't know what
he's talking about either I don't like
doing no he gets it fine
prove it then at the same time what are
we talking about we're talking about my
body sizes not teaching about Percy
ruining our image dollar to lose fast at
some secret organization doesn't use it
to take over the world and the reason
why you can't just come on and say it
publicly is because whoever the person
and/or persons that are targeting her
bless you thank you I'm powerful enough
to stop her from saying anything I don't
know what just whatever you guys really
think that's what happened yes don't be
so naive what I said you're being naive
ie don't become words it's a real word
no but why didn't my knee do something
about this sooner why now isn't it
obvious the secret organization can only
brainwash kids which is why Miley was
brainwashed when she was a kid but once
you became an adult they lost control
and that's why she quit had him on town
on the show when she was 18 so dumb
you're just making up ridiculous
assumptions basing off with no evidence
whatsoever don't be so naive so Miley
sacrificing her career to save the world
not just that see it be amazed when she
was twerking I think I saw something you
see this it think she can tell us
something tell us what the secret who
this organization is and what they're
trying to do with that
look the VMAs are huge everyone watches
it but you know what gets more views in
the VMAs the Super Bowl and who
performed in the last Super Bowl Beyonce
and Beyonce performed with our old birth
name Destiny's Child and one of the
city's child's biggest songs is say my
name say my name yet nobody knows
Destiny's housing's we know her mother's
name destiny and guess what Miley Cyrus
his real name is destiny destiny hope
Cyrus if Miley is destiny and Beyonce's
originally Destiny's Child Miley is
beyond his mom which means jay-z is
Miley's son-in-law since she's married
to Beyonce and jay-z as we all know is
rumored to be a part of what secret
society that's represe
by a pyramid with an eyeball on you
don't mean I do they're all apart with
the infamous one and only Key Club Key
Club think about it what shape does a
pyramid with an eyeball on it resemble a
keyhole and a key will represent
something lock something secretive and
the only way to see a secret that's
locked up is with the symbolic one eye
by looking through the keyhole really
you really believe that the reason why
Miley Cyrus has changed because of Key
Club the program for high school
students who do community service
project you really don't get it do you
no I don't get how do you open a keel
with a key and what does that key you my
desk Miley was trying to show us the
whole time what do you do when you have
a key you put into the key go and you
twist it a little bit and jerk it around
until it unlocks you twist and you jerk
you twerk that's the key to our key if
we twerk we'll be able to see the truth
you've got to be kidding me what I'm not
gonna lie out with you up until naive
but that wasn't like the very beginning
of the video oh my god guys here just
just watch me okay here look
[Music]
working children while I was going to
show us the whole time that's the key
[Music]
hello right Miley Cyrus I see you've
found the key behind my greater missive
wait what you discovered the truth
behind wild things working so much so
it's not a cry for help an attempt to
expose Key Club as a brainwashing
organization
no silly my song we can't stop my being
made before MS my entire change in
persona it's just a statement a
statement I'm gonna be Who I am that's
pretty close
even if some people might think I
mentioned it [ __ ] some might even
describe this ratchet at least some
being myself but what about all the
people that say you're a bad influence
for kids well right they're telling kids
to be themselves bad and I don't know
what good is it
look people may not see my message right
now but I can't give up just yet
cuz there's all it's gonna be another
mountain I'm always gonna wanna make it
moving but I just have to keep climbing
the climb because I can almost see it
that dream I'm dreaming between that I
can have the best of both worlds to be a
good influence you have to keep partying
here in the USA and no matter how many
little wrecking balls flying to my life
trying to break my Achy Breaky Heart I
know deep down I can't stop and I won't
start I can't be I just got to keep
being
I gotta keep doing me I gotta keep doing
my lots and lots of mouthing Wow
so sorry I had you all wrong we all do
what's important Ryan is that now you
know knowing is half the battle no no I
wouldn't say that knowing is half the
battle would even say it's it's 25% of
the battle doing so no I was just trying
to give you a cool note to leave on but
I guess you want to end this awkwardly
so wait does somebody say Molly what no
I said Maile shot hello Ryan hey you
there where where's Molly what what are
you talking about you're in the middle
of your sentence and you just froze yeah
so do you have an idea or you know what
guys let's let's not make this video
what we have to well if we do we're not
gonna bash her like everyone else and
what are we gonna do tell them the truth
the truth about what the truth Oh Miley
Cyrus
so what is it what you just said the
truth about Milan wrote it down what is
it weren't you watching the flashback
the vision I just had she she twerks to
make the world a better place
[Music]
yes the target has been incepted he
doesn't suspect a thing
cool very well my lease has that mean
yes you're in
[Applause]