stairs
scoop the dirt dirt take the dirt back
upstairs please check on dirty Bowl okay
now what is it what this is a check on
dirt
so what dirty money it's in a bowl so
check on dirt that's no better check on
dirt in a bowl what does that mean check
on chatter on dirty Bowl check under the
book on dirty whoa oh my gosh it's check
under table check under the table I was
here the whole time we almost had that
one guys we're close you guys were close
woke us up in the middle of night just
for them what no not just that I
actually want to tell you guys that I
think I might have made a breakthrough
on project B project B you mean you're
finally gonna tell us what you've been
working on yes and that is because I
need your guy's help
like really close him why didn't you
just wake us up normally is that not
normal there guys why are we wasting
time let's get to the lab what lab you
don't have a lab this is a house well
don't I stand back
there we go you did all that for a pen
what I need a pen how am I supposed to
show you guys what I've been working on
huh ton of ink though ya got a new one
right here anyway Oh see I knew you
didn't have some kind of secret lab uh
yes I do I just didn't access it yeah
let me guess some kind of keyboard comes
up again you put in some kind secret
code I scare comes down and robots like
hello Ryan and then it transforms the
whole room but no you just have to clap
hello Ryan lemonade anyone not bad
actually can I just come back I cut out
these the bathroom just pee in a cup
that's what I've been doing what the
heck is wrong with you why just go to
the bathroom it's right there told you
I've been working nonstop that's all the
time I've got time for pee breaks
actually I don't have to pee it's my
stomach kind of hurts no that's all the
more reason you should have some
lemonade it's good for your stomach
really so as you guys know our past
investigations have gone very
successfully as you know figure out the
truth behind Miley Cyrus and of course
proving the Illuminati is real but now
we've been asked to investigate another
mystery mystery of Beyonce's lemonade
album how is that even a mystery it's
just her oh but this album is completely
different see nobody knows what this
album is about there's a lot of
different theory some people believe
that this album is about infidelity and
how jay-z cheated on Beyonce but at the
same time some other people say well if
you really did cheat on her why are they
still together and more importantly why
did she release her songs and title the
platform that jay-z himself owned and
why is it even called lemonades there's
no explanation for that some people
believe that okay we get it there's a
bunch of conspiracy theories but this
better not be one of those Illuminati
thing no in fact it's a complete
opposite you see last time we talked
about the Illuminati we started with
apples because apples are by far the
most popular fruit they're eaten by
children and adults are used in schools
to represent our teachers all of our
technology comes from Apple even the
Bible speaks about apples in the story
of Adam and Eve all of a sudden in less
than a month nobody's talking about this
powerful fruit because there's another
fruit on the rise the rival to the app
with a complete opposite oranges like
apples and oranges
no what about bananas like more bananas
than anything see that's what I thought
at first oranges and bananas are way
more popular than lemon so why did
Beyonce choose lemons over all the other
fruits mixed to the letters C orange
banana six-letter words they don't fit
apple and lemon both fives but there's
an even bigger hint that beyond sea
lettuce that proves that there's more to
this album than we all thought what she
named it lemonade not lemon so what
that's just juice see but it is it what
you see every other fruit can be made
into a juice but not lemons apples
become apple juice oranges become orange
juice pineapple pineapple juice Kiwi
juice even tomato juice but not lemons
lemons become lemonade strange
Chum that is stream okay fine let's say
you're right and there's something more
to it now what we start with the most
famous saying about lemonade when life
gives you lemons you make lemonade
that's not the case here is it because
we're being given lemonade not lemons so
so Beyonce wants us to work backwards
see Beyonce has crazy following most of
them girls and they're so in love with
her they want to dedicate their lives to
being her followers they're so in love
with her they literally say things like
Amaya Beyonce is life and in this
scenario that's absolutely correct see
if we work backwards when life gives you
lemons you make lemonade
but if Beyonce is lie it should be when
Beyonce gives you lemonade you may
lemons exactly but that doesn't make any
sense oh it doesn't not yet one of the
first things that come to mind when you
say the word lemon sour I don't know
yellow right sour yo and if we continue
to work backwards the phrase we make
lemons becomes lemons make you what the
lemons make you do when you bite into
him squint because it's sour exactly and
when you squint you look more like an
Asian what dude that's racist
- and you squint you look more like
you're tired because your eyes are
smaller like an Asian yeah of course and
Asians are stereotypically known to be
yellow just like lemon again we continue
to work backwards yellow backwards is
Wally Wally like the Disney movie about
the earth coming to an end
see in that movie we think that wall is
the only remaining individual on earth
but there's another and coincidentally
her name is Eve just like Adam and Eve
who supposedly were the only two
individuals on earth as well and since
Eve is obviously Eve then Adam must be
wall-e
and since wall-e is actually wall-e
yellow backwards what they're really
saying is that Adam is yellow yellow
Adam yellow Adam in chemistry you
learned that cpk coloring is used to
distinguish atoms by color and the color
yellow is assigned to sulfur and sulfur
is an atomic number of 16 and it also
smells like rotten egg however if you
smell rotten eggs and you're not near a
volcano chances are is just somebody's
rotten egg farm and since eggs are
measured in dozens coincidentally the
same number of songs and Beyonce's album
if we take the atomic number of 16 and
count out all the songs we come all the
way back to the first song with the
remainder of four track four happens to
be the song named sorry but who else
just recently had the biggest hit in the
world name sorry Justin Bieber who if
you didn't know recently just dyed his
hair guess what color that's right yeah
but recently only a week after Beyonce
releases her lemonade album Justin
Bieber Shaye's off his yellow hair he
goes right back to his natural hair
color which is still kind of a off
yellow color which is awfully symbolic
and similar to peeling 11 as you peel
off the yellow outside and the inside is
an off yellow color which means the Pugh
is nothing more than a cover speaking of
covers when we see the album cover of
lemonade instantly you see the shape of
the lemon but there is a lot more to it
we work from the bottom up we see fern
if I had to guess what I don't want that
look like I would have to say it looks
like a bear and above that you see an
ear which is strange because if she were
a part of the Illuminati that'd be the
perfect place to put an eye but no this
is something new she put him here and on
her ear rings eerie and as we mentioned
before above that the lemon what don't
you get it
no bears rings lemons Beyonce is bearing
fruit and bearing fruit for a tree means
that it's growing fruits for a person
bearing fruit means that she's growing
something else if you peel off the cover
what she's really trying to say Yonsei
is pregnant see that's what lemonade
it's really about this has got to be one
of the dumbest ones you've had so far
there's so many holes in this well I
didn't say I was done yet there's more
yeah I told you guys I needed your help
I still haven't figured out what these
are yeah you really think Beyonce's
pregnant I don't see how feminie could
be about anything else well if she
really is I don't think she should be
drinking lemonade look how many carbs
there are 53 grams for one bottle that's
crazy
didn't eat three grams for three crab oh
my god
it's numbers what
53 grams you said you said there 53 in
there yeah 52 grams 83 grams 53 Grammys
huh Beyonce has the record for the most
Grammy nominations 53 of them way there
you go again connecting two completely
unrelated things it's 53 grams of
carbohydrates not granny exactly that's
was leading us to the next part if we
break it up it's just car bull hydrate
when you hear car bowl a bowl the size
of a car that's a really big bowl
hydrate has to do with liquids but if
we're talking about a bowl what kind of
liquids do you put in a bowl lemonade
but no it's soup oh now you have a
really big bowl of soup no a huge bowl
of soup a Super Bowl the Super Bowl
Beyonce was a halftime show performer
for to love him Super Bowl xlvii and 50
but she wasn't even really a made
performer in Super Bowl 50 she was just
in it there's kind of a big difference
oh there's a difference alright but
ain't that big what the difference
between Super Bowl 50 and 47 is 3 and 3
is our magic number one might say how so
beyond just 34 Jay Z's 46 when we add
their ages together we have 80 okay we
take our magic number three and subtract
bottom 80 we're left with 77 and 77 as
we all know is the product of 7 times 11
7-eleven 7-eleven the hit song that
Beyonce released three years ago but if
she planned this three years ago why now
he's on the anniversary of seven lemons
released this year Beyonce be 35 in 77
minus 35 at 42 the exact age jay-z was
when his daughter Blue Ivy was born 42
what what does their daughter even have
anything to do with 7-eleven was made
for their daughter come on if you really
listen to the lyrics wave your hands
side to side clap clap clap clap it my
hands up my hands up I stand up with my
hands up it does sound like a children's
song exactly because 7-eleven was
disguised to be for us but really it was
just for their daughter that's why the
lyrics are so bad of course since this
song is made for their daughter don't
tell me it's a coincidence at their
daughters 4 years old yet in seven years
she's going to be what
it isn't eleven the exact number of
songs that's on her album no you said it
yourself there's twelve songs precisely
see there's twelve songs but we got
eleven we were almost there we were this
close we were an inch away six inches to
be exact
the only number in any of her titles and
it's six the number six on her sixth
album six is our special number one
might say but I thought you said three
was our special number but no three is
our magic number because it's half of
six you see if we take it from where we
left off at eleven and we multiply it by
our special number of six we end up with
our final number 66 fifty-three 342 11
66 but but what do they mean I don't
know but it has to mean something if not
Beyonce when animated that obvious
obvious nothing about any of this is
zombie what are you talking about it was
so clear literally forcing these
connections they make no sense at all it
makes it what's even worse is you ended
up with nothing nothing what we have the
last piece those are the last five
number five hours I mean nothing
oh my god seriously it's a bad one sorry
I told you I wasn't feeling well dude
what the heck did you eat it smells like
rotten egg that's him huh rotten eggs
sulfur they're elements although
fifty-three 342 1166 the atomic numbers
three is lithium iodide lithium
molybdenum sodium dysprosium it's a
formula it all makes sense now
what does everything why Beyonce made an
entire album bashing her husband a man
why the majority of Beyonce's songs are
all about and for women even why there's
an ear on the album cover instead of an
eye Yonsei his giving
but to an idea no I group no one army
women to take over the world
what it's all starting is that formula
Shawn check that lemonade bottle head
dine the film but Minneapolis it's all
here see the see it's already begun but
we've been drinking this lemonade
exactly look at us we're fine yeah for
now who knows what's gonna happen later
look this is so stupid how do you even
come up with these ridiculous conspiracy
theories I really have to spell this out
for you look at the abbreviations see
this is not about the Illuminati the
Illuminati's around by men see Beyonce
starting something new she's giving
birth to a new group of powerful women
to not just take over the world the
previous Illuminati as well think about
it think about everything you've ever
heard from Beyonce she wants who to run
the world girls she wants although what
single ladies every single lady to rise
up in formation to go to flawless
irreplaceable army of grown women to
create the new Illuminati the lady
the 1180s I have that or she's just
pregnant look 10 minutes later we're all
drinking lemonade and we're still fine
but are we though oh wait how come my
name change oh that's right it wasn't a
cup I peed in a bottle