hey wait a man what's up hey what's
wrong man have a seat I know there's a
whoopee cushion under that pillow what
what are you talking I don't know what
you're talking about not stupid it's
April Fool's Day it's April first I
didn't even know do this every single
year strong man have a seat there's a
whoopee cushion there what telling
that's just how my new pillows look all
right April Fool saw a man ever see
there's a whoopee cushion there again
and this time you put a moustache on it
as if that's gonna trick me into why are
you always judging my pillows just sit
down man all right two years in a role
did the mustache was fake dude that
really wasn't whoopee cushion
and what's wrong man have a seat look I
know there's a whoopee cushion under
that pillow see at least this time you
didn't put a stupid moustache on it
thinking out a trick me really okay I
get it you're mad because I got you two
years in a row and now you've been extra
careful because you didn't get me I let
you prank me for the past how many years
because of how terrible you are this
whoopie cushion is not an April Fool's
prank it's barely even a prank at all oh
because you know jokes you haven't even
gotten me one spritz because I haven't
been tried then why don't you is that
really what you want or you already have
I was bringing me my favorite movie a
joke the sequel really now you've gone
too far you son of a you Kimmy
screw this place man what do you think
I'm stupid that's the oldest trick in
the book ain't falling for that one but
you didn't think I'd go back inside huh
oh hey oh thank god
please sir I need your help $3.00 cool
new tail isn't it lucky
I guess ice cream some soda and Funyun
see I give up okay I give up to stop all
the pranks you're the better prankster
you win okay you win what I want yes
okay you can just please stop I can't
take it anymore but I didn't even do my
prank yet what you mean this is the only
prank you set up yeah what about the
paint can and the clean wrap the
skateboard Legos no I didn't do any of
that what what about the other dollar
outside what other dollar it was you oh
my god Ryan are you okay I'm dying I
didn't do any of this I swear I didn't
do any of this at all
no it wasn't you what do you mean
because I did it what I set up
everything the cling-wrap
the dominoes the skateboard even the
dollar outside because I know that
random guy walks by everyday with his
gun looking for that dollar so you knew
you're gonna get shot yeah why just to
get you to this very spot what ah
April Fool's shut up thank you guys
again so much for watching if you want
to see bloopers and behind the scenes
for this video click the one the left if
you want to see the previous video click
the one on the right and from all of us
here at the right eager production
company we just want to wish you guys a
happy April Fool's I went on the wrong
key