hey guys so one of the most common
questions I get all the time man is here
Ryan are you single and for the past two
years I've been giving you guys the same
answer yes and then I get a whole bunch
of comments that are like how do you not
have a girl for your girl I can be your
girlfriend I'll be your girlfriend
honestly I appreciate it it is so
flattering it makes me feel good right
here on my boob but to be honest guys
you have no idea what it's like to date
someone like me there's a reason why
I've been single for so long I probably
have every single quality of the worst
boyfriend I am the opposite of romantic
I am the epitome of unromantic surprise
happy anniversary
oh thanks draw nothing but I mean most
couples give each other flowers or roses
the flowers are useless they just die
your Weezer you needed one right no in
why have your legs been so sandpapery
lately oh and you did need the
toothpaste because I've been using yours
for sir mine what about the cactus it's
for the bathrooms reminding to do
something about your pokey legs whether
I'm wrong or I'm right I have to win
every single argument even if I'm wrong
I didn't know the biggest animal in the
world was a blue whale no it's not it's
an Onix here's some cute you're stupid
I'm reading it right here then it's
wrong you always want to argue with me
why do you always have to argue with me
you're being really immature right now
you're immature you can't just copy what
I say you can one-zero right also I can
be very controlling no you can't go it's
just a family dinner are there gonna be
any guys there no was your dad going he
is I'm sold right now I get jealous very
easily mmm this is good I love it why
don't you just marry it then I always
leave the toilet seat up hey honey could
you start putting the toilet seat down
when you're done well then could you
start putting it up when you're done
two-zero Ryan and the worst quality of
all and probably the main reason why I'm
still single is because I tend to
overreact
just a little bit do you have to go you
already know too well how do they fly
have a safe flight have a safe flight
how dare you put that kind of pressure
on me I love the pilot I can control the
safety of my own planet No let alone the
entire flight you know sometimes you can
be really insensitive okay so maybe I
exaggerated a little bit we all know
that everyone has these qualities at
least to a certain degree because as we
all know nobody is perfect whether you
think it's your favorite celebrity or
youtubers or new boyfriend or girlfriend
you've been dating for the past month
they're all just as messed up as you are
because we're all human and the trick is
not to find the perfect person or the
perfect person to find the trick anyway
if you're in a relationship or if you're
single no matter what I just want to let
you guys know die Hey hi I just saw your
video and you're right how I'm still
filming it no one is perfect and I
forgive you because I still love you one
sec oh yeah I forgot to tell you guys I
have a really hard time saying I love
you to people
me too what did oh I just told you I
love you and you can't even say it back
to me I said me too
I love me too you know what just forget
it I can't believe I wasted all this
time on you goodbye Ryan and have fun
find someone that can put up with you
that could still hear her words echo in
my head as if it just happened yesterday
and that's when I realized I could not
would not shan't not let things end like
this
you have fun finding something they can
put up with you three zero right