hey guys so I don't know if it's just me
but I feel like lately a lot of people
have been a lot ruder to other people
than they have been in the past ruder
ruder I'm rude but he's ruder ruder what
why does that sound so weird little
spellcheck ruder nope no squiggly red
line so it must be a real word don't act
like you guys don't do that but anyway
kind of notice that people in general
seem to be getting ruder more rude earth
I feel like growing up I didn't win this
nearly as many room people as I do now
then again I did grow up in Hawaii and
if you're rude there most the time you
just get beat up I mean I guess beating
up people is a little rude too but I'm
off top anyway I feel like the world is
becoming more and more hateful and
negative place lately for example I was
at the coffee shop the other day and I
witnessed a guy who slipped and kind of
spilled some coffee and another guy who
reacted pretty ruefully problem row yes
if someone spills anything on you it's
pretty upsetting but you don't have to
go and curse them on and then another
day I was at the gym it was actually a
while back because I was at the gym
clearly you know I don't even lift bro I
was walking by these two fairly
attractive girls and being the nosy
person that I am I was kind of
eavesdropping on their conversation
basically they were talking about
another girl that they were looking at
that was on a treadmill do you see what
she's wearing you do not come in do it
mmm she ever heard of shaving and then
most recently which pretty much inspired
me to make this video I had to go to a
place where there's nothing but built-up
anger frustration and just all-around
rudeness and hate throughout the entire
facility next I said next if you're a
driver you know exactly what I'm talking
about but you get the point I mean I get
it everyone has bad days including
myself I mean I'm not gonna lie
sometimes I do feel like pushing back
the guy who bumped into me on a crowded
street or yelling at a waitress who
brought me the wrong order after making
me wait an hour or even flipping off a
guy who cut me off in traffic but then I
think of a motto that I kind of made up
and it's helped me be a much more
friendly and positive person we all know
all the generic sayings we heard growing
up you nicer to others or tree people
you want to be treated those sayings are
so vague and overused at the moment
something bad happens or we're having a
bad day we just completely forget about
which is why I created a new campaign
that is even more straightforward and
hopefully a little less forgettable they
treat people like they're dying can be
no it might sound a little negative but
it's the complete opposite if everybody
treated each other as if they were dying
people would be friendlier and more
forgiving for example if he knew a guy
was dying and he accidentally spilled
coffee on you I guarantee that you would
not yell at him and you would not curse
him I seriously don't worry about it
it's just a shirt most people would not
yell at a guy who's sorry the world
would have less Mean Girls because no
one talks crap behind a dying person's
back she's so inspirational seriously
she's so brave in general people would
just be nicer to each other hi so sorry
to keep you waiting look I do for you
but not only will people be nicer to
each other when people realize that
they're dying a lot of times that's when
people live life to its fullest no
longer will people have to put up all
the things they wanted to do in life no
longer where people have to wait to
their father's deathbed to hear the
words I've always been my son no longer
when people wait to chase after the real
dreams some people may know their
expiration date and some don't but in
reality we're all dying right now
because none of us live forever every
second of every day we're one step
closer to death and I think it's about
time we started treating each other like
it so the next time someone does
something bad or upsetting to you and
you feel like responding negatively just
remember if you want to make this world
a better place
spread the positivity treat people like
their died
hell that was so bad that was so cheesy
this entire video is so dying
inspirational I wish I had that kind of
courage so thank you guys again so much
for watching if you want to see bloopers
and behind the scenes click the one on
the left if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the right and if
you want to order your very own I'm
dying shirt well then you're in luck
because there is none and we kind of
made it up you got it from Target and we
just turned it inside out and we made
our own thing good but Target what