hey guys so I don't know if you guys can
tell her not but my voice is gonna be a
little bit more annoying than usual
because I'm sick in fact I've been sick
for a while now with be okay that the
illness has been gone for a while now
but really though I have been sick for
like two or three weeks so I apologize
for my voice and also my my hair which I
did not cut I don't know why I never
remember to cut my hair before I vlog I
know so many of you wonderful people
loved to point out how ugly my hair gets
minutes long but being the extremely
self confident person that I am it's a
good thing I don't care what you guys
think about my iboga oh now that works
what you love those days when you have
magical sneezes anyway I'm pretty sure
you guys know what memes are and one of
my favorite means is the unpopular
opinion meme you know the one where
people write their opinion on something
that most people don't agree with either
that or they agree with it and they're
too scared to say it out loud why did
you guys know I'm always gonna give you
guys my honest opinion as unpopular as
it may be I mean it does get me into
trouble sometimes but this isn't TV you
can't tell me what to say can't tell me
what the thing this is YouTube I can say
whatever I won this is the land of the
free in the home of the bees what yep
definitely have to pill today anyway
today's topic can be another touchy one
cyberbullying if you watch my draw my
life video you know that I was bullied a
lot when I was younger so of course I
think bullying is a problem but recently
it seems like cyber bullying is like the
main topic that people report on these
days you know from articles to new
stations to groups being started on
Facebook just to target cyber bullying
well I'm just gonna come out and say it
this is my unpopular opinion for the day
cyber bullying is a first-world problem
there I said it now bring on the hate
comments not just kidding don't cuz that
would be cyberbullying look don't get me
wrong I do believe that cyberbullying is
a problem but don't you think we should
be more focused on regular bullying
that's done in person coming from
somebody who was bullied in real life I
don't think it's really bullying if you
can escape it and I was being bullied in
school there was no escape I felt like I
was being backed into a corner to the
point where I wanted to kill myself cuz
I thought I had no other option I was
forced to be there with him I was forced
to go to school I was forced to go to
classes with them if I had the choice I
would have avoided them at all cost if
you're being cyber bullied whether it's
on Facebook or Twitter or whatever
social media you are not being backed
into a corner you have so many options
you have the option to unfriend your
boys you have the option to block your
bullies you have the option to escape
your bullies by deleting your entire
account you are not being forced to be
there having social
Media is not something you need to live
and there's no law saying that you have
to be on it
unlike school that's your own choice I
believe that if you're gonna choose to
be on social media you're gonna have to
learn how to deal with it if you can't
handle it then just don't be on it
there's no shame in that because no
matter how much people try to stop
bullying through empathetic news stories
or campaigns I honestly believe that
bullying especially cyberbullying is
never gonna stop
that's just how some people are and also
on a side note all those stop bullying
campaigns where all people do is hashtag
stop bullying does almost nothing in my
opinion I'm pretty sure there aren't any
bullies that looks at a tweet with
hashtag stop bullying and things oh okay
yeah stop and for all the kids that are
being bullied that do see that hashtag
I'm pretty sure they're not gonna be
thinking huh that'll stop them instead
of campaigning to try and stop bullying
I think there should be more campaigns
trying to teach kids how to deal with
bullying I'm sure at the time I would
appreciate that a lot more hashtag
bullying isn't going away so let's teach
the kids how to deal with bullying and
other stuff yeah that's pretty catchy
that'll catch on I can honestly say to
all you kids out there that are being
bullied right now if you can survive
being bullied it's gonna make you a
stronger person when you get older not
older older well I guess older too I
think the real way people are not aggro
is either inspiration or desperation and
if you're being bullied to the point of
desperation where you feel like you have
no options you're gonna figure out
something a little off topic but other
than mentioning it and might draw my
life video I never really told my story
in detail publicly before being bullied
is not something you're typically proud
of kind of want to just erase those
years I don't know the next time I'm
gonna be talking about bullying so here
is my story cue emotional music and I
was little boy I never thought I'd make
it out okay that's a little too dramatic
let's tone it down so when I was going
into sixth grade I moved to a charter
school where I basically didn't know
anyone and I already stood out because I
was really really short and skinny at
the time and there was also not many
Asians there and blessed because it was
a charter school we all took a placement
test to see which group we would be in
and to this day I still don't know how
but I scored really well on that test
and they put me with the older kids so I
was even smaller in comparison to and
from there it was pretty much like I was
in a movie in terms of getting bullied
things that I saw in movies that I
thought never happened in real life
happened to me I mean it wasn't anything
crazy but I would get shoved pushed to
the ground praying tea made fun of her
being small and Asian this went on
pretty much every single day I used to
make all these random excuses to my mom
why I couldn't go to school until I
finally told her why and remember she
called the principal one night and the
next day we all had this big assembly to
talk about how we shouldn't be bullying
mother and that pretty much did nothing
and at the time I just hated like I used
to stay up every single night feeling
angry and sorry for myself sometimes I'd
be so frustrated that I have thoughts of
just bringing my metal back to school
just start swinging away at these
bullies but then I come to my senses and
realize that I don't want to go to jail
I'd rather be dead than go to jail which
actually led to even darker thoughts but
luckily I'd fall asleep and in the
morning be somewhat grateful that I
didn't do it but then I remember one
specific night I was just sick of
feeling angry and sorry for myself and I
started to think in a different way
sorry I chose to think in a different
way I remember thinking to myself that
everything happens for a reason I'm
being bullied for a reason my bullies
are bullying me for a reason and I just
asked myself why and I came to realize
that everything they did was just to
make each other laugh and I was just the
easiest target so then I thought how can
I take that away from them and once I
started thinking like that I changed my
entire outlook on the situation I made
everything a challenge no matter how
much someone was gonna prank me or do
stuff to me to make each other laugh I
was gonna make them laugh if one of the
bullies made fun of me I would go with
it and make their joke my joke like if
one of them said why don't you open your
eyes you little chink I would say what
do you mean chink I know understand and
then everyone laughed because they
weren't expecting me to say anything and
just like that it was my joke and then
if I got tripped or shoved to the ground
I'd make a joke out of it I remember
this one time one of the guys were
behind me and they did that thing where
you take a step and they kick your back
leg trip and fall down and I did and
basically he said move it jab and I
would just be like man Richard that was
a good one you're so strong
shut up okay I don't know I didn't seem
like I want that time but then I just
kept doing it over and over and
eventually it stopped
I took the fun out of it I didn't get
mad I didn't retaliate I just made it a
joke like I wanted to fall down and
instead of being known as the small
nerdy Asian kid I was known as the small
nerdy Asian kid that was sometimes funny
nobody wants to bully the small nerdy
Asian kid that's sometimes funny because
that's just me but that's basically my
story
cool story broke thank you that's what
it would sound like if you were here I
started using comedy as a defense and
then I just fell in love with making
people laugh which led to me making
videos and now I'm here talking to you
guys and for all of you out there that
are going for the same thing it doesn't
mean that if you do what I did it's
gonna work for you you have to figure
out your own situation the point is for
all of you out there who feel like
you're being back into a corner and you
have no other options just remember and
know that you're not going to be there
forever and if you manage to survive it
it's gonna make you a stronger and
smarter person when you get older I
don't know it based on a little messed
up
and another unpopular opinion by being
bullied is kind of a blessing in a
really really good disguise because if
you get to that point of desperation
where you're backed into a corner and
you feel like you have no options and
you still survive it at least for me you
live with this thought that there's
nothing that you can't do because you've
been in a situation with no options and
you still made it I can honestly say
that looking back I'm almost thankful to
my bullies because without them I
probably wouldn't be talking to you guys
right now in fact if you happen to be
watching this video for some reason you
know exactly what you are I forgive you
for everything I wouldn't be Who I am or
where I am today without you so in a way
thank you
whoa when super off-topic on this one
sorry I get really passionate when I
talk about bullying but anyway thank you
guys so much for watching I know this
wasn't the funniest video but it's
something I've always wanted to talk
about remember to post the hashtag
bullying isn't going away so let's teach
kids how to deal with them and stuff I
don't think that was it and also
remember if you're being booked if
you're being bullied
[Applause]
shut up okay thank you guys so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the left if you
want to see the last rant video that I
take which one on the right and just a
come over here and say hi my darling
this is gone Dietrich C Dietrich say hi
Hey