oh hey um if you're wondering why my
pants was down you'll see why in a
little bit hey guys so a lot of you may
be new subscribers or for those of you
that have been around for a long time
you know that I'm back home in Hawaii
right now and I thought it'd be pretty
good to make a video in here because
yesterday was the first day I made my
YouTube account six years ago so yes
it's another boring thank-you video go
ahead click away no go and you know i am
i hate when people get all cheesy and
sentimental on youtube videos but thank
you so much but seriously to all my
subscribers out there and everybody who
is continuing to watch and support thank
you thank you thank you for putting up
with my terrible language comes from a
window thank you for putting up with
poor sound which echoes around in the
room because i don't have a mic thank
you for putting up with my ADHD where
often times thank you for putting up
with my weird transitions that actually
make the video not make sense thank you
for putting up with all the randomness
thank you for all putting up with my
lack of skill thank you for always
putting up with my poor comedic timing
[Music]
thank you for putting up with my
maturity thanks for putting up with all
the bloopers and thank you for putting
up with my terrible editor what my
editing is fine no it's not and what I
don't have actors thank you so much for
putting up with my lamps actually you're
welcome that's awesome yeah thanks just
kidding I hate them but more than
anything in the past six years thank you
guys so much for all the memories see
this is why I said you're a terrible
editor what when I look up that means
cue the flashback well how am I supposed
to know that uh you're me you should
know so I am me now
and thank you guys so much for putting
up with me fighting with myself I mean I
know it happens a lot but some
wait what what not seriously you're just
gonna cut me off in mid-sentence you
said you wanted a flashback yeah when I
kill you
stop it you used me to do it no I did it
yes you did watch when I kill you no
I'll earn it stop it see I told you see
I had to do with this for six years do
you know how hard it is to work with me
gonna be any harder than working with me
oh wow yeah so you're gonna just turn on
me like I'm a crazy dream I know right
this is turning into Inception wait what
am i editing right now get back to work
now
alright this is just getting repetitive
now she make a video about this oh hey
um if you're wondering why my pants was
down and that's the story of how I came
up with this video seriously though I
have no one else to think but you guys
how my editor Don my actor is especially
without a lab because everything
I've ever done and everything I've ever
accomplished was because of you guys the
fans
[Music]
good what's wrong little man I had a
dream that you replaced me with the fan
oh that wasn't a dreams right next to
you what