my DMS are always about I'm gonna kill
myself my sister killed herself my
brother killed herself my father killed
or something by an Asian I was like I
have both invisibility things in the
media I just don't woman I'm such a
controlling calculated person already
that I want someone who can sort of not
be pushed around by my energy and can
push back just be like welcome back to
another episode of off the pill podcast
a little late and today we have a very
special guest miss Anna Kay Akana ooh my
phone I know we checked your Wikipedia
she is a American actress filmmaker
musician author and comedian she does
everything she and also a youtuber with
over 2.5 million subscribers and over
285 million views we also have David in
the moderator seat hello and we have
Paco sitting right next to me anyway
yeah we're here with I should you know
what I should start doing introducing
the guests last it's a little less
awkward no how do people normally do
those yeah maybe yeah we're so there's
only our third one here in LA so we're
still figuring it welcome thank you for
coming away from Montana yeah thank you
for coming out here things are having
again we just learned recently actually
that well I just learned recently that
you're actually part Hawaiian yeah I'm a
source icon is actually holing yes and I
went to Ewa Beach High School did you
really yeah I've had this conversation
yeah remember yeah this is from the I
dare you we did yeah and also Arden just
been friends are you okay well what my
bad what's the other three 3/4 Japanese
Filipino and then a bunch of white mmm
any foreign language I speak Japanese I
also speak Spanish roughly very roughly
sort of but none of my family speaks so
I'm really rusty and also I grew up in
okay now
which is more like hillbilly Japanese
that's me yeah so I'm hairy and dark oh
nice yeah are you serious
I am oh but I lasered it away so I'm
fine and you also speak pidgin nowadays
we're bilingual now I guess I don't
really count it I think I just okay well
I mean we were also talking about you
just when did you release your music
video my first one came out in May
uh-huh so you are uh I don't know if I
don't know if I talked off camera about
all your music videos coming up I don't
know if you want to talk about yeah I
saw I did a visual album that's 13 music
videos a fourth are animated and I've
been releasing one a month and I'm
currently working on my second that is a
lot for people that don't know that's a
lot of work for people who don't know
and your your you started off on YouTube
I sort of didn't stand up as a teenager
and then I started doing YouTube
simultaneously because my brother
actually showed me one of your videos
you and natalie tran and he was like
look at these people
yeah I did a video community channel
with her and I was like oh because when
you start stand-up you're doing it in
like laundromats or coffee shops and
people are very annoyed that you're
trying to talk to them and I was like oh
I can voluntarily like click on a video
I want to watch like I'll do that as
well like so I don't feel like I'm
harassing people all the time and so I
sort of really fell in love with
community channel in you and happyslip
and I was like oh I love the format that
these people are doing and so I started
on YouTube as well how long were you
doing stand-up comedy I started when I
was 19 so pretty young yeah about a
decade you did stand-up comedy for a
decade yeah I just recently quit to
transition to music so you and you're
saying you did that here in LA yeah so I
would drive out to LA and when I was
underage I had to wait outside of the
comedy clubs till it was my turn to go
on stage be escorted onto stage and then
be escorted out no idea I thought you
just started with YouTube
nono YouTube just kind of what took off
because I feel like I don't know if you
guys have experienced this but when
YouTube came around I was like oh this
is the only
place I see other Asian people doing
anything like comedy lifestyle Beauty
anything at all and I was like this is
so cool like I didn't I'd never seen
like Michelle Phan watching her video I
was like oh that's how I like do makeup
for my eyes like I've been following all
these other tutorials that were wrong
for my eye shape and so I feel like it's
like specific - yeah because we need to
put on like eyeliner you'd be like where
to go you know and so there was a
difference that that is all the same no
no it's very different doing it makeup
for an Asian face is different she was
here on the last two podcasts ago and
after the podcast she did stuff to our
faces put stuff on us yeah I don't know
why exactly we were just hanging out and
then she that the what is it called
eyelid yeah that stuff is awful man
that's worse than like when we did the
BGA stuff for the kpop makeup it's like
torture you do that to yourself every
day yeah every day I wouldn't you get
used to it you just not used to touching
your nerves there yeah or like if you
try to put in like in your waterline and
then you should just tattoo it so that
you don't have to ever do it again
but then if you have to do as an actor I
I can't cuz I have to do natural makeup
how is that going by the way it's great
been acting a lot been acting a lot I'm
doing uh I'm doing a to Netflix thing so
I'm in a Netflix Christmas movie called
let it snow which is based on a John
Green Book and then I'm also I don't
know if I can announce it technically
but I'm also in Jupiter's legacy which
is based on a graphic novel so I play a
Japanese assassin in that it's awesome I
know dude it says Netflix originals yeah
in it crazy hot that's like oh yeah I'm
doing ABC show oh cool that's cool I'm
doing like a NBC whatever but Netflix no
that's yeah efflux is like the new thing
like I would rather see somebody they
have more consistency yeah yeah they get
to be edgier yeah it's really cool
apparently they trust creators a lot to
do their thing okay you you are a
hustler you were I mean I was reading
through your Wikipedia you've you know
come out with music you've done music
you've done YouTube stand-up comedy
acting came with your own clothing line
up book what like what dude do you sleep
I do I get seven to eight hours a night
and you're very uppity yeah yeah I don't
know I think I get like I really like
what I do I get bored very easily
so I always want to try something new
and exciting I really love learning and
so I see YouTube and all that stuff is
my own film school yeah and I also think
it's very fun to juggle projects because
when I get stuck on one I get bored I
can just shift to another and feel like
invigorated but when I go back to the
other project that I was stuck on before
and yeah you know there's like the
impending sense of like oh I'm gonna die
and nothing matters so like maybe I
should just work harder mm-hm
and I think I want to bring up a Twitter
question when it comes to that somebody
actually asked I just want to make sure
that I get the proper name and credits
to them
Caroline Road said can you walk us
through your creative process of making
videos but I wanted to kind of expand
this because when making videos it's
gonna be completely different from how
you do your other projects that's just
music or such as when you write your you
know short films and then start wanting
to direct them so what is the process
like different housing oh man so
differently well YouTube I'm sure you
know when you've been doing it for a
decade I have no ideas anymore so I
write my YouTube videos like the hour
before my crew arrives and often all
like still be finishing it as they're
setting up so you - I've trained myself
to just procrastinate till the absolute
last possible moment with everything
else I'm sort of concept based first so
there are certain stories like I've
wanted to tell forever like I did a
stop-motion short called dolore that
I've been working on for 10 years but
kind of accepted like stop-motion as a
craft I'll never be able to do on my own
so I waited until I had a quarter of a
million dollars to do it right and I
wanted to use that as sort of like a
proof of concept because I love
animation and directing and I came up as
a freelance storyboard artist when I was
doing stand-up so I would do like I
learned how to draw anime I think when I
was a kid and so doing storyboarding and
doing animation was like a huge part of
my childhood if you could please adjust
it that would be great so yeah I don't
know what my creative process it's been
very like I'm emotion driven like I feel
like i transmute a lot of my favorite
deep feelings into art so my album was
born out of a wanting to quit comedy
because people have come threatened to
like come shoot me at shows and comedy
shows don't have security every
venues it's one of the big reasons I
salad reason yeah but I okay so I was
really afraid of like you know not only
putting my life on the line but somebody
else's life on the line especially after
christina grimmie got shot and but I'd
always done music in my stand-up comedy
sets and so I was like well every music
venue I've ever been to have security
like that's just something embedded in
that culture so I feel a lot safer and
capable of doing that and then also I I
went through a really rough breakup and
a suicidal episode and so music is sort
of what really helped me come out of
that and writing it as well okay let's
go back a little bit because I mean I I
mean I feel like that's uh DAST I mean
that's one of the one of the reasons
obviously there's it's not the only
reason why you stopped doing stand-up no
I mean I've been doing it for so long
I'm also I'm a coast comedian so my
stand-up sets all about my abortion my
sister's suicide dysfunctional Asian
family Midwest audiences don't like it
oh sure yeah so I could I was very
limited as a comedian and what I was
able to do in the audience is I was able
to reach and once I did it for ten years
I was like either have to really commit
to this and figure out a way to make
this funny to Midwest audiences or I
just have to accept that I have to step
away from comedy for a while right were
you focusing mostly on like Asian topics
or no a lot of death like a lot of my
comedy was death based Jews are dark
yeah very dark so you're saying that in
the comedy world that that when you get
that dark it's not is like Midwest
people want to they go to a comedy show
to escape so they want to hear like guys
are like this and girls are like this
whereas in LA in New York where you're
exposed to a lot more you are down to go
on that kind of journey with me like
you're over should further yeah like
you're okay to laugh at an abortion joke
whereas in the Midwest everyone's like
thought no that's murder
really Blue Collar Comedy Tour like
that's so wall out there yeah it's very
light-hearted easy to digest that's
interesting though when you so you so
the Christina Grimmie thing I mean that
happened how long ago like two years ago
yeah yeah that I mean even for me not
that I went to a lot of events and
traveled and stuff like that but after
that
I literally stopped yeah everything
never really did any more events since
that and it affected me I'm sure it
affected a lot of people but did really
like that's a big thing to you that's
why you one of the main reasons you
stopped well I've had I've had stalkers
over the years and one stalker when I
was promoting a comedy show was like I'm
gonna come and I have something for you
and he'd been emailing me all the time
and like started talking about how he
wishes my sister was alive so that he
could [ __ ] her and like I would be
jealous like he was really disturbing
[ __ ] and then he's he's sent an email
that basically alluded to the fact that
he had a gun and that he was gonna come
see me and so I was like I dropped out
of it I did I had hired a private
investigator but we couldn't figure out
who he was so we think he's actually an
IT because he was able to mask his IP
address and stuff like that Wow yeah do
you think that because you're I mean
generally your skits and your like use
of your comedy your sets and stuff are a
little bit darker do you think that's
why it drew somebody like that cuz I I
mean everyone we talk about girls every
girl we've had on the podcast has talked
about a stalker experience yeah but that
one is pretty I haven't heard one that
that's that's pretty dark well people
because I'm so outspoken about suicide
and mental illness like a lot of
mentally disturbed individuals latch on
to me like my DMS are always about I'm
gonna kill myself
my sister killed herself my brother
killed herself my father killed there's
not like so many of them are that or I
want to [ __ ] you in the butt or
something like so it's like sexual or
death and then I also get the people who
have both and so it gets a little scary
cuz you're like I don't know where this
person is how serious they are if
they're just sending something across
the internet because they can or if they
actually have a gun and they're gonna
come drive across the house effect you
like like it has to mess with your mind
though like yeah definitely paranoid all
the time and getting like serious like
yeah yeah they're so casual ball which I
find funny but I know it's not funny
yeah I mean I was a girl you just get
used to a certain level of danger in
everyday life mm-hmm but I also feel
like with your stand-up background you
kind of take like that pain or like that
awkwardness and you turn it into
something that you know can be seen more
lighthearted yeah I try but also um
nevermind forgot my question okay all
right
I just think there's like if I were in
your position and in getting DMS about
like not the sexual stuff I mean that I
wouldn't yeah that's like me but more
about the II like the more deeper stuff
like I would feel a very heavy burden my
shoulders and and I wouldn't know how to
deal with that like do you I mean I'm
sure you kind of have to go through
things like that and and it's not like
you could save everyone you know I mean
we all want to but I mean I how do you
kind of deal with that like it's it's
very there's another question actually
yeah I wouldn't know how to so yeah
therapy man like I've been in therapy
for ten years and I think it's great and
my therapist was like do not respond to
any of those people
yeah she was like first of all someone
who's very seriously considering suicide
is most likely not going to send that
out on the internet they are you know
internal and they create a plan and you
don't see it coming and she's like
second of all if you respond once that
person becomes relying on you and it's
gonna guilt you into having to respond
to them every time and also for my
mental health like I can't like I've had
friends who have used the suicide thing
it's like a way to get me to do things
or they're like emotionally manipulative
because they know that's my trigger and
so now I'm just like I can't engage like
if someone's is very seriously suicidal
I know them and they're my friend like I
know how to be there for them but if
you're a stranger on the internet I
cannot help you in that way right yeah
you gotta go to therapy on the record I
want I promise that was my question
totally forgot blanked out of my you
went from your head into Davis because
like a lot of people do deal with like
people reaching out to them and saying
oh I'm very depressed and it's just like
how do you mentally like oh is this my
issue you know so I think for a lot of
content creators hearing that it can
guide them through like oh this is not
for me it's not my burden to take care
of yeah
I've come to the same conclusion I think
to not respond but I've definitely had
like moments like I know I like DMS
where I don't want to open it because
they'll see that I've read it and didn't
do anything about it like the top line
is like I really need to talk to you
because I like I'm contemplating suicide
and like I feel a sense of like even
guilt
not opening it but I know it's not gonna
help to do that because like what's to
stop from the next like hundred of them
you know when I just open that one and
then I'm just caught up in this I never
actually talked about this before but I
came to the conclusion not to open it
but I do feel like guilt you know
because like I don't know what happened
to that person you know and like what if
I had opened it and just said one thing
and they're fine I know I think he just
said I we I came to the same conclusion
but I did always have a little bit of
guilt of not opening it cuz it's not
that hard you do but I guess hearing you
from it I should go see a therapist but
the thing is like yes I understand your
guilts you're like well I have the power
to influence person yeah but the thing
is then that becomes all-consuming
because times that by like a thousand
times it by a hundred thousand and it's
like then what happens if you say
something and then they kill themselves
now you have the opposite go effect
you're not a licensed like psychiatrist
you don't know what to tell people and
so for me it's like I will make my
videos and I'll be vocal about these are
the things you can do here are the
solutions for depression here's here's
the resources you have but I can't be
accountable I'm not trained for that
right yeah that's fair yeah I had a
conversation with another content
creator we kind of came to the idea of
the time spent like helping us one
person where you're completely unsure of
what you're doing if you just focus on
the stuff that you usually do you help
like way more people and that's stuff
that you're good at so it's just like if
you keep doing your thing you'll you'll
be positively impacting a lot more
people definitely well you said that
that's like one of uh obviously you have
personal reasons that that's a trigger
yeah with your sister but like you said
you also talk about it in stand-up
mm-hmm how is that so I mean I know it's
obviously personal to you and that's
probably why you use it but if it's a
trigger to you don't you think that
that's kind of you know a touchy subject
for you yeah I couldn't make a suicide
joke for seven years so I was doing
stand-up for seven years before I could
actually make a joke about it and laugh
and so then it became a thing of like
ooh I like that it doesn't have this
power over me anymore because before any
time someone would colloquially mention
in conversation like oh her head is in
traffic for one more moment I was gonna
kill myself
I would just feel crazy and I got to a
point where I finally was like oh okay
if I can make it funny if I can find a
lens to laugh at it and to allow other
people to laugh at it that's so
empowering for me and it's also normal
I think suicide ideation should be more
normalized because all of us we're so
isolated every day we don't we're not in
the food chain anymore so you just like
live this weird existence where you're
watching everyone's best lives on your
screen alone in your [ __ ] bedroom
feeling like a loser I feel like a lot
of us go through periods of depression
and wanting to kill ourselves and
wondering if our life means anything and
there's been sort of this alarmist view
like oh god if you have any of those
thoughts you're freaked and like you
need to be on medication and you need to
like go to therapy because you're crazy
whereas I'm like no I'm pretty sure
everyone gets to a point in their lives
maybe once or many times where it even
just crosses your mind like should I
kill myself and so I like to try to
normalize those feelings while also
pointing out that that's not the answer
yeah I mean I agree with that I think
everybody I always assumed growing up
because even as a little kid I didn't
understand it really but I like
contemplated not doesn't mean I was
gonna do it and I just you know
everybody has those thoughts I thought
everybody would have those but maybe not
I don't know I've thought about it
everybody has and you're like I think
even in the opposite side of that
spectrum like we've all had like a small
thought like man I really want to kill
that person yeah but you know you
shouldn't do that every time I hold a
knife and I'm by someone like I could
just stab ya that's wrong or like like
we're driving you're like there's a
bicycle and everything like yeah it's go
Lane you're like oh my god nd yeah I
could get one star in GTA right now it's
crazy like when you're driving the only
thing that's stopping both cars on the
other side is just a lion just one line
sometimes it's it's dashed it's not even
a solid line yeah you could just
literally just go left and there the
person goes left
just a line it's just a line so you know
life is life can be short never know go
dark deed wasn't she brought the first
Twitter question you might keep rolling
with that oh no it's just like you're
something because usually we do Twitter
questions in the end where there's good
questions there's interesting fans
there's a tweet here it's you actually
your tweet July on July 7th you wrote
money fame success status oh [ __ ]
disappears and has forgotten how you
help people inspire others empower and
amplify voices other than your own the
extent of your kindness that's the [ __ ]
legacy is made of I really like that
thank you
like what prompted you to like come up
with this this sort of tweet um I I
think we all get caught up in the game
of oh I gotta be more successful I gotta
make more money I got it you know do all
the cool things and then you lose sight
of what is actually important and I feel
like life is this really annoying cycle
of doing that again and again and again
and that was just a reminder for me cuz
I was looking at Instagram obviously and
like looking at things everyone else was
doing I was like am i doing everything
wrong like should I be doing more of
like what this is or be more of like who
this person is and just feeling like I
feel very lame a lot of the times I feel
like everyone's so much funnier and
smarter and like or inspiring or
whatever and I just never feel like I am
doing enough and so that to me I was
like you know what I can only affect as
much as I can affect like there's a
really good quote by Mother Teresa that
was like I alone cannot change the world
but I can cast a stone and create many
ripples and to me that's that's always
the way I try to live is like you know
it gets really overwhelming when you
watch the news and you're like I want to
help the world but I can't so it's like
well I can only cast as many ripples and
hopefully those people cast ripples as
well and try to be a positive force in
the world because I feel like apathy has
become very cool like let me not care
let me know vote little bit but I'm like
well in 11 years global warming is gonna
be at the point of no return you guys
like let's let's all chip in let's all
care um so yeah I think that was just me
reminding myself like don't get caught
up in that [ __ ] too much what what
like you know you've done a lot of
things in what what's driving you to
like do so many things I think earlier
you said you get bored pretty easily but
but what is it inside of you that that
that feels like makes you feel like you
you need to do all of these things
really ambitious kid like I remember my
first dream was to be the first female
president of the United States like when
I was five I was like that is my path I
am Amy Poehler before Amy Poehler
existed and I've always just felt like I
want to do great things for Humanity and
ultimately I've realized like my
strength is taking my life experience or
taking things that I'm feeling and
turning that into art that can hopefully
like make people feel less alone or
inspire them and so for me I love
playing in different mediums because
then you get all your life experience
and in a new medium it's all up for
grabs again like versus YouTube I'm like
I've talked about every topic there is
to [ __ ] talk about I don't have
anything else to say but if I go to
music I'm like everything I've ever gone
through is now up for grabs I can say
all of that again in just a new medium
and so I like I like medium hopping as
well I think it keeps you creative so
what are you gonna do when you run out
of all of those feelings that you can
sing afro I don't have right you may
come back to the other medium yeah when
you have more things to talk about yeah
but that is interesting though and it I
feel like you have to have there's
certain people in the world I feel like
just have more energy than others and I
feel like you're one of those people
there's like you know the people you
watching it's like like Kevin Hart right
buddy like you're just looking like man
how can he do all these things I call it
how does he have the mental capacity is
that something you've always had that's
like like you said as a little kid or is
it something that you had to like train
yourself prolific nasai feel comes from
organization and attention management so
I'm very very good at time management I
can structure my time in a way that I'm
like oh this is how I can maximize the
amount that I can do some day is like
I'm tired and I don't want to do
anything and I clear my schedule and I
just like lay around but for the most
part I'm very good at when I have a task
to do I know exactly how to do it in the
most efficient way possible you don't
get lost in that like you know a lot of
artists once you're like in a zone
nothing else matters you just keep going
until
you realize I just used up my whole day
you don't go through that I do but like
I I do it a per project so I get very
obsessed with one project I complete it
and then I do all my others I see oh
well that's discipline then at that
point
ya have the opposite thing I get excited
about things get into it jump onto
something else kind of forget about it
come back just I'm everywhere I think
that's a good process too if that's what
works for you it's better to just finish
things have a lot of unfinished things I
was like this is a great idea and
sometimes I'll forget about it come back
and be like man I should did that back
when it was relevant yeah sometimes you
got a we work off the muse energy yeah I
have those too yeah do you like being
crude II like the business aspect of
what you do I do
and versus a creative I mean is it like
a 50/50 thing for you yeah I really like
like Excel spreadsheets and
color-coordinated calendars because your
organization though that's like so left
brained you know it's fun it's a relief
from creative because there's like oh
there's one way to do this right and if
I numbers don't add up then I have done
the math wrong whereas creative like the
box there's no box so you're like oh
you're anything yeah where's the
business side gives me a break from all
that and I can be like let budget so you
enjoy that so yeah I personally think
that like there if you you have to have
a little bit of that like a little bit
of organization to become a successful
creative because if you don't have that
or some sort of structure in your life I
feel like what you just said you know
when you're treated it's just there's no
walls it's just like oh yeah energy that
just goes outward but you have to kind
of bring it in and be like okay I'm
gonna use this energy to create a song
oh yeah film or a script so I think that
that's super important yeah I mean I
have so many friends who are like way
more talented than I am they just don't
have the discipline every day to like
stick either follow through just likes
finish something or their perfectionist
and they like just finish it over and
over and over again until they hate it
and they throw the whole thing away and
I think for me it's always like I want
to be at least 90% there and then I have
to let it go like nothing's ever gonna
be perfect so let it go once it's 90% of
the way there I mean obviously if
there's anything glaring
you want to fix yes but I also know when
to be like okay this has been enough
time on this leg move on yes
so I read in your bio that your your
father was an officer in the United
States Marine corpse
thanks thanks to him thank you
Thank You mr. O'Connor do you think like
because I have friends who grew up in
military families as well they travel
all over the place they're never in one
place it's hard for them to make friends
there go to different schools all the
time
but the thing that I respect about them
is they're very well cultured and and I
think that's something that people who
travel a lot you know to really
understand is you just have a general
idea of just people yeah like a really
good balance of like understanding of
people do you feel that I mean were you
traveling a lot and oh yeah every six
months to two years Wow so it was really
difficult to I liked it you like I like
decks like even as a kid yeah and I was
like oh I get some believe and I can
become whoever I want to be at this new
school understand yeah I think I'm an
actor because I'd be like I'm gonna be
the shy girl here in North Carolina and
there's like I don't like being the shy
girls like I'm gonna be the obnoxious
about in here in Hawaii committed to it
yeah I stayed in character for those
yeah I was like a chance to like
reinvent yourself over and over again
until you found out like what you liked
what you didn't like about yourself and
I got very good at chameleon ink so I
could see I can read a room and be like
I know exactly who I have to be to fit
in or I can just be myself
so you know who your base is then yeah
that is that you right now yeah yeah I
mean I'm a little turned up because
we're performing but yeah yeah um yeah
and cuz you drink some milk and tea and
water no that's that's do you do you
feel like the discipline also came from
being in a like having your father being
a yeah I mean I think I had the perfect
bifurcation of show and business so my
dad was all like every page you read you
get a penny if you like pluck the weeds
in the yard for two days I'll give you
Titanic on VHS and so he taught me like
hard work and discipline and like really
valued education and my mom is like more
of a flowy like really funny clown type
who loves artistry so she was always
either painting or doing crochet or like
some kind of like hobby and so I grew up
with both like discipline but also like
a really big emphasis on creativity that
sounds like good like I feel like I've
seen that Disney movie before like a
Disney Channel original but like the dad
who's like the officer and then like the
mom was he creative and then that's
about you that's me it's very windy real
life that's very interesting
Oh Wendy whoo that's other what Justin
was on oh right I don't know yeah you
don't support your friends
all right well speaking of hydration we
are going to our quick shishi break so
we'll be right back
right on time with my bladder and we're
back we've been back anyway I just did I
just did right now okay yeah and now
we're officially back so let's let's get
right into it
Paco I think you should talk about your
tweet yeah no we're talking about you
guys you see this tweet is so stupid
right you told I don't have it in front
of me read it guys papi we did yeah
mouth was trying to stop stop the Chanel
but he tweeted out loud so go ahead no I
was waiting so okay let me take control
of this do you think Paco is cute it had
the most parts it did he got like
married to the top nice I said it as a
joke and to send it and he actually sent
it so oh you tweeted it at yourself with
questions to ask yes okay I thought
you're just asking your audience in
third person and maybe not you're cute
you can be honest you don't have to make
him feel good actually even the stall
makes me real good that's kind of the
theme of this boss guys
cute Wow sound effects cuz again the
theme was that he just made his life I
think I'm good yeah I would say you're
objectively Q dark joke you know
nobody's they objectively motion right
now
that means like Oh personally I don't
find you you know I can see okay you're
an attractive man yeah yeah thank you I
appreciate that but objectively I was
I'm just talking about physicality like
in terms of like if I'm personally
attracted to a person when I think women
have the capacity to fall in love with
people who aren't attractive and they
become attractive to them based on your
personality so for me I can see a guy
who's really hot and like that's a hot
guy but I don't feel anything until I
know them I mean I could say that what
guy - yeah but speaking about that we
also have in our notes recently in 2018
that you came out at a Streamy award
show I did that you are by I am bisexual
I actually didn't see that clip but I
just we just looked it up okay
yeah I saw the video of you coming out
to your parents yeah that was that cute
yeah thank you
your parents are very very sweet they
seemed very like very sweet people so
I've asked them to do another video and
they're like not yet we just not yeah
yeah they're like we need we need some
more space people need to like miss us
more okay something you knew for like a
long time hey but you just didn't want
to say it so I had a crush on a girl
when I was like 11 or something and my
friend I told my friend and she was like
Ana you're just trying to be interesting
she said yeah so for a long time I
thought like oh I'm just a straight girl
trying to be like interesting what you
didn't even know no and I'm bisexuality
I thought you had to be like half in
half and I'm not half and half I skew
more male and but in talking to some
bisexual ladies in the last year or so
they were like no like any amount of my
sexuality is valid like I have a friend
who's predominantly a lesbian but she's
attracted to like a guy here and there
and she's like I'm still very much
bisexual I don't identify as a lesbian
it's like a spectrum right yeah it's a
huge spectrum and no one's like on the
very opposite end
no because if you're on the opposite on
your gay it was like by is like I'm
attracted to both but it may not be the
same amount per and obvious I think it's
like actually very rare to have like an
exact 50/50 you'll have fun interesting
sorry that I I didn't know this but I do
you did you get a lot of pushback from
the gay community because there is
pushback there and they feel like it's
so interesting to me because it took so
long for you to accept gay people and
then now that the people are coming on
is by gay people there's some actual
pushback yeah by people they think like
straight people think it's either a
stepping stone to being gay and gay
people think like you're actually
straight and just like having fun with
the other two generous selfish yeah it's
selfish or whatever and there's this
funny like I think being by an Asian I
was like I have both invisibility things
maybe I just don't woman but yeah I have
had some pushback from gay people like
especially cuz they're like well have
you ever had sex with a woman have you
ever dated a woman I was like do I need
to ever have sex with a guy to know that
I'm attracted to a guy like that's not a
thing like it's just ridiculous um but
it's fun it's been a fun journey when
you said you were 11 right was it 11
yeah I think so you said you had a crush
on a girl I I don't know about the
anatomy of a female like in terms of
like sexually when you start feeling
sexual desire mm-hmm
then I want to press your face to their
face okay so so I'm sunni what hasn't
done that yet yeah I'm in experience but
when when you're 11 you weren't sexual
like that's like puberty right like even
like it's great great okay wait I was
reading like naughty novels I stole from
my mom yeah why you had to grow up fast
right because you're traveling all over
the place
yeah yeah I don't know I'm just assuming
so when you were 11 you did have like a
sexual kind of like desire for the other
girl that yeah I don't know if I was
like I wanted to [ __ ] her when I was 11
but I definitely like I liked her like I
want to kiss her you want to
okay yeah it wasn't like oh she's so
pretty like I want to know she was she
was like more of a butch girl she was
more of a tomboy gosh I've always been
much more into tomboys yeah what I've
always been like kind of curious about
that like what what draws a girl into a
butch girl versus like a more pretty
very pretty like whatever I'm in
feminine girl I don't know I guess to me
like tomboys have always been like
they're cute and they're edgy and like
they're a little rough and tumble and
they have really good hair that's like
short but it's like gorgeous and and Oh
quaff and I don't know I feel like yeah
I want to sit on the back of her
skateboard or something though the way
that like you kind of like portray
yourself is like you're very edgy
yeah aspect and a lot of times people
will say Oh opposites attract no does
that mean like if it's true in your case
that opposites attract that I guess in
your more personal life you're kind of
more docile and like you're very no I
mean I don't know I'm very masculine
energy in my career so I feel like I
have attracted a lot of women who are
more feminine but I know in my
relationships I need to be the more
feminine one because I get I get to like
resentful if I have to be the one who
plans everything and does everything and
controls the relationship so I think
I've been always attracted to types that
have more of that masculine energy
because I'm like oh I can like relax in
my relationship but then like have my
masculine energy in my career yeah
interesting so you I mean you're pretty
openly like a very strong feminist right
yeah but you still see well I mean I
know there's different definitions of
feminist these days like it doesn't not
everybody has the same definition but
like in terms of like in that
relationship you're just describing like
having a guy have it to plan those
things you don't think those roles
should be equally split up between the
man and woman no I'm a feminist in the
sense that I advocate for equality for
women but also for equality for men in
the sense of emotional vulnerability
like I think feminism is also trying to
get rid of toxic masculinity so I have
been attracted to men who are like kind
of feminine in their energy it really
just depends I mean there's so many
variations of like what can get along
with a person but I do know in my
relationships like I can be so I'm such
a controlling calculated person already
that I want someone who can
sort of not be pushed around by my
energy and can push back just like me I
wouldn't actually want somebody who
would be no no ya know what the fight
not even just a fight but someone who
can like you know have a boundary and
hold their boundary but it's also and
this is what I got also from like Ali
Wong special is because she's somebody
who's also very much so like driven yeah
calculating in that aspect but they want
to be like it's almost like not
necessarily the opposition but that they
can respect the other person yes okay
all right it's not gonna be easy I don't
just get to control my own yeah like you
want someone who like it feels like you
you know you're an equal like I've
financially supported partners before
and it just doesn't I just hate it and
so I need someone who's confident in who
they are and who's doing their own thing
and is down to be like no we're not
gonna do that I don't want to do that
okay Co Co Co Co Co but you won't push
back you like push back for sure
that's interesting because that aspect
of like that you're still working
towards something you know you know that
oh they're invested in this yeah I like
debate I guess like one of the thoughts
I have with the whole bisexuality thing
is that me correct me if I'm wrong but
me do you kind of see it as like you
don't see guy and girl you kind of just
see personality and kind of what they
stand for and then you because I like
when do you choose to date a dude versus
date a woman you know a woman yeah like
like or is it like leaning more towards
male I date more men mm-hmm I have been
dating women since I've come out and I'm
sure they're very different they're so
different I made a video about I hope
it's not gonna be offensive but it's
called like I've dated women and now I
understand men because in cousin I like
would take women out on dates and they
never offered to pay for they're having
dinner or like interesting yeah and I
would be like what the [ __ ]
and like I was talking to my male
friends like I feel like this girl's
just asking me out so like I'll buy her
dinner cuz you always suggest he's like
nice restaurants like I'm like what the
[ __ ] and he was like oh yeah that's the
thing women do yeah what is it how did
you decide that I mean between you two
like why didn't you be the one like I'm
not gonna pay well I've felt awkward
also are you gonna want that ask them
out no she asked me out
Wow you got you got I got but but that
was just one experience with one lady
yeah but with other women it's been like
I had someone invite me in and she was
like do you want to come in and make out
I was like yeah all right pretty
whatever and then she just talked the
lake till 3 a.m. which I don't mind but
like I was like we're not making out at
all you're a liar what if what if a guy
like what is more of a guy thing what if
the guy said the same thing then I would
expect to make out exactly what it would
have happened no more than that guy
brings you in then he talks about his
emotions till 3 who are you more mad at
the guy or the girl oh I think it would
depend on what they're talking about
like the girl was talking about it was
it was same thing I would probably be
pissed too well the thing is the premise
of bringing me into the house with
promises of kissing thing yeah like if
you just said you want to come in and
talk I would be like yeah cool unlike
expect talking but to say let's make out
and then only talk to me until 3:00 a.m.
I'm like I gotta go just tender people
know I can't do tinder so I do riah
what's that
Rai is like people in the industry oh
yeah so you're talking about other
actresses actors directors DPS people
who are on gaffers gaffers that's
probably a good Network yeah actually
they have a section just for networks oh
really they have a section for dating
yeah going back so cuz I don't know if I
like my answer was my question was
answered um when do you choose a girl
versus a dude like this is it based off
of like your a certain season or you
just want to try it like Trey Trey I'll
get bored like you get bored because
you're just recently you said recently
you've been dating women yeah right it
but it's like but wait wait why are you
only dating women now I'm dating buzz
it's a mix you're going back and yes
okay it just depends on like who's cool
who's trying like who do I vibe with
when we meet up for dinner finally like
dating in LA is its own special thing so
it's kind of awful and this about that
no so I don't know what that mean oh my
god Ryan it's so bad dating here is
awful because it's expensive it's not
just that people are people are weird
there's
super flakes because everybody here not
even just that like people are really
commitment-phobic like all the people
I'd date for three months about okay
it's time for us to be in a relationship
now and they're like no no no it's yeah
a super I don't even think it's just
like in LA think it's very la focused
but it's it's coastal yeah no way like
the west coast is kind of like that was
just like hey I'm just trying to live my
best yeah con New York is right that's
what they're never like hookup culture
yeah they're always like it's like when
you're at a party and you're talking to
someone and they keep looking over your
shoulder to see who else is in the room
that's what dating here feels like I
haven't had that happen I probably was
the person but didn't notice yeah I
think I did I think I think everyone's
trying to like look for the next best
thing
yeah in dating and in work and in
everything right in LA because
everyone's yeah it's like a transplant
City and everyone's trying to make it or
you know they don't have a strong
foundation here yeah and everyone I
think settles down a lot later on the
coast whereas like women we're still
bound by our biological clock if we want
to have children and you know the what
do you call it way the physical way
versus like adopting out and so I mean I
think women are just ready to settle
down a lot sooner than all the men here
you do you want to have kids
I do really bad does that mean a girl is
out woman I would I would adopt or like
do artificial insemination but I have
always seen myself ending up with a man
because I am more man skewed yeah so you
mentioned that you have a video that's
that's speaking on what was the title
again I dated girls and now I understand
men what are some of the like couples
like a few things that yeah well they
were like the makeup thing the make-out
thing I mean and then
this one girl kept joking about us
getting married like on our first date
and I got really like I don't know you
for two hours and I've been guilty of
making those kind of jokes on dates it's
just like a fun flippin thing to do and
then I was like oh my god but it's not
on the first date right I mean I've made
jokes if it's obviously a joke I don't
see anything wrong with that right but I
could see how that could freak someone
else yeah what is it
what does a fun day look like for you I
love activities so like an escape room
bullying laser tag like I love going and
doing a thing but see so that's
something that I've kind of adapted as
is dating yes a lot of times guys would
be like oh do you want to get dinner
yeah then it feels like an interview
yeah
and so when you do an activity together
not only are you guys working together
to do stuff you're creating physicality
and you're allowing for like playful
touching and stuff and then mid Grobe
and it was giggling playful touching
sounds a lot nicer so after the playful
touching you guys can have dinner and
then like talk like oh it was really fun
and then you have something to talk
about yeah yeah yeah I also think you
learn a lot about people and doing
activities for them like versus just
sitting down and talking to someone at
dinner as Commun that boring cuz actions
speak louder than words yes this is true
touching that's my mouth David you ready
for some playful touching David was the
last time you asked labeled touch we
turned in Julia Dean just good advice
now we know don't make jokes about
getting married on the first date
actually you know what if both of you
are making those jokes is that okay
I think if both of you are on the same
page yes but I wanna feel like people do
people like do you go on dates like you
just met them because I feel like if
they didn't know your comedy because you
are not the I don't think you're
considered the average girl in terms of
your comedy right is there some kind of
disclaimer because if you were make
those jokes you have that not like
deadpan I'm not making a joke face right
I don't know you do
sometimes no I do yeah it's funny yeah
dry humor yeah but like I can see
somebody fat we just met I was like I'm
not sure if she's being serious or not
uh I try to make it obvious that I'm
joking I try if they watched you they
would know yeah I try to get people
though that don't watch me or know me
yeah I feel like we have a preconceived
idea I try not to Google anybody before
I go on a date with them other than just
see if there's like a crazy headline
about them being like I don't know
problematic yeah if they have a hashtag
yeah and then when I like them is when
you deep dive what's the best thing
about dating a guy and what's the best
thing about dating a girl I think the
best thing about doing a dating girls so
far has been the conversation like if
there's anything that comes up like I
feel very safe to have a conversation
about it like hey you said this thing
and it made me feel a little bit like
this but like I know you're in touch it
wasn't this way but it can get to be
over communicating I think the best
thing about dating guys it really
depends on the guy but for the most part
I like feeling taken care of like
emotionally and I feel like a lot of
guys are very nurturing in that way yeah
like they're down to like I like hanging
out someone and they take initiative so
he's like oh I'll call the uber all
schedules a date or I'll do this like
I'll take you on a thing which I don't
have to like mentally worry about
whereas when I'm with a girl I'm usually
the one planning and like taking action
so generally speaking would you say that
females it's it's uh it's more of a
commute it's great communication on an
emotional level and then guys generally
tend to take care of people better or
take care of women just take care of
women or men yeah in general yeah on a
date I feel like men are very good at
taking care of you if if they're the
kind of personality that can't it's hard
to generalize because everyone's so
different but yeah I do find with women
the communication is a lot more clear
mm-hmm interesting I think most guys
aren't though encouraged to be a trainee
they said on average a woman speaks
sixteen thousand words a day and a guy
speaks ten thousand really yeah yeah I
uh yeah I guess I could I could see that
yeah I think I speak probably of
three thousand well is that all we have
for our questions and we got away from
that for a little bit yeah yeah I think
that's would you would you consider
yourself to be a successful person
that's from that's from Twitter actually
hmm I know from the outside yes inside
no really why it's quite now I don't
know I just feel I guess because there's
different levels you can have success
right like yeah I have a personal
success career success so do you just
overall see everything is unsuccessful
or do you see it as unsuccessful I just
see it as like a process and I still
very I feel like I'm still in the
process versus if I look out objectively
and I see what other people see I'm like
oh yeah I guess I would consider that
successful compared to most but inside I
don't feel like I am successful is that
because you think once you feel that way
you'll stop wanting to pursue all these
different things or pushing yourself to
do it I don't know I just feel like I'm
still me if that makes any sense like do
you consider yourself successful I think
I would if I'm thinking of what I wanted
when I was younger but then when I got
here I don't yeah yeah yeah it's the
same thing yeah there's like levels to
it right yeah it's like I unlock this
achievement and now it's to the next
stage yeah yeah it's so incremental and
small to that it doesn't ever feel like
oh I have reached my peak you know yeah
I mean when I was like a kid my idea of
success was just like making X amount of
money yeah
like that was just like okay this is
what I gonna get this job do this and
once I did it made that amount that I
was trying to get to I realized okay
this is not success yeah and maybe it
might be because I got there maybe if I
never reached it then it would have been
like I'm always chasing something yeah I
think there's it I think if you once you
consider yourself successful it's hard
to say is everyone's definition but I
think then you kind of just do nothing
well isn't success also I feel like
success is always changing like your
idea that is changing as you're doing
more things and so it's always away it's
always farther than you if that makes
sense like I always was like my
definition of success is when there's
two projects I really want to do and I
have the offers on both and I
to choose between them and then I got
there and I was like okay now my
definition of success is being the lead
of a movie and I got there I'm like okay
well now my definition of success is
being a Marvel superhero in a movie or
like and so it just keeps like going
farther away you're in a Marvel movie
well I wasn't a superhero I was a
journalist but you were in tomorrow you
know what you be still pretty crazy or
you come across like a magic pen and
it's like I mean I think that is a
character all right I mean you still
have the goal of becoming the first
female president no I don't want to be
in politics
it hasn't been taking it you're pretty
aren't you pretty opinionated on that I
am but I I'm not educated enough in
politics I don't understand how the
system works intricately I have friends
that are way more qualified than I am
and I just was like I can't I feel I
feel the same way yeah but even about
like opinions I'm swayed easily really
not really it's not swayed it's more
just like I'm very open to hearing every
side I think that's a good quality to
have them but is also I've been told
it's bad because it's like oh you're
just sympathizer eccentric and I'm like
well I just want to hear both sides
there's a reason why both sides are so
like a hundred percent they're right you
know mm-hmm so I just like to see both
sides because I'm not smart enough to
know like I find it interesting right
there's only two sides I mean there are
many sides
yeah but technically speaking but I it's
like why is it just blue and red can't
there be like purple and brown and I
mean there are they're just too strong
yeah yeah it's like well we got if you
can't no but you can't support that
because then they'll say you're actually
helping the other side because it's
never gonna win yeah bro it's never
gonna win him I don't know I think I
think these little parties should get
some love too I agree like yeah they
don't have a shot but they should they
don't have a shot at all but let's give
him a shot I'm starting my own party
I'll support you okay well I mean that's
pretty much it yeah is there anything
you want to I have a question okay yeah
it's more about the standard thing
because you're not in the beginning and
I was so when you're is there like
because you know you're strong feminist
and when it comes to comedy though are
there things that you feel shouldn't be
joked about I think every topic is up
for grabs if you can a make it funny and
your be not perpetuating some kind of
hate speech or violence or any kind like
I think as problematic as he is louis
c.k made a really good paedophile joke
where he talked about like you know it
must be so good for a pedophile to do
this because of the repercussions
involved in or like he was the first
person who was like oh I had a baby and
now I understand why there are dumpster
babies so he was really good at taking
previously taboo topics and putting them
in such a specific lens that they were
okay to laugh at and they weren't
necessarily condoning the behavior of
people it was just putting it in a very
unique light that you were looked at and
you thought yeah okay I understand
that's funny so I think like any topic
is up for grabs as long as you can find
one of that unique light is but I think
the hard thing with comedy is were
incredibly politically correct now and I
think that has a lot of pros to it but
it takes a long time to craft a
masterpiece [ __ ] joke and you have to
try it out over and over on audiences
and now when people record you in that
process trying to find that lens you can
be viewed as incredibly problematic
cancelled yeah cancelled immediately
because when Louis came back you heard
about how they set was yeah so I guess
who is exempt from you know having to
always be politically correct because a
comedians job is to find like oh this is
a line that we shouldn't be crossing
were supposed to push boundaries well I
think the Louie things different because
he he had a problematic you know me to
movement and everyone was mad that he
came back and he didn't talk about it if
he had made his entire set about that
behavior and made himself the butt of
the joke
and really showcase some learning along
the way from that experience I think he
would have been embraced
that's what we really wanted right we
wanted him to learn from it to grow and
to apologize and instead he's just made
a bunch of jokes that were completely
irrelevant so it was like a an elephant
in the room I don't think anyone is
exempt necessarily but I think if you're
in comedy you have to be hyper aware
that anything years you say on stage can
be taken at face value because people
are not comedians they don't know that
you you know you're going onstage a
hundred times to figure out this one bit
and get it perfectly right that's true
yeah but I mean like even just being on
stage you I feel like that gives you a
certain like freedom like even just like
if you were to say something on Twitter
the same thing if you were tweeted that
same thing can come to haunt you but if
you sit on a stage with a mic and it
looks like a stand-up set you can get
away with a lot more yeah definitely
that's a whole Kevin Hart thing you know
he had some tweet what he'd say that he
got the most recent no it's like the
whole like calling his friends like gay
or the f-word yeah something like that
and then like I feel like if someone
said on stage it's like a different lens
like it's like that's okay
well there's also no tone on line so you
can't really understand that something
as a joke she was like it was like ten
years ago and like yeah dad I think is
an important thing to look at because
people dig up all these old tweets I'm
like it was okay to say that back then
it was okay to say [ __ ] back then
like you have to look at it the cultural
lens like I watched bring it on at the
Hollywood cemetery recently now movies
so homophobic it's good but it's like
every time they called someone like a
dyke or a [ __ ] like the whole audience
was like boom and it was like
understandably so that's not okay
anymore but at the time it was totally
accepted different language almost yeah
I mean I have a video that's still up
that has the word [ __ ] in it mm-hmm
and like I don't want to take it down
because at the time like I said it
wasn't nobody complained about it yeah
if they and I called it out so I know
obviously said like this is a different
time and yeah but I'm not gonna take it
down because of what it was mean and
it's clear that it was a different time
and I've I said I'm not gonna use that
now yeah right but yeah it was it's
crazy that that's out there and like
give people if I tried to hide it people
would find it 100 make it a thing oh
yeah people have pointed out like I used
to do a podcast with an X where the
whole point was shocking answers and so
one of the questions like if he could
get away with a crime what would it be
and I was like I would
rape a man so like that's so funny it's
impossible or whatever and we all
discussed to the questions and answers
ahead of time but it is cut like blew up
on reddit as me later down the road
layered way later like five years later
or something and I was like no this is a
horrible cringy joke I was trying to be
funny also like that's the way you cope
with assault when you've been assaulted
you try to make light of it or you use
that kind of language and culture cancel
culture yeah man yeah well that's a good
note to end off but with that being said
thank you is there anything anything you
you want to plug or talk about I'm
releasing a music video every month on
my channel every single month alright so
go to anaconda this is anaconda yeah
okay you have 13 songs I do one a month
so for thirteen months yeah doesn't mean
one year it's a leap year so 13 yes
thank you again for being here yeah
thank you guys and make sure you follow
us at off the pill podcast on Twitter
and at off the pill on Instagram I might
have mixed those up was that right nope
at off the pill on Twitter at
off-the-field podcast and Instagram it's
an ongoing joke that we're never gonna
make it the same thing right yeah yeah
sure with that being said thank you
again this is how we end it um we never
really told you but we just breathe into
the mic in three two one
by this time since you're the third
person that my price smells a little bit
we don't all clean I cleaned it oh but
they're all girls too so it has been all
girls