basically we sold Smosh in 2011 and I
thought I had control of it for a couple
years and then come 2015 I was like oh
whoa whoa this is not mine anymore
I feel like youtubers now honestly have
it better in every regard except for the
over saturation in the market did you
feel competitive with Brian when you're
talking to you yes just get the clampy
claps going welcome back to another
episode of off the pill podcast that was
a nice timing this time today we have
very special guests mr. Anthony padilha
saying that because I'd say that you
earlier today yeah no I said it actually
on the is it too soon I said that on the
one with Ian oh just kidding sorry
talked about then we'll go through some
of that we also have Damon in the
moderator seat and Paco right next to me
[Music]
he's just used to it early at this point
yeah so yeah I mean I we are here with I
mean I'm sure most people know probably
I I consider you and obviously Ian D
like grandfathers of YouTube because you
guys started in the very beginning I am
honored I am honored but I mean you were
like you were like was there people
before you nobody even knows I don't
know I don't know I can't really uh I've
never been able to take that in people
say that seemed like a shut up
but if you think about it though when
you guys started I don't even know I
wasn't on YouTube in oh five yeah yeah
yeah we started uploading a November
2005 there was there wasn't really
anyone that that uploaded consistently
alright time there were other people
obviously but not personalities per se
you know not people that people would
come back to say over and over again
well for people who don't know just
probably a lot let's be honest yeah
everyone's a different time people who
don't know you and Ian who we had a few
a bunch of episodes ago are from Smosh
and Smosh has over 25 million
subscribers
you recently started well recently like
two years ago years ago start your own
channel which is at about three point
three million subscribers which is
pretty crazy in like two years right
it's nice and healthy and I like it
yeah and yeah you've been just working
on your own channel we just did
something together as well yeah yeah
how's that been it's been really nice
now it's really nice there was a
transition period that was really
difficult going from a channel I don't
know how many million subscribers I had
when I left 23 million or whatever to do
my own thing and then people came over
and wanted to see what I was doing there
but truth be told I was still trying to
figure out what it was that he wanted to
do on my own you know and when I started
Smosh with Ian back in the day we were
able to figure it out without anyone
watching but now I was trying to figure
out what I wanted to do on my own and
millions of people were watching and it
was a lot of pressure but eventually
years later now I feel like I finally
figured out what it is that I want to do
and I am really enjoying it yeah I mean
your your content is more geared like
towards an older audience um yeah where
is that I feel like Smosh was a little
bit more for younger people right coming
in yeah for sure you know I it was it
was just outright just straight-up
comedy for lack of a better term I'd say
it was a little bit more shallow because
there wasn't really a message that we
were always trying to spread or anything
like that was just comfort laughs and
leave with a smile on your face right
and now the stuff that I'm doing I hope
has a little bit more of a deeper
message you know I hope people leave my
video is now feeling like they
understand people more mm-hmm
with the yeah it was I spent a day with
blank you know so the one that I just
shot with you Ryan was I spent a day
with legendary youtubers and basically
gets a funny way to describe legendary I
mean dude like you are one of the most
legendary youtubers I don't know how
funny because it's like you were first
like you guys were the first we're not
talking about me they know but you're in
it and you haven't
address that right you guys refer I
remember I started to not see actually
David was before I was oh really
yeah and I remember watching your
Pokemon video it was featured on the
home page of YouTube that's when I first
crazy yeah copyrighted material yeah you
do homepage Wow
well there is no money to be made so
there was no one complaining well yeah
that's true yeah yeah that is crazy
though I'm honored yeah you guys are I
mean people call me og right but then
when I think of Smosh I'm like actually
no I mean no it is really difficult for
me to take a compliment so probably good
to stop there yeah so what else do we
want to talk about that's really nice
eight point seven billion total views on
Smosh channel that you helped create
yeah yeah created I I initially made
Smosh as just a website and I was just
for me and my group of friends in high
school and you know so that that logo
and everything was me as a 14 year old
kid you know in my bedroom just like
tinkering away with a little logo and
stuff and it's it is strange that you
know it became a brand and then you know
I can leave that continue to do my own
thing and that brand still exists out
there how not to get right into it but
how I mean it wasn't a split instant
decision when you decided to leave Smosh
No
how long were you unhappy there I know
it's a long story
yeah yeah yeah I started having my I
started second-guessing everything in
early 2015 which was about a year year
and a half before I eventually left
because I realized how much this brand
that I thought I had ownership of was
really just you know the it was we
basically we sold Smosh in 2011 and I
thought I had control of it for a couple
years and then come 2015 I was like oh
whoa whoa whoa this is not mine anymore
other people are controlling it they
wanted to be a certain way I want this
to evolve I want this to kind of
keep up with me as I age and my values
change but because it wasn't mine
because it was owned by a company they
had very clear ideas for what that brand
should be and what it should remain as
he gave me or give us an example of like
like something that they let you try to
do and they were like no no no that's
not like like I guess the cousin you're
doing now is that something you tried to
do earlier or no I didn't I didn't
necessarily you know I got to be honest
I didn't necessarily try to do something
that they outright said no don't do that
but they were now you know 20 30 people
working without me necessarily giving a
direction to them and they were all
doing this thing and plans were being
made constantly I couldn't tell everyone
to stop and you know whole production on
a million different things that were
going on behind the scenes so I could
come in and change things it wasn't it
didn't operate the same way as just two
guys obviously you know I there were so
many more moving elements to it that it
became apparent that it wasn't mine
mm-hmm you know so when you say in 2011
right you said we sold so when you say
that you sold what did that mean cuz you
guys were still like I never understood
that yes because you guys were still on
it could yeah all the time yeah what
changed basically from 2010 or right
before you sold it mm-hmm what changed
um a company approached us and said hey
we can offer you X amount of money in
stocks and we will now own the company
100% you will be employees of this
company you will be salaried we will pay
you well and you know me growing up from
a pretty poor family in suburban
Sacramento I was like yeah you know that
sounds great I don't know what the
future of this is gonna look like and I
get to have a guaranteed paycheck which
is very strong like especially at the
time oh yeah it wasn't like we weren't
sure at in 2010 yeah that this was gonna
continue yeah I was 23 and I was like I
need to make sure that I am set up in
any way that I can
and I just had a fear that I was gonna
be stuck in poverty forever so I was
like this is my way out you know give me
that give me that paycheck and you know
that monthly paycheck and that that
stock that you value the company to be
worth I will take that and hold on to
that and hopefully sell it for a lot in
the future and then you know I could
retire or sell my own company on the
side or whatever and spoiler alert when
the company shut down last year that
stock just evaporated into nothing ever
ended up - yeah you guys got screwed
uh yeah yeah yeah we got screwed but I I
also I also feel slightly responsible
for that you know so I feel like I if I
were smarter I would have asked more
questions I would have had more people
looking into it for me I would have done
more research instead of being so
excited to sign that dotted line right
did you have a lawyer look over your
contract well as a lawyer but I don't
know if the lawyer really had my best
interest you know yeah and and there
were other people that had their hands
in it that I know didn't have my best
interest in it so maybe it's safe to say
that you know a 23 year old from a small
town was taken advantage of or two of us
I guess yeah we're you and Ian on the
same page during all this we were yeah
we were but I feel like we really didn't
do enough research we didn't really look
into it enough and there was something
about the the pace at which we were
creating content and just moving
constantly that it felt like we couldn't
really take time to to really take it
all in yeah we weren't able to really
soak it in and understand what we're
really doing or that you know I can only
speak for myself right yeah well I mean
I I mean that makes sense because I I
think it was around that same time maybe
2000 a little earlier like 2009 for me
where I almost gave up my channel to do
a Nickelodeon show whoa
it's it's a show that actually was
created yeah it was called Supah Ninjas
uh-huh and it was kind of based off of I
don't we did a lot of ninja stuff yeah
yeah that should I
it went out for like two seasons I think
but anyway it was a Nickelodeon show and
Shawn and I were gonna do it but then
they said you got to get rid of your
channel or everything on it's not
Nickelodeon appropriate yeah yeah I get
I was pretty clean though but I mean
they were clean that's really again I
get because Nickelodeon super super
clean yeah but it was a time where like
I had literally I was considering it
like I was probably making more on
YouTube then I was gonna make on
Nickelodeon but there was something
about it being a real thing right yeah
nobody knew YouTube is gonna be a thing
so I I completely understand like if you
someone told me hey here's a salary I
mean and it was a great amount oh yeah
oh yeah yeah then for sure
yeah so I mean I don't think that's uh I
don't think they can be helped like I
said you guys were like a pioneer right
so nobody there was no rules back then
no there's like the business it was the
Wild West and you yeah you didn't have
any figure it out and that's what it was
mm-hmm so yeah people definitely saw the
goldmine oh yeah other people did yeah
probably specifically artists right yeah
yeah I remember back in the day there
was talk amongst the YouTube community
about you guys working with the Disney
executive maybe he was a manager yeah
yeah he started off as our manager and
he became the president of the company I
don't wanna get too much details until
now or went when the company dissolved
he was he was still there I think he
left about six months before I did for
his own personal reasons yeah got it
well uh just going back to kind of what
you said so there there seems to be like
a lot of different pros and cons to
being like a legendary og youtubers you
know like one of the big cons of being
taken advantage of clearly yeah back
then when no one knew was going yeah so
I guess we want that if there's more
pros and cons that you wanted to explore
on or maybe in comparison of like the
youtubers now then they haven't that I
guess a lot of people can thank you for
in a way because you had to deal with
those hardships oh I see you're saying I
I feel like uh youtubers now honestly
have it better in every regard
except for the oversaturation in the
market there's so much more competition
and really that's that's the only
downside that I see maybe there's more
that I don't see because I'm kind of
disconnected from that now but I feel
like back in the early days it was
figuring things out on your own it was
the lack of money in the market there
were obviously less viewers on the
market to to to have content even be
viewed by and brands didn't take it
seriously companies in take it take you
seriously and I feel like all of that
has changed yep and the only thing
that's that's become difficult is that
now there's just so many people that are
that are part of it yeah well I mean a
big difference to is like you know back
in the day there was I mean we say
there's a lot less people but there was
still a lot of people oh yeah I mean
yeah but I feel like back in the day
it's like if somebody made something
awesome yeah eventually people would
find that person right I feel like now
you gotta be with some you got to get
some kind of hookup like you gotta be
collabing unless you're like magnificent
mmm I hate like you have to like be with
an MCN or you gotta like be friends with
somebody there's always like you gotta
have like connections in collab and do
all these things were like back in the
days just just make good stuff and then
eventually it'll pay off yeah used to be
my advice to people they'd be like how
do I get my content like how do I create
a fanbase and I'd always be like just
make good stuff focus on making good
stuff don't try to get fans they'll come
to you and eventually people will find
your stuff when you make good enough
stuff you can't say that now nope that
doesn't mean sadly yeah like it used to
be like just just do your follow your
dreams and no no no through the math yes
follow the algorithm there's there's
like twenty one day's worth of content
uploaded every minute on YouTube or
something ridiculous right yeah that's
crazy yeah it's just insane and I don't
know if YouTube like wants to admit it
or not but I feel like YouTube has
become just a gaming and music platform
the things that are there are on
trending at the time is just like music
yeah I I don't know if it was always
like that or not but I feel like it's
it's gone that direction
the trending tab to check it don't want
us no not really I think it was out
because I'm curious yeah so but it
doesn't I don't I don't understand it
maybe there'll be a video with like
10,000 views on it no one understands
how trending works I think it's some
combination of the speed at which
viewers are coming in and the
interaction they're having with the
content and also where they're coming
from mm-hmm I don't understand the exact
algorithm though yeah I have no idea
either
I think the algorithm is always changing
the advertisers and yeah different times
it's always change you said we're always
chasing the algorithm yeah and you never
you never know what is gonna work really
you know the the best way to do things
now is just like try to get an audience
to stay with your video as long as you
can mm-hmm that's the only thing so it
goes back to what you guys were saying
make good content make good conscious
keep going yeah but it's different now
it's not just it's not just make good
content but it's make captivating
content that people feel like they can't
click away from yes they're constantly
you know on that page there's always at
least one other video that can be seen
on the screen at once unless it's in a
full screen yeah and that video is
always enticing them and you're battling
to keep people watching instead of
clicking that other person's derail but
that's thing to like you need to have a
really good title and thumbnail yes so
that they they click away from someone
else's we're here to go to yours and
also you know the title and thumbnail is
all that really matter if you think
about it in this context and your video
content is just there to prove that it
was worth that click it's it's almost
backwards now exactly up well that's the
secrets of YouTube well I want to
explore this a little bit more because
uh you decided to step away make your
own content you know you had millions of
people's eyes on you yeah we're I'm sure
you felt the pressure of like you know
your former boss is looking over your
shoulder now yep a lot of eyes looking
over your shoulder but you do have this
open creativity how much did you play
around the algorithm and stuff or were
you more strictly like no I want to do
what I want to do no you know how do you
how do you play the game like what's
your mindset now yeah
tackling you ah initially I didn't even
know what
once it from me I just made content when
I first left and I experiments it with a
million different types of videos and
the things that's the thing that stuck
work was content that was a little bit
longer and appealed to a general
audience that didn't necessarily know
have to know who I was to view it so
then I started making more of that and
that eventually evolved into that I
spent a day with series which is what I
just shot with you today Ryan yeah yeah
and I think that really works because
it's it's captivating in the sense that
it's a subject that's easily digestible
people are like oh I want to learn more
about whatever it is legendary youtubers
or you know Pro cosplayers or
flat-earthers or a SM artists and they
stick around because the way that I edit
is I think it's captivating or Mike my
editor is extremely good and then the
contents long enough that the YouTube
algorithm rewards you for that watch
time right right yeah it's kind of a
formula it's a way yeah for sure and you
got it you have to unfortunately I tried
to fight it for the longest time really
short content like no I'm sticking to
what I grew up with like it but you have
to you have to certain degree you want
to be able to keep ya audience keyboard
keep doing it as a career right hi yeah
you have to you have to find that
balance and I was always so against it
but I like I finally got to a point
where like okay I'm willing to give
because there's no point if if no one's
seen it right yeah yeah and it's a hard
position to be in because you're like I
wanna make the content that I like
that's why I started that's why I want
to keep going that's what gets me up in
the morning but at the same time you
want to be able to keep doing that yeah
and you're not gonna be able to keep
making content at all if people aren't
watching exactly so you have to find a
happy marriage between this is what my
audience wants this where the general
public wants when they find my videos
and also this is what I like to do and
it's a game they get to play figure out
what it is that you like versus you know
what's gonna get people tips from a
legendary youtuber go check out enjoy go
check but check out is serious I dare
you do was it C on that and I don't know
if this is why I mean we already cuz we
already talked to Ian so we know that
you guys are cool and
stuff but how weird would it be to have
en on the show to have him on my show
because it would be you to you and yeah
yeah I mean I've distance myself from
doing anything Smosh related and I'm
happy with that for the time being
because I really want to establish
myself as an independent creator as
someone that's doing their own thing and
people will always say Anthony from
Smosh which doesn't bother me but the
same time I I feel like I could be known
for what I'm doing now just as much and
I feel like I need to do that before I
mm-hmm start pressure revisiting my past
and and you know inviting people used to
being small or short or whatever you
know I feel like I need to establish but
that's what I mean that I feel like it's
so you're saying legendary youtubers I
can think of more like fitting than you
guys that's why I brought that up on
your show like what you should be really
asking yourself a lot of stuff but it's
just a weird scenario because I guess it
makes sense it makes sense because you
can really interview yourself well yeah
also I know I know what the hell's going
on in my life oh I know what you see
your answers to other questions too well
you could ask him right now no on off
the bill pot yeah that's the stuff out
when we were talking about all I want to
ask you the same I got a question here
so you know you're a lot of youtubers
they want to make the transition into
Hollywood and it seems like you you know
you're one of the very few youtubers
have stayed true to the platform and
creating mmm you know being a youtuber
mm-hmm and in every sense of that word
mm do you have do you still have desired
I mean I don't know if you ever did but
do you have desire to cross over yeah
yeah I I I do really enjoy acting and I
have really been enjoying learning how
to get in touch with my emotions and
express those emotions not just you know
through my therapy which you know helped
me get over all that stuff that we
talked about with with companies and my
old company and all that but it also
helped me realize that I've been
avoiding being in touch with my feelings
for so long
and acting kind of goes hand-in-hand
with therapy I feel it'll I've been able
to tap into why I'm feeling the things
that I'm feeling and acting is a lot
about that it's about feeling things and
not not saying or trying to show things
which is actually feeling them and I
feel like that's something that a lot of
people don't really get a lot of on
YouTube so I've been taking some of that
like I've something like I'm just gonna
talk about my feelings on here and see
how people feel about that and then I
feel like they also people want to
listen more when you talk about your
feelings and you're vulnerable so I want
to get good at acting too so that maybe
people will listen to what I have to say
because you know they could they see me
exploring my emotions on screen mm-hmm
do you feel like those videos where you
do explore your most emotion do a lot
better yeah for sure for sure and people
have I think they feel a little bit more
of a connection because they feel like
you know I'm being real yeah and I feel
like on YouTube it's kind of hard to
find people that are being real mm-hmm
are you referring to some people when
you say that I'm not referring to anyone
general I'm just saying for my general
person but I have a follow-up question I
guess because you know you said this
platform is being oversaturated yeah
where a lot of in the beginning was kind
of like you know it is a lot more raw
this is we are this is our how we feel
hmm and then it became like mass
production where you took the feeling
out yeah because it's so much so like we
need to keep pushing these out just
content content that in a way audiences
now are looking for something more than
to continue in that swai you do have
that connection a lot more yeah exactly
I feel like I'm just I'm tired of
shallow content and I don't enjoy
watching it I don't enjoy making it and
I'm honestly like I I feel like people
must be feeling the same way I'm feeling
because I'm just tired of it was what's
shell what is shallow content for me
it's it's coming it's it's it's almost
like a it's watching something and
feeling like it was really just
entertainment
you know it's um it's like a challenge
video or I don't know I can't think of
something specific because I honestly
don't watch that stuff it's something
that I feel like doesn't really make me
leave feeling like I learned something
or you know maybe I learn something
about a subject or learn something about
the human psyche in some way so how does
that sound pretentious that's your
interest what are some things on YouTube
that you like watching anything that has
education attached to it in some way
what's the German channel that starts
with the K that's all animated and so
educational cursed well I don't know
something like that starts with the K I
can never say what say we say I hope I
hope I offended someone when I say
definitely yeah I'm getting cancelled
right now just with a case that would be
the Russian version um I'm if just
offending everyone yeah you're gonna get
so cancer I'm getting Hansel Germans and
the Russians yeah um but basically
education is what you're saying you want
to learn now that's that's where I
that's what I feel like I didn't waste
my time coming out of you know or you
know something like this like a podcast
where people are talking about how they
feel in their experiences right I also
enjoy that but coming in for content
laughing and leaving unless that content
that makes me laugh kind of says
something about you know human behavior
in general or something I I will enjoy
it but I don't find myself compelled to
keep coming back over and over and over
well I mean like that's one of the
reasons why I like doing the podcast as
well as cuz yeah
for me it's taken by my own selfish
thing it's like Helen I like to like
these conversations I could never
normally have you know what videos right
and then also like talking to people
that you relate to other youtubers yeah
and you know up until recently a lot of
the you know talking about like burning
out and like and feeling like the
pressures and all that stuff was very
kept to yourself up until like the past
few years that's true I didn't know
you're feeling any of this yeah I mean
no most people don't and yeah and for
the most part like you don't really put
that into your content like if when you
were with Smosh like you didn't
that kind of stuff it was just like
skits yeah this is how come you laugh
but like I mean for you yourself I mean
at what point were you when you were
with Smosh feeling that kind of I mean
if you were feeling that kind of burnout
mm-hmm and it was it more a burnout
because of workload or was it because
you just didn't want to be creating that
kind of content anymore it was more than
I just didn't feel like creating that
kind of content I am a workaholic so I
love working all the time so it didn't
really bother me you know the workload
didn't bother ya it was more just you
don't you wanted to get out of it yeah
and I still I still enjoyed it you know
so it wasn't really black-and-white
because I did still enjoy it but I felt
like I enjoyed or as more being pulled
toward other kinds of content mhm but
even like you said you always enjoyed
acting did you enjoy acting in that
style I did not you got over it right we
got super over it after a couple years I
would imagine so yeah you know just
acting [ __ ] it was like that's basically
how I would define my acting and smart
yeah just like high-pitched like kids
like that right it's like it you know we
got over it yeah you know I started when
I was 17 18 and I was making content
that I thought was you know funny and at
the same time people a couple years
younger than me which ended up being 12
13 14 year olds thought it was funny and
that kind of fit in with with what their
interests were but as I grew you know I
left some when I was 29 I feel like I
couldn't keep making content for the
same people that I was making it for
when I first started right right so and
then so when you first cuz you said you
are doing what you want to do now yeah
when you first had left and did your own
channel hmm how long like what what kind
of I didn't watch enough to know yeah I
saw the first couple videos it you know
it was being talked about but like how
how was that process because it must
have been I know you had some struggles
I saw some interviews and stuff but like
what were you thinking of feeling during
that time it was pretty supportive right
oh really supportive you know I was
really happy with all the support that I
had other other youtubers fans from from
back over at Smosh
the whole community seemed really
supportive of everything but it was it
was a struggle because I wanted to make
stuff and I didn't know what to make and
I also felt like this opportunity had
been given to me to create content on
YouTube and speak to a large amount of
people and I knew that I made a lot of
people happy when I was making content
as Smosh and I wanted to do that for
myself but I didn't know what to do and
I was also giving myself pressure to
immediately get bigger numbers and
appeal to just as many people as I did
on Smosh so I had immense amount of
pressure constantly over my shoulders
and I feel like it wasn't really until I
got over that that I was able to focus
on what it what is it that I like to do
like what kind of message do I want to
spread by these videos right you know I
realized that I am tired of watching
like I said shallower stuff but also
negative negativity on YouTube is such a
huge thing that's popular right now yeah
from a lot of commentary channels and
reaction channels and things like that
and I'm not saying react channel that
that is a positive space but there are
channels where people react to things in
a negative way and like roasting is so
popular and stuff like that and I just
I'm kind of tired of it I'm like we have
a choice about what kind of a message we
want to spread and how we want people to
feel after watching our videos so why
not take that and make it something
positive that makes you feel good and
not in the cheesy wholesome way where
you know I'm like ooh this this feels
gross this feels like I'm in a cult like
this is not you're not being honest when
you're trying to be wholesome here yeah
so I try to make my content I try to
have be like wholesome and make you feel
like just make you feel happy at the end
of it but at the same time come at you
with jokes and be really fast-paced and
a little bit edgy at the same time god
I've never explained any of that stuff
before so I didn't know how to put that
into words so yeah that's that's good
though cuz there's clearly shows that
you thought about it a lot
so and yeah like you said you went to
therapy
yeah I'm still going trust me that's
good it's good and I would recommend it
to everyone that can because it's it's
made me realize things about my past may
be more sympathetic toward my past self
and therefore made me more sympathetic
toward my current self because I
understand why I am the way I am more
right okay well with that being said
we're gonna take a quick little shishi
break it get some therapy
ooh and so we will be right back and
we're back yeah so what were you talking
about just now how there is there is a
connection between you and Paco oh you
guys first met there the shishi break we
just found out yeah you guys were
actually you guys have met before
yeah very pleasant terms we did a I did
a show called internet icon and it was
like a American Idol but for youtubers I
think it's more survivor kind of server
you're getting hold it all oh yeah every
day let's call America no no but you
have to like okay I never watched
survivor okay so anyway yes I did that
show and I had Anthony on is one of the
guest judges it was the final episode
before the top three were picked yeah I
was within those four groups by date the
top four it was Smosh jenna Marbles and
PewDiePie
oh the with you guys all judged in the
same episode yeah that was a big episode
yeah yeah and all of them relate you all
in the same day [ __ ] that Paco guy I
don't know
know what I said but I apologized oh no
I kicked you off the Nellis that was his
rightful place
got to that high in that case you
deserve that anyway that shows how far
back we go we're old school friends wow
that's old school to think beautify and
jennamarbles our old school because I
can still imagine them yeah I remember
when they were new yeah I was like I
remember when Jenna came along I was
like all this girls oh yeah I remember
she wasn't even that big I just like
this girls funny she has some guys she's
gonna blow a beauty pie I honestly
didn't believe like I knew he was big I
just didn't believe that his content was
gonna be well he changed it right but
yeah I didn't believe that was gonna
last it transcended it completely and we
need a justice child that smells like
okay this guy's brilliant yeah yeah he's
doing he knows how to craft things he
knows how to give people what they want
yep he's smart he's smart and he's
number one right now right to still or
is it a series but we don't talk about
that yeah speaking of number one this is
the question that I'm I'm kind of
curious about there's not even Twitter
question she's not a Twitter question
since David show my question yeah it
straight from the heart okay so I know
that both of you guys were the top most
subscribed in the world both number one
at certain points in history yeah you
guys made history Wow I think I think at
a certain point either when Ryan was
number one Smosh was number two and when
the Smosh was number one Ryan was number
two I mean I'm asking is Anthony yeah
did at any point did you feel
competitive when you didn't really know
Ryan did you feel competitive with Brian
yeah when you're talking to Ian yes yes
so you guys talked a lot of it no no it
wasn't that it wasn't like it wasn't
like oh this sucks or anything like that
about the content or Ryan personally but
it was just it was a cool space to be in
it was like we were racing for
subscribers at the time and it was a it
felt like the whole world was watching
even though we weren't making videos
about it we weren't you know you weren't
trying to milk it or anything like that
but it felt like people were watching
and me maybe we were just in our heads
about it but you know comment sirs we're
constantly you know when you could
comment on people's channels people
commenting on the channels and you would
just see it there all the time so it
would get in your head when you're up
there and that that race is going on and
people are posting the the difference in
subs and stuff and it was it was
exciting and even back in the day on
your profile page it would say number
one most subscribe I I'd like that great
good for the day right it was like a
number one most viewed for the day yeah
yeah I like that stuff I'm sure it I
mean subscriptions like we we talked
about before it doesn't matter as much
yeah but yeah but at the time it did
yeah it was a big deal because it
actually you know meant something like
people act your subscribers would get
your videos yeah always
and there were top subscriber lists
exact they were top most viewed the day
of the month of that whatever and those
would be lists that people would
frequent and that's how you would get
new viewers is by making something that
landed somewhere on those way exactly
yeah and now they're gone no but all
right it's funny cuz there was so a bit
of like competition
but like I think like the first time I
met you was YouTube live yeah and even
deep I just am I gonna met everyone even
keV all you guys so 2007 I think or nine
I was in college dirty and that's Bo
Burnham is kind of shy awkward but like
super talented so yeah he's awesome
yeah but then like we met everyone and
everyone was like super nice it was such
a different feeling cuz I just went to
VidCon yeah the first time in like eight
years yeah and this is even before the
first VidCon I know it's such a
different feeling like when we that
first Youtube live when everyone met up
I was just like
this is like a sense of like like family
it was family everybody yeah everybody
was so nice and like welcoming inside
yeah oh I think I review yeah definitely
seen you before yeah like it was such a
nice feeling now I mean not to say that
people aren't nice but it doesn't have
there's so many people and new people
that yeah it feels a little it does it
feels different it's not it's not that
we're expecting it feels very
disconnected people know how to network
now and it'll exactly we're almost
trained to networking yeah so they meet
you and they talk in a very specific way
and you know it's you know it's a
rehearsed thing that they say to
everyone yeah and the tone of their
voice was like oh hey oh my god yeah so
nice and but it's like not Daniel
genuine it's like you're actually
connecting in any real way right but I
don't think people realize that it's
weird cuz it's so common I would assume
it's common now because I haven't been
to one of those convinced that was my
first time to anything in like a long
time yeah I was like wow this is so
weird
different wasn't overwhelming it was it
was and it made me feel really old
because I grew up watching you and
they're like huge now got three million
yeah you're like 25 people saying I wash
you in elementary school and they're
like like eighteen year like adults yeah
yeah yeah it's it's crazy yeah I
actually interviewed a joanne acedia and
she is 19 and I realized that she was
four years old when I started uploading
a new content to YouTube while yes so
another question I don't know if it's
too personal but I'm curious right well
I think a lot of people are curious
about hmm how do you as a large youtuber
mm-hmm
when you're dating mm-hmm just talk
about that
you're like oh hey dating is um it's a
confusing landscape to be in just
because you never know what people's
intentions are I have a personal fear of
being cancelled and for some reason in
my head I think that someone is gonna
set me up in some way so I'm like okay
so someone yeah I'm like I'm like
there's gonna be some crazy reporter
that's gonna go undercover and date me
and then they're gonna like try to get
me to say something I don't know why I
like I have these weird irrational yes
so it's it's complicated I actually kind
of remember that about you there was a
couple irrational fears no yeah he
mentioned something else in the past too
that you what I don't remember what is
some kind of eggs aiya tea anxiety thing
I have intense anxiety right and I had
panic attacks for very long so maybe
that's the thing I'm trying to remember
maybe what triggered that um what
triggered panic attacks or what what
triggers it for you now it's just
feeling completely overwhelmed it
happens a lot less frequently now the
last time I had a last time I had a
panic attack was I was about to karaoke
with a bunch of people that I I didn't
really want to hang with but I had
agreed to do it and I was like I'm gonna
have to sing in front of these people I
don't even want to hang out with them
and that was enough that was enough to
do it for me oh really
but for the most part it's it's a fear
of fear that's what a panic attack
really is so it's because you start
getting anxiety and then anxieties
anxiety everyone feels anxiety but then
it really starts spiraling out of
control when you start getting when it
starts building on itself you start to
feel fear and you say oh I'm about to
get a panic attack and you're like oh
just business this is this thing this is
gonna be such a terrible situation this
is not the right place to get one and
then you start going bigger and bigger
and bigger with the way that you feel
like your whole world is crushing down
it's gonna be the worst thing ever and
then it becomes that because you have
that fear mm-hmm and did a going to
therapy
is that when all of it kind of changed
where didn't happen way less I don't
know if that I don't know if that did
maybe but a big thing that helped me
back in the day get get over because I
was having panic attacks multiple times
a day for a while and I think what
really helped me get over that was I
read some article online about it and
they said no they explained about how
it's just the fear of having a panic
attack that gives you a panic attack
which is a really weird thing to read
I'm like what
that doesn't make sense and then they
mentioned that it's the fear of being
out of control so they mentioned also
that it be very difficult to give
yourself a panic attack because you'd
feel like you're in control of giving
yourself a panic attack so I sat down
and tried to give myself one and I
wasn't able to get one and I realized it
was because it was the fear that was
causing it and then I felt more in
control of it and that helps me that
that didn't get over that's a good
advice for people who have panic attacks
try and give it to yourself it's also
scary though because some people might
not be ready for that you have to really
be ready for that because okay we don't
want to give advice anyway this is
Anthony's experience I do remember you
mention it well I don't know if it was
that specifically but I remember
something like that my mom or phobic and
for the dumb people like me was that
mean that means that she has she has a
very she gets panic attacks all the time
and an intense fear of not being in
control as well and that's kind of made
her reside only within the boundaries of
the house because that's where she feels
most comfortable so do you feel like
learning more about yourself and how to
deal with the the panic attacks that
you've learned to kind of like let go in
a way are you holding on more tight and
a little bit doing that now and it's
helped me let go a little bit more and
I've become more comfortable knowing
that something that makes me
uncomfortable may happen because I'm I'm
just I don't know I don't know why I'm
just like if it happens it happens and
that's really helped me do you do you
feel that what you were feeling with the
anxiety and panic attacks had to do in
part with you becoming very famous at an
early age
oh maybe but I think most of it was that
I I feel like it might have happened
regardless if it wasn't if it wasn't you
know cuz maybe it was from the fear and
anxiety that I felt around maintaining
this status of you know whatever I was
like number one most subscribed at the
time when I was getting I don't know
it's like 2009 or something when it
really started happening pretty
intensely for me and I was up there on
the top maybe that's why you know I had
a lot of anxiety about that but I feel
like if it wasn't that then it would
have been anxiety about my finances or
something because I grew up without much
money and I felt like I would have been
stuck in that and I would have probably
been really stressed about that as well
I think it's great that you're talking
about this right now because there are
so many more than ever young kids who
are getting super famous like on tik-tok
like I'm at VidCon you see these little
kid these 12 year old left 10 year old
kids who have millions of fans and they
don't know how to deal with theirs know
I always say this there's no book or
therapy book on how to become famous
yeah there's there's no right well
there's probably a right way to do it
but there's there's no one that will
teach you how to do it you just have to
navigate that I feel like I feel like I
was fortunate enough to blow up in a
time where the general public didn't pay
attention so I was able to still go
right to the store I was able to still
do whatever you know I don't feel like
people like Jeffrey star or James
Charles can go to any store without
having mobs of people be excited to see
them and I feel like yeah I was number
one most subscribed at a time where you
were able to be a little bit more
incognito and I was I'm glad that I was
able to kind of warm up to it and write
figure things out but if I were to go
from zero to a hundred now if I were to
become number one most subscribed now
going from yesterday not having you know
any following it would be completely
overwhelming and I would probably feel
burnout and fear and like all these
things that would probably made me pull
away from it III think majore like I
wouldn't recommend I don't know at what
age but like people who are I'm gonna
say at least fifty
like you have to these people who are
under the age of like I don't even know
what the exact number is but kids kids
becoming famous I don't think it's good
for them and any kid I mean look at look
at every single like Disney star back in
the day yeah Macaulay Culkin Macaulay
well they all go through some kind of
phase some of them making out okay a lot
of them end up really messed up Miley
Cyrus Miley Cyrus I mean a lot of people
and and she kind of turned it around a
little bit
right but everybody goes through that
phase and and it's it's bound to happen
yeah and a lot of it stems from like
they're on top of the world at one point
and you grew up with that becoming your
normal right
can you imagine thinking that your whole
normal is this Fame that you have as a
ten-year-old and then or whatever even
younger and then you know reality hits
you when your knee goes well and that
that fame is gone or you don't have
people mentoring you in the same way and
would you treat you differently people
treat you differently yeah and I'm sure
part of feeling like a has-been probably
really does that to you and that only
applies to certain people I'm not saying
the people you mentioned and then also
just having it's almost like a lot of
power to do whatever you want and then
not knowing what to do with that mm-hmm
it's it's uh like I think the only way
you can really survive the Hat is having
like really really tight circles and
having it making sure those people in
that circle know how to educate you on
that a support system yeah it's I mean
cuz it happens it happens to I mean even
for me like having like different stages
of like thinking I'm more important than
I am and then going to the stage of like
wait up wait no this doesn't mean
anything like and it's and then seen
them like becoming number one and then
becoming number two in like going to
that psychology as a kid is different
like maybe now cuz we've been in in it
for so long it doesn't really mean much
but as a kid and now we're older kids at
the time right yeah yeah only happier
like really but imagine like a
twelve-year-old if when you were 12 and
that happens soon you're like the
biggest thing in the world you see
yourself a certain way you don't realize
like when that gets taken away from you
and it will it's you got to go through
that psyche like something's
gonna happen there like it's not a good
combo unless you have like the best head
on your shoulders right right which can
only be provided by a support system of
probably older right which is really
like when you're at the top of the world
whoo yeah you gotta imagine the people
around you people circulating towards
you oh yeah you know positive
reinforcement yeah things you don't
necessarily deserve
who was your in like your circle like
who are your mentors and people that
kind of kept you in check is you you
seem all right right now like I don't
see I don't know I found it person I
don't think I really had any back then
but it was different you know I wasn't a
Macaulay Culkin you know it was whose
youtube and it was weren't so much under
a microscope as it is now yeah I also I
wasn't going out I wasn't super social I
wasn't going out to parties where people
worshipped me or something like that you
know and I was I was also I feel like I
stayed pretty humble I think part of it
was that I felt like I was not deserving
of anything that I had so I feel like
that helped me not get into into my head
and I still feel like that you sometimes
you know I learned that it's imposter
syndrome which is a real thing where you
feel like you don't deserve whatever it
is that you have and assume people are
gonna find out that you're a fraud and
you've been faking it this whole time
that's the only reason people like you
but I've always had that and I think
that as bad as that feels to have to
think of yourself that way it it's it
helped me where do you think what do you
think that feeling came from of you
feeling like you're not really worthy of
all of these great successes I don't
know I feel like bringing maybe I don't
know let me know part of it maybe was
that I was just like I'm just lucky you
know I always just told myself I was
lucky and I don't I can't say where that
came from
maybe it was my parents thing maybe my
parents are great at that man I think
that's I mean like even for me I felt
the same thing yeah like I mean
obviously there's a lot of work that
goes into which you I'm sure can admit
to as well yeah but a lot of it's luck
right and I think that's the same case
for everyone to a certain degree right
and there's like a there's actually a
lot of people who are very successful
that have the
imposter syndrome hmm and the reason why
it's a real thing yeah yeah oh the
opposite is Dunning Creek Kruger oh I
don't know what that is it's the it's
where somebody feels like they know a
lot they don't know that much so it's
the opposite of them ha
it's like they're deserving of
everything yeah and they're like I'm
very smart so it's people who like talk
a lot but aren't well informed yeah so
okay I've met someone like that reason
exactly okay you know a lot of people
who are very successful well not a lot
you know the people that are successful
and had the impostor syndrome the reason
why they do Wells because they don't
feel like they deserve it so they're
constantly working to try and get that
feeling like I deserve it right that's
true it is a struggle though because I
feel like I'm constantly proving myself
to who knows who but right yeah never
never really satisfied in the sense that
I I feel like ooh I did it yeah I think
I did this I think that's good because
as long as you don't feel that there's
more in life to accomplish more to look
forward to and build towards yeah yeah
but like then I think about that makes
me think about like like Floyd
Mayweather right like he's great he's
greatness in boxing and he's he's all
about him like I did this and but he's
still great you know I mean like I I'm
your biggest fan
that's why I'm saying I unless some of
the best athletes like Michael Jordan
yeah Kobe Bryant like not saying that
they're saying you know oh I got lucky
they're like I did this I feel like it's
a happy middle ground right yeah like
they've had aware that you earned it
they to me I think their personalities
are not normal I think they have
something wrong with their breasts no
really I just really think that
something's wrong with them but that's
why they're so great yeah like you have
some kind of issues I mean if you think
about what Kanye says if Kanye said what
he said without his accomplishment he'd
be wearing different types of sweaters
can you imagine if Kanye had impostor
syndrome
[Laughter]
like him yeah I would there is something
likeable about that my dark disadvantage
he would be a completely different
meaning yes what would you be doing if
YouTube disappeared tomorrow if it
disappeared tomorrow I think um change
platform mixer let's say social media
disappeared hard I was boring it is I I
just went to to a retreat where for one
whole week Monday through Friday there
was no internet reception my entire
premises and I did that right after
VidCon I knew I was gonna need it I was
like I got a detox from this I and I it
was the longest I ever went without just
having some kind of technology
accessible it always descends it was up
north in Northern California yeah it
felt so good yes the first three days I
think I'd be miserable in first three
days I was reaching for my phone like
okay I got a look at that video see how
I people liked my video I posted because
I posted it right as I was driving out
of the reception I was like did I say
something the video that people are
going to notice and then I'm not gonna
be there to remove it but and we have
the same thought just really yeah so
you're not to your degree but yeah it's
pretty bad for me but it is cool to know
that that's that's go through that yeah
so for the first three days or so but
but the last two days it felt really
nice to not look down at my phone and
and also not waste time on social media
because that's that is most of what I do
on social media is just waste time and
fill gaps I'm like if I if I'm walking
up a set of stairs I'm like well that's
kind of boring we've got my Instagram or
like I'm like out of urine home like
well you know I got 15 seconds at most
what about when you looked oh yeah
that's one of the worst for me like I
know it's a habit but laughs it feels so
boring now I remember without I remember
looking at the wallpaper and coming up
with that looks like yeah
kids and I don't even do that anymore
yeah but how was that it's great it was
great was pooping pooping was great hey
I was like I was a present pooper but
don't bring their phone into the
bathroom really just took everything in
yeah let it all out at the same time it
was the whole experience was very nice
and it gave me a little bit of
perspective and I brought a journal and
I wrote down the ways that I felt and I
documented it in that sense and I just
referred to it I was like oh that's
really nice that's a it's a nice
reminder I wrote down how much I don't
like looking at my stats and how much I
felt really good not looking at social
media and feeling like I constantly had
to be in the know and you know looking
at the news just because I had to be in
the know like that stuff doesn't
actually matter as much as I saw a
challenge the five day no but you know I
but then that does goes like it there's
some meaning behind it
yeah the challenge that has meaning it
is that day no technology challenge but
then how are they document that sure it
does defeat the purpose because people
only one talking I spent a day without
my phone who thought about doing the
video I spent today with people with
that don't have cell phones or something
that's like that's really not that
interesting actually they just walk
around it may have life and read a great
experience to people without their phone
are generally a little bit happier yeah
cuz you you have your phone on you cuz
you constantly wanna be connected to
everything but there's a lot of distress
that that you're connected to constant
that things happening in the world or
that stress of feeling like you need to
keep up to date and post stuff or
whatever you know you said earlier to me
that you feel pressure to post on
Instagram and when I didn't have my
phone at all I didn't feel any pressure
right it's a post or anything to keep up
no way it's almost like like your phone
is a shovel and you're constantly
digging to find more and more and then
digger you deep the more like in a hole
you feel and you're like why can't I
can't stop I can't get out and you're
you keep thinking thinking maybe I'll
find ya
down here yeah maybe there's something
good that'll make me feel good down here
but you're also finding a lot of stuff
that makes you really feel not good or
makes you just kind of feel like a
little bit crazy
yeah more often than not yes once in a
while you'll find a nice doll oh yeah
yeah I mean it's like it's like looking
at YouTube comments incessantly and
you're like look at that one look and
then every once awhile you get that bad
comment you're like I knew that was
gonna be there why did I go this is why
right like you're almost looking here
OMA you almost want to make sure there's
none there by looking for them right so
what did we talk about in this podcast
that you're afraid of that's gonna be in
the comments oh what's your fear how are
you getting it canceled yeah we're just
hanging out I mean it's almost nice
that's why I like I said it's doing
these are fun for me because I catch up
with people like you and yeah you know
it's um we're still making content yeah
but it's just hanging out yeah yeah it
does kind of make you feel like it's the
right environment to talk about some
deeper stuff exactly which I might not
normally in a normal conversation yeah
but after this goes off like we're just
gonna get into the dirty yeah yeah dark
stuff I'm gonna be crying I'm going to
your therapy sessions yeah
come along all right well I mean that
flew by from me we're gonna pop
something up for you but anything you
want to plug or strong answers inventing
a pipe paper strong alternative I hope I
don't know if you are but me and David
are an agreement like we're trying to
get rid of get rid of favorite straws
cuz they're awful yeah there's gotta be
a better way to recite like there's got
a
other things we can recycle and get
straws back I don't know
no anyway check out the video I did with
Anthony yeah I spent a day with
legendary youtubers - it's gonna be the
second one I'm there with legendary
youtubers it's gonna have you it's gonna
have jacksFilms it's gonna have Brandon
Rogers it's gonna be good fun I would
also like to say go to therapy if you
can if you're thinking about it and you
can afford it or you have a therapist
near you you should I think it's great
for everything was gone
stigma should be gone it is like now
like cooler I hope so I hope it has been
things like people are cool with that I
feel like it helped me learn how to like
talk to people because I learned how to
talk about my feelings and not be scared
about what they're gonna say about it
right right and just be good to people
be good again spread positivity advice
from a legendary youtuber with that
being said follow us on at off the pill
on Twitter at off the pill podcast on
Instagram and like all we always end it
we just breathe into the mic 3 2 1
aggressive one yet
[Music]