let's see focused I am so I forgot what
this was light I'm filming by myself
today it's been like years since I've
done that in fact I am gonna be editing
this all by myself which I haven't done
in a long time but then I realize I got
a new computer and I don't have premiere
so I'm gonna be using iMovie remember
this stuff stuff we used to do old
school YouTube hmm hey guys so just like
the title says and I'm sure many of you
have already noticed I have been taking
a little bit of a break from YouTube and
I know that sounds a little bit
misleading because I have been posting
every week but just the podcast and I
have been posting twice a week on higatv
but when I say take a break I mean you
guys know if you've been on this channel
long enough this is not my normal type
of type of content and I know I probably
should have made this video before I
took this little break because that is
what normal youtubers do instead of just
you know upsetting their subscribers and
making them comment like where are you
haven't you been posting but do you know
me I like to go against the grain and by
that I mean go against what you should
do in order to maintain your YouTube
channel but that's okay because there's
still quite a handful of you that are
still here and I'm I actually very much
so appreciate that very much so a pre I
actually very I actually I appreciate
you guys and that's why I felt the need
to kind of explain myself in this video
for those of you that don't know I had
been making videos for a long time on
YouTube since 2006 about 13 years you
know I started in a time where you could
not make money off of YouTube and the
videos I started off doing a really
crappy you know so for me the fun part
was always just trying to get better
than the last video and just keep
improving and draw more fans to you and
see what you can do to be better and
essentially just make better content
because the better your content was I
mean the more YouTube would promote it
and that kind of just fit with my motto
of always wanting to improve and make
something better than the last video
that was always my goal but in the past
five or six years YouTube changed that a
lot and maybe it was even earlier than
that YouTube's algorithm change and
basically it became about watch time so
you wanted to make longer videos
and you wanted people to be watching
them all the way through and for the
longest time I tried to fight that
system and I always believed that you
know you should focus on quality and not
quantity even though that the sacrifice
you know a whole month of not posting
videos which will take a hit on your bun
your buns there's no other way to
describe that just snorted a little bit
but no other way to describe it it would
take a hit on your income because you're
not posting obviously less people are
watching your other videos as well and
for me I was actually okay with that
because like I said it was never really
about the numbers and stuff I just the
thing I really cared about was putting
out good content and stuff that I was
excited and happy to make you know me
and the guys were working on it we were
happy about it we didn't necessarily
care as long as you know a decent amount
of use or I could still pay everyone it
worked but over time as I kept trying to
do that the videos got crazier that
times it took to make it got longer I
don't know I don't even know when
exactly it started to happen but I was
subconsciously I think getting a little
frustrated with YouTube and getting
getting really just bitter I guess with
how what what YouTube had become seeing
the kind of content that was suddenly at
the top of the food chain that I mean I
have nothing against you know when all
the dish traps and stuff was happening I
actually it was one of the people who
said I don't blame them at all they're
actually doing what's what's what you
should be doing for your career that's
smart if I was a smart businessperson I
probably would have followed that trend
I am NOT I go against the grain but
anyway I'm getting a little off track
essentially to make this long story a
little bit shorter I was getting
frustrated with the way YouTube had
become and I guess I don't know when it
started to happen but I started to I had
a I got a very bad attitude having the
hollows to describe it it happened very
slowly like over time like I don't know
if you guys know this or not but over
the past few years I'm not gonna say
every single video but there's a lot of
videos in the past few years that I
posted that I knew for a fact could have
been better it wasn't ready to go out it
wasn't something I was proud of and I
was not happy about if I wasn't laughing
at it it wasn't good to me and I was not
laughing it I would see 90% of the
videos I posted in the last three years
and the finding is the ones I really
liked or the ones that didn't do well
the ones that I hated did super well
just because they were the right topic
or because they had the right like the
right title or the right thumbnail
we're soul encouraging they're like oh
my god right this is so brilliant this
is so smart I love this oh my god you're
the only genuine youtuber or whatever
it's not making funny I'm not making fun
of you guys I actually really appreciate
it all I'm saying is I'm trying to
explain that from my perspective I don't
know why but I would feel worse because
I knew that it wasn't I didn't deserve
it I don't know what see I have some
psychological issues I don't know what
that is and I know like I said it sounds
super first world problem problem me I
mean it is a first world problem but
it's a real it was a problem for me like
I said maybe you have mental issues I
don't know what it is
this is a hard video for me to post I
know it's not fun or funny it's not what
you're used to but it it's just more of
an update and I don't know why I vented
this to you guys but I felt like for the
few of you that cared this is the reason
why the content has changed but again as
much as I said I haven't think in a
break from YouTube there has been videos
that we've been working on if you do is
that I actually had fun doing here's a
little little preview of some of them
coming out I brought back a little bit
of cooking but not really oh oh oh do
you know no see kids you want to cut the
nipple off so they do the longer shows
they're hella fast ever watch those
videos you're like pretty good yeah I
did another ryan tries where i got to
paint some similarly kinda like a bob
ross type a video just because i always
wanted to paint just continue to paint
the entire canvas same color it already
is there's no mistakes here hopefully
gets a little bit lighter it's not
instruction across okay that's that's
not a happy cloud it's a little angry
might have gotten a little bit of black
on the brush another big whoops free
tree needs a friend there's no trees
that have no friends because they would
die you can't tell what one color starts
and where another one began
I can't see it also colorblind we did
another trickshot video and that one is
not something I mean that's one I gotta
thank our old videos but really it's in
the arcade so like it wasn't excuse for
me to just play in arcade games all day
anyway I'm living the life I know I'm
sorry I'm having fun making videos again
that's my main thing that's why I
haven't been posting videos because I'm
having fun making them that makes no
sense we actually have been working on a
crazy video it's about three months in
the making
stop motion and it's for this right here
for a ninja man for ninja mill yes I am
still doing this as well go to Walmart
comm slash ninja mill I think I'm gonna
post that one next actually but anyway I
just made this video to update you guys
thank you to those of you that are still
here watching I have been very afraid to
release this video um I actually wanted
to release it when I was gonna take the
break which was three months ago just
kept pushing it back and in the process
I saw a lot of you got very frustrated
and upset so I want to apologize for
that but I yeah at the time I didn't
even know I was gonna take a break at
the time I was gonna either take a break
or quit but I think I finally realized
that now that I'm creating different
types of content that's not stuff that I
hate I don't need to quit I'm I feel
good I haven't felt this kind of freedom
on this channel since the very beginning
of YouTube I would have never posted
this video of two years ago just me
talking that's not funny it's not
creative for those of you that are still
watching and are okay with that thank
you so much because it trust me it kind
of brought me out of a little mini
depression and I don't use that word
lightly and I know it seems like I'm
just complaining about like minuscule
things there's a lot bigger problems in
the world I know some people can't
afford to just because they hate their
job they can't just quit their job and
do something else you know like I get it
but for anyone out there that is in a
scenario like this just know that
there's a way to get out and you just
have to wait for the opportunity and not
be afraid it's like jumping into a cold
pool you know it
day I need a better quote when trying to
say is don't let fear stop you from
jumping into the pool does that make
sense you know cuz the pool would be
like the new direction that the analogy
is like cuz you're hot right and you
know the pool is nice and cold but it's
scary to jump into it that transition
moment is the scary part so that's the
fear that stops you let me rephrase
don't let fear I guess I guess the
difference in my scenario is some people
don't have the luxury of being able to
just jump into the pool because they
have other responsibilities maybe you
have a kid don't let fear stop you from
jumping into the pool unless you have a
kid to take care of bring the kid in the
pool with you but he may drown you
because you have to swim for you can
jump into the pool if you have really
good legs straight also depends
Hollywood have to kick in the kids where
the kid can stay in the Sun suffering
push the kid into the shallow and don't
let fear of the kid drowning the kid is
on the shallow end of the fear and kids
or don't have fear of just orb don't
jump don't keep you don't have kids is
the lesson so what do you think yeah
think I'll keep editing the videos from
here