oh sorry hey guys so I probably should
have made this video before I went
mixing in apples for about three weeks
but the reason I haven't posted in a
while is because well there's actually
three reasons why first reason is
because I recently just got back from
Singapore and Malaysia cuz I had a
couple of shows it looks something like
this the second reason is pretty obvious
I'm sure you guys can hear it but I got
pretty stick on that trip and it looks
something like this sorry and finally
last but not least the third reason is
because well I'm filming a movie let me
do another date I the last reason is
because I'm filming a movie since you
couldn't understand what I just said
that's right I'm a freaking mainstream
Hollywood movie star now well I mean I'm
not exactly the star of the film so I
guess you can't really call me a movie
store and it's not exactly mainstream
because it's an independent film and
it's not even shot in Hollywood it's
shot in downtown LA but it's still a
real movie okay and I'm still a real
movie star okay I had so many lines it
looked just like this no buttons yes
they really don't want us to leave would
want to leave I'm a movie star this is
hair okay even though I'm making jokes
right now it's true I really have been
working on a movie and I'm not gonna lie
it's been a little tough for me and I
know a lot of you guys think that I'm a
good actor but acting in a movie is
completely different from what I do here
especially since the movie I'm doing is
actually not even a comedy it's actually
a thriller slash oror slash I don't know
what it is I didn't read the script
point that I'm trying to tell you guys
is that I'm a movie star now I'm famous
I don't have time to be doing these
silly amateur non movie videos anymore
I'm moving on I'm moving on see I'm
funny too I'm so funny look Hollywood
called and they want a new movie star
okay well maybe they haven't called yet
but they're going to because I have
everything it takes I'm going to be the
next movie star here's all the reasons
why I should be the next movie star I
can cry on demand
I can't stand the paparazzi oh please no
no no photos today please no photos I
have an agent that I always yell at look
you've been teaching for over a year
where are all my auditions
sir this is stay firm I'm your insurance
agent I walk the red carpet pretty much
every single night I always take a
really long pause before I say things to
make them more dramatic hey Ryan you
oughtta go grab lunch soon
yeah not to mention I always make the
fan screen and I'm already on a show
called Teen Wolf which many of you might
know it's just that people don't
recognize me because of the makeup you
can even ask some of my cold sores from
the movie I'm doing right now they've
already seen and witnessed the
awesomeness that is my acting and these
guys they love me they're gonna tell you
how great I really am like nathan kress
for example a lot of you guys may know
I'm from the infamous TV show iCarly
you knows I'm good ah naked hey right
okay ask your question no Ryan you can't
well because I know what you're gonna
ask you gonna ask me if you're good
actor anywhere not a good actor okay
mundo do my work oh yeah thanks you can
ask that but yes you were oh hey I'm
gonna come in no like I said Nathan was
on I Courtney or whatever that show is
it's a TV show it's not a movie meaning
he knows nothing about nothing it's a
double negative he knows nothing about
knowing he knows everything about
knowing nothing I'm a movie star I
didn't say I was a mathematician my
other clothes are Ginny Garner which
some of you might know from the movie
project Almanac a huge studio film she
knows exactly what it's like to be a
movie star and she'll tell you how great
I've been oh hey
Ginny can ask you a question right uh
yeah sure um okay so on a scale from 9
to 10 how great of a movie star actor
would you say that I am uh you only gave
me two options
yeah 9 to 10 so what would you rate me
uh I mean I guess I would give you a
nine but again I only have two options
yeah not 9 as in mind being the highest
like thousand nine being like the lowest
out of the cheap options at you you know
that's still a 90% that's an A like I
respect Jimmy but like she wasn't the
stars to her a project Almanac if she
were you know she would've gave me a 10
cuz she would have known better
or even my other co-star Kirby she's
from Project X another huge film she
absolutely adores me and tells me how
close I am to breaking through Hollywood
and just blow it up there I don't know
what that visual was hey Kirby can I ask
you a question sure so you know
Hollywood heartthrobs right like I know
them well yeah Ryan Gosling who's Ryan
Sheckler Ryan Seacrest
yeah and Reynolds
um don't you think it's about time for
some Ryan Higa somewhat fine right here
me your name's Ryan see cuz she's used
to calling me the king of acting or the
best actor ever so she doesn't really
call me by my name anyway and last but
not least my boy mark birdie is from
well he's she's from Australia so I
don't really know the shows out there
but he's on something out there it's
probably one of my best friends on set I
always got his back he always got mine
conceived and I was a YouTube channel
hey Mark can ask you a question oh okay
sorry well you know what mark you're
just me you make youtube videos okay
once you grow up and get a real job nerd
anyway now that you guys have seen the
facts for yourselves you should be able
to understand where I'm coming from it's
time for me to move on it's time it's
time for me to movie on see I'm funny
twice Mel so as I was saying I made this
video to let you guys know that this is
gonna be my last video ever I'm not
going to be posting next week because
it's time for me to move on I'm moving
on to Hollywood speak of the devil
well hello there I've been expecting
your call yeah okay
oh my god that's perfect okay bye okay
so Hollywood is saying they hate me they
don't want me to never do so I'll
probably do YouTube videos for the rest
of my life I guess I'll see you guys
next week I can later good bye so once
again thank you so much for watching if
you want to see bloopers me at the
scenes so you go on the left you want to
see the previous video click on the
right and once again sorry we haven't
posted a video in such a long time the
movies actually done so I'm gonna get
back into it we're gonna post another
video this coming week so I'll see you
guys soon and bye soon I mean like a
month cuz we're gonna post videos for
months just kidding but seriously sorry