[Music]
hey guys so let me first off this video
by saying we recently reached a goal
that seven years ago I never even
thought was possible for me at least and
this goal just so happens to be drumroll
please
hello can't give you a drumroll if you
have the drumsticks yeah but that's for
dessert I want the drum roll only have
the sticks for the drum you have the
drum roll sticks tastes like bad pun we
just reached 10 million subscribers know
what's gonna clean this up oh it was
just editing anyway on a serious note
thank you guys so much I know I used to
make a thank you video after every 1
million subscribers and I haven't made
one since the 6 million subscriber video
but the reason for that is because those
videos never get many views so I figured
you guys don't like to watch them
because they're not that interesting but
it doesn't mean that I'm any less
grateful for all the love and support
that you guys show me I know I always
say I have the best fans in the world
but the more I think about it you guys
are more than just fans to me you're
your lamp's don't get me wrong having
fans are awesome they make you feel like
you're well cool thing is fans come and
go you're the new hottest thing they're
fanning all over you once you go cold
they go and find the next hot thing to
fan lamps are more than that they're
like friends even when you're not the
hot topic and you go completely cold
lamps never leave you in fact when
you're cold they actually give you one
and no matter what shape or size I don't
even need to know what they look like I
know that when I hit that switch lamps
are gonna be there for me in my darkest
times
[Music]
no was you I didn't know I landed right
on my balls
you you what like Bob slip balls my ball
how are your ball listen to me right
what is it I want you to forget about me
move on find another stamp I can't do
that a little heavier you always been my
little there's a lot to see they won't
work they're gonna be all wet 5
five one five five second rule-- what
the Trump stick it's still good
[Music]
am i burnt out no but you're fine
everything's gonna be all light now
oh yeah apparently I just have to change
your bulb every now and then hey do you
know the drumstick we can get all the
drumsticks you want buddy
[Music]