I am one of the few candidates in the
field that Donald Trump has never
tweeted at or acknowledged for a young
person now you're looking at a less than
fifty percent chance of doing better
than your parents I will share what's
going on with aliens of the American
people unless it's just too damn scary
all right clappy claps and we're good
welcome back to another episode of off
the peel podcast today we have a very
special guest well first of all we have
david choi in the moderator seat we have
michelle phan joining us as a co-host
and we have pretty popular right now
Andrew yang Andrew yang so crazy I need
this like help the chief you can't you
can't hear it but there's a lot of pause
so again this is I've been tweeting and
stuff about it all week that I'm pretty
terrified this is very different for me
but thank you so much for being here in
our little or a little setup right here
in LA no man I'm thrilled to be here and
you know I've been in touch for a little
while like I've been looking forward to
this for a while I've been wondering do
you actually run your Twitter because I
was wondering if I was talking to you in
you know Indians or is it someone else
it's me with a little plus sign next to
it like dip in there and do stuff yeah
well like the tweets of all like like
you were talking about like the like
basketball and football is that I'm a
second only me okay
I'd be very troubled if someone else
pretended to take over my sports fan
don't make me like you know 49ers
panting some [ __ ] I just yeah I mean
you know my teams are terrible Jets its
Jets Mets Oh Nets I suppose you'd have
to say no I was a long time they
transfer my entire life until they
dumped jeremy'll and honestly and then I
was like [ __ ] this [ __ ] was a bright
brightest spot of being a Knicks fan for
years and then they drop him and then
you're like why did you drop him and
you'd put up with so much stuff leading
up to that time so then I became a Nets
fan because Jeremy okay I was playing
there and
and you left and now I'm still in that
span because now I'm friendly with the
incoming owner Joe Tai who's Oh
Taiwanese Canadian I don't know if you
know about this I know the ownerships
changing right
the ownerships changing from Prokhorov
the russian oligarch who spent money to
Joe Toye who's like this Taiwanese
Canadian badass he's essentially like he
went to high school in college in
America so he's essentially in my mind
like you know pretty American but he's
gonna be the first Asian and be a owner
I believe
oh really yeah so he's gonna own the
Brooklyn Nets so if you have no sports
allegiance in the NBA and you're you
know like opened a new team and might be
the Brooklyn Nets okay okay well that's
I mean that's I didn't even know that
honestly I'm a bad agent for not knowing
that so you you were a fan of Jeremy Lin
like you say how do you feel about mail
then oh you know I mean now Melo is that
a bad rap Tamala should clearly be in
the league and I hope the Nets sign him
but at the time when they dumped Jeremy
Lin you know that you had this a little
bit of the sense that Melo was not too
upset that they dumped Lin and said it
was a period when I was sort of sad
about Melo okay so it's true you do
actually watch basketball clearly I was
always wondering you know you never know
you know if you had a basketball
ghostwriter yeah that'd be pretty
difficult oh one of the reasons why I
wanted to come on with you all is that
that I'm really a pretty normal dude I
mean you'd have to be a fairly weird
person run for president so there is
that one thing but the things that you
like I probably like to I think that's
one of the reasons why I mean I'd
gravitate towards I mean I I told you
from the very beginning like I don't
know why you would want to be on the
show because I don't know much about
politics and you said that's exactly why
you want to do it well first Asian
Americans are not that into politics
generally we vote at lower levels we
donate money at lower levels we run for
office at lower levels and I tell people
very plainly it's like when you're
growing up and certainly the way I grew
up it's not like your parents were like
you're gonna be President someday it was
I get good grades
make a good living do something reliable
and consistent and politics is not
something certainly I was emphasized in
my household I think that's true in most
Asian Americans households and so one
thing I'm grateful for is that I think
my campaign can help energize Asian
Americans in a different way but if you
arrive to the scene like you just said
where you're not that into politics that
would be totally normal and to me it's
one of the you know the things I'd like
to help change because if we don't get
politically engaged at some point then
things are just gonna keep on changing
in ways then we might not like mm-hmm
yeah I mean I think the only time that I
really got into it was when Trump was
running right so I I mean that's when I
finally was like kind of getting
interested and I guess that's the one
thing you can say that he did do is
bring a lot of injuries I mean like you
said it's like a reality show and he's a
star so he got a lot of people to care
about politics now let's say that and
then now again talking to a lot of my
friends they all know who you are nice
they do they do but I will say there is
some pessimism where they everybody
keeps telling me cuz I don't really know
that much and I'm a certain they do know
more they keep telling me like yeah we
love Andrew yang but there's no way he's
gonna win well stranger things have
happened in American politics that's for
sure so right now I'm at 3%
nationally and I was five percent in one
state poll and just like the people
watching this right now most folks in
Iowa New Hampshire have not tuned in and
have no idea who they're voting for
right so anyone who tells you that they
know what's gonna happen is lying
because no one knows better what data
you have a you know you have your hands
on and the fact that we've gone from
nowhere to 6:00 in the polls and I'm
gonna be on the debate stage in Houston
this week to me that's actually a harder
leap to make than being in sixth place
raising millions of dollars being in all
the mainstream news outlets and then
going from 6 to 1st in part because the
honest truth is that if you look at
Canada the candidates who are above me
people have reservations about frankly
all of them well use nobody thought
those same people who said no the
no way Trump was gonna win so right
there was a point when there was a lot
there were a lot of people that said
there's no bomb was gonna win yeah you
know and I said too it's like no you
guys this is gonna date me a little bit
Bill Clinton kind of came out of nowhere
he was like the No Name governor in
Arkansas no one was like Clinton's gonna
Clinton's gonna come and save the day
like so
stranger things have happened in
American politics than my becoming
president in 2020 right you're one of
your main messages in your campaign is
you be I'm sure you've talked about it a
million times but for some of our
listeners that don't really know what
that is we have a lot of young younger
listeners what what exactly is that so
you know universal basic income is a
policy where every citizen gets a
certain amount of money to meet your
basic needs to do whatever you want with
so my plan the freedom dividend would
put $1,000 a month into the hands of
every American starting at age 18 so if
you're 18
you'd get $1,000 a month if you're 16
and you wait two years you'd get $1,000
a month and that seems incredibly
dramatic but this was a plan that was
approved by the House of Representatives
in the US Congress in 1971 this was a
plan that was championed by Martin
Luther King in 1968 this is a plan that
has sort of been adopted in one state
Alaska where everyone in Alaska gets
between one and two thousand dollars a
year in oil money so if you were family
at four you're getting $8,000 in Alaska
and what I'm saying to the American
people is that technology is the oil of
the 21st century we're now your data our
data is worth more than oil and and
that's a true fact
and you all in many ways are an example
of this 21st century economy and here we
are in your beautiful Southern
California David's house Home Slice
studio but I mean it's awesome like this
conversation is going to be seen or
heard by hundreds of thousands maybe
millions of people I mean that that's
something that's very recent it's like a
new innovation and there are many things
that are happening in our economy that
are unprecedented so if we cling to this
notion that everyone's gonna work a
nine-to-five and you're paid in twelve
bucks an hour and
it's gonna work out it's gonna work out
for fewer and fewer people over time and
in my view this is why Donald Trump won
in 2016 is that more and more Americans
are feeling like it's not working for
them mm-hmm well I mean again those same
people keep because I asked them because
I want to know like Oh what questions
should I ask cuz I don't know enough a
lot of them and I've seen your answer to
how are you gonna pay for this and you
bring up Amazon and the VAT tax I don't
completely understand what a VAT tax is
can you explain that
like really dumb down though sure so
Amazon's a trillion dollar tech company
paying zero in taxes right now less than
I mean you all you know pay much more
than zero percent I'm sure and so that's
not an exaggeration they're paying zero
they're paying zero oh yeah that's not
like zero is not a number so and it's
not unusual like if you look at their
lifetime taxation rate it's something
like three percent so there'll be zero
in some years five in others so you have
to ask yourself okay you're gonna have a
revenue problem in this country if your
biggest companies are paying zero are
near zero in taxes and it's not just
Amazon it's Google its Facebook its
Netflix Netflix also paid zero in taxes
last year so these are some of the
biggest companies in our society and so
then you look at it and say okay why are
they paying zero and the reason they're
paying zero is we have a corporate
income tax system that is pretty easy to
game you pay your executives a lot and
stock compensation you can expense that
you have a global business you can push
all of the earnings through Ireland or
the Caymans or a Bahamas or whatever the
heck and so these companies play a lot
of games and so then you look and say
well what did other countries do when
they were faced with the same situation
and every other advanced economy in the
world has something called a value-added
tax where if you're selling something
then you pay a toll and so if you
imagine that in Amazon's case then all
of a sudden you'd have a lot of tax
revenue very very quickly because they
sell a lot of stuff so instead of zero
in taxes you would get billions and so
that's the change I want to make and the
trick with my plan is that I want to
take the billions we get from Amazon
and then give it to us in the form of
$1,000 a month so then if you get this
money what are you gonna spend it on
you're gonna spend a little bit of it on
Amazon again but you're gonna spend on
other things you want like in your case
it might be food clothing education a
car something along those lines and then
that money just flows back into the
economy and ends up creating a virtuous
cycle and so that the plan is to try and
get more of the value into our hands and
then take a toll when we're spending
money with companies like Amazon so what
what happens then if so do you plan on
imposing some some rules and regulations
so that these big corporations can't you
know create companies like in the Cayman
Islands or Ireland like you mentioned
well this is the beauty of a David that
if they decide to move themselves they
came in Islands and then they celled us
a still have to pay the toll that's why
these other countries have done this and
it's like oxygen it's much harder to
game because these companies are very
smart and they're very good at avoiding
paying taxes sure so how much revenue
can be generated from taxing these big
corporations the the estimates are that
if you were to adopt a value-added tax
at half the European level you would
generate about 800 billion in new
revenue per year in the United States
which is enough to pay for a lot of
things and it's enough to pay for a lot
of this thousand dollars a month that's
coming to each of us and then the beauty
of this thousand dollars a month
dividend that we all have is that when
we spend it it just ends up making the
economy work better generates another
hundreds of billions in new revenue
because your economy has more jobs and
activity so we get some of that money
back we also save money on things like
jails and hospitals and homelessness
services because a lot of those people
need less help and then we're making our
people stronger healthier mentally
healthier more productive also more
entrepreneurial and artistic because if
you imagine a country where everyone's
getting a thousand bucks a month how do
more people would want to do what you
guys are doing right now
absolutely working for necessity yeah
also not worried about literally like
starving the next month and I've been a
serial entrepreneur now for years and
years it is almost never the case that
someone's like oh my gosh I'm down to my
last dime you know I'm gonna do I'm
gonna start a business the way it works
it's really like when you start a
business often you have a little bit of
security and you feel like you can take
a risk so we do is we making our entire
culture more entrepreneurial and more
enterprising mm-hmm so this is for
millionaires and billionaires they still
get the same thousand dollars a month
well the way the system works is that
someone like Jeff Bezos would end up
paying hundreds of millions into the
system and so if we try and send them a
thousand bucks a month to remind them
he's an American he probably take it too
because you know rich people didn't get
to being rich by turning that money so
there's some some people here saying
that you are a socialist what do you
have to say to those people well I'm a
serial entrepreneur who's run businesses
and what I say to people is that this is
not socialism this is capitalism where
income doesn't start at zero us having
money it's good for businesses it's good
for markets it's good for consumers and
then if you were to get technical and
very Asian and smart you would say the
definition of socialism is when nation's
government takes over the means of
production which is not what anyone's
talking about here what I'm talking
about is sliding some money to us we're
the owners of the country and so this
money is gonna go back into the economy
I see you really seem to like running
with the the Asian stereotypes I have no
issue with it
but I can see some people being
sensitive about that especially other
Asians and is there is that intention or
is that just always been you like no
math thing and then you know talking
about like like you just said you're an
Asian I'm Asian that likes math I mean
this is just playing along because you
know you know middle America is gonna I
mean there's a certain way they view
Asian people right yeah so I know that
we have a very diverse community and
that the model minority myth is not an
accurate depiction of the way
many many or most Asian Americans
experience life and so certainly the
last thing I'd want to do is somehow
perpetuate stereotypes that aren't you
know like helpful to the community but I
think most people can tell that I'm
joking they are serious but they're
positive ones and you definitely know
your math that's for sure thanks man
so so I think people generally know that
like I'm sort of poking fun at both
myself and the images and yeah it's like
most people taking the same spirit right
but I think like you know I mean just
based off the internet I'm sure you see
voices and opinions from everyone I'm
thinking like when you become the
nominee right don't you think that's
gonna be used against you a lot like I
mean even I can just picture like Trump
being like you know how are you gonna
work with China conflict of interest you
know well our office has a wager on what
his nickname is gonna be for me and
we've come up with comrade yang okay
because it's a little racist a little
like communist socialist and I think
people are going to realize that it's
not gonna work so well on me and part
because if you listen to me for five
seconds like I sound like the least
socialist dude around because I'm
literally like you know like an
entrepreneur who's run businesses and I
think the anti Asian thing is also a
real loser for him you know what's
really interesting is that I am one of
the few candidates in the field that
Donald Trump has never tweeted at or
acknowledged and he said something at a
rally in West Virginia where he said
he's excited to run against all the
Democrats and his only concern is that
someone new comes out of nowhere
mm-hm and that's me I'm a similar
profile that I'm from outside the system
and I am one of only two candidates in
the field that over ten percent of
Donald Trump voters said that they would
support and so that means if I'm the
Democratic nominee we win in part
because the attacks that he would use on
politicians don't really work on me
speaking of Donald Trump and
10% now you mentioned how do you plan on
reaching out to the the rest of the 90
no I I'm one of the candidates who's
willing to go on fox like talk to people
from different yeah parts of the aisle
and I can make you know it's been fun
it's like I've been meeting tons of
Trump voters campaigning around the
country and a lot of them like me in
part because they can tell that I'm not
really talking down to them in any way
like I just look at them like hey yeah
like some of the [ __ ] really sucks like
we gotta try and solve some problems
like oh that's different
oh dude even in the debates you talked
about it not having like everybody was
talking about you not having a tie you
know and how why does that matter
so much like why is that it as important
especially Brian Williams man what the
heck's with Brian Williams and his
fixation on neckwear well I mean I think
that's what what I mean that's my for
once I feel like when I'm watching the
debates and I hear you talk I feel like
for me personally I'm actually
interested and I tried to figure out am
i biased because you're Asian or is it
just because the way you
I don't know pretty much just seemed
like a normal person
it doesn't seem staged if that makes
sense I'm sure you're calculating yeah
thank you I'm happy to say that there
are many people of every different
background and said the same thing to me
white black Asian or you're like oh you
seem like a normal dude that's one
reason why I'm here having this
conversation with you all is that I
wanted to lean into the fact that I'm a
normal dude who decided to run for
president because I saw how [ __ ] up
[ __ ] is getting and it's not gonna
unfuck itself honestly I mean like it's
really broken very very badly broken I'm
now deep in the process I'm sixth in the
race to become the nominee and I see how
badly we need to win because I see the
machinery around me and it's not
designed to solve the problems it's
designed to make certain people money is
designed to keep certain things the same
so certain people can make money and the
people problems challenges of this era
are secondary the feedback mechanism in
our government is essentially broken and
it's one reason why Donald Trump became
our president is that
tens of millions of Americans were so
fed up they were like let's take the bed
on the nurses history Aldi TV star wants
to drain a swap it can't be worse than
what we're getting now and so that
that's the lesson that Democrats need to
really listen to this time around where
you can't say you know what our antidote
is gonna be business as usual because
many Americans don't think business as
usual was working and many Americans
made the same choice that you all have
made which is like I'm just not gonna
pay attention this [ __ ] because it's not
relevant to my life it's depressing
they're talking about stuff that in ways
that does not seem relevant to me so the
fact that it's a very rational choice to
ignore this stuff is a sign of the fact
that we need to change things so besides
the thousand dollars a month that you
you're proposing how do we have a lot of
younger viewers here and a lot of
first-time voters as well why should
these young volts vote for you like
besides $1,000 a month I'm really
passionate about this because how old
are you all 29 29 32 33 I'm 44 and what
I'm passionate about is that we have
left a total mess to young people in
particular and then the worst thing is
we blame them for it they're like
somehow it's your fault we're I mean the
clearest examples are that we've gotten
rid of a lot of the secure livelihoods
and jobs moving forward ninety-four
percent of the new jobs that are getting
created in the United States are a
temporary gig or contract work that
don't have benefits and have a very
precarious path forward Thank You bird
driver as an example our youtuber or
youtuber because I know you guys have to
scratch and claw I get it and then you
have to you know you put out a video and
then you have to be like oh how's it
gonna perform and then you know it's
like it's it's hard like everything's
hard so that's where the economy has
gone and then we made college two and a
half times more expensive where you look
at the price tags holy cow then someone
just told me today like you know some of
these schools like 60,000 a year so if
you want to attend for four years it's
like quarter of a million dollars so if
you're a young person watching this
you're like what the f you know you're
looking up at that and and then you look
at climate change and say hey
turns out why there's gonna get worse
and it's gonna get hotter the sea levels
gonna rise they're gonna be storms and
floods and droughts and problems active
shooter drills in schools you go to
school me like what the heck's going on
like kids actually I to practice for
this stuff so if you're a young person
you look up and say why does it seem
like things are going so poorly and that
the world I'm inheriting is not really
set up for me to thrive and succeed and
be happy and prosperous and that even
have a secure livelihood by the numbers
and I'm a numbers person if you were
born in the 1940s the United States of
America you had a 93 percent chance of
doing better than your parents that's
the American dream like you know your
kids are gonna do better than you are if
you were born in the 1990s which I guess
is some of you right yeah you're down to
a 50/50 chance and guess where the doubt
to thousands are going it's not going
back up so in 93 5050 and then for a
young person now you're looking at a
less than 50% chance of doing better
than your parents you know who's figured
this out your parents they're looking up
being like wow I'm not sure my kids
gonna have a better life you know what
else is figuring it out the kids kids
are like why does it seem like things
are not gonna go better for me so this
is the mess the shambles that young
people are inheriting and then young
people are being blamed for it because
we're saying it's like somehow your
fault because culture lazy smartphone
social me I don't know even what the
accusation is millennial being a
millennial right well if you want to pay
your dues whatever like the nonsense
narrative is to clarify when you see a
better life what exactly cuz you said
you did the math on it like what exactly
are the calculations like what are you
basing that off of just money or yeah so
so when I said the 93 percent of 50
percent a little better life right
that was straight socio-economic success
are you gonna make more money than your
parents do okay yeah now is that the
end-all be-all obviously no I mean
there's there are a lot more important
things in life than your paycheck but if
you had to go society-wide and try and
figure out are things getting better or
worse for people that would be a good
place to start so so if you're a young
person you have these concerns and
misgivings about the world you're
inheriting the country are being left
you're not sure the country is really
working for you and it is not working
for you
it's right now not even designed to work
for you so the goal has to be to change
that and I'm a parent now I've got six
and four year old boys and I want to be
able to look them in the eyes and say
we're gonna leave you a country that we
can actually be proud of that is as good
as the country I came to and my parents
immigrated this country met as graduate
students at Berkeley here in California
they had me and my brother and it's been
great you know in the sense that they
came here for better opportunities and
my you know I just became an uncle
yesterday like my yeah I haven't met her
yet because I'm busy campaigning that
affected your like your actual personal
life like I'm sure I mean I'm not sure
actually with your wife and your kids
like is it's got to be tough and it's
gotta be there's gotta be some oh and
I'm just assuming things right now most
of us are fighting it's stressful or
like not there no it's very human man
it's the biggest downside of running for
president is I don't get to see my kids
as often I'm on the road a lot I would
miss my you know I have paced time my
wife this morning
she's been a superstar champ she's been
a rock if anyone's making a sacrifice in
this race it's her because my kids are a
lot of where all kids are a lot of work
like my kids are a lot of work and so I
want to be able to do that work with her
but I'm not able to right now so she's
taking it on the chin yeah it's it's a
definite change in your personal life
yeah that's the biggest downside of
running for sure was she all in when you
told her you're gonna do this or was she
like this is crazy oh well there's
definitely part of the crazy element it
was there but she thinks that I'm being
driven by a higher purpose she's
Christian and and believes that I'm
doing what I'm meant to do are you as
well I grew up in a secular household
but I've many family members who were
brought up Christian and obviously my
wife's Christian and we're raising our
boys a Christian so I go to church every
Sunday I'm home
but I grew up secular okay I wanted to
go back to the changes that you want it
to make so let's say hypothetically
speaking you become president you have
four years do you actually think you can
make a meaningful impact knowing that a
lot of different sectors like the energy
sector Big Pharma they're owned by
lobbyists and you were just mentioning
that earlier I was just curious to see
like what is your strategy if you want
to make change yes so so thousand bucks
I want to be a game changer for tens of
millions of Americans so then the next
step is how do we get the government
working for us instead of the lobbyists
and right now the lobbyists have
essentially taken captive our
legislature legislators so the way we
break that captivity is we give everyone
in America who's an adult again 100
democracy dollars a year that you can
only give to candidates or campaigns or
causes that you like in value this would
wash out lobbyist money by a factor of
eight to one because you have to look up
and say what rules can I put in place
that'll keep the rich people and the
corporation's from getting a hold of the
legislators very very hard it's like
life in Jurassic Park money finds a way
you know I mean like the corporate
lobbying money would just like still get
its way in there and so the new plan
should be to wash out the corporate
money with people-powered money I've
been running for president now for a
while and I have to say I'm incredibly
fortunate where we've now raised
millions of dollars in increments of
only like $25 each just people donating
you know 15 20 dollars to the campaign
but for the vast majority of people who
are running for office they have two
things they're the people and they have
the money and so over time they started
listening for the money because it's
easier to measure the food is better the
people can give them jobs afterwards I
think this is where they end up falling
so we have to do is we have to combine
these two things we have to make it so
the people the money are in the same
place and then if you're a legislator
and the lobbyist comes and says hey I've
got a $50,000 check for you you can be
like I'm getting five million from my
voters my constituents I'm not gonna go
against them for your $50,000 but right
now asking
legislators to ignore all the money when
that's where the bread is buttered is
just not realistic so this democracy
dollar that you're talking about is this
essentially US dollar well you know the
great thing is democracy dollars it's
been rolled out in certain communities
here in the US it's been rolled out in
other countries so you can even imagine
it being something as simple as you get
a coupon code and the beginning of the
year and then any time you want to give
to a candidate or campaign just use your
coupon code and then they you know
reference the code against the federal
database and then they just get the
money also accepting cryptocurrencies
I was curious on what are your thoughts
on Bitcoin I've many friends in the
cryptocurrency community and I'm a
believer in the underlying technology in
particular the blockchain has a world of
potential it's like a lot of other
technologies where right now the hype
sort of got a little bit overblown and
ahead of itself and the rest of it but
then the underlying technology is very
powerful and so what happens in these
cycles it tends to be that the hype gets
in front of it and then the air comes
out of the bubble but then the reality
ends up catching up over time have you
thought about I mean this is just
hypothetical UVI could essentially be
universal Bitcoin income no instead of
the money being taxed essentially it
could be based on a hard asset like a
Bitcoin yeah
Toshi's is you know you can fraction out
Satoshi's 100 million units 100 million
units to people I love where your head
is oh because I learned a lot from my
friends in the cryptocurrency community
around some of these principles and when
you start to think it's one reason why
just about everyone in the
cryptocurrency community loves the idea
of universal basic income or the freedom
that you care about and you believe yeah
I mean Facebook they made so much money
make so much money and and so what I say
to people sometimes is like do remember
getting your data check in the mail it's
like no but someone's getting your data
check in the mail I mean these trillion
dollar tech companies are profiting to
the tune of billions of dollars off of
our data
the interesting thing is our data could
actually become more valuable if we were
participating in some way right now it
just gets kind of anonymized and sold
and resold without our knowledge and it
could become more valuable if we were
part of the part of the process do you
have any plans to implement that like
how would you go about that yes I do
so one of the policies on yank 20/20
comm is your data as a property right
and so the plan would be to say to
companies that are profiting from our
data that there are a few principles you
have to adhere to
number one is you have to tell us what
you're doing and how much money you're
making
number two is you have to let us express
preferences as to how much or how little
of our data that we want to be made
available and number three you have to
let us turn it off if we want but part
of the number one is like tell us how
much value there is is that they have to
share the value with us so I'm just
being I'm a normal dude so what did
normal dudes do when they see that giant
like you know click and agree thing they
just ignore all right I mean like that's
what we all do and so we should be able
to keep doing that because I love
convenience as much as the next person
but if you're making money off me you
have to cut me in on the deal yeah and
so yeah and so that that's where what I
want us to be at is essentially at a
certain point you express your
preference you're being a look I love
convenience just give me some of the
convenience back to my pocket and then
if I ever want to change my mind on that
I can do so right just for like I mean
like a ballpark cuz I have no idea what
kind of numbers are you thinking for a
person's you know I have no idea how
much that's worth so right now the art
data is worth a different amount
depending upon who you are if you travel
a lot your data's worth a lot more
because then they just want to sell you
like hotel chains and stuff and stuff if
you have some kind of health condition
your data is worth a lot more sometimes
people's health data is getting sold for
thousands of dollars per user per user
based on how much you consume
essentially whether it's there yeah
there different factors that affect how
valuable your data is but it can get
into the
per user but you are saying you want to
take a piece of that and give it to the
person who's essentially given it yes
because it's so dope I mean why who else
should be getting the well most of us
didn't know it was even happening you
know I mean until that documentary came
out recently on Netflix telling us
basically it was good timing yeah
seriously okay
yeah we should go into the environment
so you mentioned that man you mentioned
we're 10 years but I mean like that's I
appreciate the honesty
we're 10 years late when it comes to
saving the environment what are some
things that you want to do as you know
as president to kind of slow this thing
down
yeah the climate change we have to do a
whole lot more I just at least a
five-point plan which includes some of
the stuff you probably hear from other
places which is try and move towards
renewables the big piece of the puzzles
that 85% of the world's emissions are
from non-us sources so if you want to
try and curb emissions in a serious way
then you have to go to Africa and say to
them you know that coal burning power
plant that China is installing for you
for free I'm going to try and convince
you that these solar panels and wind
turbines are a better option and so then
you have to subsidize that to a very
high degree if you're gonna make that
competitive the third thing is that we
should be trying to make our communities
more resilient and literally and
figuratively move our people to higher
ground where you know if there's a
hurricane who suffers poor people who
don't have great shelter or cars and get
into to drive away and anyone who thinks
this stuff is a little doom and gloom
we were already moving climate refugees
in the United States we already took a
town of people in Louisiana where their
land had essentially become underwater
and uninhabitable and we said well it's
time to move you so if we're doing that
there then we should start looking at
other places where frankly that's
starting to happen and it's happening in
more and more places around the country
not just Louisiana the fourth thing is
that we have to try and undo some of the
damage we're doing so that involves
reforesting tracts of land it involves
trying to repair some of the oceans by
seeding plankton beds it sounds a little
far out but four to eight percent of
marine life in the Atlantic Ocean is
dying now every year so if you
extrapolate that over time you're
talking about massive massive problems
and so we can't just try and do less of
the bad we have to try and undo some of
the damage so those are some of the
plans I have on climate change I just
released a 5 trillion dollar plan to try
and take those steps the these are
things that you've I'm assuming you've
worked with scientists or something but
correct me if I'm wrong you said it's
already 10 years too late though right
it's 10 years too late to keep the earth
from warming ok the earth is going to
warm it is already warming the last four
years have been the four warmest years
in recorded history which sounds like a
remarkable coincidence I mean it's not a
coincidence it's because the earth is
warming July was the warmest year in
recorded history so when I say it's ten
years too late it's ten years too late
to keep the earth from warming in a
significant and measurable way it's
never too late to start trying to repair
damage make our communities more
resilient make your economy more
sustainable there's a proverb the best
time to plant the tree is twenty years
ago the second best time is now it's
like one low situation it's like should
we have done it 10 years ago or 20 years
ago of course in the absence of having
done that do we need to take dramatic
action now yes essentially you're also
providing more jobs like infrastructure
jobs for people to build yeah I was just
with this gonna sound so politician II
but I was just with this entrepreneur
Ned Reynolds in New Hampshire and he now
has 260 solar installers working for him
who are just putting panels on people's
roofs and that's a really good job and
we need it and it's gonna make us more
energy efficient and it's gonna lower
people's heating bills so it's just a
win-win-win those are the kinds of jobs
we need to be creating in very large
numbers Trump said that he brought back
many manufacturing jobs more than anyone
thought possible is that an accurate
statement it's an accurate statement
that there's been a slight bounce back
in manufacturing employment but big
picture we were at seventeen million
manufacturing jobs around
thousand and then we went all the way
down to 12 million or so so that's five
million loss and now we're somewhere
between 12 and 13 million so has there
been a bounce-back yes have Donald
Trump's policies had something to do
with it presumably yes is this partially
Donald Trump just blowing his own smoke
like usual also yes why is it that
whenever I I mean I watch everything not
just like fox or CNN or either side
whenever I see the pro Trump side it's
always you know the economy's doing
great much better under Trump and then I
watch I just see Connor it's just all
counter-arguments and it what's the
truth
like why are there numbers supposedly
that support that under Trump
everything's better the economy the
major there there are a few economic
moves that Donald Trump's made the two
big ones were a tax cut and the second
one was the trade war with China so the
tax cut cut corporate taxes by 1.5
trillion dollars which ended up boosting
the economy in a particular way that is
true only 6% of that those gains went to
workers the vast majority of it went to
shareholders of corporations and
buybacks and the rest of it so have you
seen better economic numbers at the top
line yes
was that the right way to go 100% no
that was a terrible way to go because
that 1.5 trillion tax cut ended up just
boosting deficit which you know we're
gonna eventually have to do something
about and then the trade war has been a
huge net negative for the economy so if
you were to go and say hey Donald
Trump's been good for the economy it's
narrowly true if you ignore the fact
that he also increased our deficit by
hundreds of billions of dollars and if
you were going to for example spend the
trillion and a half dollars I've got a
great idea why not just give it to the
American people in the form of a
dividend and instead of having it all go
to corporate buybacks it would go right
back in the economy into our hands it
would increase the actual health of our
people because that's what happens when
money is in our hands we end up becoming
healthier mentally healthier
better educated like all these good
things happen so to me it was a tragic
misuse of resources that went directly
to the corporations that needed at the
least
okay so just selective reporting then
yeah it's like if you were to want to
tell a story it's like Trump's been
great for GDP it's like just like kind
of seen both sides because I don't want
to just pick one side and just go with
it because they're so conflicting you
know
well you summarized a big problem today
in America is that you have different
news silos people getting news from
different sources no one can agree on
anything and some of these channels
don't even pretend anymore like
sometimes they get called out on bad
reporting and they're like we're an
entertainment business we're not a news
business and you're like are you
[ __ ] me do you have any plans on
working with those news outlets and
maybe I don't know figure out a way to
make you more accurate reporting fake
news and things like that you know I
think that's that's gonna become a more
serious problem when you have deep fakes
and technological things that you know
it's like then you really need someone
to come in and be like yo that videos
not who had a deep fake voice of his
convinced the CFO to transfer two
hundred and fifty thousand dollars into
the deep fake voices account so there's
and this is just the beginning of deep
fake sorry what is deep fake it's
essentially when you do either a video
or audio that sounds like or looks like
a person but I made it up but now the
technology is so good that it's
indistinguishable right okay well yeah
and it's someone distinguishable that
even if you know it's a fake you can't
actually necessarily like say this is a
forgery
I know it's so frightening I mean that
could be like the end of society or
worse like you know we can't trust
anything we have to confirm each other
by memory only memory that we go back to
campfires what would you say are some
things that these young people should be
studying in order to secure a job for
the for the future since AI is
so here's the good news according to the
projections so there's not good news but
all presenta it's good news the
proportion of jobs that are likely to be
lost automation the range of estimates
is between twenty and forty four percent
which still means that a majority of
jobs will continue to exist so it's not
like you know end of work as we know it
and the work that will still be
available to us all falls into two main
categories non repetitive manual work
and non repetitive cognitive work so
I'll start with non repetitive cognitive
this is like team-building interpersonal
creative stuff like you do design some
of the STEM fields so that stuff is
going to be with us for a long long time
sales like you always gonna need sales
these sorts of things non repetitive
manual are things like plumbing and HVAC
repair and a lot like can you imagine
would take to make a robot plumber be
next to impossible yeah it's too
expensive so that there so so there are
going to be jobs that are with us for a
long time on the high end you want and
what I say to young people and this is
gonna sound like that like [ __ ]
movie advice you got that there's a peer
in me like I don't believe that advice
but it's going to become better advice
over time it's really important to find
something that you enjoy and like
because if you enjoy it then you're more
likely to invest time in it and become
good at it and develop like skills that
are resilient over time so believe it or
not if you're a young person you can
find something you really enjoy doing
you should lean into that and a lot of
that revolves around interpersonal
dynamics and skills because
team-building is going to become crucial
over time in a world where you know
dealing with people is going to become a
massive value add so that that's one
thing I'd say is and it sounds like 80s
movie that is advice or something but if
you can find something you'd like doing
just really trying it good at it
can we go into foreign foreign policy
sure so I get my presidential
how do you have plans to continue
president Trump's like confrontational
approach to China economically and
geopolitically
well I think one of the traps that the
US tends to get itself into is seeing
the world as a zero-sum game where if
someone else is doing better than it's
somehow like hurting us and I think that
is going to drag us into a cold war with
China or worse and to me we have to see
that other countries can become more
successful and it's not necessarily a
bad thing
for the US are there things in the
us-china relationship that are serious
issues that we need to try and address
like their piracy of intellectual
property and increasingly some of the
things they're going to happen in terms
of human rights and and there's the
protesters and and other things like
yeah they are very very serious issues
but is China's success necessarily
destructive to the US like I I don't
believe so so we have to take that
stance where we protect America's
national interest but do it in a
disciplined way where we also don't
confuse economic success in national
security
if something's national security then
you have to go hard and that that's just
the stance but the economic interests
sometimes get confused with security
interests in a way that I think is not
very productive what about North Korea
Middle East well I think engaging with
North Korea is not a bad thing I think
engaging with foreign leaders that we
disagree with is generally productive
and so I wouldn't you know I wouldn't
say that
you know Donald Trump did something
wrong where he went wrong with North
Korea is that he kept meeting with Kim
jong-un without clear parameters in
terms of what he needed to get out of
the meeting either before during and
eaze had this all-or-nothing approach to
the diplomacy and denuclearization where
there are goals you can set that are
short of complete denuclearization that
would be very very good for the u.s.
that if you're gonna meet with with them
and that needs to happen and this is
personal for me my sister-in-law's in
Seoul right now so anything that happens
in the and the Korean Peninsula
you know it actually affects family
members if you had to choose what
country outside of the USA would you say
is doing a pretty good job of running
their country I think that Denmark in
the Scandinavian countries have done a
really good job of helping build robust
social safety nets and structures that
have helped people manage very very
difficult transitions I think we can
learn a lot from them but do you think
they're able to do that because it's a
smaller country compared to the US and
the u.s. being like a melting pot of so
many different cultures yeah they have
some advantages in terms of their
ability to get some of these things done
and to me one of the great challenges
for the United States is to be able to
get great things done despite being
heterogeneous you know like it shouldn't
be that we all have to look exactly the
same to get big things done you know I
mean okay well I mean we were just
instructed you have like five more
minutes so before you go I have to ask
you something or ten minutes before you
go there's something I want to ask you
and see this in five minutes so what are
your thoughts about aliens and you know
Bernie Sanders came out on Joe Rogan's
podcast which he also did and said
basically if he becomes president he is
going to what do you say he's gonna like
release the information about aliens and
the truth and stuff like that they do
but that's what I'm saying like truth
they get told the truth and we're like
it's too scary to share I am on the same
page I will share what's going on with
the aliens of the American people unless
it's just too damn scary don't you think
that's already happened then like I mean
I've seen interviews it's like
conspiracy theorists say like you know
Barack Obama went on certain interviews
and he kind of hinted at it but he
doesn't want to say it he said he was
gonna release that stuff too right so
let's just say my threshold for not
sharing would be astronomically high
like I would share it unless it was like
we grew up watching every alien movie
that's where I am you know I think
watching x-files yeah so let's just say
that I would like to be able to be
transparent about these things the
American okay pretty much I'm a regular
dude what would a regular
the situation but like it always seems
like that it always seems like a regular
dude until they become important right
they become the president or somebody
and then and then somebody gets to them
gets to them what them yeah I mean yeah
one of my primary qualification is to be
president is that I think I'm fairly
unchanged through this process become
president to like there's so many
trappings of the office that I could
take or leave you know I just want to
solve the problems I'm on the record
saying like if I could saw the problems
not being president I would take that to
like I don't have any native intrinsic
burning desire to be press which means
you would help another candidate if you
weren't the nominee you'd help another
candidate oh yeah I had one of my major
life's goals it was to like to elevate a
major national candidate and my wife saw
these goals and you know was not on the
list be a major you know maybe that's
partially an Asian thing too you know
what I mean that's a health or just like
you want to get the stuff done and like
being front and center is not you don't
need to be the guy you just want to get
the solutions yeah that's right in the
group project okay America needs
solutions and a smart president oh thank
you for saying so I think so too
like a bull version okay well before we
get going where can people go to support
you if you'd like to join the yangyang
just go to yang 2020 comm give a buck
five bucks it makes a huge difference
because the media keeps track of number
of donors as a measurement of support so
yang 2020 calm you'll see all of my
policies and plans there we also have a
really fun social media president's not
as fun as yours but you know we've we
have like videos and a lot of people are
making art about me and the campaign
which is a lot of fun and awesome and
some of it MC Jin did yang Yang Anthem I
don't know if you saw that I haven't so
yang 2020 calm and let's take the
country back and make it work for young
people in particular awesome I always
said I was a very interested in you and
I wasn't
consider myself yang Yang until I met
you and I will say the people watching
the reason why I was hesitant is I want
to see if you are you when you're not
you know on TV and stuff and I will say
you're exactly the same
yeah it's thank you again for being here
it's it's this is a big deal for us like
for you to come to like David's house
and do this little podcast when you're
on like Fox and all these other big
things Joe Rogan's podcast it's awesome
you guys are awesome you guys are
inspirational you know we need more
people in our community in particular to
be creative make art ala and express our
point of view so I'm an admirer of your
work a great deal I know that you don't
feel it as much because you're in it
every day you're like you're doing it
you're like oh we're just doing our
thing but there's so many and there are
a lot of people who when I said I was
coming your way they were excited so you
know like it's a great opportunity for
me
awesome well great thank you so much
yeah appreciate it don't sell yourself
short you guys Rock all right well don't
forget us when you're president so we'll
run this thing back again from the White
House that's a promise
all right you can follow us at off the
pill on Twitter and off the pill podcast
and Instagram and how we always end this
we basically just breathe into the mic
so in 3 2 1
you're not really doing it are you hi
definitely all right awesome well thank
you