[Applause]
hmm
wow this is actually pretty entertaining
actually pretty good fighters for
youtubers hey Wade all the scones see
everybody's getting fights now even Matt
Jacob Williams got a fight and he just
started you two like I'm one thing cool
I mean he might have just started but
his numbers were huge and he's really
controversial and really good at
starting drama like like when he called
out the blah blah brothers and expose
them on Twitter oh yeah that time he
roasted in sternum TV yeah literally he
lit his house on doing sick burns so
what I can do things like that like the
other day I tweeted out all these
youtubers fighting in real life seems
pretty interesting and then I added one
of those hmm emojis you know which one
right on the iPhone it's like and yeah
that's not a good call up what are you
talking about I did the hmm that's an
obvious invite to fight that's not even
a good tweet actually someone did
respond to that a lot who's Alex what's
up I was a be weightless ah be
interesting I'll show you something
interesting girl respond back if you've
been a skirt if you don't respond you
ain't beep just kidding but for real
AB me bro or DM I'll be waiting fam
wow you guys are equally bad at
call-outs that was real call outs look
he's been trying to get me to fight with
him ever since the whole drama trend
even started even back when they was
just diss tracks so I don't get it then
why don't you just fight him or they
start some drama or something yeah he
has over 10 million subscribers and he's
like the same size
yeah already wants to fight you
you guys are like a perfect fit so I
don't see why you're the one it's my
first time all right
you mean like your first time ever well
yeah
not even like a sub tweet or anything oh
okay I'd never had online drama with
anyone okay I just I just want my first
time to be on a special
I'm not stupid what no we get it
yeah we just didn't know how much that
meant to you well it's never gonna
happen anyway so what's the point
come on no you know tons of big
youtubers I'm sure at least one of them
wants to you don't think I've tried that
you think I've tried reaching out to
every single one of the contexts I've
built upon YouTube over the past twelve
years hoping that maybe just one just
one of them would be interested in
finding me you don't think I've tried
that no I should probably try that you
really should all right so this is the
list of youtubers that I can get in
contact with that are either in the
drama scene or they're just really
popular so what you guys want to start
with yes we'll start from the top Felix
what's up man how you oh no I didn't
mean any disrespect by that like I
didn't mean to clay that I'm sorry mr.
pie yes I'm a boy how you being JJ Oh
disconnected yeah Jake's not answering
neither is Logan drama okay
boozy what's up bro slice gum what's up
wait you do want to okay no that's
that's great yeah we could totally I
don't know like a hundred fifty five
pounds but no no no I can well I can
lose the weight like I can change no
dude I think I just got fat shamed okay
who we got next
well there's only one left who is it
Matt Jacob Williams okay what's that
supposed to mean
come on I don't want to be a downer but
let's be realistic really I am being
realistic I know the guy personally okay
I met him at the steamy shorty awards
right you just had the biggest fight
ever
everybody wants drama with them you even
have his number yes okay just watch
man DJ will is nice to talk to you again
first off I just want to congratulate
you on the last foot wait who's it Alex
oh it's the wasa big change your name in
my phone what did you even get that
chance to do that you know where I live
no no no no I don't want you to prove it
doctor don't you dare
yeah so Matt said he's busy face it
she's never gonna have a real beef with
anyone I mean sure I could start drama
with some random person but in order to
escalate that drama from mean tweets to
a diss track to an actual fight that
people want to see you need the real
stuff you need that passionate loathing
that authentic disdain that only comes
from two people who just know how to get
under each other's skin and just piss
each other off to the point of hatred
that's what true hate is that's what
people want to see that's just not who I
am never be that way
what hey this skunk run you said you
didn't take the last one really that's
what you're gonna focus on just spill my
heart to you guys you're not even
listening look maybe you just haven't
met the right guy yet or girl what you
its 2018 guys sure you'll be teased a
little bit in the beginning but hate is
hate you just have to have an open mind
I'm gonna fight a girl okay
I'm not kool-aid I like guys I fight
guys whatever I don't have to be so
hydrophobic about it hey you just got a
text from magic of Williams what really
he says he's here
what would Matt chick of Williams beat
oh that's Sun of hope hey Ryan
it's good to see you again you want Alex
well I've noticed that you haven't been
responding to my texts tweets dm's
Facebook messages Henry I don't want to
talk to you okay so what's your point
well my point is when you called me
earlier I was literally in the middle of
packing for Europe and I got offered a
fight and England I was going over there
and I thought I can't leave without
figuring out what this is what what is
this between us first of all I didn't I
trying to call you I don't know when or
how you did it but you changed your name
in my phone oh that was when you left in
front of the Steamies secondly I don't
know how you of all people got a fight
but I don't care so if you came here to
just rub it in my face oh no no no no
that's not it at all and what are you
here for I came here because cuz you're
my dream fight something about you
rejecting me over over over
over and over and over and over and over
it yes over and over a lot of times yes
what again and again it just built up my
hate for you and I won't be able to
focus on this fight in Europe or any
other fight until I get a definite
answer from you
so once and for all Ryan Anthony he goes
not even my middle name will you fight
me Alex I don't know how it could have
been any more clear than I've been up
into this point wait wait wait I feel
like I know you're going with this and
before you do Alex
okay I don't know if it's just because
you're stupid and you really can't
understand what I'm saying maybe just
went deaf through your own high-pitched
girly voice but get this through your
thick dumb disproportionate dad to a
breeding head I will never ever fight
you if this is about the dander I
believe ever
okay I get it pull this up
no Ryan you will never find true hate in
your heart unless you will shut up
what look at you
what about me you're glowing with rage
what do you talk him I've seen you upset
before but that that was different yeah
you're gonna had some decent it I know
right it was like where was that coming
for I thought he was actually gonna
punch him in the face
like in my cancer I'm not gonna fight
Alex okay I don't care how many times
you guys keep bringing it up but you saw
what he's like okay he's just he's just
weird and he is annoying and sure I
might dislike the guy maybe a little bit
but I don't like seriously okay like you
you saw what he's like he hacked my
phone that's that's not just crossing
the line that's illegal okay I'm just
even thinking about him right now and
freaking makes me like it I freaking
just hate him look what no kind of it
I don't hate him I don't just I don't
hate him I dislike him a lot but Ryan
go get on
[Music]
[Applause]
cuz you're my dream fight Oh pepper ever
write something about you rejecting me
[Music]
Brian
why did you park so far man what do you
want dude
haven't you yelled at me enough no I
haven't not even close
what it's hard for me to admit this but
I was wrong like you and everyone else
around me could see that there was
something here and I just didn't want to
admit it because I don't know I was
scared
how do I know you're not just saying
that I've never felt like this about
anyone else before I mean just just
thinking about what your face looks like
I just get so angry you know I've been
looking at you right now I can see our
future together I can see us fighting
you don't know how bad I want to put you
in a rear naked choke put me in an
armbar we don't even have to stop even
after the tap because how excited I hate
you so much you make me more hateful
person than I ever thought I could be
you mean it I do every last bit that was
really mean and now I stand here
just boy standing in front of another
boy asking him to fight him
we don't need gloves
[Applause]
[Music]
this is sad seriously