here you are
oh thank you oh oh my god that's not
here let me mug you instead don't even
worry about it
well man with a knife
you think pretty genius huh
well maybe not ingenious but definitely
ingenious do you see how irritating that
is this video is actually nothing like
what the title says well I mean
technically it was about a woman trying
to mug a man who happens to have a knife
and what he did next was kinda genius
but definitely more Gina SH do look this
video is about something that I've been
irritated with for a very long time now
and even more so because I feel like
it's happening more and more these days
as you can probably already tell I'm
talking about misleading titles I don't
know about you guys I get really upset
when there's articles that have really
intriguing and interesting titles but
then when you click on them the story or
video or whatever it's supposed to be is
nothing like the title basically these
websites and post these articles and
videos try and come up with any single
title that will get you to click on them
even if the article or video is barely
related they'll still try and exaggerate
the title just so you click on I mean I
guess it's kinda exactly what I did in
this video the sad part is this video is
actually more relevant to the title than
most articles these days you know which
ones I'm talking about
you'll be on Facebook scrolling through
your newsfeed and all of a sudden you
see an article is saying something like
this man boom the secret to a living
forever exclamation point exclamation
point exclamation point but really it's
just about a 95 year old man who can
still run a mile or something or maybe
you're on Twitter and you see a tweet
that says something like click on this
link to see the most amazing 5 year old
kid that ever lived and then it's just
like a video of a little boy on x-factor
who can sing amazingly well for his age
but it's still like pretty average in
comparison to most singers maybe you're
even on YouTube and you see a video
called woman tries to mug man with a
knife but what he did next was genius
but really it's just a video about a
stupid asian kid sitting in a chair in
front of a camera with no pants on but
it's not like you can see his bottom
half in the frame anyway what anyway
I've been tricked so many times into
clicking links that I'm almost at the
point where I just don't click them
anymore which actually sucks because
sometimes there are really good articles
and videos that actually do live up to
their title so again I'm sorry for
anyone who actually got tricked by the
title of this video I'm just trying to
make a point and spread this message so
that people stop using misleading titles
or if they do people at least call them
out for if you're like me and you're
consistent victim to these misleading
titles then help me spread this message
please I know for those of you who've
been watching for a while you already
knew this video was gonna be nothing
a woman bugging a man with a knife and
it definitely wasn't gonna be genius at
all or dot dot dot is it you think
pretty genius huh
well maybe not ingenious but definitely
ingenious yeah dumb pun
empty your pockets give me everything
just take it take it
what the hell is this it's everything
and you thought my puns were bad
yeah right yeah I am right this was good
and you didn't even know it because when
it comes to this game I'm a god and you
you're terrible now if you still think
you can beat me in this game go it's
your turn
well I you are you up just say your name
fine you win okay I'll just cut it out
uh-huh you mean this whole time you you
tricked me that was Tina SHhhh no this
time it was genius but might try
give me all your money
nope here here's my wallet my phone just
yeah no this video still has nothing to
do with the title so so thank you guys
so much for watching if you want to see
bloopers and behind the scenes click the
one on the left if you want to see the
previous video click the one on the
right if you want to see a bunch of the
giraffe fighting it the dubstep music
pick the one at the bottom and what what
is it what does it sound like I'm so far
away from the mic it's right here so
echo hello
[Music]