hi I'm dr. hunter wakizashi cell Tadashi
teriyaki Suzuki Honda Civic and I'm
gonna making you a little less dumb with
every video my goal is to increase the
vocabulary of every kid parent auntie
uncle dog cat frog and so on
today's word is the word poem beep beep
ooh bombed the total domination over
shutdown of a person place or thing the
word pwned originated from the word ohm
which derived from the word own which
came from the word cat poem has become
one of the most frequently used words
throughout the world it is used in such
spaces as Australia just got powned by
Hawaii all right I know you got Pokemon
Japan
North America you just have poem South
part of North America y'all just got
pwned and just a little bit more salt
event no man s upon you homes here's
some example as a oh and now that you
increase your knowledge return the favor
and send this to another kid parent
auntie uncle dog cat frog or whatever to
increase their knowledge and make them a
little less dumb with every video thank
you