Hey Dude come on why'd you do that it
was just about to start I know you guys
stopped watching the thing and help me
with this come on man we just wanted to
see your part didn't even do it this
year remember what why not we were
filming something near that time
remember I think it was the oh the
cardboard video you turned down youtube
rewind to play with cardboard well yeah
that video took so long yeah we are
never doing a stop motion ever again
well the basketball trickshot video take
just as long yeah we're not doing that
either from now on we're not doing any
more videos that take a long time to
make thank goodness then what are we
gonna do I don't know that's why I'm
asking you guys to help me out here man
what if we did our own version of
YouTube rewind what yeah actually
YouTube rewind is just showing all the
biggest videos and trends of the year we
can do that yeah but with a really high
production value and a bunch of
youtubers making cameos how are we
supposed to do that
we can't but you know what we can do a
really crappy version of it with no
cameos from other youtubers just me and
we'll call it YouTube rear ioan ah boom
I love it I love it I love it didn't you
just say that you weren't going to make
videos that take a long time stop living
in the past Derek that was 15 seconds
ago alright let's talk about the past
now if we're gonna do this we have to
think about all the biggest trends that
happen this year ending with the biggest
so if we work backwards what was the
biggest trend that happened this year I
would say Adele Adele yeah she was one
of the biggest things this year
I don't recall I think he means a Dell
computer right what no no Derek tell
computers were not a big thing this year
I know I'm time Adele the singer her
album her song hello hi oh her yeah I
mean I guess she's up-and-coming but I
wouldn't end the whole video with what
are you talking about she broke records
this year over million sales in a week
27 million views in a day did YouTube
rewind do something about her no exactly
fine what ideas you guys have been what
about the pizza rap video that was
relevant for like a week with a girl
throwing the shovel that was even this
year hitting the Quan know I still think
Adele's bigger iPhone 5 that was like
two years ago
I mean 5s okay I got you hotline bling
by Drake okay that's actually a decent
way I told you Adele wasn't the biggest
thing no I still think Adele's album was
just as big look even if they were equal
who's gonna pick that del over Drake
well it's either del or Drake and
there's two options there's three of us
yeah so let's take a vote fine
I vote for Drake fine I vote it down
what about planking what planking it was
huge everybody did it well he does have
a point now was five years ago
well now we have three options so we
can't vote what are you talking about
that's not even an option let's just
forget the ending for now that just go
back to the beginning what are we
starting with well what other things
happened this year I don't even remember
can we just watch youtube rewind and
write down all the trends that they did
this is some kind of joke to you Derrick
what you're not gonna copy anything that
you to rewind did I didn't say copy I
was just saying that with YouTube rewind
Derrick okay this is YouTube Ryu Ryan
got it I got it
what if we started with that skeleton
video and have it dancing just like
YouTube rewind it yeah yeah YouTube
rewind did that it must be a good idea
right yeah exactly how we're going to
start it
you
wait don't do it shut up silence said
silence silence dog
water
you
the 2015 celebified
well I know
that's what you ended with you did all
that you ended with planking yeah what'd
you think yeah it was all Ryan yeah it
did kind of feel like the ending was
missing something obviously you didn't
even mention a delt once you really love
Adele huh no but if you're gonna show
the biggest trends of 2015 how you're
not going to show the biggest party I'll
just do it okay if it'll finally make
you happy I'll do it yes it will kiddin
me I this is the biggest trend of 2015
hello it's John