hey guys so I know what you're thinking
why the long face bad jokes Brian that's
a bad way to start a video hey guys so
something a little fishy has been
happening on YouTube lady and I just
wanted up I'm sorry could I please get
rid of this stupid joke who wrote this
anyway I didn't which is also you Oh
that our good one
anyway back to the YouTube fishiness I
posted a video last week and usually
after I post a video I gain about $5 an
hour more subscribers but over the past
week I lost about a hundred thousand
subscribers so I was like there you guys
really did not like that video but then
I checked I saw the other youtubers like
Smosh and Shane Dawson and
raywilliamjohnson and other on since
we're losing subscribers as well every
day we're losing more and more and we
just keep falling deeper and deeper into
this whole pad so she said run for once
I finally make my first serious video
and and you're treating this like it's
some big joke so why is this happening
YouTube is once again deleting YouTube
accounts so instead of deleting just
inactive account I've been getting a lot
of comments and tweets from people
saying that they've been automatically
unsubscribed to some of their favorite
channels that they go to every day have
you ever thought that people just don't
want to subscribe to you guys anymore
well then that would be just one big
sudden coincidence and then we don't
believe in coincidences right dr. house
I agree but on a real serious note I
appreciate every single one of my
subscribers but that's not the reason
why I started making videos I didn't do
it to gain subscribers or to make money
or to gain popularity I did it because
it was fun so just so you guys know I am
never gonna stop making videos even if I
lose all my subscribers I will never
back down I will never say never except
for those past few times I will not stop
making videos good as nothing in this
world it can stop
and don't worry guys all the paper you
saw me using this videos is going to be
recited what you ruin this entire video
you're boring man it takes two of you to
make one interesting person who mean
you're like them you're like the mean
version of me you mean like me TV that
was a goodbye high-five for them all
right I have lots of friends