[Music]
introducing the all-new
completely redesigned iphone 7
iphone 8. when we released the iphone 7
people complained that it was basically
the same thing as the six just that we
added another camera but this time we
made sure that wasn't the case
we added two more cameras to give us the
first ever quad camera experience people
who think it's stupid or unnecessary to
have
four cameras on one phone just don't
understand that now with the quad camera
you can take one picture and you'll have
four of that same exact picture you can
never do that before just think about
what you could do with that if you're a
parent of quadruplets you don't need to
get all of them
sit still for a picture you just need
one you take two pictures you got the
point of view of a spider just like that
you don't have to take eight individual
pictures anymore i mean even for video
the video resolution alone you film 1k
you're shooting 4k now which is kind of
one of the main reasons why we went from
the dual cam straight to the quad cam
and skipped the tri-cam because you know
if you film with the tri-cam the
resolution is a little
well too samsung for us it's a little
too edgy last thing we want is people to
get heated over this and explode on us
you know another thing that people
really criticize us for when we released
the 7 was the lack of new iphone colors
even though we did introduce two new
colors black and jet black
people still weren't pleased for some
reason so this time around in addition
to the original colors we're also
announcing a bunch of new and fresh
colors for the iphone 8 ranging from
matte black to shiny matte black light
skin brother black
jack black jack black on a hot day look
i could keep going but we'd be here all
day
just know that all these new colors will
never get old because they're all black
and black black don't crack and even
with all the things we announced so far
the craziest thing about the iphone 8
the price you ready for this we are
pricing the iphone 8 at exactly one
dollar one dollar
it's pretty much free i mean of course
there are a few add-ons that you're
going to need just like the 7 the iphone
8 doesn't have any headphone jack so if
you want to use headphones you have to
buy the wireless ones
not a big deal we did change the charger
port again
we actually added two more charger ports
to make it faster all three parts are
different so you have to get all three
different chargers and actually they
don't plug into the wall anymore they
only plug into our three new macbooks so
you have to get those as well a couple
more fun new features for the iphone 8
we also took all the lighting
capabilities out of the iphone so you'll
have to purchase the eye light if you
want to use flash or
flashlight on the phone we made it a lot
easier to text and write messages with
the iboard so
your phone actually doesn't have a
keyboard anymore you actually need the
iboard if you want to write anything the
iphone 8 comes with the premium color
version of every app so you also have to
purchase youtube red and facebook blue
and snapchat yellow and so on
also if you want any reception or
internet of any kind you'll need the i
cell phone tower mini this one is
actually not wireless so that the
internet's faster so you have to bring
it wherever you go
also siri is no longer in the phone we
actually made her external so you have
to buy a person as well
[Music]
oh and i almost forgot to mention one of
the biggest new features we developed
unlike the seven which is only water
resistant we
finally developed a way to make the
iphone completely waterproof all i have
to do is use our new highly advanced
iphone case called the
ian droid