Oh welcome back gamers as you can see we
made some large let's make a mess hello
quiet quiet ground look at meatball so
beautiful so pretty
I couldn't be bothered to fix it okay I
thought its color you can see inside it
it looks that big
alright cool that's it's under
construction it's under construction
it's in that right here against Morgan
kissee well that's right deep don't go
near me you're disgusting what else do
we have
oh yeah I made this safer shut up quiet
what else did I do yes
where are my Rockets god dang it I have
to walk that's way too much effort oh
are you kidding me Rockets go I have so
much stuff to show you guys
I'll make some quick Rockets quiet quiet
quiet
smack I'll take the boat I'll take the
bow alright here we go let's see how
much we got oh my God we're gonna get so
much I will wait for some to die hello
jump please
I mean don't do it also do it alright
well we have plenty of these come on
that's right keep keep them coming
yeah jump little creeper don't be scared
little creeper your death is here jump
little creeper soon you will die chop
little creeper it's time to say bye bye
a little creeper give me your strength
that was beautiful thank you I want
little creeper to die in my bed that
rhymed Hey
two feet apart two feet apart come on
stop it knock it off goddamn there's a
lot of chickens here no bathing on my
property no walking on my property what
was i doing you're going to remind me
okay I remember call now we can go yeah
yeah look at this alright so I built
this on my spare time where fun alright
so this is supposed to give me XP as you
can see it's melting bamboo and bamboo
damn it's made a lot why am I not
getting XP yeah look at that now it's
work I forgot to turn it on that's cool
well you can see it works yeah yeah be
quiet
quite odd all right so we have some
actual stuff to do today cuz I know and
now I know I've been ridiculed for not
finding nether right I will find it as
my last name is elaborate uh Smita yeah
that's right all right what how about
this i turn around and i shoot the
random person oh god I coulda shot two
little bita lucky
where's Sven by the way there you are my
main good boy that is gonna go on
business trip I'm gonna come back and
I'm gonna find that the right you
understand what could a much done
okay you understand don't talk to the
pigs
see you on this other side on the other
side on the other side
Oh Lord Alabama I pray to thy bidding
please bless me to find that the right I
cannot stand being ridiculed any longer
I bring of course sacrificial take them
they're yours
beside you want gold alright alright
make it rain make it rain Alabama
make it rain it's all yours oh yes yes
yes yes I forgot about this so I made
fun of these lives turn one in though
stop living now hey listen to me listen
to me anything that walks on lavash a
cat I forgot about that shouldn't live
oh god this is scary what are you doing
here juice Michael J says he scared me
you can walk on these okay I got it
Oh God I don't let me just get some of
these this is a little scary I'm not
gonna lie I feel like I could die any
second okay all right we got to get out
to them Oh God
why can't I what it's a glitch ooh
that's scary dude I don't like this
okay okay whose fault was that huh
whose fault was that huh that's right
your fault you little crappy pappy well
that's probably the worst way you can
start a minecraft episode I'm back all
right and this time you were supposed to
bless me I gave you chicken and gold I'm
taking those back Alabama I'm taking
those back dude I'm so poor so poor I
wanted to try if I could fly them that's
all I wanted why didn't even come from
I'm back for revenge's I'm gonna get
what I wanted this is not the end I'm
gonna ride those Frings this is supposed
to be fun huh why did I even come from
all right I'm looking at now apparently
have to look ow
dumb body was told me yeah yeah yeah I'm
coming for you I'm coming for you you're
not supposed to live this is happening
100% thousand come here stop walking
away you're ugly stinky I will ride you
gosh you're so far away oh we found the
girl there she is hey listen listen go
Oh God bring it oh god yeah done it's me
and I don't know what your name is
hey I bought that saito that was good
Chi
bring it back please please come back
come on stop this stop this stop this
let me write you yeah yeah this is cool
all right so what can I do
can you take me back take me back I
changed my mind
take me back Oh God and then I'm done
I'm stopping oh we are back yah yah
oh you're really clear I'm going in I'm
going it I'm going in and I'm not gonna
make it I'm gonna make it our life you
better be quiet that's what I get that
go back to your land go back to your
home this is not what you live sorry
Alabama you want to beef with me he
wants a beef with me stop it stop it I'm
in a sense why does he want me I didn't
do it listen listen stop it now stop it
if I attack you everyone else will
attack with oh this is bad oh god what
am I going to do die a death you didn't
see anything right
yeah did you see anything it is see
anything all right cool so I read
comments and the way to find nether
right right is you have to go somewhere
you haven't spawned in before so it has
to be in one of the new areas I need to
change my settings cool hi guys oh they
made babies hope they go bye-bye
how knowing it is to be in the nether so
dark okay we're at a new place here we
can find nether right at last gold I'll
take I'll take some money I will find
you I don't care how long it take it can
take a year it can take tomorrow Oh God
I don't know what the fastest way to do
it is I don't even know it's possible I
just want to look cool in black so I can
sing I'm fully stacked nether right
fully stagnant alright they just had to
change it then God dangit Mojang at
least I can see now I don't think so mr.
lava lava so apparently it's the rarest
thing in the game as far as I understand
that's pretty rare it must be so epic
yeah yes it is
so your mom am i right oh I II maybe
they spawn near lava maybe they Mojang
it's just like yeah screw people that
play
they would definitely do that ah I'm
bored something happened I don't even
know what it looks like
I'll pick ax about to go bye-bye oh I'll
take it
I'm about to go buy a buying oh Jesus
thank you pick ax you served me well Oh
God I got something in my throat it's
game over guys they try to kill us at me
a man in a caveman
I'm gonna go forever I don't care I'm
gonna go forever yeah I knew I could do
it mom
glorious oh I thought it was more that's
just so Lysander okay here we go or we
take a long time yeah girl you're
difficult yeah
ancient the breeze gamer said I couldn't
do it just jump the poppy and we keep
going we're crazy like that mm-hmm
I'm gonna fully dip the black watch me
die and lose it on maybe I should go
back dude if myself saw this she'd be so
impressed she's been talking about
ancient debris left and right he's like
dude I wish my husband had ancient
debris but I cringe every day that he
does not I might just go ring up Ricardo
and see if he has some ancient no no no
that's what I said just like that no
don't was you boil it oh go old man yeah
I get you go I don't want gold Felix I
want ancient debris called a plane you
know don't go plate alone Ricardo me you
do me dirty all right and you should be
pretty confirmed on floor 16 gamers
now get out there and get that ancient
Deborah you you snakey snake stop it
yeah my dad they really killed me no
they really killed me when I said I
hadn't had the right saying he will
never get near the right you're spitting
out cereal right now aren't you
this diamond pickaxe is literally
unbreakable my other one just got sucked
up so quickly did I not have I'm
breaking on it damn you get a lot of
gold I didn't realize so I think you
melt the ancient debris and that's how
you get another right you don't get
another right right away I knew that
because I'm give me three give me three
give me three give it damn it dude I'll
take two yeah come to me come to me come
to Papa baby yeah we're gonna fully
stack nether right fully Stagner the
right you won't see me crying a boys
back no the right more it's like Oh
kinda once you get a little bit you want
more forever yes I feel powerful the
scary noises in Minecraft no longer
scares me I feel so alive I feel like I
unlocked 10% of my full power
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
they said I would never be gamer yeah
yeah
all right mission get out of here alive
let's not get greedy here I don't like
this that means we're getting close to
surface I think right we're out
hallelujah praise ow
praise be legs or am i some weird cave
here we go I'm free
whoa so we were in this volume I
probably shouldn't go here just wanna
lick just wanna look where we are again
yeah this is where we were last time
all right cool we can trade there the
gold hello hey oh oh I'm just innocent
sweet oh if I could trade with you that
would be so great how lucky I found you
trade with me imbeciles fools you will
trade with me no you don't touch me you
don't know oh I was going to friendly
offer to this makes me angry I forgot
they attack anyone that doesn't have
Goldust goddamn dumb blobs those flicky
and dumb Blum's
I give me all of it okay so I need to
make it like a hat or something yeah
fine
waste of gold but so be it hey guys
look I'm just like you I worship the
gold do not hurt me do not hurt me
because I will cause you more pain than
imagine then imagine their capability
you you want all these guys don't like
gold dang it as your witness I'll find
them
I'll find the ones that like the gold I
just really don't want to die right now
that's literally the number one thing on
my mind
oh she neither kudasai hello I come from
far north I bring you gold
give me another right give me give me
another right what if you actually did
it that'd be so good there this is
garbage
do you understand this means nothing to
me nothing
uh okay fine I'll take that but come on
give me better I'll I'll see you get the
sword you don't want the sword do you
know you don't thought for a second
again made do it again
[Music]
what was that
so they can do enchanted books soul
speed one never even heard of that allow
us to walk quicker on Soul send that's
actually pretty useful to be honest now
in this new update at least what are you
doing
look you doesn't want to train with him
anymore come on dude and now you shall
die alright so this is what I got out of
all that I would say pretty good we just
got a fly home now without dead dude
look at these they're so cool I think
it's cuz a castle is trapped in there it
just spawned in a really awkward way
like I bet you there's a castle in here
okay maybe not all right maybe not it's
just weird
well look there is a castle look at that
come on that's kind of cool look at this
it's so weird
minecraft be like brah oh hello sir this
be your child I'm just kidding I was
kidding
gosh the attitude did it's a joke cringe
we have returned
that's right Alabama you blessed me weld
you did me well I will give you cream
because I know how much you like to skin
cream use face mask and I'll save the
rest for your brothers which you will
never say oh my god I'm so excited we're
gonna get nether right you don't belong
you're dead you're dead
oh my god swim cat son
I got you chicken you loved chip okay I
got you all he loves boots
there you go swing I know fine you get
some leather whatever
Jurgens Merrigan I got two nether ride
but I'll get the string capably got 22
nether right that's pretty crazy
I got you soul sent because you have no
soul after what you did you're
disgusting
all right so what do I do with the
ancient the breeze I gotta look this up
ancient dead breeze I know y'all jealous
right now
you smelt it and it becomes nether
bricks okay no problem
ooh nice what if I mess this up come on
baby
wait this is not nether right these are
not nether breaks I want another breaks
come on okay so what do I do with that
then with a scrap I do with a scrap
mm-hmm I need a gold oh my god yeah I
must have it somewhere oh look at that
already found some lucky me hi it's my
lucky day
oh god please heart please do not please
reconsider please oh oh they will all
pay Alabama I do this in your name it
will be mine is that gold
what are you gonna do huh I am not
afraid of no piggy piggy
drop your gold drop your gold sir hand
it over
yeah gold gold gold oh god it's that
thing oh god it's a lot of them ye Oh
sir there's a lot of it oh they got
backup oh this is little Harry I'm sorry
Pete that I'm sorry
pathetic pathetic yeah I'm the king I'm
the game game yeah you see that Alabama
yeah chicken with that me number that
was with that but with that but that but
that yeah yeah yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah they so good all right
getting gold is apparently very easy now
how about that all right
III don't want to risk it Oh God
oh it lit sup that's not cool look at
that
stop you're against Megan we're gonna
get nether Oh can I make it can you make
horse armor oh my god oh my god guys
it's happening guys guys I'm freaking
out I don't have enough alright find
more Caroline okay so I think it's like
this no what is it then what do you want
from me Oh what the hell
okay we got one we got one one we got
one we got one out of that are you
serious
we got one we got one one really
all right I'm making a helmet should I
make it that oh god this is the question
cuz I can make a I think it works like
this what the hell are you serious what
am i I thought I just needed a whine
what I need to sell my soul Mojang what
do you want from me okay let's see if
this works please work what call the
elevator works so well I'm so glad it's
fun like years building it to be
replaced by a ladder do I have to make
it hear me
I'm so man what am I doing wrong
big brain oh my god is it not out yet is
that what's happening
okay guys hope you enjoyed that episode
if you did smash like subscribe for more
content and I see you guys next time
we'll have nether then all right right
deep or egg do all right that's what I
don't you know what's big peepees do
they play PewDiePie's pixel ings of
course pixel ings is a creature
collecting game I'm the primary
shareholder over a Brazilian players
have downloaded and it's got a perfect
score it's safe to say it's the most
popular game of all time
PewDiePie pick slings it's awesome deal
with it deal with it
[Music]
you