what's up gamers today we're playing
dreams it's a game with many games
inside of it that's all I have
understood basically you can make games
with this game I don't know how that
works I'm just gonna play other people's
games this one is southpaw cooking it
looks like I have one minute oh God
okay what's your weather how do I grab
stuff oh there we go
I got oh there I think I got I just just
give me one minute and your order will
be right there your pizza will be right
there
it's in the oven right now are two grabs
things okay cool I'll put the onion and
it's done zero calories that's a great
price yeah let's try that again I guess
I'm trying to get as many calories as
possible drop nice oh it's cooking it's
cooking let's just take that out nice
gosh it's on fire it's fine
more calories all right we got to chop
the onion obviously just once all you
need catch nice how do people do this
add some thyme
250 calories nice my office in Brighton
got 250 calories that's hilarious
yeah I'll give that a thumbs up trending
games sonic boss battle how do you think
they have license for this so another
reason I wanted to play oh my god that's
insane I'm boosting and my boots sing
I think I'm boosting
we're aiming we can slash oh whoa yeah
take this it's a little hard to aim I'm
not really used to playing on console is
that no did I do it I don't think I did
it
oh god it's Annika with bus bet those
surprisingly this is better than any
Sonic games over the past decade I don't
really care all right I'm sorry whoa
they got PT no they not PT the greatest
demo of all time I'm controlling this Oh
God
whoa it's actually pretty tight no I did
it oh my god
this is so legit even bit the
head-bobbing movement and everything how
oh my god it's the beach up there I know
you're there girl
I missed this game what a wasted
potential
hey at least instead we got deaf
stranding am i right gamers yeah we won
that one Legend of Zelda no its legend
the legend that's how they get around
Cup right that's all you need to do what
yes
mortals mere mortals whoa all right
let's give me get my sword nice so I can
roll I can light whatever that means the
music and everything it really captures
the spirit of Zelda why is it so foggy
of this roll the classic the classic
technique is that speedrunners do it
they just run through the whole level I
made it nice that was it did I enjoy
that
absolutely Super Mario Sunshine this is
such a strange concept of a game that I
would never think would work like I've
heard about it a while ago and I was
like that sounds stupid
guess I'm this stupid oh my gosh do I
have to possess him yeah there we go hey
look it's me Yoshi
Carl this is wonky hey I did it
okay so what is this it's this greasy
food oh here we go
nice look at that texture very nice
tonight yeah that feels good that's
gross skin
why so yeah one reason I wanted to play
this game was cuz I was hoping oh my god
its crash bandicoot you guys could make
some levels if you want and I'll play
them just tag them PDP and I'll search
for it oh my god they have the loading
screen that's a loading screen that's so
confusing crash bandicoot eyelet they
have the loading oh my god no way oh we
got alright level 1 let's go yeah this
is amazing do it I got 29 1 foot the
sound effects and everything it's like
I'm there it's like I'm back in the game
once you bite dream so you don't need to
buy any other games really don't have to
jump if I can just spin fast enough I've
gone at the British level I ain't doing
that again I mean I I was referring to
it was actually a bit crash but what
does happen I don't think that's
supposed to happen brah look at my neck
shoulders my naked muscles I mean Jesus
you don't mess with a forever spam
forever spin yes I'll spend forever
month decent Crash Bandicoot is no FAP
somebody think about what Adventure Time
hey I like the I like the graphics
that's cool she's like playing a weird
vapor of wave dream or some [ __ ] it's
pretty tight platformer a super said
time can i oh hey Joe
I have been in the States before high
industry and
is my time to go Spence commit tax fraud
I knew it
we caught him here what up gamers should
sense how God what the hell is hand
[Music]
bandicoot versus Joker interdimensional
cable but why my god don't do it crash
what the hell is a is oh do I pass do I
pass
oh god do I pass please I think I passed
I definitely passed quest for cheese
that sounds like a good game yes yes oh
oh it fell versus a good hello well is
it's me Homer Simpson they're looking
for cheese well there isn't any around
here there might be something in the
backyard thanks Homer Simpson my god you
look beautiful
alright let's check the back oh it's
morning great alright I'm going here
alright weird space now and there's
sands good good and we're checking all
the memes and spongebob alright we were
we missing here really all right
spongebob the man you climb up this rock
if you want cheese alright I'll do
anything for Chiefs really cheese in
sauce the two greatest condiments there
we go
all roblox hello no stop
I'm leaving Oh God
oh hey little buddy want some salami -
now aren't you just the cutest little
beggar here you go little guy that was a
thumbs-up absolutely oh no not to
princeps it D oh my god it's so cute
what is that can I flee in fact maschino
1965 oh no it's happening
oh I'm sorry gee sash whoa shoot laser
[Music]
yes
I'm climbing I'm climbing it I'm
climbing it oh I'm a oh I shoot it then
Oh Oh God
I did it I'm so sorry guys
nothing news a whole fight this is so
satisfying why did they call it a
natural disaster I'm like a weird morph
between Pikachu and Godzilla if they had
a baby or something no one dares to go
against me I'm too cute please hug me oh
come on oh come on don't do it ah this
is so sad
there's one left please I just please me
you gotta let the live for me don't do
it huh
is he gonna hold it alone I'll jump off
I can't even
wow that's great
Jesus Christ dude oh you're oh you're
going down
[Music]
guys remembered though roblox cars be
like yeah of course of course
yep
I guess it can make animations - Wow
for tonight versus family guy god
there's too many I need backup in
McDonald's the phrase is just a game
it's such a weak monster
all right we're playing worm am i doing
anything did I break the game
don't cheat says
don't ever do that thank you what thank
you very much I understand what you did
them that was good you got me fine
Explorer mode creative mode oh they got
the newbies update huh Wow amazing
spen these with me fine but herobrine
was born in this world what spongebob
bikini bought no way oh my god this
looks legit there let's commit tax fraud
best game I have ever played I wonder if
I search PewDiePie if there's already
something that's not bad I'll take it
it's like a weird avatar maybe now
avatar 2 will finally come out oh my god
they got Lego Star Wars finally due to
popular demand I'm playing Lego Star
Wars yeah oh my god
due to popular demand we're finally
playing Lego Star Wars whoa I'm rich
brah this is like that gif that this is
super annoying
oh my god stop oh my god
you bet assistant yeah come on now
[Music]
I'll make it stop this is torture great
all right gamers if you guys enjoyed
this video smash like and if you want to
make a level for me
tag it PDP like the letters and I'll
play it for another episode if you guys
want it's much like if you want me to do
another one and yeah that's it subscribe
and I'll see you gamers in two days
because I decided to take weekends up
now ok I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
hey go bye bye bye bye Mario