nicer guess who's early
[ __ ] yeah
that's me
surprise [ __ ] i'm here
what's good
oh man just finished my workout i'm
still sweaty
it'll start in a second i'm just waiting
for people to come in then we play epic
game
i'm so excited to play more of this
hey look add me on psn i dare you
[Music]
zebra mix home brew no big deal get that
protein
oh oh man
quality should be a little better now i
don't know why i set such a low bit rate
the other time
let me start up the game
oh that was nice
[Music]
are you letting it green yeah
maybe i should have waited like 10
minutes before i went live
god damn [ __ ] leg day
pressure straight streaming time
precious video game time
lunges man deadlift man
squats man i hate them all is there
anything good
there's nothing good in this world
humans don't know how to develop tripods
they don't fall over
give me one sec what an
epic fail guys so it's so embarrassing
and this [ __ ] band god damn
oh [ __ ] all right let's not
freak out like yesterday or last time
it's fine i'm not mad
i ain't mad i ain't even mad
we're just gonna laugh it off ha ha
i was legit close to just
losing my [ __ ] again goddammit
it doesn't [ __ ] bend it so
frustrating
so weird
all right
see now you know at least it wasn't
personal from yesterday it's just who i
am i'm sorry um
all right
let's pull up the motherflipping chat
how does it look does it look all right
i find myself to be a little tiny if i'm
not gonna
i'm gonna be honest with you guys
i don't want to look small i'm huge a
bugaboo
uh
oh look how good the frame looks
what is happening
i'm gonna lose it again oh my god
sorry to keep you guys one second
oh
okay video game time
here we are ghost of tsushima
apparently it's an island i didn't know
that
thank you for all the comment that
pointed that out
um i'm not
really that immersed into the story so
far i'm not gonna lie it's kind of
not that interesting so far what do you
guys think
hoping it picks up but the whole it's
just that we just played a game
with a revenge plot so it's kind of like
i don't know do i really want to
another one
but it has some really nice [ __ ] to it
okay now i can see and now we can play
and now we can talk to lady with flute
oh lady with flute why are you wearing
underpant
epic
should we explore a little bit there's
the kamatsu forge
we can get waxwood guys
why don't we just explore while we're
still here
why not just get some wax float
while we're at it what the hell is
happening there
i can't call jurgen right now are you
serious
this revenge plot is better than last of
us to to be honest well
i it's gotta be hard not to make it
better than
oh man thank you terence ross
holy [ __ ] i'm playing a float
swipe left and you play a flute
[Music]
i love that
what happens if i swipe right
i draw my sword or i draw my flute
i can bow by swiping down and swipe up
is to win cool hey damon what's up man
oh now i can call you again
now how the hell do i get up there
i feel like i gotta remind myself a
little bit how to play
i know i haven't finished the task but i
kind of want to just look around
i know i'm annoying like that
[Music]
so many people are getting annoyed that
i'm playing on jab with j oh that looks
pretty
should we go there we're japanese
dub it is annoying how they prioritized
english with the uh with the dubbing
there's the mongolians
but it is what it is
damn so pretty
they really just went full out on
atmosphere
ipads my first first time doing it
through a stream but my
thank you say hi to edgar edgar says hey
some comments i read said that
apparently the mongolians did
try to evade japan but they failed
mainly because of a typhoon
and not because of the samurai but i'm
sure that's just what the
mongolians like to tell each other
we found a little house
such a cool looking game
let's see what we got
oh my god that bug is so disturbing
it's the second time
we out here we're entering random
people's houses
maybe we should go back to the objective
my bad just wanted to look down around a
little bit since it's been a while since
i play
uh and yes some people are cringing over
me speaking japanese
i think people misinterpret me wanting
to learn
japanese as opposed to me being
trying to pretend that i speak it or
like i'm an annoying
weave that goes
uh full on the hunger
epicly i feel like uh
it's such a difficult language that any
chance i can get
to immerse myself or or remind myself of
a word i'll take it
i don't care if it sounds cringy you're
cringy shut up
so long story short i'm not a weeb okay
just so we're clear i'm not a weeb
all right let's go to the objective then
my bad
let's deal with the
lady masako can we fast travel there
let's just do that then
[Music]
i feel like the most effective way to
learn is to suggest to immerse yourself
um at least from what i can tell
you can study it all you want but if you
don't practice actually saying words out
loud it's such a difference
uh where is she
i read somewhere that 9 out of 10 that
try to study japanese don't
learn japanese it's pretty crazy
because it is such a language where like
you have to dedicate
your next couple years actually really
studying it
all right here she is
let's continue this quest
forever
i don't think i have enough
but yeah i'll prevent myself from
repeating the japanese just so you guys
can't cringe at me
just kidding i don't care okay i don't
care
uh where's the armor lady was she here
[ __ ] i forgot where she was
oh it is here
now we're missing supplies god damn it
all right
i should i knew i shouldn't have
upgraded my sword now i pay the price
um yes
echo oh there's echo in the audio my bad
maybe i can turn it down a little bit
okay that should be better holy [ __ ]
this area changed
[Music]
i understood epic didn't [ __ ] hear
though
there oh my god i'm blind
we got some supplies let's keep grabbing
it whenever we can because i really want
a cooler armor
i wonder if i even remember how you play
and then i change stand with r two
that's right
i'm a real samurai guys
i fight with honor everybody loves
pewdiepie qf
qfs aviation mini thank you so much god
damn
your attachment to food which makes you
suffer nice
oh [ __ ] i forgot i had to do this
we're gonna track that son of a beat
okay how do i cancel the arrow shot i
guess i did it i just let it go
i'm so dumb now i can cancel it but it's
before i drawn it that's why
that was so confusing
what the hell she was just sitting there
and it's like oh you lost your target
great
and then [ __ ] jurgen was there too
we can get down here
foreign
why did he walk up there that's so funny
he didn't walk up now
i got you now mr monkey
why is he not going there now
[Music]
i wonder if anyone saw me
no way you saw me i'm a shadow
impossible to be seen
[Music]
thanks for playing these gamepads loving
it thank you apollo 69
rainbow [ __ ] thank you
it's a really fun game
[Music]
you didn't see nothing
uh chica means dear and i know that
because i'm nihongo as [ __ ] you guys
aren't weeb as me
shut the [ __ ] up
[Music]
sorry
all right this is boring i hate these
kind of quests
this game is really good all right this
is boring
i don't know where he is i'm not even
joking
ah
got worried there for a sec
[Music]
i i also got some people saying um oh
wow
his uh pronunciation really improved and
then someone was like
yeah well he can afford paying any
teacher in the world
so it's it's like why does everyone
think i just paid for everything
felix got a little bit of muscle well he
can just pay a teacher
okay every time every time
all right go to the side of the entrance
you guys think everything can be solved
with money
[Music]
oh [ __ ] they're gonna go dead
all right let's see if i remember how to
play
damn she's [ __ ] crazy dude
water stands yeah i know but he is
already dead
i know that stop it you just interrupted
my flow will come with come on
i don't want to
[Music]
i thought i dodged
[ __ ]
[Music]
i still suck apparently that was so cool
for a while
i think i understand the combat more now
i feel like i've been playing it like
dark souls
but it's more about flow of combat it's
just i suck at it
but i'll get better just give me time
thank you for your patience
[Music]
name
i'm getting worse best way to play this
spam l1 yeah it seems like it yeah just
quick parries
okay i'll take your advice
but she is [ __ ] crazy and you know it
[Music]
come on
there's so many
all right new strategy
i died maybe i should change to normal
no normally it's for cowards i can play
this
easy first try watch it
[Music]
this is like if they get one hit on you
i'm dead
oh my god can i please
[Music]
oh my god i'm dead again
they all swarm me i don't know what to
do
[Music]
help me help
come on
all right i got this first we do this
cheeky long
[Music]
oh
there it is all right watch out for the
spear
[ __ ] you
[Music]
nice
there it is
[Music]
oh [ __ ]
come on yes
nice
[ __ ] i don't have any arrows
[Music]
so close oh my god they keep [ __ ]
coming
[Music]
no how many are there there's so many
[ __ ]
oh jesus [ __ ] christ
kunai i forgot i had the kunai
i guess i just gotta get good
good start
[Music]
good start good start
i forgot the controls for the kunai i
think this is the problem
all right we're getting better sort of
not really
[Music]
yeah i just gotta make sure i don't get
surrounded
why don't i have arrows
[Music]
i dodged that i dodged that for [ __ ]
sake
[Music]
it's fine i have plenty of help
okay the wind is on my side
nice
[Music]
nice bring it [ __ ]
[ __ ] yeah easy zero deaths
that's always done hell yeah
hell yay
all right all right all right we're
warmed up now no problem first
first try feels good man thank you thank
you
thanks for the tips guys appreciate it
i know i know i should probably just
play on normal
and it would be nice and flowy gameplay
but
i i wouldn't get that satisfaction it
wouldn't feel like [ __ ] yeah
you don't get that
that's what's fun so i'm just looking
for supplies really quick
there we go
let me hear really quick there we go
sweet
feels good man
sorry
that's like this uh japanese food in
case you guys didn't know that
foreign
[Music]
am i right
what's that what just happened
we got searched in and [ __ ]
oh there we go
nice hey i have this in animal crossing
that's cool
we got more perpetrator
this a room no
we definitely can afford getting the new
armor now [ __ ] yeah
that's how we walk ladders at samurai
no camera is back don't worry about it
[Music]
foreign
them
did you guys hear that was that my
whatsapp
all right
nope even japanese said it was a typhoon
that saved them from the mongol that's
why they call it kamikaze
gods win oh kamikaze i never thought of
that i knew that
that's what i meant that's funny
that means god's wind uh
all right is there anything we should
upgrade i feel like i should upgrade the
deflection i didn't realize just how
important that is
yeah let's do that cool
parry an unblockable spare attack yes
and uh also yeah i was just joking
obviously about the mongol thing
it was so obviously a joke uh
all right what's next back to our home
home base
[Music]
i just keep missing weapons i don't know
how i do it oh i can upgrade my stance i
didn't know that
oh and i can upgrade moves oh my god
i've been not been utilizing
explosive arrows whale flame
whoa use oil to ignite this is some dark
soul
[ __ ] kills me terrifying there by
enemies
so i have to complete the undying flame
to learn
this technique
and i don't have enough technique points
for exploration
great well we're getting an armor that's
all i know right now
just bow to my bros
i think she's over here
i'm busy
all right epic samurai armor time [ __ ]
yeah
yeah look at us [ __ ] yeah
[ __ ] yeah
standoff upgrade is big help early on
boss man
did you mean that i'm bosch man or that
they're helpful on the bosses man
please help me specify hey what are we
listening to
hundred gigs [ __ ] yeah you too
uh all right what quests should we do
what quest should we do
we have two active tales and we have
some mythic tales
but there's a musician
let's show that on map where is that
that's pretty far away
might be fun to check that out
sorry about that just can't help myself
uh i'm sure there's a ton to just
explore around here
we don't need to go north right now what
is this then
let's track that
what happens if we speak to the lady
does she have anything for us
look at my new
[Music]
all right i guess we're doing this
yeah the exclusive tier three merch is
super close
they're just trying to fix the website
so only the tier three can access it
uh but uh yeah
the setting the time the gameplay is so
fun but i'm not
really into the story and that's
probably why because i'm talking over it
over every time
[Music]
um
i should buy arrows because i have [ __ ]
all
right we're searching for hatchi
is he on the stone
the main story is so good trust yeah
we've been doing a lot of side quests
and [ __ ]
i'm sure he picks up
this is the kind of game where i really
don't care about
doing don't mind
rather i want to get the full experience
is that what he said i didn't read
he calls his horse apple
why can't i just walk up on this
oh
all right we're doing the stealth [ __ ]
[Music]
do the mystic quest okay
yeah we're doing that later
technique i should look at them okay i
don't think i have anything done
we're following the horses now
foreign
whoa
close one i'm supposed to switch stances
for different enemies
so like during combat i switch if i
fight a shield guy
i'll try doing that
don't forget i'm a boomer multitasking i
can't do it
[Music]
all right let's talk to masako
she's busy uh hunching
[Music]
okay uh so
oh i see
so can i i don't have enough technique
points
uh and then there's ghost yeah i know
that
kunai r2
life to equip it and then r1 to throw it
okay
grow your legend
yeah need more points guys
[Music]
some enemies and stand up will attempt
to trick oh okay so is that happening
now then
i guess i didn't fall for the trick
[Music]
are you gonna fight me
why am i so slow
[Music]
nice
oh [ __ ]
getting better where's the arrow guy
let's
take him out
don't run away from me [ __ ] whoa [ __ ]
yeah
where's the other one
that was [ __ ] awesome surprise
[ __ ]
nice
getting better
what
there we go
yeah you should be scared
[Music]
foreign
i look so pimped out it looks so funny
nice jurgen here all right we got some
upgrades maybe now we get some stuff
[ __ ] yeah all right cool so now we have
now we can spend some techniques
people's hope
that's me maximum health
we can choose a new ghost weapon
uh black powder cool
smoke all right epic
sticky bombs epic wind chime
wind chime uh throw a wind chime to
attract an enemy's attention
nah i wanna yeah
bomb i'm going for the bomb
so
okay so i gotta quit them and then i
gotta throw them gotta make sure i
remember the controls for this so
r2 or r1
letter from sadat were in my involvement
in the adachi massacre has gotten
out i'm sure it didn't come from you you
know the danger of talking not only to
my
life but yours as well remain hidden and
silent until i
send for you trust in my cousins they're
loyal to me and skilled with the blade
if you meet
anything bearing this month take your
own life
if you meet anyone bearing this month
all my love
somehow damn all right i guess i'll just
kill myself if thing goes wrong
that's the samurai way ranged
weapon swapping okay so now he's telling
me what i just read
so that's the bomb and then to select
the kunai
i used r and then right now that's year
again
was it r2 and then is this that's
i already have it selected that's
annoying okay
target
dude we get some silk
why don't we ride to her and then we can
check this out on the way
how does that sound
let's just follow the wind see where it
goes
we're just one guy causing all this
difference
very epic epoch yes
can i go up here
[ __ ] we got some bears and [ __ ] i ain't
[ __ ] with the bears
you're getting got bear killing skills
yet we're working on those
very soon
oh we got a bird toady's on
whoa look at this
[ __ ] yeah
oh we found a hot spring thank you bird
thank you kindly
let's have a little uh meditation
what do you want to reflect on my
favorite food
or a lover's touch rub one out
or not
we get more hell sweet tori
is burned in japanese yeah that's why i
said it yeah
now i feel like a weeb thank you for
asking
cool why does jurgen knot jump in
can a mane
can a man not share a hot spring with
his horse
do you guys ever meditate what do you
meditate on if you meditate lovers touch
uh upgrade standoffs and assassin skills
double points
okay thank you
observe manga leader before you kill
them for double points
for unlocking the next test okay cool
thank you
golden summit shrine
nice thank you very much epic stuff for
you
nice nice nice nice
big peepee
chinchin okay
[Music]
at least i don't think i've gotten any
i tried to do it before
oh okay we have some charms thank you uh
seven point five percent of healing
when helpful in healing fifty percent
increase to regain
resolve gains i'm going for the gains
man
all right that's all the charms we have
now
follow the game
all right our journey ends here again i
think it's a little too slim for your
fat ass
sorry
he's got to do that jump before he goes
on him it's so funny
can i crawl through here
wow
that's a good angle that's better
what
what that's so cool
so much you could do
so wait this is just like a photo op
[Music]
place
wait sucker punch are the ones i made
infamous
no way
i love the infamous series that was a
good game
am i died i think uh
i think i may have dead [ __ ]
why did i jump there i guess we'll have
to find another way around
i see a tree i yank it
i see a treat flower gotta have it
do do
nicey
papa frankie
am i supposed to be here we can climb
here
you should
so it's so dark i can't really see that
well it's hard to really tell where i'm
supposed to go there we go
let's have the lights on me
this is gonna be an epic view oh god i
almost died jesus
oh my god this is gonna be nightmares
nice
bet jurgen wish you could come simp
let's honor the shrine
nice
charm of kami of the sun nice
sounds cool
uh equip it
excuse me
excuse me did i not
am i crazy
did i not get it what am i doing wrong
am i crazy is it this one
let's just equip that
equip golden major slot so it changes
which slot i put it in
there we go okay
understand okay
there's my main my main my main [ __ ]
alright so the real reason we did this
is because we're walking here so let's
just go there
such a cool game
cool immersive
like i don't usually i hate exploring in
games
[Music]
[ __ ] i fell for his uh little fakeru
these guys are tough let me change
stains
it's not going great let's kill this guy
[Music]
nice
yes
okay close call end suffering goodbye
easy easy don't ever come near me
what their stains motherflipping water
stains
[ __ ] got no change
that was a tough guy i want that armor
mongolians cheating and [ __ ] oh another
bird
let's do get that thank you
it's easy to get distracted use kunai on
bigger guys
keep forgetting i have it thank you i'll
do it next time haven't used the smoke
bombs either
remind me next time and i'll use it
do do are you okay there bird thank you
another hot spring what do you guys want
to meditate on
[Music]
what do you guys ladie masako masako
i just want to clear my mind i don't
want to think about any
any girls any problem
just empty my mind
i feel better
i think the favorite thing for me with
meditating is
it puts you in the moment
when you're always doing stuff
um especially nowadays it's so easy to
get distracted you just go on your phone
or you just
watch someone's live stream you just
click click click there's a click away
to always get distracted but
take some time and meditate because it
really helps
changing your uh mindset of
it breaks you away from that cycle of
constant distraction and it puts you in
the moment
i recommend that's right
why did i call jurgen here clearly he
can't go
how the hell did he even get up here
because once you're put in the moment
you actually enjoy things differently
in a better way healthier way
the idea of just me uh being distracted
my entire life and
not enjoying the moment to me it's a
very terrifying
thing i would never want to do that
you can you can live a life where you're
just comfortable
with distracting yourself they are and
then your whole life flashes by
without any ever doing any reflection
not epic
i think that's why i hate these uh
youtube channels that uh
i don't hate the person but i hate the
idea that they send out uh
don't mean to call it i'll tell you
after this
let's kill these [ __ ] [ __ ]
that took so much damage i'm so dead
oh he did that attack
oh he used any friends
they did you dirty man
[Music]
nice that's one more right
poor archers nice
what was i talking about
uh distractions can you make a clip of
that
oh put minecraft music on it
all right we're almost there might as
well walk
uh these channels that are focused on
maximizing your uh
productivity which i i think is there's
something good in
a middle ground there but when you see
these channels that are like i don't
sleep i sleep four hours
i have every minute of my day scheduled
out
i am so productive look at all these
things i do in a day from eight to nine
i do this and then from nine to ten i do
this and then
from 10 to 11 i do this and then i do
this and then i do this and then i do
this and then i meditate for 10 minutes
uh
i can't even explain why i hate it so
much i think because people
it's fun to watch in a way it's engaging
so you kind of get swept into it
but in reality i would hate to live a
life like that
i think it's selling this idea that
you're
you're gonna be happy if you're really
productive or something like that
you're just distracting yourself
the husband
speak with hina okay
what's up hina love hina anyone read
that [ __ ] love love you know
[Music]
please try the mystic quest on the golan
temple okay let's do that later
but now we're doing this
all right back to talking to him masako
this isn't
okay we got some supplies it was worth
it
love hina is old school dude i owned
every single volume of that manga
foreign it's like yeah
with instagram they live in a fantasy
world
it's like a social currency
that makes everyone feel like [ __ ]
oh
just like the odyssey
[Music]
are we gonna chill here [ __ ] yeah
laying on my dirty laundry so i've left
to play the flute
[ __ ] yeah
[Music]
how can you not love this game you play
flute
[Music]
guess we should hurry
where's the entrance here oh oh
oh we just had to play the flute
i don't see any [ __ ] trails
do you
imagine if you could whip out a
tambourine yeah
yeah i love how they just turn up the
saturation in this game
colors
we lost the trail
they went in here no
why does the trails trail off ap
it's fine since 2010. i'm from the 90s
love hina was fun hell yeah this game is
gorgeous floor again thank you
so pretty yeah
uh so
return to the assassins tracks
well i'm sorry track the assassin they
made a jump
[Music]
all right let's pick up the pace
hell yeah
[Music]
[ __ ]
let's make sure i don't [ __ ] up the
[Music]
stand-up
nailed
[Music]
nice
i swear i dodged
[Music]
nice combat is so rewarding once you get
a hang of it
how you doing here missed the guy
apparently
[Music]
nice he had arrows oh there's more
never mind
oh we gotta connect
[Music]
any last words
brother sadao the headman of kuta
farmstead
it details the supply routes hachi
travel
okay
[Music]
back to camp
did we get almost god damn it's so
little
charm of dual destruction offense charm
we got a charm [ __ ]
can we upgrade any nope
five percent chance double damage yeah
let's go to that
and we got some silk yes
yes
whoa [ __ ] do you go all across this
no
so what was the mystic or mythic quest
was it this one
we can only track one of them
what do you guys want to do continue on
this quest or
go on this one legend of tadayori
swipe right after a battle or a kill
oh of course
what charity are we supporting this
month thanks for joining me today
thank you for uh don't know um i haven't
decided yet
any suggestions
all right it's pretty far
like that's a long way to go
we can do it
we just gotta stay on track not get
distracted
so beautiful i'm already distracted
god damn
don't think so
it'd be funny if they just got scared
and ran away
big mistake
nice nice
cool
[Music]
so we did upgrade something there
yeah we can use another technique
can we upgrade our stands yes
hold and then tap
torrent of rapid strikes
cool
maybe you should do that
getting a hang of it yeah
i think i missed something there
whatever
oh god there's so many i mean i can't
stop for everyone
we're never gonna get there otherwise
as much as i like killing mongols no
offense mongols if you're listening
all right we traveled 600 meters 900 to
go
whoa
what a jump
cute
you can do a mystic quest in the golden
temple
it's closer oh for [ __ ] sake well now
we already came this far
might as well commit to it i'm a sword
fight you irl whoever wins has the
bigger pp
challenge me kyle king accepted
i'll cut off your pp if it's bigger snip
snip snip
i want to get heavenly strike then [ __ ]
i did this all wrong why don't you tell
me before
it's all right we're riding with the
wind
it's only 300 meter away
you can do this and then do it after
here it is
you're gonna [ __ ] with the
is this an enemy base
i think it is
[Music]
nice hopefully it is an enemy base
i don't have any more arrows
[ __ ] how do i get in now oh i made a bee
goopsie
[Music]
are you serious
through the river maybe yeah
[Music]
nice
yes
[Music]
so good i love the camera
i need to get into using the canize and
black bombs and [ __ ]
let's just go for him
so down
love it
[Music]
hey you're safe don't worry hey you're
safe with me
don't run
kill the innocent what the [ __ ] is wrong
with you
i'm liberating people they're not
enemies are you serious
no they're enemies
oh god what have i done
oh god am i the monster oh god did i
just
no oh
uh
uh what did i no
now they're bad look there's a bird here
show me bird
show me i'm a good person tell them
i didn't do nothing where's the bird
genocide route oh god what have i done
[Music]
where's the bird i saw the shadow there
you are
show me little bird
well i can't go there
whoopsie kill all the innocents whoopsie
oh sweet
nice
[Music]
bamboo result what does that do guess i
have to make an apology video again
god damn it sorry what does the bamboo
result do
i like how i judge you guys for saying
kill the innocents
oops fine musician
let's not tell him about his home found
him
love from florida thank you benny bear
for calling me a sim epic hey guys you
you don't live in the village nearby
right because uh
don't go there
what are we playing
[Music]
mythic
do you ever feel sad irl when you make
an embassy sad or upset in the game or
am i just a beta i don't know how to
answer that yeah
so now we're going to travel north again
fine
it's an archer armor though we don't
really need it but i kind of want to do
it anyway
uh i've gotten upset if i make the wrong
choice in games yeah for sure
if i'm really invested in it yes
this is the way
especially uh what's it called tokidoki
literature club
but yeah also you're a beta mongol
territory
here we go
whoops
i'm not killing innocents they came
right at me you saw that they came at me
they attacked me you know
[Music]
let's go for the archers guys
did you see that dodge
[ __ ]
[Music]
nice it worked the new technique
sweet and suffering
mr baldi
yes
or nearby pacifist round can you do that
in this game that'd be funny
doubt it
you just meditate the enemies away
enemies
[Music]
keep forgetting kunai all right let's
[ __ ] fell for his little trick
[Music]
this is around the last bit
let's not forget the most important part
search for violet flowers
help me there they are
we found them see if they lead somewhere
it must be down here
nope
golden hour
english how i speak it help me
jesus got a painting
so we're looking for the shrine yeah
find the location shown on the map
so it's the south of it on the other
side of the road
let's find the road and then we can
navigate
there's the road now
yeah so there's more growing on this
side
am i going wrong way or right way
it makes sense for a shrine to be up
there no yeah there's something there
climb climb climb climb climb hmm
but there should have been flowers as
well oh no
this is not right is it
what's happening [ __ ] i don't kill
innocents don't worry
oh that's a river so it's the other way
great
how we doing here folks don't have time
to chit chat
can you jump here here again come on
[ __ ] yeah
nice landing
that's my boy that's my boy right there
so it's on the other side of it
that doesn't represent the map well
is that enemies [ __ ]
[Music]
you guys are weak
yes
i'm [ __ ] blind
[Music]
is there one more no that's it all right
we got a box
30 supplies [ __ ] yeah
oh my god there's so many people here
[ __ ]
okay they look strong
nice
oh they got a little scared by that
that's funny
what is happening
[Music]
[ __ ] i'm almost dead
mike's happening
he's so strong
i died
[Music]
oh he has a shield
[ __ ]
god damn mongolians too strong
i didn't see his shield he has a tiny
shield
fine doesn't matter
so the other side don't die die die die
well i did one of those things all right
let's get up
[Music]
they're a lot easier
here we go see if there's a river down
here
tactical respawn honestly yeah
is it this way
there's no [ __ ] river
this doesn't seem right at all i don't
know why you guys told me to go this way
yeah this is definitely the wrong way
do you guys know what you're talking
about i don't know why i listen to you
guys sometimes
yes
i think this is further back
ah shitty mongolians
ain't got time for mongolians
[Music]
so
which one find the location shown on the
map
okay let's actually look on that
this does not look like the right side
this looks more like it right no
there should be a lantern thing oh there
is isn't it
and then there's a house so there should
be a house
sorry thank you i would see
uh why am i struggling so much on this
you guys confused me there it is okay
there's the line
and there's woods and
nailed it
go north but that's where i went and
people said it was wrong
it's the opposite side of the mountain
that's the most brain
big thing i've ever heard
i got upgrade available i'll do that in
a sec but now or right now
they only grow on one side it can only
be that we go
all right let's just go here then
so apparently there's something here
i heard a bird
oh there it is
right
and there's a bird let's follow the bird
[Music]
seems worth it
this is an enemy base how do we know
it is
thank you bird this is not what i was
looking for
oops
yeah well that's easy
four really
for
i did not hit a wrong button
there we go
[Music]
i mean kind of busy right now
kind of in the middle of something
oh yeah i forgot there's a bit delay i
need to add for that hold up
no should be fine actually is it
right no that's a big delay hold up
one second brush
right right
it's a lot of delay
sorry guys three uh 400
900 100.
let's try this this is better right
right yeah that looks better
right
playstation hard at work
dude if this game has soup you better
believe
you better believe i'm gonna drink the
[ __ ] out of that [ __ ] do you eat super
do you drink soup this is the real
question
[Music]
toscata
so this is where the mountain was that's
where that was so it should be around
here
i've gone way too far right
[Music]
i ain't got time for the mongols
[ __ ] mongols
we're looking for the shrine must be up
here right
it's too sheer to climb must be another
way
well well well what do we got here boys
wait here jurgen smergen yes we found it
finally nice
how nice of him to leave a little map
i knew i was going to make that no
problem
how did they find this place impossible
[ __ ] yeah i would love a fight here like
a boss battle
that'd be sick
yumi
well well well let's check inside
give me the armor
i forgot i have upgrades but then again
i probably shouldn't upgrade my armor if
i'm about to get on better armor
yeah let's wait
investigate the cemetery again
yes yes yes yes yes yes
nice
[ __ ] is gonna get the win stone stance
yes yes
what the [ __ ] she's strong
[ __ ] she attacked the light
ow she poked me she poke
poke was i in water stance
ah big mistake
i mean stone stains
[Music]
nice
easy that was easy
i like how we nearly kill each other
oh god that's so far which way oh god
itself
oh god what have i done embarking on
this quest
all right
god i love the anime vibes
that's like let's just go here and pick
up the armor
whoops shortcut
tactical shortcut
yeah again you're against merging
i love you
so much my oregon
you're the best you're my
one and only hast
what's happening here boys what's
i ain't got time i'm getting armor
that jump is what i'm talking about
thank you
all right we're going as far as we did
in the beginning
i can't fast travel there i haven't
discovered it yet
should we take a break from the quest
and and maybe wait until
later and go back here
yeah let's let's do that i didn't
realize how long that would be
i'm sure we're gonna go south again
we got some upgrades available
m we can upgrade this
that's what they were telling me [ __ ]
off i don't want that upgraded
i'm a samurai
oh there's linden yoink
well god damn all right so everyone that
said heavenly strike
where is it doko defroco
find the musician in komatsu
[Music]
where's kumatsu
where bish where
yeah bow
we can fast travel there anyway if we
want to finish the armor quest
stop crying
i missed some linen in there assistant
[Music]
you got a present for me
two gifts available
i assume this is the golden temple
i'm lost i don't know what to do
are you telling me we can't fast track
fast travel
no no no no
oh god what have i done
what have i done
there's komatsu
found it
wait i can fast travel
oh i can
okay nice okay well [ __ ] it armor
i'm sorry guys we're doing armor now
[ __ ] you
[ __ ] you can't tell me nothing
apparently we're almost done with the
armor so we might as well finish i don't
know how long these things are
i can't read the future it's thunder
yes
i'm watching uh i think i said it last
time i'm watching science gate every
morning
i love it it's so good
it's a it's an anime where this crazy
scientist discovers a time machine where
you can text
people in the past send text messages
it's pretty cool recommended
hey pits you should watch patlabor the
movie too i think we like the
philosophical political commentary on
post world war two so-called peace and
how it comes at the cost of the nation's
peace
yeah that sounds interesting i'll check
it out
thank you
i usually find characters like that so
annoying but she's so sweet
i literally had a whole rant yesterday
about it
it's so ingrained in my head now
oh tori's on
there you are
show me
survivor cam
have we not been here
ayo holmes was good
foreign
what is this oh they weren't loading
sakai katana
summoned fears and cards of a dragon
what is that
is it worth buying another sword
is it just vanity gear
yeah it is just vanity stuff
ah it doesn't look cooler does it look
cooler yeah i think it does look cool
so do i have to equip it
there we go
[Music]
nice
are those cannons or is it thunder
it's thunder okay
mongol territory
kind of want to kill them
so how do i observe the leader someone
told me to do that
you're literally getting new armor [ __ ]
i'm so dumb
if it's a very great day i am thank you
hope you guys are as well
remember to enjoy the moment
no one saw that right
okay so that's how you observe the
leader
guess that answers that question
yeah we cheeky with it
dead
sweet
the leader is dead
let's get this game of bread
they'll never find me
uh
[Music]
hey how's it going homies
this is very bad
[Music]
uh guys i have an appointment i just
remembered
[Music]
already
thanks guys oh yeah i have black powder
i can't forget ow
i have low health don't shoot
what's up
nice did it
this place is free
[Music]
i am the one don't weigh a ton don't
need the gun to get respect up on the
street
under the sun the best it's underneath
the blocks of
the family enemies my enemies
hey what's up horsey
i kind of have no idea what we're doing
and i have no problem with it
yeah i'm still on hard mode as you can
tell by
a hardcore
sakai tanto upgrade available
visit a swordsmith to upgrade
right you can go in here
i'm full of kunai
but i don't know why
my brother
uh all right we're almost there why is
this not liberated yet
there we go
i'm gonna get you name it
everybody be like
it's our new um
[Music]
nice we're getting there very nice
let's kill the mongols
fake me out and you die nice
you get so many points for that
let's watch out for the archers
[Music]
what's going on rescuing hostages
the mongols have taken hostages if the
enemy spots you they will start
executing
what
[Music]
he shot you
don't even look yes
oh he died oh [ __ ] oh no [ __ ] i wasn't
looking
god damn it i was so preoccupied by my
shitty move no
[Applause]
[Music]
they can't see me i'm a tree
i meant to do that
[Music]
[Applause]
oh [ __ ] i didn't expect that i'm not
ready for that
[ __ ] i almost died
my god i can't do it for some reason
[ __ ]
damn it sorry guys i do it now
i learned my mistake yes yes yes yes
look at this
perfect this time what we're going to do
we take this guy you see him
bye bye you're in bye bye lane
and then we go this guy
can't see me i'm a tree
then we do this jump like i did last
time calculated
this is all part of the plane
are you serious he died no he didn't
uh i think i'm dead
nope
uh
i don't have time to kill you
[Music]
nice that's how it's done
yes
[Music]
sweet you're rescued
give me armor
it's mine it's mine
where [ __ ] where
armor belongs to the legendary archer we
got it
looks pretty simpin who's shooting
why aren't you blowing up
do that again
[Music]
are they still shooting me
oh my god they shot him
can i push him off
[Music]
and then i died
is he actually not gonna kill me what a
[ __ ] [ __ ]
not epic
the old armor look better yeah for sure
why did we do this
all right no no
no yes
oh [ __ ] oh [ __ ] man
i can slow time
[ __ ] yeah
don't think so buddy
[Applause]
[Music]
don't you dare [ __ ] kill him
where's the last one oh god oh
god
no
ah [ __ ]
[ __ ] how am i canceling
[Music]
where are you going
push him
oh my god they're so annoying
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
is
now
not happening
[Music]
not happening no
that was tough not gonna lie
okay
[Music]
why do i never use the kunai you [ __ ]
idiot
nice nice nice nice nice [ __ ] yeah
that's what i'm talking about best
goddamn player in the world at this game
told you
oh there were arrows and i could have
just collected them
welcome to the brain of pewdiepie dumb
very dumb
all right we did it at least now we
completed something
feels good man all right let's go back
to golden
smolden temple splempal
use arrow that's the reason you have the
armor yeah thank you
i ran out of the arm archer arrows and
then
[Music]
i [ __ ] up okay i [ __ ] up i [ __ ] up
yeah i better feel like shelbert play
this oh cringe
all right let's go there
it's worth upgrading this armor see how
it looks like
how does it look like now can you load
please
playstation be like nah now i can't
too much effort just go for
dude i get a hat dude i got a hat now
i got a hat now
worth it i look like a [ __ ] postman
now
i used to look like a badass samurai
sir that's so far in this playthrough
feels pretty good man
feels pretty nice let's look for the
heavenly sword [ __ ]
oh god he's fine jurgen
just needed to squat
he's fine
yeah we're still on uh miners deaths
actually because uh i
did something so epic that game was like
whoa
you need the more health health uh we
don't have lives in this game but we had
for you thank you
so good
we're doing the postman quest right now
delivering amazon packages to samurais
delivering amazon packages of katanas to
neck beard
wear boots my favorite part of the quest
challenge me don't ever [ __ ] stab my
horse
you [ __ ] triple dead you just
guaranteed yourself a triple deck
forgot i could do that
can't i pick it up yes
do the main quest please cringe
is there anything ever a main question
in real life
don't you all just go where the wind
takes you
what you just calculate your moves
cringey yeah
stand me up [ __ ]
[Music]
what's up with your hair [ __ ]
that's just
how do you like apples
whoa that was cool
you don't [ __ ] with the post man
oh it's something happening over here
that's some dawardo [ __ ]
hey guys
worth it
never underestimate your enemy
may look like postman
but i'm more like post malone man
yeah cause i spit rhymes left and right
yeah
[Music]
where's my man right there you are
postman gotta do what a postman gotta do
i remember in tibia
this all the mmorpg i played there was
this epic postman quest you could do
it was so long but it was so fun i loved
it
this makes me feel like that all right
where's
general where
i don't [ __ ] know
find a musician in komatsu
that's what we're looking for
there you are
no
that's where we're supposed to go for
[ __ ] sake
noises
what's cracking homies your musician
oh my god
is that not in
i can't interact with her
they're full of [ __ ]
i miss the jet pack [ __ ]
so close
the barn wait what is a barn
the [ __ ] is a barn
what is a barn barn
is this the barn
is that a barn
oh my god i don't know what the barn is
that's a barn this is the barn
i already went in [ __ ] ain't nothing
here
this is a barn
is this the barn like what the [ __ ] are
you on about
oh god i'm i'm getting worked up again
oh no it's happening
what the [ __ ] do you want me to do i
can't select the quest
i can't do it [ __ ] it out
you [ __ ] you [ __ ]
i can't track it it says find the
musician
i can't track it
mr backseat gamers anything else select
the quest
brian aj
[ __ ] oh it's happening
i can't select the quest i can't select
the quest
it's there but i can't select the grace
do you understand do you understand
go to the barn tell me to go to the barn
one more [ __ ] time
i didn't change the quest no i did not i
did not change the quiz
[ __ ] you i get this now
not tails quest what's the difference
mate it's there
isn't it
it's undiscovered
quest not a tale all right i guess i'll
go to the quest
options oh wait let's see that is the
tails
[Music]
[ __ ] you know
[ __ ] hell guys the [ __ ] are you
smoking
i'm going there
come out of town
no i'm not
go to the barn you [ __ ]
god damn you guys go to the barn
i'm doing this now all right
can't do that okay i'm doing this now
why can't i do that
can i fast travel there i'm doing this
now
talking out the backseat gaming if you
got a backseat game
at least be right that's all i ask
i appreciate people helping but man if
you don't know what you're talking about
understand go to the barn all right i'll
go to the barn this is the new soup
apparently
where's this [ __ ] sim
not the best place for jurgen
we can climb up right what's faster
probably running around
[Applause]
well all the way down i ain't doing that
i wasn't even supposed to go to the
[ __ ] barn
jesus christ oh my god
let me just play the game okay
let me just play
i'm doing the main quest now because i
got
spent two hours getting a goddamn
postman outfit
[Applause]
sensei i got the armor
i'm just like you now
sensei and student
to unlock the heavenly strike go to the
golan temple
to a stranger to unlock the quest great
[Music]
thank you
a large building on a farm animal hey i
went inside it
didn't i two times
oh my god i'm done you guys
it's over
what the [ __ ] how do you get here cheat
nobody is using hacks
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yeah
i'm on the flippin postman
with my little post head
it was totally worth it
[Music]
not the dogs
like life
look away look away
[Music]
excuse me you were supposed to die
i guess the armor is pretty good it is
pretty good
that was cool
[Laughter]
[Applause]
um
uh
there's echo how
i'll turn it off later i'm uh i've been
in the livestream in 10 minutes probably
so
[Music]
this is a tough one but i can do it
no way they saw me i'm invisible
[ __ ] i didn't observe them
[Music]
[ __ ]
i love the archer thing it was actually
worth it it's so cool
let's chat bro
yo bro there's echo in the game really
all right i'll turn it down
i don't know why the game got louder all
of a sudden
well you said that before and then it
didn't have
[Music]
foreign
sweet what should we upgrade
we can upgrade our range even further
throw
so this this a passive sword the other
one
no this is still the same charms
hat for life bro
[Music]
i need to do the heavenly strike i guess
i will do it
don't worry
that seems worth it
the past never passes
because i got a lot of assets that i
keep them
in my asses
i play games on my asus
sick freestyle yeah
okay
[Music]
oh look there's a barn here guys guys
there's a barn here
holy crap dude what is a barn a lot
gourd
a lot gourd wow
thanks guys thank you
i just want to shoot people
[Music]
um
five minutes left guys the past never
perishes
i should end it here marcia has been
cleaning i need to help her out
i don't wanna do to do today
save the game cause we done
i love playing this game guys thank you
for being here
very fun
i'll see you guys in the
day after tomorrow probably
[Music]
but thanks for being here very epic
hope you had fun members should have
already seen today's video but i'm about
to publish it now
and uh see you guys soon
see you in the barn i'll hit you up in
the bar now okay
let's just chill we'll have some soup in
the barn
does that sound good deal
all right cool i'll meet you guys there
the barn yeah
was it the barn should i go in the barn
we're going the barn
just making sure i understand okay cool
all right bye
bye bye bye