what's up what's up [ __ ]
what's up
i'm not late i've been playing 10
minutes what are you talking about
let's just jump into it
i go from recording video boom i go live
i'm an entertainment machine god damn it
you can't stop me let's go
we don't intro [ __ ] it's all flowing and
[ __ ]
hell yeah thanks for being here guys
who's ready for some more
ghost of tishima hell
yeah i am i love this game
i got about two hours maybe a little bit
more
i'm hoping two hours and 30. we'll see
i got [ __ ] i'm a busy man
yeah how's everything does it look good
i
forgot my microphone so i borrowed this
from jack
that's why part of the reason why i'm
late
lifesaver jack appreciate it thank you
postman journey continues
let's go notice
uh the gameplay needs to be lower higher
you guys tell me and then
jack gave me this microphone
i feel like he's sending me mixed
signals
how am i supposed to keep this in front
of me huh
i can't do it though it's not mine it's
not mine i'm not gonna do it
i want to wait jack's here
i don't see him
[Music]
we
so for those you who missed last live
stream we seriously
know
half the live stream going for this
armor i'm like a mythic armor that's so
cool
i almost gave up on is there one more
that i didn't see oh there's two more
murano
uh and then
it is
that can
the game sound is way louder than you
[ __ ] off
how about this
all right we're going through the
coastal road delivering amazon
come on jurgen smergen
is it better now or is it not
let's go where is wind
maybe we shouldn't take your again i
kind of want to just jump down
assassin's creed style although he has
his horse oh wait
i want to get some arrows
me the arrows
headband optimism in face of adversity
is the samurai spirit
oh dude i need a headband
oh
[ __ ] man
how's this
it's jack's microphone man uh
disappointed
i put on 420 db if that doesn't work i
don't know what to tell you
all right now we get jurgen
young [ __ ] yeah do you think he jumped
down as well
should we jump in the water [ __ ] it
let's do it
what's up i said what's up
which one is bao
is it better now cool epic
we have a long way to go apparently
jesus
it's fine i did that on purpose it's an
old samurai move
happens all the time all right yoga come
on
ain't got time we're not spending two
hours getting a shitty armor this time
bamboo though i will get you
go mourinho that was a cool quest though
someone saw me can i not challenge
them
[Music]
bring it [ __ ] i don't remember how you
play every time i take a break it's like
take me a while to get into it again
oh they killed the horses
[Music]
[Applause]
it's still so nice
i got delay
well well well it's one of those days
where nothing [ __ ] works is it
first of all let me turn this down
okay
and suffering now you keep suffering my
dude
not my job
beer looks good today thank you ellie
thank you
no one ever says that thank you
oh my god you made my day ali
i am ruthless when necessary
uh this looks dangerous
all right let's use the arrow this time
and i'll show the armor for those so you
didn't see it last night
it's [ __ ] cool here we go
[Music]
damn so pretty
oh we got more people [ __ ] i didn't see
them they didn't see me it's all good
no i wanted to get him [ __ ]
oh come on that hit him
how am i out of battle
[ __ ] i am uh let's see if i remember
i don't want to throw the can i how do i
switch there we go
oh [ __ ]
whoa
cool probably should have saved those
in retrospect but you know oh there's
ours here
and they're dead now great
oh we got people shoot him in the knee
[ __ ] your knees bro
no that's his horse all right
easy i'm the best guy
of the world
not a problem i keep forgetting to
observe
[ __ ] i didn't even know he was there
gotta look at him
because i'm another flipping post
[Music]
i'm sorry
was that it that was so easy
we need to play on hardcore mode this
game too easy man
zero def run by the way in case you're
new in the live streams
thanks for all the members god damn a
lot of you appreciate you
now you get you get one more point if
you observe them before mr cassie smith
you're
wrong don't waste my time ever again
that's a warning cassie smith
so yeah i think next we gotta find the
barn
i'm looking for the barn there's like a
secret in the barn
100 confirmed all right so what's next
we could check
out this area or we can go back to way
of the bow
it makes sense to do that but let's
check out this area since we're here
maybe kill some mongols
that hat the hat definitely makes the
fit
i'm fashioned as [ __ ] dude everyone else
oh mongol territory jurgen you better
stay back this is dangerous
defeat the mongols assassinate the
enemies from above without being seen so
if i can't kill three enemies without
being seen i get extra
you didn't see me come on you didn't see
me but here i am
could i just do a quick meme so there's
two people here
[Music]
stop it stop it
he makes samurai amazon delivery amen
yeah that was cool i like that oh here
you are
[ __ ] that was the leader again i'm too
good at killing i can't help it guys
too strong oh we got technique points
sweet
i told you bro
i'm the best in the world at this game
sure i was [ __ ] at the start
but once i get started unstoppable dude
i just watched my playthrough of dark
souls
the dlc beat the hardest game boss of
the game
i didn't even realize that's how good i
am once i get good
you don't understand pro game
what their i mean water stains stone
stains
are we done here gotta get my crickets
bro
nailed it all right let's go back to the
quest
mr yoshi smoshy son that's not his name
sending big peepee all the way from yoku
sakka say hello to the voice
of the uss blue rodge what's up uss blue
rodge boyz
was good are you still on hard mode
yes yes yes yes
i think i am
i don't know where you see it all right
uh gain moderate resolve by using a
parry
i can save for mythic harness the power
of guiding wind
so they they give they let me go to
specific locations
is that good
i feel like i should upgrade my stances
i always forget i have that move what
are these then deliver three piercing
strikes
increase stagger against swordman
drown your foe with flood of rapid
strikes
what their surging strike that's kind of
cool
save up for the maybe i should say but
i feel like i'm strong enough right now
and i i'd hate to get stuck
later because i'm not good enough for
which won't happen obviously
but yeah i agree let's say but
you're getting where the [ __ ] are you i
don't have time to play around
there's ain't no game we gotta make a
lot of progress today
i ain't got time
no more postman quests no more looking
for barns
jump jurgen ah come on you're again
you gotta work on your knees my dude
yoga you your knees should be like the
guys
that reflected every single arrow
rolling is for cowards we ain't playing
dark souls
wait this guy's not here
all right you're again i'm off
this is kind of annoying why can't i
just teleport to his base
i have to walk every time
i was born to do this [ __ ]
you're gonna chill at the floor he's a
true floor again
could you place your house somewhere
else mister bolts and then
the way of the boat continues epic
i got him
[ __ ] french
[Music]
nice
oh what's good
not even close my dude
ease me yeah
use the kunai
i keep forgetting so it's i don't think
i've used the kunai a single time
i keep forgetting all right so there's
kunai there so i use it with
r1 is that it oh cool
okay i'll incorporate it
so funny just jump around being like a
[ __ ] badass
gameplay they nailed it dude
especially when you're this good
uh we'll defeat tomorrow
should we get our horses
up
looking for a barn and our mating call
is
that's i think that's all you need to
know
whoa look at that i want to go there
[Music]
right left
right it's fine it's good enough
[Music]
or is it my lips that are not synced
thank you
is it better now
pee pee pee pee
pee pee poopoo it good
you're fine i'll take your word for it i
don't want to spend time on this i just
want to play man
i mean last of us yeah i should
hey would you say this is the most
graphically beautiful game ever
made i don't know ever but it's
it's very nice
those barrels should do some damage
and we have the hornet this is where i
messed up the first time
they were like going through all these
things and i just like you know what
they
did and it was painful
shoot the half bow ignites enemies cloth
and dry
grass
are they shooting us oh i see them now
he's crazy i ain't going there
[Music]
sorry bro
oh he burns the grass
[Music]
they can do that too though
i don't see it
here
any more hours
[Music]
oh this is fun it's about spraying them
ah bro you walked in front of me
don't even try it bro don't try it
don't shoot are there flaming arrows
[Music]
nice i love this quiet
oh my god oh my god it's not happening
[Music]
[ __ ] shoot him
nice you don't [ __ ] with the postman
i wish there was a way to soon like [ __ ]
can't barely see them
oh i got it let's do this
that was it damn it i wanted more it was
fun
zero devs hard more baby
no problem thank you easiest game i've
ever played
kyotana
oh i'm sorry did i just beat everyone
tie it you see what happens
am i the one with the postman hat
[Music]
foreign
the game just tip talk to anyone you can
get them
yeah i want to do a heavenly sword after
i do this one everyone's telling me to
do it so i'll do it after
[Music]
now the pressure is on it to not die if
there's a [ __ ] bot that took
it
here
we'll get that b hey hey felix thank you
for awesome streams
you mean the world to me i'm going
through a very hard time right now i'm
sorry to hear that and you and the bros
are always there thanks for everything
flowing again for life vlogging for
election now thank you your good man
puts
eyes wind you you youtube sure yeah
hell yeah i'm sitting on a rock what's
up guys
storming falcon half bow die
we can re-dye our bow but it looks like
pewdiepie bow i will never change it
who it is
we're gonna ride
foreign rumored location
yoshihiko um
i wanna it's so easy to get sidetracked
in this game
kind of want to stay on point so wait we
finished his quest
was that nine out of nine well i'd be
damn i don't see his face
huh all right then i'll do what i said
i'll do which is
do the heavenly sword one
oh my bad i named the live stream too
but it's three
i got a headband i don't want a headband
i have a hat
yes riding hiking is my favorite
minigame in this no way that's so cool
okay so me
dissecting your mumbo jumbo i'm supposed
to speak to someone here
that will tell me about the heavenly
sword strike or whatever it's called
then we can initiate that quest what's
up baby
rumored location at it sweet
so it should be in our journal now
mythic tales heavenly strike yes
track it done can we fast travel
anywhere
it's here can we fast travel here come
out to forge
what about here no yeah okay nice
finally we found it god damn
this mission is great yeah i really like
the other mythic one
it was cool
it's a cool idea to separate like
abilities and
uh stuff like that a side quest
all right let's deliver the amazons
cringe
kind of hungry i kind of want to get
something to eat
can i do that can i get a fruit or
something am i allowed to leave the
screen guys
promise me you won't go anywhere
i need the fruit man's gotta eat you
know
no okay sorry i'll stay here my bad
my bad cool to see you enjoying the game
hell yeah
i mean sweating in swedish good name
oh we got a bird let's follow you
where the [ __ ] that now there you are
what he's on
show me
i don't want to have an aneurysm like
last live stream
oh this is where we need to do the quest
that's okay
what a pimp what are you doing here
yes
i love them let me just get a snack then
i can eat and watch it
[Music]
all right let's watch it thanks
for watching
foreign
wow
let me show you guys something have you
guys read the
book of five rings
is this book i talked about it before on
the channel it's written by an old
samurai
how cool is that by the way uh
it's super interesting let's see if we
can show it
it's very short but i really recommend
it and there's strategy in it that
strategy of the samurai yeah musashi
can you guys see this
so i have the the ground book the water
book the fire book the win book
let's see if i remember son
oh yeah that was about school and stuff
like that i remember
let's do the fire book no
[ __ ] off i own the book
it is difficult to move strong things by
pushing directly
so you should injure the corners
you must study this yeah he always says
that here so you must research it deeply
he always that's it's so funny this
happens when you injure the corner of
his body
and this weakens him it is important to
know how to do this
so you must research it deeply
[Music]
some something something something
simultaneously with flourishing the long
sword
we shout during the fight to get into
rhythm research this
deeply you must understand this
what is meant by mingling it's a spirit
of advancing and becoming engaged with
the enemy
and not withdrawing even one step you
must understand this
it is necessary to consider how to renew
also applies in large-scale strategy
research this diligently
oh i gotta reread it so fun
anyway back to the game
if you've never read a book in a long
time and you're genuinely interested and
interested it's a really fun one to just
dive into
musashi's martial arts nitenichi
nitanichi
is still taught in dojo no way
how old is the book i should say in the
beginning right
in 1573.
no way that's oda
naga
it's just so cool to get these this is
why i love literature
no other medium can trans
transport you in time like them
the way of the sword is the moral
teaching of the samurai
fostered by the confucianist philosophy
we shape the tokugawa system
together with the native shinto religion
of japan
from the kamakura period the muromachi
period the wars
court of japan encouraged the austere
zen study among the samurai and zen went
hand in hand with the arts of war
in zen there are no elaboration it aims
directly at the true nature of things
there's no ceremonies no teaching the
prize of zen is essentially personal
makes sense are you guys bored
you don't think it's interesting should
we just read your book instead
i'm gonna
me
i said this before but i would love to
do a short story reading for our live
stream
have some music set the mood discuss it
afterwards could be fun
i'm not walking the right way
i have not been studying diligently
i did not research it deeply
he's under the bridge it's a troll under
the bridge
foreign
guess i followed the woman
we're just doing out here doing squats
funny hat it's not a funny hat it's cool
hat take that back
dominic
what why am i doing it again
this is the way
[Music]
yeah i was thinking we could start with
a horror story
because that's simple and anyone could
get into it and then i would love to do
borjes
at some point i love his short stories
but there might be a bit tough to start
with seasons
deeply nice
[Music]
it looks like a communist hand oh great
you really thank you
yeah i don't fall for your trick grandpa
anyone else
[Music]
is that all you got zero deaths count
them for me boys
[ __ ] i thought i could do it yes i could
nice
thank you for waiting bro
my dude
[ __ ] almost died
whoa that's what i'm talking about
[Music]
that was close i really don't want to
die now
supplies [ __ ]
more surprised research the watchtower
all right
wait
there we go
hey someone asked the bond how many
deaths i have
do it i dare you oh my god here it is
no i meant to do all of this
hello thank you for being awesome hope
you're doing well please stay safe while
the worst night is happening everyone's
around the world keep smiling you
awesome human thank you megan very nice
appreciate you we must research
that woman
[Music]
foreign
look for white leaf tree
we must research this white leaf tree
thiefy
have you ever tried a martial art i feel
like you would really enjoy something
like jiu jitsu
yeah maybe i should maybe i will
where do i start
how does one study deeply
you know what i mean
it must be up here
stay
oh
am i blind again
you're so close
i'm blind i'm blind oh no
follow your heart yes
i will follow my heart deeply
oh we found a hot spring i'll take it
what is it called when they uh study the
sword
the martial art something on b i forgot
or is it i already discovered this
supposed yeah we just need to find
another route
google maps check my google maps
with my heart
we probably just need to go around it
whoa we must study it more deeply
there was something left of the fire
really
let's just try walking around it for now
nope that does not work
no not bushy though
kendo that's right sorry my bad i don't
know i thought it was
okay let's just
if we had a grappling hook you know what
i mean
here we go
i'm blind basically i didn't follow my
heart and this happened
can i hang on there only one way to find
out
followed my heart i did reward them
i was this is the way
cool
yes thank you
easy
with superior swedish strength immense
height
and enormous pp energy you would be
perfect for brazilian jiu jitsu
train this deeply
all right guess jiu-jitsu it is
[Music]
nice gorgeous
charm of kagutsuchi
hell yeah so we can apply that a golden
one
deal bonus damage while at 50 health or
less that's kind of cool
try that
yes
yes yes yes yes
we found it
heavenly strike will be mine
it will happen
whoa
there it is
so beautiful
yes
which one do i click to take the shot
respond they said
whoa
right d-pad
no it isn't do i take the shot
you just made me redo everything
why there's so many
that's it
[Music]
i don't want all the particles
there it is no
no there we go
done sorry for wasting time
remember when i said we're not wasting
time today
[Music]
come on it's part of the game it's part
of the fun
it's what i was saying telling you guys
before the last live stream you gotta
enjoy the moment
oh my god
if you just focus on doing one task
after that another that's my way of
living
that's not my kind of life
i like how they incorporate in the game
because it totally fits with the samurai
philosophy at least i like to think so
let's follow the bird
there's something happening but i'm
following the bird god damn
it oh we got a hike here
we can ride a a hiker
nice dude
all right how does this work
reflect on fear yes
so usually japanese haiku always
are have some sort of base on on the
season
and autumn leaves falls
are birds
[Music]
singing and ultimately falls
a bird
flies in the sky
i want to die now
that's a haiku
quick question could we see my act and
edgar after the stream
um sorry i know
[Music]
swifting shadows back and forth oh i see
so we're doing the haiku now i didn't
realize
cloaked in beth's armor hidden from all
sides
guided by the night by night's glow
dude i love that
that's so fun
we got a headband
that is such a great thing that they
added that
because that's what i was saying before
being samurai is more than just killing
it's about the softness as well
soft and strong that's what i aspire to
be all right let's rescue the [ __ ]
hot stage
enough for this
[Music]
how you doing there next to the wall
buddy
don't think so [ __ ]
huh
[Music]
uh
oops gotta be careful
i did it nice
[Music]
that was pretty good count them for me
boys
count me the depths of course i'm
winning dad of course
i just wrote a god damn haiku and then i
killed people
we can upgrade our attire now sweet
we can be
upgrade our postman delivery armor why
can't i find the entrance
hello you're free
kids you are playing way better than the
other day
yeah i told you i'm a slow learner
fool
playing this game like full immersed way
it's like
playing gta and follow traffic rules
this is the way
gonna get a boss battle soon
this part is awesome
nice look forward
don't break up the duel oh god now
you're putting pressure on me man
i'm doing my best
cute
oh [ __ ] i hit his helmet
give me arrows keep forgetting the
[ __ ] canine
whoa
here we are look forward to this
damn that's cool
search
i assume the flowers are
yeah it must be up there this is so
extra i love it
don't ever ever take me to
tell me to take off the hat
oh god that's a lot of them
that is not what i meant to do
i'm out [ __ ] this
they're like where the [ __ ] did he go oh
there he is
ah no
i could die [ __ ]
[ __ ]
no damn it
i shouldn't have done that
what i ruined everything by
i was gonna assassinate and then i just
sliced him
it doesn't count that does not count
everyone knows that does not count
come on uh what a ball
buster come on man
there we go that's what i wanted to do
[Music]
a little easier this way
don't you say i ain't changing armor
shut up
i ain't doing nothing i ain't doing
nothing
whoa what just happened
[Music]
and that's another package
the bot better not update the bot better
not
update because that didn't count
here comes the door
change armor man shut up
foreign
so is he gonna use a heavenly strike
i love this so much
this game is [ __ ] awesome lightning
just [ __ ] struck behind it
i'm wearing a post hand
click
good start
i'm fine
[ __ ]
okay i may have died i may be dead
ow i'm fine we didn't know we don't know
for sure if i died there actually
how did he hit me there
yeah i can do it
because i actually want to change armor
it's a part of the plane
you can change armor while fighting oh
okay
no i was so close
didn't teach me good enough damn it was
so close there
i totally had it
[ __ ] it wasn't raining
he's not even hard i know i can do it
easy
i say that
come on
i think i'm trying to fast lock him and
that's still screwing me over
i bought that i swear
[Music]
i'm just studying it's tactical dying
you guys wouldn't understand it
uh don't ask the boss stop asking about
how many dash stop it
it's not even hard
that's how you do it
how am i getting worse
i parried it i did it
don't hurt me i'm swedish i'm swedish
postman ikea oh
uh sex death shut up
i gotta research more deeply
bring it
i was trying different things there uh
my pc reputation is on the line how many
times have you taken the ppgi
don't worry about it oh the game is
patronizing me [ __ ] off
shut up game don't ever patronize me i
haven't died a single time
i keep falling
i'm fine i did about ten times
you can't die if you don't give up don't
ever patronize me game
i know what i'm doing
heavenly strike will be mine come on
i was so close the second time and now i
suck
life attack will counter everyone you
want aggressive to stagger him yeah i
keep forgetting that
come on
shut up shut up shut up
do it
almost died
[ __ ]
i don't even care again
come on i was doing so well
i'm using the armor i'm doing it [ __ ]
every starting
easy
[ __ ]
come on [ __ ] you're nothing
what what it
easy that was so easy
are you serious i can't believe i died
so many times
[ __ ]
this package consider it delivered
heavenly strike is mine [ __ ] heavenly
strikers mine [ __ ]
i didn't stagger him that's why that was
the problem
i kept using light attacks
postman armor for land for laughs
such a gate under the dead
try feels good that was the first time i
actually tried so i think
technically first try
why was that attempt so easy lamount i
don't know what happened
it's cool
we got jack in this [ __ ]
me and i
yes my legend grows
was inspiration i didn't even see him
give me some taters
all right we have a new ghost weapon
sticky bomb
wind chime i never use them so i might
as well upgrade can i
no i can't upgrade smoke bomb
they lose sight of me yeah i feel like i
can use that
all right we should upgrade for sure um
let's not upgrade the things that i
always forget to use
that seems 15 does not seem enough roll
just before landing to avoid damage
for hearing don't care stand up streak
after successful standards one enemy
will
rush into the openstack to a killing
well [ __ ] yeah
what about our stances when we out here
in kansas heavenly falcon
strike without warning like the hunter
of the skies
yes jack said are you winning son
yes i'm winning that was first try
thanks for joining in
on the first try jack thank you quick
fire weapon swapping yeah i know that
i knew i knew that shut up i knew that
i knew that thanks for the microphone
jack appreciate it this livestream would
not happen without it
everyone say thanks to jack thanks for
the microphone it looked like big vp
jack
now what did we do we did it
we did all the side quests bros
let's go to her can we fast track nope
can we go there fast track can we go
here fast track yes
yes very nice
[Music]
i call on thee he died 10 times
sh
what irish don't know does not hurt
irish
why do i never see his comment
oh you're saying thanks now okay i got
it it's a bit delayed
all right let's try the thing if it
works now
yes
after you win a standoff additional
enemies rush you wait until the charging
enemy swings the weapon
then attack
yeah i like that cool
so you get two in one
[ __ ] waste
i should have killed him
four for you do not started the blade
you must research more deeply
these packages don't deliver themselves
it's my motto
come here again
such a cool game love love
yes jack is out huh
what a potato
he came like the wind and left just like
it
whoa [ __ ] blue dude oh they're
fighting a boar
my kill don't worry borah i will save
you
the boar is laying
[Music]
live a peaceful life i will dedicate
this song for you
mr ball you sleep and snore
your mom's a horn
meets the board thank you
let's follow bird
take me to the hot springs
are you guys trolling me that jackie's
oh there he is gamer never leaves okay
nice
bro i gotta mod you jack just so i can
see
an old ban ban everyone that says that i
died 11 times on that boss because
they're just trolling
and it's not epic
what
[Music]
uh
i must study the flute deeply
okay so i play the flute mister boy
mr boy
[Music]
what are you saying
i can't play the flute it will be too
obnoxious you'll have to do it
oh that's a building cool i want to go
there
the trader
it's a lighthouse let's uh
see if we can upgrade something
range capacity upgrades ooh
[Music]
quick fire upgrades
vanity i like our bow looks like
my daughter just came home after seven
months of being in the hospital
paralyzed oh no
from neck down to car for a car crash i
want to say thank you for the videos
you make they've helped me through a lot
ride your daughter's back
hopefully safe oh this looks more
pewdiepie doesn't it
we got the red and black
should we do that one yeah
i already have the best hat so i don't
really need
i forgot how you change it
we need more linen
and supplies then we can upgrade it
there we go
yes now we're a postman
[Music]
oh my god what are you doing
there's the lighthouse i found it
[ __ ] crazy
i can unlock songs by finding crickets
cool
all right so another one will charge me
now
yes can we do this
[ __ ] that was head shine
don't talk you made postman mad
oh [ __ ] i thought it was her [ __ ] i
almost died
nice
this is the way
[Music]
that was cool come on
what are they doing
[Music]
oh god oh god
[ __ ] the spear guys
yes
i can't play the flute excuse me sir
why can't i play the flute there's
someone left
why i can't play flute this is so unfair
don't make me laugh
what the [ __ ] this does not work out god
damn i was trying to be cool and [ __ ]
[Music]
yes
love it
it's important don't ask why
what's happening
how does one climb ladder i don't know
[Music]
birthday party
thank you helen thank you
another [ __ ]
mama
never got a reply from jack about the
tambourine
stand relaxed with both his swords and
his both hands and was prepared for both
offense and defense
he called it intangible stance
nice we asked him in the sight
so
oh jurgen you're blocking the view my
man
there it is
the land of the rising sun
why am i doing this
it's fun to watch like after you're done
look at jurgen stance dude now this is a
screenshot
wow this game's so pretty
all right let's continue
go where the wind takes us so we're done
with her quest
we're getting there man we're getting
[ __ ] done and [ __ ]
hey look it's the barn guys
share pics after stream sure
all right so we can upgrade our bow
which i definitely want to do
thank you
you are the most beautiful horse
they call me jabba
for major legend increase if i do that
quest
okay let's do it
finish the fake samurai mission which
one is that
you can't just say stuff like that and
make me
which one is that
[Music]
let's invade some mongols for the [ __ ]
and giggles
sorry mongols look away from live stream
oh i see we're here
what's the quickest way to get down
yeah i like how the game loads quite
quickly
you think we're like a game like this
pushing that because i remember when
dark souls
3 came out on uh or sorry dark souls two
came out and play station three like
right as uh
the next gen console was about to happen
and it was
so slow
what is this
a bird show me the way
i i found it bird yeah i don't need your
help you can leave now bird
i did that for no reason what is wrong
with me
i need leather sorry bambi
oh i didn't even drop any leather what
the [ __ ] bambi
mud
have i not found this already
alright meditation time i will reflect
on my favorite food and mcdonald's happy
meals
was made to program children
fast food for the rest of their life
he read from azeram gives me hell
gives me strength
[Music]
time to kill mongols
what the [ __ ]
stop simping for the character
i want an entrance
take your time my dude
don't ever challenge me
this is the way
bamboo gotta have it
where's my sim queen there you are
thank you
this is the way
oh [ __ ] it's right here oh they saw me
hide behind jurgen
works
oh that's funny
[Music]
that's justin
there's the leader
oh my god i'm dead
[ __ ] i'd actually died the leader was so
strong
i mean i didn't die
that was an epic fail let's do that
again
no way
he's gonna rush me
i went through him dude
oh my god i suck now
that's how it's done
all right let's see we can observe the
leader
where is he
10 hours sweet
whoops
why did i do that
they never saw me
it's your boy pewdiepie
oh
he's so strong dude
[ __ ] this
i'm done i ain't doing this
[Music]
no this is the way this is the real way
of the samurai i'm done
oh you fell for the old i'm done trick
didn't you
whoa
god stop that
oh my god he's so strong
easy first try [ __ ] kunai
i need to use the kunai against the big
guys
it breaks their stance
nice
easy
i told you easy
i keep forgetting the ghost weapons
i'll keep forgetting everything help me
help me
help me i'm stupid
first try though feels good i will say
so
what's up mr boar
mine mine mine mine mine
whenever he says kunai i think he's
mispronouncing knife kunai
that's probably how that word came to be
honestly
that's mine
yeah i probably should upgrade evasion
because i'm really struggling against
spirit
can jurgen swin come on jurgen don't be
scared
good boy swim yeah [ __ ]
this is fun to kill it for a while
one second wait
so smooth
right uh wait a little bit we'll talk
about it in a bit
epic
travel attire upgrade [ __ ] yeah no wait
not travel god damn it
oh there's a bird show me the way bird
mods are hard at work thank you
you can upgrade post manhattan i should
really do that shouldn't it
what should we reflect on
[Music]
exhaustion i picked the lamest one
you really feel like i'm badass playing
this game i really love it
if only i had time for a short nap don't
nap just think of naps and your health
will be increased
[Music]
okay i guess it's time to go
i have a gift why don't no one tell me
i want gifts
jin should settle his hot spring water
nice
nice nice nice
give me a gift thank you
what not
hell yeah people give me gifts
i play live stream no one donates
in-game mucha donates
yeah i'm donating shaming you guys i'm
there you're not giving to a millionaire
here i am working my ass off man well
you think it's free
five dollars
it's a joke
god damn it all right we'll upgrade it
soon
can't help myself
me and marcel should have a swedish
versus italian food competition
yes yes yes yes
when do i ever use this this is the
ghost weapon isn't it
i'm not wasting all night [ __ ] no
i can't upgrade my katana
i wanna i'm so close i should do the
armor first
i have an upgrade with a boyer again
already
where is the boy
over here
no it's not worth it right now merry
christmas you filthy animal
thank you jordan
come on
you
rumored location added
why don't we check that out do a quick
little side quest
honestly i think it's quicker from here
there you are you stinky
let's go bro a last one for the bros
i keep forgetting i have heavenly strike
when do i use it it's
triangle and circle
this okay let me try it against these
guys
thank you nightbot
all right let's have a look strike
yeah it is cool
[Music]
make another girlfriend pick my clothes
video that was fun
maybe when we're in japan we'll do that
that might be fun want to buy clothes
right now
god damn it bird i don't have time for
you now
whoa look at this field
what's going on in here
[Music]
killing npcs
i don't even know i'm playing this game
i already know revenge is bad
i've already learned it
why are there stones on the ceiling
how's this
i'll find the merchant card
and we'll flip and slay it
yes i was hoping we would go here nice
god damn so
pretty
foreign
investigate further i must i must study
this area deeply
honestly this game is better than i
thought it would be like i watched a lot
of gameplay
to see what it would be like but it's
even cooler
mangos yeah filthy mangoes ow
ow stop okay
that's
yes
[Music]
no it's hard to time this
try to look cool
yeah i keep forgetting i have the
shotgun
my bad guy
i think i might have to end the stream
here
thank you all for uh coming i sent well
being here really fun
i have a lot of fun playing this it's
fun to hang out as well
for the memes love the gameplay field
zero death gang thank you david
thank you very much
all the best guys appreciate you thanks
for all the members
online [ __ ] you
you're not so bad after all how about
that
you want to you want me to pull that one
out for you bro
don't go i got it i'm sorry
let's make sure i save them
sarah that plays through continues
did i save it
yes okay
cool all right
gotta upload a video in a sec