[Music]
come on
is
it's better to have love and lost
[Music]
seven seven six four three tango seven
three two five seven three one one seven
eight eight eight seven three two four
seven six seven eight nine seven six
four three seven six
lock when i have plucked the rose
in faith i do not love thee
shall i compare thee to a summer's day
when i have plucked the rose
[Music]
is
up
[Music]
what's cracking my apple batman
i'm early
how about that huh you're just picking
me yeah you're still with me
all right again i'm early
i'm very tired very tired
this apple will give me strength
the apple is not working
everything
[Music]
how many people can get in here
i'm having me eat an apple and not say
anything
the one and only [ __ ]
thank you
i'm not gonna again
24 000 people apple gang
[Music]
let's go to 69
apple a day an apple today
keep the doctor away well guess what
doctor
i got two apples
[ __ ] and guess what i ate a
[ __ ] bear
i had a baby for an ice cream
[ __ ] you got nothing
you got nothing you know it stopped
i take out
just now proposing my friend jesus shoot
what's up
i'm almost done oh god
we're getting hot in here [ __ ]
you see that is that a worm
what is that that's a bad
it looks like someone put a cigarette in
it
oh it's like a star
we're done i'm done
i'm done oh
all right thanks for watching guys
let's go i'm so excited to play this i
look forward to it
so much i'm putting my friend at the
friend zone today could uh you wish me
luck i'm very nervous you're putting
your friend in the veins now
just unfriend them instead do the man a
favor jesus christ
what are you crazy literally opened my
eyes 20 minutes ago
the apple parent is interesting to try
and process
i stop the snoozing
and i feel like i want to die
that's my life right now watch me have a
mental breakdown
on the live stream
i've been trying to hide it but it's
like everywhere but the thing is like i
knew i was going to quit it anyway
it just helped me quit alcohol and now
i realize it's time to quit this news
but i just hate life
right now that's all i got to say
but we have ghosts of tsushima so that's
okay
so i feel good return to track let's
kill some mongols
that make you feel better
can we do this no we didn't
i'm not gonna suck the mic
especially another man's mic i'll suck
the mic if it's marzias
if you know what i'm saying yeah you
know what i'm saying
here we go we track at the mongol
the thing with the snooze is like i
really
during quarantine missed sweden
it's like a swedish thing and then
there's this there's this uh one uh
brand from gothenburg it's like a
hundred year old brand
and the smell you're so dead man
that word
uh it's called yet to bosch rapia and
it's like
i cannot get that flavor anywhere and
it's so reminiscent of sweden for me
like a childhood memory like swedish
pancakes
but yeah don't snooze that's the reason
i hide it because i want i don't want
kids then you don't do it it's not good
it's bad for you
but now i will live as an empty vessel
throughout the rest of my life
it'll be great
delivering amazon packages all right
let's say inspect the [ __ ] lead
what the [ __ ] are you doing
what a guy
uh
[Music]
this definitely could have gone better
what the [ __ ] just happened
i'm so confused
zero damps all right this will be the
[Applause]
this will be the live stream where i get
it
this is a zero death playthrough
you're dead my dude you're dead
you're double dead don't ever come at me
[ __ ]
is that it no leader
i play the flute flute the flute
thank you nine point i've died several
times so far
ish
keep forgetting i have a heavenly strike
i want to use it
all right you're rescued you're welcome
you eyes mooney just hit hundred subs
congrats is mooney
[Music]
time i wonder if they do have harakiri
in this game
it's such a huge part of the japanese i
mean samurai
but it's such an ugly
side of it but it's still part of it
i'd be i'd be disappointed if they don't
have some element of it
what do you have people played it do you
guys know
yeah i'd be disappointed
did i finish a shitty quest
the best gamer alive
that's me you're talking about me thank
you for bringing me up
you want me to bump up the gameplay auto
a bit
beautiful
four upgrades on the trapper dude
uh upgrade armor yeah maybe we should do
that
i mean i already turned it up a bit and
people still complain about it i don't
know what you guys want
last time it was way too loud when i
checked their live stream
i don't know why you guys didn't [ __ ]
tell me
[ __ ] virgins
y'all the bonjour virgins aren't you
huh
admit it you're scum
i'm louder today i guess so good for you
[ __ ] god damn it i need 40
supplies whoever told me to come and
upgrade my armor
[ __ ] you [ __ ] you apologize
wasting my god damn time [ __ ]
you ever waste my time like that again
you're dead
y'all dead
ah
don't ever game audio's been lost
complex
topic that is what it is
do you understand game would you be low
i don't make the rules
apologize
i apologize hey where's my apology huh
with my [ __ ] apology can you lower
your mic volume please
that's all i hear from you guys
sorry i'm sorry
how's that that better
it was so [ __ ] low the last time
how's this is that better
[Music]
you like that are you satisfied
you're
[Applause]
so
you like that i'm glad you liked this
just hope jack wasn't watching me
violate his microphone
her name is key what the with the wii
i want to upgrade my postman armor
[Music]
then i'll suck the mic and you know what
i'm not gonna lie it's kind of weird how
you guys keep asking me to suck the mic
do you understand you're weird do you
know are you aware at least
i didn't [ __ ] see any supplies
let's look for supplies around here
found them
that supplies right there
i don't see any [ __ ] surprise
surprise [ __ ] there we are nice
all right we need like 38 more
49 from the one and
it only says the one and i'm guessing
the one and only
get a haircut [ __ ] ugly hair
ugly
[Music]
[ __ ]
now it comes here it comes here it comes
[Music]
i believe no i wanted to play flute
well they're not all dead oh [ __ ]
[Music]
oh come on
oh god i almost died can you stop that
you're hitting my legs
don't ever hurt my legs again
[Music]
ah [ __ ] you don't ever the word of the
world
there's so many more than i thought
there were
where's the archer i see you
[Music]
where you going [ __ ]
can you stop doing it
that thing is [ __ ] op dude i'm the
warding you
[Music]
that's right [ __ ] i'm delivery
man
is that all you got is that all you good
yeah i'm the realest aliens the killers
of the villains
yeah now we upgrade
zero dabs you're watching it live
a
i am the one don't weigh a ton don't
need the gun to get respect up on the
street
yeah yeah
all right can we upgrade my
motherflipping postman
stop telling i'm sucking the mic on 69
[ __ ] no other number
don't ever ask again mom just start
banning people that ask for sucking
it ain't happening it ain't happening no
premature sucking
why does it take so long to load
shut the [ __ ] up nightbot shut the [ __ ]
up
whoa look at that hat dude
holy [ __ ]
[Music]
look at my hat look at the size of my
hat
look at the size of my hat
holy [ __ ] holy [ __ ]
hey madam you see my hat [ __ ]
yeah she crying cause she never had this
hat
[ __ ] yeah [ __ ] yeah
i would could suck this hat and suck the
[ __ ] out of this hat
hell yeah ain't nothing gay about man
sucking the head
ain't nothing wrong and even if it was
gay and want sucker he ain't nothing
wrong about that
ain't nothing boiling
yeah all right well what was that
yes the quest yes
we will travel we will travel to tangle
crossroads
hack gang heck gang that's what it is
gang
[Music]
it's a [ __ ] taco with a penis
on it
that's what this is
i am so glad we went with his armor
it's the best [ __ ] move in my life
everyone kept telling me
through this playthrough don't build the
armor
pick up the better armor oh yeah
i'm sorry do i have a penis on my head
[ __ ] you
[ __ ] you man where's jurgen i thought i
called him
kids it's my birthday i appreciate a
shout out you're the best
keep being weird what do you mean weird
hey there you're a hater now hater
thank you happy birthday i hope you have
a great one
hope you get a hat like this as your
birthday gift
cause that's the only way you're gonna
have the best birthday out there
but you could get a second good which
would be
if you get the smaller hat version
in short if you get a hat good birthday
hat game
i've always been hank gang always
always stay true to hack gang
some people doubt it
some people know they're wrong for
doubting it
it is what it is
i'm the best youtuber ever why thank you
can't argue with facts and fiction
facts and logic i meant to say
[ __ ] all right here we are
another quest
what up [ __ ] i got head you see this
look at the size of my head look at the
size of my hat
oh man's got a command respectable hat
as well
[Music]
if you know what i mean
i mean this is a 30 year old man with pp
on his head
cringe bro
[Music]
[ __ ] cringe
what kind of videos does leafy do now i
haven't checked out
surely he's not making the same thing
but it's funny how you say that and i
know exactly what you mean
do not draw any unwanted attention bro
look at my hand how could i not
draw unwanted attention everybody wants
to [ __ ] me within hey
shut up nightbot who the [ __ ] is doing
that stop [ __ ] with night bye
i died zero times and you goddamn know
it
it's japanese
[Music]
i want to kill them
i guess we have to hide huh i got a bad
feeling about this boys
a bad feeling a girl asked how big my
peepee was
i didn't know what to say because you
have never raided my peepee
so i told her i'd ask you also all of
her tree thoughts
love you thank you
medium
there's no way i've died 327 times no
[ __ ] way
i haven't listened to oliver's new
tracker album i don't know what he
released
but everyone's talking about it so i
have no idea
stop asking okay playing tsushima okay
not a music discussion
channel ain't me that ain't me me
that's what sounds like a copyright
nightmare
[Laughter]
all right we in we out here
remind me to use the kunai now i always
forget it
and then afterwards i'm like damn that
was hard oh wait i could have just used
the kunai
[Music]
into submission
i take their face and i pee be
pissing
oh me and myself watching speaking of
piston
we're watching prison school i've been
i've been
avoiding trying to watch it because i
just knew it was very itchy
like really perverted and i'm kind of
not interested
but uh it's so [ __ ] funny
i was laughing out loud so much
watch watch episode one it's hilarious
it's so funny and i like the style of it
too it's really [ __ ] funny
prison school probably not if you're an
actual nine-year-old but uh
otherwise i recommend it it's really
funny
because yeah it's some weird [ __ ] oh my
target's getting away for [ __ ] sake
got me talking about prison school and
now i failed my mission god damn it
sorry
doesn't count as a death though doesn't
all right here we go
i'm supposed to go on the [ __ ] roof
uh steins skate season season one
should i assassinate
[Music]
whoa
you only coward
forgive me uncle for i have sinned
i do have this pimpin ass hat though
i wasn't supposed to allow my target but
it's so much more fun
i want to have fun my bad
guess i'll have to suck this microphone
do not raise alarm follow the mongols i
guess i don't have to kill them
i won't do it then
[Music]
assassin's creed meets japan yeah
this is a lot cooler though
conveniently placed ceilings that attach
i like it i like it
i got them pro gamer moves
oh you
do you think he'll hear if we jump on
top of it
he would have definitely heard that
yeah i'm kind of cringing right now
we're on the ceiling
this is [ __ ] cringe dude what are we
doing
i don't want to be here i swear
opposite i don't be here
that's how we ladder gang all right at
least at least we're wall gang right now
oh we're back at ceiling gang
find a way through the market
guess we can go on the back you're
supposed to destroy sailing gang
not join them
you were supposed to bring balance of
their force
[Music]
how
yeah i'm not i'm not
okay i wasn't sure if i was like a
normal citizen or something but they do
see me
maybe let's uh let's kill some people
home is just chilling
let's just kill some people
like bad things happen to people all the
time
i cannot be held responsible
i am innocence
how maybe this way
oh i got it gamers
can i grab this armor it looks cool
[Music]
the bigger they are the bigger they
blob
you know i'm saying
they didn't see me but here i am
beastmaster64 i nailed that
why is that guy just not forgetting
about me
yeah that's right forget
stay in the market area
no but i'm [ __ ] back
cringe
god damn cringe i'm cringing gang cringe
gang
find a way through the market do not
raise the alarm
well [ __ ] me man
i'm i actually did that on purpose
i just got a little frustrated that's
all
bro that tucker really be looking thick
though
i'm glad that you realize
real eyes realize real lies
billy ellis said that
[Music]
i know i cried too when i heard it
how
keen star has your 10 million play ball
and will you take it back
i could not care less
is that guys sleeping or what's
happening over there
oh his back is turned against me
oh my god that would have saved me some
time
i was like how the [ __ ] does he not see
me
i'm not saving the slaves though that's
just taking it a step too
far
oh cool i'm stuck midair
i think i may have learned a little bit
i only have my uh 100 mil award
the other ones i don't care to really
have
i don't like having things they were fun
to get and i'm obviously proud of
getting them but i don't really see a
reason holding on to the item as a way
to
display to people
i'm kind of weird when it comes to items
though i don't i generally
don't like having things
[Music]
even stuff that are kind of cool right i
still don't really like having him i'm
weird
and i understand that i just wish people
would stop talking
about my awards because i don't want
them
i don't care they mean nothing
100 ml one sure that's cool
you know what i mean
do i need my silver plaque still i don't
think so
that's just how i feel man
can i go through here
oh we can go up in this window maybe
nice
it's so annoying because like i got i
been hanging on to my youtube awards
for so long just on the basis that
i don't want anyone else to make a big
deal about having them
and here we are like
people who find them off ebay are like
oh look i have pewdiepies
i have pewdiepie i'm like yeah i don't
it's not mine
i don't care it's so [ __ ] annoying
does she want it back
i'll give it back to you bro like no
just [ __ ] leave me alone that's all i
want
that's all right no big deal
it is worthy to use
i suppose someone
found them and sold them i don't care
none of my concern
that's kind of the point of me getting
rid of them
oh my god all right can i oh yeah i have
the listening mode i keep forgetting i
had that
[Music]
sorry to hear the anus floor gang
all right we need to get rid of that guy
somehow
oh literally i just have to walk here
okay
[Music]
power
oh wow so it triggers it yeah i was
literally supposed to go here
come cheer up my lads come cheer
up oh okay walk that
all right well i guess she did it
still here i just got a bigger hat
that's all don't want your old awards or
you know it without their flaunting them
i should melt them into a samurai blade
that'd be sick and then i kill anyone
that asks me about the awards
is this annoying when people put more
importance to items than i do myself
it feels like i'm supposed to feel a
certain way about it
or or they try and link me to stuff that
i don't care about oh it's pretty
like i don't care doesn't mean anything
to me [ __ ] off
ow
what are we doing what the [ __ ] you guys
doing man
where's north not that way
there we go
[Music]
can i just go here
no but that's north
this mission sucks so much
at least i've gone this far without
dying feels good man
let's find some sea turtles
[Music]
feeling very cinderella today very nice
pewdiepie yelled at me oh my god oh you
don't see those
should we kill them
[Music]
let's kill them i'm bored i don't kill
people
easy where's the third one
and that's how it's done
you want to tackle
that bow armor is the best thing ever
dude i love it
[Music]
a very nice i did not do that
what
all right dude the wrap of japan sings i
love that rap that was fun
should we kill these guys as well for
[ __ ] thing giggus
sorry what is my objective rescue
eunice blacksmith brother recruit straw
hat ronin
that's our objective all right let's
don't forget heavenly strike thank you i
keep forgetting heavily strike
god damn it and i'm too good though i
don't need it
i don't need it too strong oh too strong
there we go
sweet
[Music]
i'm deliver the tacos
japan thinks it's not that good to be
honest what the [ __ ]
you smoking i thought it was great
what you do not like about it explain
this
now or else you'll die
inspired by me they have this ethiopian
youtuber
and it has my old white hair
and i can't help but to wonder i know
the creator know who i am
i had a quick interaction with him truly
the most legendary man to walk the face
of earth louis wilson that's you man
you're talking about yourself
i don't know man i love japan's thing i
thought it was great
um and then i read reviews about it and
it's the cringiest [ __ ] reviews i've
ever read
it's like uh it's by little kids who
think
they need to add more difficult words
and that's all they need to do to make
an essay
or something worthwhile when you write
like five sentences and they haven't
said
any reason why they don't like it it's
just like it's bad
okay can you explain why it's so
annoying
it's just cringing bad and i hate it
[Music]
it's fire alarm day i don't know if you
can hear it it's [ __ ] obnoxious
[Music]
i can't do anything about it i can't the
egg will go off
did you do it no this closed door it
will go away
[Music]
the whole building goes up all right
guys
i am going to burn to the ground but i
commit to this live stream
keep watching and we'll see if i die or
not it'll be epic
no matter why i'll keep playing
you thought it was the game guess i'll
die
i'll let it go for two more minutes and
if not oh look we're just sipping some
titty juice
[Music]
[ __ ] yeah man's gotta sip some teddy
juice
now's a good time to do a screenshot
having a relaxing time
while the whole [ __ ] world burns
[Music]
everyone wanted me to share the photos
that i took i'll do that
oh thank god the moment i saw kite i
instantly thought of you
thanks for recommending it 10 out of 10.
that's a man of culture or woman i
didn't read your name
i guess i won't die finally join floor
again only fans
nice thank you very much beat smith
what do you guys think
okay sure
let's say i want something i don't know
what you want
what you really really want
i'm taking photo are you winning dad
are you winning son yesterday i'm taking
photo and video game [ __ ] what i'm
[Music]
winning
there it is all right guys i'm just
gonna
don't go anywhere i'm just gonna check
what mercy wants
did i go do something he was in here
what did he do
who called me a sim
how do i get the background to pop
how to get the background to pop dude
i like it like that
all right got it all right enough
[ __ ] around
i'm not a slim that's so mean hello
come on guys
if i'm nice to my wife
no i will not make me a shrimp
everyone can be nice to the wife it's so
toxic now i'm so
toxic
why i can't be nice
how is my wife doing
that how far it's gone it's concerning
i'm worried about youtube
and how people react to things
i'm not a tip
i'm not here
uh
wow
um
[Music]
okay
mccool
whoosh
you gonna [ __ ] die piggies
i stabbed the piggies
excuse me piggy that water though
[ __ ]
stop it whoa
[ __ ] [ __ ] from flip
all right we're gonna take the mongol
i'm gonna take the mongol territory say
it with me motherflipper take a [ __ ]
tower
but yeah yeah everybody thank you mango
teller totally take a monkey
little we take among it oh
zagawagawago
is that racist i sort of came away at
chan i didn't intend for it
up now
[Applause]
for the love of our
how i get inside this [ __ ]
it ain't much to ask and [ __ ]
oh i got it
i got it
i'm in i'm it
the [ __ ]
maybe if we jump from jurgen
i want to kill mongol we sang the mongol
kill song oh you don't think this is the
way
you think this is funny you don't think
either way
yeah well adam yeah
you need the horse
i'm doing it let me end
that
all right all right
all right i didn't think i would have to
do this
i didn't think i would have to do this
no no no no no no
nothing happened nothing happened what
happened
oh that's so weird oh that's so weird
what happened what wait what the hell
guys you won't believe this
uh we're here now
oh [ __ ] dude
all right someone will pay for this
ow
dude is it lasting longer than before
[Music]
he's like super fast arrow guy
[ __ ] it let's kill him i'm too strong
honestly i'm scared of how strong i am
heavenly strike is for cowards
[Applause]
it's my stand i'm playing on hard mode
not easy mode shut the [ __ ] up
headshots increase the timer that's kind
of cool
god damn game look pretty
all right that i think we're going for
the other entrance
in a zombo bay with my [ __ ] bae
it ain't here that's what i know
jurgen you can do it don't fall
you can do it you can do it don't be
scared jurgen
jump jump you coward jump
jump you coward
yumpa yum
speak with the villagers all right
i'll ch i'll cheat it chatty what's up
villagers
you don't like this
damn i got a
[Music]
all right so he's gonna open the gates
sweet all right [ __ ] you [ __ ] yeah
welcome nugent martindo
i just i slept with a fan on me
because our room was hot and i got a
cold because it was too cold on my brain
my brain gets cold i get cold
and brain go cold hot lemon and water
honey
okay thank you
open the gates
do it do it [ __ ] i did you
[ __ ] did it he did it he died
you fight with little honor you have not
studied
deeply
you fight with little peepee
your moves predictable like a spurred
that sings you must study the blade
more deeply
i steal the linen more deeply
is that the leader because i kind of
want to study him
deeply
shoot them in their face come on that
was good
i kind of wanted to study him but it
didn't work i don't know why
though
[Music]
pathetic
recruit the straw hat ronin forge a tool
to climb the walls of
castle canada hey
hell yeah [ __ ] you sleep now
[ __ ]
three village elders
where
the kunai is really opie i can't believe
i haven't used anymore
can i not go in goddammit
okay i see where it is now
the crate on this guy
feels good man
so epic dude
i think they saw me
oh that's bad
oh [ __ ] he's gonna kill them forgot
about that
no oh he shouldn't die nice
no [ __ ] oh my god i'm so stupid
the hostages
where are we [ __ ]
all right i just want to get up there
pure view
was he inside where was he
easy my dude
no matter what got killed kill now i can
never kill enough
and when i stop within the kill then
everybody cling kill kills
okay so now they're gonna assassinate my
dude he's gonna assassinate my dude
what am i doing does anyone know
all right cool we're just going from
house to house checking around
seeing what's happening hello okay
there's the quest
let me assassinate you thank you
i didn't i'm not assassinating him we're
just chilling
full supplies here thank you
that's cheating [ __ ] you then
all right new move
[Music]
oh [ __ ] he's about to do the thing
[ __ ] i [ __ ] up there again didn't i
don't kill him
[ __ ]
i keep [ __ ] up
i just want to kill no matter what
people say hostage it's cool i'm reading
it now
after uh kill the mongol leaders
how is my dude still alive
hey we should just start with here do
one area at a time
[Music]
oh
nice nice sarah devs [ __ ]
you're free live a life
get a wife hell yeah
i may have failed for stupid [ __ ] but i
don't fail because i'm dumb and [ __ ]
i'm not stupid
uh all right who do we got left there's
three left three hostage monsters
no that's just one of the village elders
god this town like is kind of [ __ ] not
gonna lie
all right i guess we'll continue this
way
cool village though i like it
[Music]
all right we're getting [ __ ] done
[Applause]
i kind of want to throw a bomb there but
i think there's a hostage there isn't it
[Music]
so how do i inspect him
the oh wait though
i think i'm out of i'm out of barrels
[Music]
oh i got flaming arrows never mind
oh it went right past his head
[Music]
that was [ __ ] nice goddamn that was
sweet
sexy sexy sexy
too strong man we got another stance
cool wind stance against spears and axis
we definitely need that
okay cool i'll take it
uh oh typhoon kick
all right all right
all right all right i'll take it i'll
take it
how do i study the leader
thank you
i must study him deeply
how does one study the leader deeply
i can throw a bomb on him that's fun
oh we unlock moon stains [ __ ] yeah
i want the moon stain
[Music]
come at me bro you're weak you have not
studied the blade
you will never have a hat like mine
because you're weak
you're nothing but a bunch of pitiful
scoundrels
you must study the blade
wow
i think we're pretty close done with
this [ __ ]
[Music]
sorry about that one brother
you're welcome it says enemies are
nearby
this guy died in a sexy position not
gonna lie dude
not gonna lie what enemies are nearby
until they're dead all right
oh there he is
is that it welcome all the new members
welcome to the coolest sexiest club big
pps club in the world
biggest baldiest massive ball it might
be a problem in the future but don't
worry about it clan
yeah that's us
i was gonna do the win stance but then i
just stabbed him anyway
uh this is zero that play through so far
died zero times
uh task undone before undone
i'm not done it has never never done
before
family youtube intima never done before
never how is the lyrics for that
never done before
when do you think uh shane dawson is
coming back do you think he's making a
documentary on himself right now
do you think he's just like
how does it feel that the world
[Music]
he seems to have a good heart he's just
have a bad past
a really really bad
free villagers from cages
god damn why they in cages and [ __ ] [ __ ]
everything hurts i feel you man
i feel you
[Music]
oh there you are yes chilling in
you have to get close enough to get
prompted okay thank you
just started a leader and we started the
leader more deeply
i think shall shane will be back and i
think if he really wants to he'll be
fine
he'll be fine people just need to
get it all out there you know get their
frustrations out
and then you come back with a video and
be like hey guys
it's me all right
where's the last where's the last
motherflipping
villager says i'm 70 meter away from
apparently i haven't killed you
no you do not you do not you do not you
do not you do not you deny
what the [ __ ] oh my god its glitching
i'm killing nothing
this is go up go up
are you [ __ ] kidding me
are you serious
what was that glitch
[Music]
what the hell was that what do you call
that
ah oh
[Music]
is there no ceiling hatchet so i can
sneak in
jesus christ
all right we're doing this style now
[ __ ] them
i don't like you i don't like your
t-series
goddamn ladder [ __ ] me over so bad
so bad man i'm crying so
bad man i'm dying samara since they go
beep beep beep
[Music]
someone else nearby
where part of the plane
oh this dude
dude it's so nasty i'm on the wrong oh
i'm on wind stance thank you
i don't realize cringe cringe i was on
windstands
ah dude guys i'm sorry i'm gonna have to
make an apology video
i feel terrible i never thought we would
get
to this point
for five minutes i used the wrong stance
yeah i watched idler's new documentary
it was pretty good i didn't know who
that guy was
so i guess i wasn't really that invested
in it but it was still interesting
mr ice cream man
i thought i knew all about old youtube
but i guess not
all right where's the last cage
do you guys know
where's the last villager in a cage hey
pigs
can you wish my girlfriend a happy
birthday she's turning 26
big peepee girlfriend right there happy
birthday
have a great 26th birthday
very epic birthday
we've done everything i just haven't
found the last cage
i saw a video on you to call japanese
sword experts we had to go sushima
that's cool
is it legit that's the game legit better
be
imagine being a japanese sword expert
now [ __ ] cringe
it ain't 15 hundreds am i writing gamers
okay i found it i'm just joking by the
way
ow found you
what i want to see is japanese cage
building experts
and i want to see them react to this
part is this accurate
[Music]
is it accurate is that pardak right
i want to have a japanese bonfire expert
react to this bonfire
is this uh
[Music]
that what though
you
oh my god i actually died by a [ __ ]
peasant
i didn't research deeply what a [ __ ]
fail i have full health
and everything oh that's so annoying
god damn it that was my first death in
[ __ ]
almost three years and i had full of
everything
whatever i don't even care all right
let's find the mongol leader
all right [ __ ] yeah i love these fights
i'm into it
let's do it mangosan
have you seen my hat
a clickity clack zero death play through
so far oh there's an actual boss fight
yeah nice one [ __ ] oh [ __ ]
i don't know his moveset
i'm almost dead again
[Music]
i'm blocked i swear i [ __ ] blocked i
swear i'm not crazy
i am not crazy person [ __ ] two dicks
doesn't count because now it's one
versus one minus one
[Music]
oh that was good
i just realized this was easy just need
to use water stains
water stains
you must study the water stains deeply
okay watch this watch this watch this
that was pretty sweet right i'll do it
again
oh i almost died
[Music]
i'm almost dead no big deal water stance
you failed me
i tried to use the special attack it
didn't work at all
oh my god that [ __ ] heavenly strike
oh my god i swear god
i've heard about the [ __ ] heavenly
strike the entire [ __ ] playthrough
is getting so annoying
there it is now we're just slicin
[ __ ]
you must face consequences
no heavenly strike needed [ __ ]
you can use canis in the boss battles i
don't think i can because i can't use
arrows
it's easy trust me it's easy i don't
need to use it because i'm too strong
zero depths several derps look at the
size of my head
look at that zero devs
i guess you won't be vlogging
in hell i can't play the flute god damn
it that would have been badass
we will raise the banners you cannot use
canis well thank you for the 500 people
that told me
hell yeah we saved the village guys
feels nice
look how happy they are hey hey
dude his hand looked like a foot tell me
i'm wrong
look there's babies now they just pop
out let them run so pretty
so nice so wholesome we saved the life
hey
yeah again what did you do
what you crazy
hey jurgen don't [ __ ] touch me you
understand you [ __ ] [ __ ]
busy don't ever touch me
alright god damn i don't care how famous
you are now here again
don't touch me like that you understand
oh my stop
it you're embarrassing me here again
oh jesus is a bird
as a bird right there i follow you tori
son
let's get there
show me show me
where did the bird go
up on the mountain
or is it just here oh it's a bamboo
strike okay cool
thank you bird oops
all right let's do it i like this well
done
thank you text
easy easy easy i'm the best god damn
play in the goddamn world
i missed one no i did it nevermind i'm
pro
thank you what do we get now our resolve
has increased
oh that's what that is oh cool maximum
result
increase what up girl you see my result
what up girl you you check out the size
of my resolve
hey go hey girl i'm speaking to you
you know the size of my resolve
huge
i know you're too afraid to speak in
acknowledging me
i understand my resolve is strong
it's very large but you will one day
understand
and you'll come to me until then
okay all right what's next
what should i do someone said there was
a bow i could get if i do a certain
quest
what was that can whoever you are come
and crawl out of the shadows can you
come back please if you say the name of
the quest or the location i'll remember
it but i need you to crawl out
from your peepee hole
and can you come out i'm waiting where
are you
hello
we have a lot of undiscovered location
listen i can't i can no don't tell
marcia
about the resolve my child doesn't have
to know
but marcia doesn't know does not hurt
matthia
she doesn't need to know about the guys
i'm serious
blood on grass daniel
all right where the [ __ ] is it
how do i start that quest
there it is
or is it a miss it says i get a roan in
a tire
what the [ __ ] are you talking about
i don't have it
oh is this one oh
longbow cool yeah that might be good
should we do that hayashi
hiyoshi springs um
okay all right all right
he or she where is that
it's probably here right
oh thank you throw it
thank you thank you
thank god last year's way man's gotta
eat
i'm so happy now
oh
all right we gotta find the guy
you guys know where he is any little
tips
why should i go to the golden temper
first clearly it's here
he's got to find someone bathing and
[ __ ]
[Applause]
first to blotto grass then mythic tail
will be unlocked really
all right is this blood of grass
blood on grass blood ass blood
ass gang
all right is there a barn involved in
this mission at all
i don't know if i want to do it unless
there's a barn
you understand is there a bomb
so pretty i want to take a screenshot
can i
that's kind of cool
oh i know and then we'll do this one i
can't see the sun
yes
love it
[Music]
can i see my screenshot
where's my gallery like how do i see it
[Music]
here we go
nice
next one
cool i like it
it's all right this is a cool background
[Music]
i quite like this one
it's one of the first ones i got i think
i messed these up because i
um
[Music]
but i quite like this the ones we took
today
you guys want to pee pick a break
too we don't do those here
[Music]
foreign
all right my bad oh that's not the most
fun to look at but it's cool
yeah i'll share in the member around
there's a burning cat
where
it's a [ __ ] straw hat man
be
sorry i keep eating so much
so delicious dude
fruits are the best man
let's follow the trailer
i love big bird bit about steve jobs
eating a pear
what is that that sounds really funny
you're dead
that way
[Music]
we found him someone there
tries to have a cool hat as me
[Music]
don't waste my time
is
[Music]
what a
what a face
i like this
who's next
too easy
[Music]
i have the best armor and you know it
oh come on
almost died because it's full
[Music]
don't waste my time [ __ ]
oh
[Music]
water stains you got no
chance
damn that's cool i wish i could go in
slow-mo is there an armor that lets you
do that
with the sword
wow
i'm starting to get a hang of the census
thing although i never use heavenly
[ __ ] strike god damn it i keep
forgetting
i keep forgetting about water from god
[ __ ] i'm sorry
i'm useless that was cool
so where did i learn to slow down thing
then
what the [ __ ] is it only the arrow that
i can do it though oh my god i'm so
confused now
i have so many questions
is it the hat where is my power
what is the source of my power
heavenly strike against boss okay
can you believe that we can upgrade this
armor even more can you imagine what the
next
level of this hat is i don't even want
to know if i want to see it man
we're really taking our time on this
road are we
he doesn't want to go fast
welcome range bars 17.
oh hello
what do you mind
oh man
damn it's only okay cool we have a lot
of
more gaming to go guys stick around
i didn't realize it's only not even five
yet
hell yeah
he'll make you a samurai
[Music]
damn i feel foreign
the last upgrade of armor doesn't change
the look so this is your final form
well aren't you a ball buster dylan mars
god damn it you ruined all the hype
what the [ __ ] is wrong with you why
would you tell me that can't you just
let me live on in
misbelief what the [ __ ] man
rude unbelievable
this looks like uh the weird characters
from dark souls
i mean mine is cooler but i lowkey want
an extra one maybe one on top of mine
you know
that might look cool what do you think
uh all right we're walking with a main
man
they look like coco melon like they have
melon hats do they got
moss on them that's respectable
it's happening
that's
wonder what the oh you want to sit with
me again
god give me your soul
ronin attire weathered straw hat
[ __ ] yeah
oh that was the reward for doing this
quest wasn't it that's it
i think we finished it so now according
to the bros
we should be able to do
what was it called
this one
according to the brush
anchors are licking me it makes me a
little uncomfortable
felix my pug is cuter than your puck but
i want him to go on a doggy date
that's fair enough do you want anger
he's free you can have him
take him hey look we match now
this game looks good damn what's up
sylvan yeah
it's a very sexy game
you like the hat is that what is that
what you were commenting about
i could upgrade my bow but i if we're
getting a new ball i'm not going to
waste on it
go to the camp on the left side of the
string springs
this one or this one
or this one
can you hear edgar licking me
do we need to go to the golden temple is
that it
guess we can get some nice little uh
presents and uh we can get uh
yeah i do like the bow but it do
outro of darkness we got presents
[ __ ] yeah we got letter we got leather
than g
why is edgar licking me it's weird he
never used to lick me
stop licking me edgar
let's see how it looks upgraded
takes a while to load
oh my god
that looks barely any different okay
it becomes black yes
yes yes yes yes all right
i like that i quite like that one i
quite like that one not gonna lie
it looks slightly different we get like
the deer
fur or something on the front that's
kind of lame
what about the samurai one ah
it's not my song
i'm having the problem where everyone
tells me different things
no you need to go to the golden temple
no you need to go here no you
like can someone who knows what they're
talking about speak and if you don't
sure how about that
all right let's see if this person
leaves us
angry spirits
[Music]
i will study this deeply the map has
been updated
whisper in the woods tales of tsushima
this is a regular quest it's not a
mythic quest
so what the [ __ ] were you guys smoking
then huh
we can wear a mask as well i never
realized
that's it that's my boy
[ __ ] yeah
hey
we haven't upgraded our weapon in a long
time so i feel like it might be time
the pringle mask
nice for longbow talk to musician at the
end in
hishyoshi spring can't wait for the next
big fight
thank you all right so this this guy
named michael medina
legend paid 50 bucks to say this so he
has to be correct
for a long road talk to the decision in
the end all right
all right all right
so what is an n is that like a barn or
something
is it like a oh here's someone
everyone that told me i need to go back
to the golan temple you should be crying
right now
because you wasting my time
follow the uchi-sun
nice
what's up bee
oh anger's sleeping so cutely
we got it i'm so
excited we get long bones and
there he is play that music man
[Applause]
here we go another mythic quests aren't
exciting
[Music]
thank you michael appreciate it
what a dick
[Music]
your character looking like pringle taco
man thank you
thank you so much
[Music]
here we go guys
come on look at me
look at me it looks so
weird search for he or she calls for
blue flowers
all right all right all right all right
all right all right
down there huh
how do we even get down there
nailed it
sponsor eagle i swear i saw him
here we are
we have to look through the coast for
blue fly damn this is so pretty
not me though i look ugly but damn
is that it
oh we're back here
oh toti song
show me show me the way
i want to ride another haiku
oh it's getting night lot of people died
here
and so did the dares
[ __ ] don't run away
right bambi that's right bambi you [ __ ]
with me
you're the [ __ ] with me
what is this what
what is that
pillar of honor murderous innocent
animal
sorry sorry about that one bro
all right we gotta find the flowers and
[ __ ] i think it's those over there
search the coast
i don't see it maybe here
oh this is a co it's a fox trine
yes
cool it's been a while since we saw that
where's the bird trying to show me
though
i'm walking away from it now aren't i
yeah
oh and you're so cute he's laying on my
hand
there's a chest under the waterfall i'll
check it later then
we gotta find the flowers now
are those enemies
where
must be here somewhere there they are
found them nice
don't mind me just adjusting balls
nothing wrong with it
thank you forcing me
i gotta lick my hand though sorry that
was a weird joke i'm not shane dawson
sorry found them
[Music]
now what follow them okay you must study
it deeply
deeply
someone else has been here like every
other time
oh
that's where we'll find the bow oh
cool that's where it should have been
[ __ ] can you say happy birthday
sister taylor she's turns 25 today jinx
your sister taylor i mean taylor your
sister jinx says
happy birthday happy 20 50.
um can you after your birthday
celebration
can you help me uh
get the [ __ ] out of here
oh never mind i don't need your help
never mind
that's kind of smart bill all right so
we are looking for that
i'm
i don't give deadening [ __ ] you can't
stop me
old man
i ain't afraid i'm not afraid
okay so it's a mountain looking over
this seashore
it's got to be like down here some [ __ ]
right
could be there
this is this way
what am i looking at
what's happening
where am i i just woke up
wow look at the sky
i forgot how dumb i look and then i turn
around like god damn it
game is so pretty oh wait my face looked
like this
never mind
all right so we're looking for this
island let's get jorgen
let's get our main [ __ ] to help us
maybe we can see it from here
what do you think what do you guys think
to
live common i killed bears
you ain't going away damn what a flip
sorry vegans look away peter
look away pete dye pick up flowers peers
it's cosmo's birthday today can you wish
her happy birthday love from boomer chat
happy birthday cosmos happy
oh is that it
could be check it out chat
check it out what what what's it all
about
yeah that must be it
hell yeah
oh oh jurgen careful he's crazy
whoa what is this
[Music]
how do i get there to get this flawless
i'll let you bait us and notice he grew
that bird indeed
beep bees a night what
how to how the hell do i get
yeah i can jump right
if i can just
drum did it
yes okay plan
is going well so far now we go down here
okay
i physically can't
no it's safe all right thanks guys
[Music]
okay maybe the bird can show me
where the [ __ ] did you go
show me bit the bird
not gonna lie i could go for some
pringles right now
thank you bird all right we get more
health what should we
meditate on our pee pee size
[Music]
reflect on my mother
i'm not going to think about my mom when
i'm naked
the [ __ ] japan what's wrong with you
i'm not sure where i'm going i have no
idea
i know i'm 40 meters off oh found a hit
that's literally here
let's kill these guys all right what
what should watch this
watch this this will be cool
[Music]
oh [ __ ] can you do i kind of i kind of i
kind of
i kind of want can you do that again
[Music]
i just ready
[ __ ]
[Music]
i'm trying to parry it but it doesn't
[ __ ] work
there we go you're dead it looked cool
for a little bit
for a little bit i got some good action
in there
more
[Music]
wow they literally oh okay so that's the
shrine
follow the blue flowers in this massive
[ __ ] area
got it
[Music]
we're looking for an island
i meant to be in water stands don't ever
cringe at me again heavenly strike is
for insults oh there's a castle there
oh
should we check that out
there it is i found it
did i need your help i didn't need
anyone damn that's so pretty
oh no kojima oh mhm
what kind of pose should we do
quite like that
[ __ ] i can't
there we go
[Music]
oh you can just do that oh my god that
saves me a lot of effort
am i wasting time is this annoying
oh i quite like this
[Music]
nice
hey
[Music]
the samurai who smells like sunflowers
all right
thank you for your patience it's all
good
all right we know where to go
[Music]
i should have done the stab pose [ __ ]
next time
it's it's cool with the photo mode i
never thought i would enjoy that any
game it sounds a bit pretentious almost
but it's it's actually fun
oh no we got another location
it would be like vacation in tsushima
2020.
i'll share it on facebook it was great
guys
ah can you stop warning me i'm fine
all right so it's seashore again
[Music]
hmm
420 bro let's go
well i love the sky
i'll do a quick a quick one
[Music]
foreign
what's wrong with me
hell yeah get grease [ __ ]
with the organ
of course gotta get my man i'll put i
rather pose these on instagram than my
actual photos of me
don't come near me just don't hurt
jurgen
[Music]
peasants
too weak get on my level
29 supplies damn
i think i need i think i can upgrade a
bunch of stuff that i haven't
batted your phone with two piercing
strikes
automatically paris okay [ __ ] yeah i'll
go with that
okay what do you want again
he's jealous look at him
you smell like sunflower edgar
you crying again he sounds like he's
crying
you little [ __ ] boy again your little
[ __ ] boy
come here [ __ ]
god damn it i want to take a screenshot
all the time this is becoming a problem
oh god look away what happened
what happened nothing
[ __ ]
don't worry about it it was just a
little jump
oh we can see the lighthouse i just
realized
that's not the house is it no
okay oh
is that the lighthouse
sarah devs thank you thank you there's
no fall damage
upgrade oopsie
should have told me that five seconds
ago
i don't have games in game i don't have
a legacy game is what i try to say
nice
according to the game i've gone too far
off the deep end
i crush into dust with the drugs they're
not breathing
see ya bring both the birds i can
perceive them
where is the mountain
i'm looking for the mountain
searching for he or she follow the
mountain
getting up about
getting up by the mountain
i don't see the flowers
this is maybe i need to go to the barn
is that the problem
sorry i should stop you want to play
game or play instagram
oh found it that's it isn't it
yep there's the thing
right
scott it's gotta be here
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
whoever doubted me needs to cry right
now
i you better be showing tears on the
live screen
stream afterwards the after show where
everyone shows their tears
all right we're gonna fight the monk
aren't we because i'm ready
i'm not afraid of the old man
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
he's gonna shoot
[Music]
that's okay i'm willing to pay that
price
whoa look at his mask i want the mask
can i have the mask
hell yeah
[Music]
this is so cool
foreign foreign
[ __ ]
he's tough he's really tough
heavenly strike okay this is the time to
use it whoa what a cool
[Music]
[ __ ] i could have hit him there way more
[Applause]
[ __ ] i was so close
don't count my dabs
[Music]
is
how did i do so little damage
what stands should i be in i'm in the
wrong stance aren't i
no i'm not
[Music]
that's it
[Applause]
[ __ ]
[Music]
uh
no i was kidding
[ __ ]
he's a tough [ __ ] give him that
[Music]
uh
this is [ __ ] i got to staggered him
and he did nothing
oh my god he hit me with a double
come on
[ __ ]
never give up i never give up
never give up
good start
[Music]
you
yes
[Music]
[ __ ]
i can do it i can do it i can do it
[Music]
foreign
the [ __ ] is happening what the [ __ ]
happened
no yes
one more oh
no i just need it
oh so close oh my god i had him
what is this
[Music]
foreign
[ __ ]
i think i got him now
oh yes
[Music]
this what
what
i did it
did i
what happened
[Music]
i did it dude the power surged through
me
i like it carson uchi
networking
nice that was sweet then
i like i like i like
well well well well well well
it's been quite interesting also blind
cheeky and schnitzel
thank you
hello that was epic
all right we got the long ball
look at it look at the size of my bow it
is a very long
it is a long ball uh
yes yes yes yes oh dude we got so many
charms i didn't even realize
minor minor minor major
what's next now
we're 20 now i don't know what to do
next
to opie now
[Music]
should we go this one or this one
duals are the best thing in this game
they're very cool
i don't think i got his mask it would
have been cool
although mine is very cool as well
what's the other side of honor
[Music]
dude
oh i'm gonna die [ __ ] i'm fine
i'm all good
we're doing the barn quest is that it
sweetie
hey [ __ ] boy we're not running
you'll see it [ __ ]
how is he not dead
i thought i murdered him
all right another duel right away cool
[Music]
my hat is stronger
you will never stand a chance have you
seen the size of my hat
and my mustache for that matter
[Music]
you will never reach oh cool
foreign
[Music]
that was the toughest boss i ever done
nice one what a troll
what a [ __ ] psych dude
my bother setting that up that's so
weird
[Music]
the other side of honor
oh skill point no legend grow
we're shadow samurai now sweet
we can choose a new ghost weapon a wind
that might chime useful
all right so we finished did we finish
the other side of honor
oh this is the girl that said the woods
were haunted might as well do that since
it's right here
it's our spooky one that'd be cool
i [ __ ] with the spooky quiz
jurgen might be too scared though
i love this game
so cool we got a bird
i think i'll really see it's right there
isn't it
you picked up a sword kit earlier check
it out it's your colors really
all the
oh creepy i like it like a lucky
all right
foreign
i have to you don't understand i have to
[Music]
it's not kind of cool
so
ah all right
search for spirit with again alright i
can do that
show yourself
mushy
whoa
sorry whoa
bro oh
oh no
jesus why does it keep happening
that's just so unfortunate
story
[Music]
ah
the [ __ ]
where are you
i ain't afraid
i am
[Music]
this is child's play dude
the forest is safe or isn't it
nope they're just hanging around
logan paul right now be like
what we gotta go in photo mode
oh my god
guys check out the focal length
i can't believe
it will be a lot sadder if we had like
black and white for this shot
and then make it really still
and a lot of clouds so it's really sad
and really like late oh my god
guys my subs
are off the short dude
he loves this game the photo mode is so
realistic
i'm sorry logan that was a low blow
i apologize
lucinda
did we make some prequel to the thing
that year again
[Music]
felix i wanted to buy this sympnotic
emerge but you don't have shipping to
saudi arabia
when that when will that be available i
really want to merge i'll look into it
there's a lot of countries who are
missing that i find
hopefully we can get a hold of because
yeah i got you man
thank you
did we just get a better charm
or is it equally as bad as everything
else
all right we go to kamatsu
kamatsu
way of the flame sounds pretty cool
is that the one i found oh
i'll go with this
it matches it's a pewdiepie kid nice
[Music]
um let's take over another city
right here again my man
oh it's cookie
let's go here
now you see
you can do it here again
god damn it jargon you [ __ ] me
you understand oh this is so pretty
i want to take a screenshot guys can i
take a screenshot it's so
pretty the game is so pretty here guys
connecting
you're getting oh god no what is he
doing
can i just i want to get
i can do it
you just go here
yeah did it
let's go you're so good at the game
thank you thank you
thank you thank you very much
i'm trying my hardest but it comes
natural
really that is the secret
oh we got another bird
why do i have a memory of this bird
already
are you taking me
oh it's a high q nice so
let's do it
i'm sorry jack if anyone sends you that
we had a goal
of 69 and i got it i'm sorry i will
write a poem
as an apology
[Music]
struggle and cry out for him no
i think this
[Music]
um
nice
moment
this game is so fun
i want to play forever
this doesn't look good
what happened here
where the hell is everyone
spoopy oh i seen them
[Music]
built
so why can't i here we go
[Music]
oh he parodied by mistake
so the longbow is just for like
explosive arrows
thank you thank you thank you
i'm watching trying to forget the plot
at the same time i really wanna play
this game
[Music]
nice
feels good
[Music]
you can use heavy arrows with the
longbow oh
m
she
[Music]
let's just go come on [ __ ]
chin chin is bowing japanese shut the
[ __ ] up
[Music]
positive reinforcement for crossing the
bridge with that controversy
thank you cowboy 515. oh i see
thank you that means a lot it's every
day bro
it's just every day he was right
one step at a time zero deaths from zero
dabs that's how it's done
now that the sun is so low it's so
tempting to take a screenshot
but i must resist
shortcut
enemies nearby
what this is supplies
[Music]
this is a good screenshot
this is a good one
i want to do one when we're in action
you know
all right was that everyone
still playing on hard hell yeah baby
gaming hard though
my
are they following me
[Music]
once again
quite like this
focus is all wrong
they're kissing
uh
[Music]
this is important shut up
you don't like the red
oh
how
i'm fine
dude it's been about since 2011. that's
not for me so many videos are always
comfort my dad was in icu recently
watching videos always cheer me up thank
you for being my favorite youtuber hell
yeah
shower by role so you're going through
them
love your video keep up the good work
don't know what to write
i'm just out here focus on the gaming
[ __ ] people give me compliments
[ __ ] i'm not worthy
i'm just a little boy on the inside
[Music]
oh
where is that again it's over here isn't
it
nope
can you guys climb
see if you try
no hell above us way below us
above us only sky
imagine all the people
[Music]
foreign
out we don't care don't stay stay please
and donate please
please donate
hell above us hey some people think
we're living through hell
only hell around us
no i i got another one that looks the
same as
[Music]
his
that's why what the [ __ ] you shooting at
[ __ ]
the [ __ ] you say to me
huh
[Music]
is that a good screenshot
there's still enemies there right where
doko don't you know him loco
ah you [ __ ] uh you just
how
and then replace you so he makes all the
money from your vids
honestly i would respect that i would
let him do it
considering i borrowed his microphone
and this is what i did to it i think
that's fair
oh i just got to lead more peasants
oh we got heavy arrows now
foreign
oh
[Music]
i'm dead
i never died
did we do it
nope there's more
sweet
just waiting happy is going to react to
the ending of this game oh no
this is like abby shows up
and then she says hey a lot of people
didn't understand the deep and profound
message of last of us too
so i have returned into this game and i
just wanted to say
revenge is bad do not
perform revenge because it's bad and you
should feel
bad hey remember that dog of mine you
killed
you should feel bad i hope you feel bad
we just want you to feel bad i'm here
again
as a gentle reminder for you to feel
very bad
i can't upgrade my memory from 2-3 do
you know why no some people have issue
with it and i don't know what it is and
i flagged it to youtube and hopefully
they're working to fix
it that's all i gotta say your mother is
a gay
but that's [ __ ] okay
all right wait hold up hold up hold up
i meant to do that
[Music]
it's too easy this game who's shooting
me
what the [ __ ] they got dogs
don't kill my women oh my god where do i
enter
this is so frustrating
we're still sarah that's all good
that was close one
you there oh my god what is happening
the hell out of me
oh my god it's happening again
just stay still and you'll be fine
can you be quiet i'm trying to play game
oh
oh god there's a lot of them
no i ain't got time
sorry doggies
did i i killed myself no i'm fine
this is intense dude
[Music]
uh feet
can you shoot him i'm scared i'm gonna
[Music]
die
yes suck it
moonstands here we come moon stains here
we go
easy that was the easiest thing i've
ever done in my life
zero deaths if that's how it looks like
thank you brooke you're correct
i start off each with formly wait why
no
[Music]
that ain't right
what does it do you show off your ass
i sure hope it does
thank you
[Music]
well
best live stream thank you i'll do
another
15 minutes and then i have to go
okay that's like that would be a good
time to end it here actually
i do have to
kind of oh progress what the [ __ ] that's
been a while
[ __ ] is he going to be disappointed with
me because i stabbed people in the back
it's
[Music]
can you bring back your life you lose
you guys really like those huh
i i felt like i did too many of them
that's why i got tired
all right let's grab the day florida
all right i'll post that how do i
how do i share them with myself
first of all let me say
[Music]
so
i gotta upload them
what all right i'll figure it out um
thanks for joining this live stream a
lot of fun as always
hope you had fun as well i
sing the bye bye song
bye bye bye bye thank you for watching
do i look insane do i look as insane as
i feel like am i losing it
it's happening isn't it i feel it
yes