surprise [ __ ]
i'm live [ __ ]
i play monster energy like god
am i live yeah
damn we early early game
um
yeah i had time in the morning [ __ ] it
video games [ __ ] it
[Music]
here we are come on
what are we doing here we're not
complete this quest yet
there it is it is what it
is
major legend increase
i think for the first time there's no
real quest i
i'm like oh i wanna do that we have uh
all the mythic ones where you can get
the way of the flame
we just gotta explore more to really get
those so there's no point so why don't
we just go where we feel like
i'll go we can go here and then we can
go here
yeah yes
cloud pass
but pewds how will i sleep now
love your tribute periods you're a
really nice guy for showing love to
such an amazing dude thank you
i uh
i really like the guy i don't know there
wasn't anything more than that
it didn't feel like going out of my way
to do something
[ __ ] i'm going the wrong way
you're gonna be like jump
you're gonna be like jump god damn bye
can we jump here [ __ ] you no problem
me and jurgen coming into the party like
bruh
i think my cold is going down
very nice got a little bit worried there
that i had the meme
it's all good
oh man i am sleepy though
4am huh
yeah i realize this is not ideal um
time this is like my day off
i'm just chilling right now
all right we're finally going the right
[ __ ] way
look how pretty i love
it we got a new location
mongol territory all these [ __ ] took
our post
looks like all right you stay here again
it's dangerous
all right so kill enemies who are on
fire
find and observe mongol leader let's
really try and observe this [ __ ]
because i know let's get it i'm just
here to pay respect to god of youtube
oh there's the leader nice he's swinging
he's dangling
cool now we can kill him
definitely worth observing i need to do
that more
i get more points if they're on fire
[Music]
well that was fun
more screenshots you want more
screenshots hey pretty ever going to
make a video with mark
jack and ken soon sure why not oh my god
nice and the suffering
why is everyone fighting here are you
guys bad or good
oh they're good
look i killed them that's how good they
are
thank you game thank you game i know
[Music]
what their stains
who shoot them
feels good man
i miss
how do i set them on fire i want them to
burn
is that too much to ask
try doing workout in the morning
today i don't work out it's my rest day
i don't have to worry about that
very nice
[Music]
where's his last guy i don't see him
what is happening
hey kids love the video on sushant singh
thank you
i was writing that it was too simple but
i thought hey [ __ ] it
it's a cool video
hey man can you say good morning in
swedish for my fiance's daily
goal morons walking out for
fun
[Applause]
next month 24-month badge pink cheese
cool
arrows antelope gaming what the [ __ ] you
smoking my dude
[Music]
oh there you are you little [ __ ]
ow i was gonna say you think you're
faster than me yes you are
you're very annoying
nice we're getting really strong
hey you're again my man hey what up
boots
all right did we take this over yet
boosh
his house
or is it
sure sure why not
are you feeling shelburg yes i am
[ __ ]
no way i'm fooled by [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
don't listen to him he's lying
we need to get up on that mountain up
there how the [ __ ] do i get there
maybe over here
oh sorry son you've been my friend for
years pewds
and you just never knew it thank you for
always being there
when i need some life lord again for
life thank you man
because do you know what a navy seal is
if not whatever i'm heading to buds next
week we
wish you luck
good luck my dude
remember most people will give up for a
reason
there will be a breaking point but
that's when you push harder
oh
if anyone could do it be easy
never forget it hey pewds can you please
say jen has burger pp
bugger pp what the [ __ ] is a bugger pp
also did you know you could just hold
down the share button to take
screenshots
we got a hat my dude i already got a hat
all right where's this
bird trying to show me
down down down down down
early stream catch you guys in the
morning
have you taken your morgan snooze no i
stopped i told you yesterday
and it hurts thank you for reminding me
the morgan snooze was the best part of a
it was the best part it's the only time
i feel it
even a little bit thank you
i'm an empty vessel i feel nothing
nothing you lack an item necessary to
climb this
shrine all right well i guess i won't do
it then [ __ ]
[Music]
so this is completed okay nice
we can go to straw man let's go back
then
love you peers thank you thank you thank
you
so is back at it again today
guess so
thank you for streaming at an off
australian friendly time
yeah that's what i was thinking
before i hit live so i will get a
grappling hook i had a sneaking
suspicion there would be a grappling
hood
sorry i'm in no rush to get it i don't
even care
what happening here boy
oh no you want to tell me about it or do
i have to get off my horse
i was going to sleep but you're
streaming and i'm off work i've been a
fan for years
always bring light to my day
thank you
you crazy
all right let's check out the
undiscovered location
oh god i almost died
show me
banked show me that way
found it thank you
let's honor bangt where's edgar he's
sleeping
somewhere
just one more baby
so apparently behind me there's a
i wish you got the thing from breath of
the wild where you can just jump off
high cliffs
because sometimes i kind of miss doing
that
paraglider that's right come on jurgen
at least we get here again
it does seem kind of similar to breath
of the wild hey pigs i'm gabe i've been
watching since horror very hard days
i want to pursue content creation any
tips also currently drinking pews g
fuel cup floor gang
if you want to pursue content creations
make sure you try out different things
make sure you have fun do what you like
find out what makes you unique everyone
has something
that is unique to them and play to your
own strength
and uh
you got this man
so where are we going we're going down
there
what is that soundtrack it's uh
the is a monologue no no it isn't it's
down down down down
spirited away isn't it that's right
oh it's mrs straw hat
should we change our outfit so he
doesn't feel bad
been watching since 2012 you helped me
cope through a lot thank you so much
keep it up i know you will thank you
i know you will yeah
[Music]
thank you for the sushant singh right
video
i shared it with a bunch of people we
didn't follow you previously now that
i think they do every evening who's seen
the video appreciates you for a [ __ ]
damn i don't expect that
i'm glad a lot of people like him he
deserves uh
to be mentioned for sure
moist evan peck very nice nice nice
noise
we have a lot of outfits can i see what
the
stats are for them i love you thanks for
making a video on sushant
thank you aditya
i'm turning 22 i've been watching since
2012 when i was 14 between you and v
sauce you were a huge part of my teen
years
i always felt like your content matured
along with me
over the years also look out there is a
barrel behind you
i ain't looking at them [ __ ] barrel
all right let's go let's let's look like
this this is how we look like
15 melee damage so that are
those are the stats what about this
knocking and reload speed 30
concentration time two seconds headshot
restore i mean this armor is a lot
better
reduces enemy detection speed
reduces all damage by major amount
moderate this is so much better
when will you do a bell delphine music
video review sims unite
i'm good
this is one of those games where i care
more how i look like as opposed to
what's actually that good
so this is how i look like
it's my job to disable the lighthouse
all right
actually makes sense to have this armor
on then
your vietnamese made me cry he was from
my city fun fact he was a fan of nasa
and space travel i heard about that
uh his quality pulse love you thank you
for your video man floor gang out
[ __ ] you dead
please stop simping get some help hey
boots love everybody thank you for
everything you do also do you miss
stefano
every day my man every day i wake up and
i think of stefano
so glad finally someone asked
can i enter here maybe
i missed some of the supplies but
whatever let's do this first
what
sorry about that one bro oh we can
upgrade our bona
what about piggy of course i miss piggy
too i miss
everyone and claim me clue
can you go up please what the [ __ ]
all right just want to say thank you for
helping me through a lot i've been
watching since i was
in fifth grade now i'm turning 18 in a
month thank you for all the advice
and life throughout hard times hell yeah
ignite the lighthouse to signal the
attack
it's time
oops
i don't know man
this is clearly the best
[Music]
this is our moment where we have the
slow-mo walking towards people
where the [ __ ] shot me
oh
[ __ ]
reload your head i know that was really
the issue there wasn't it
[Music]
i would get some arrow [ __ ]
nice too easy
can we ever expect return of ainsley
i would love to make a video with
ainsley
that's the goal of live isn't it
[Music]
for me personally materials are a bit
hard to get
dubs bobby 99 what what does that mean
what does that mean thank you very much
i am very confused by that thank you
he's jealous of my hat and you know it
wish i can work with you sometime my man
you're the best i work with pixel art
game dev and animation when you need
some
one gimmick chance pixel rogue floor
bender gang here
nice all right
[Music]
other soccer pun games infamous i have
on this channel dude
it was a really cool game uh
they need sucker punch needs to make a
sequel to this game
on next gen like right now like right
now
honestly and make it a good story hire
some good writers not on
no [ __ ]
it'll be the perfect game please sucker
punching are you listening
uh would you consider playing for
honoring the streams from just members
yeah yeah i'm considered that keep up
the good work much love from
dan dan the main on um
let's serve it here
follow the story this is kind of
important here kids okay my bad well
stop
writing me
[Music]
sorry mongols
thank you alex appreciate your maine
you guys are very generous today how
about that
i was thinking today this month's
charity should be um
some something environment related
zaks thank you very much appreciate it
this this stream has increased my
testosterone level
good you should be a health taker
though the puzzle might be difficult you
guys underestimate the large size of my
brain
all the time
[Music]
all right enough enough donuts all right
i want to play the game shut up
i'm just kidding but seriously though
shut up
i'm kidding love you but seriously
though
shut up do you understand
lead ryozo down the cliffs
pewdiepie the grand minister of the
multiverse approves this stream
oh my god i'm literally just supposed to
walk here god damn it
if i simp for you can i be erlang's
captain of floor gang sure
sure you can you came josh you're
welcome
we need a couple of them
whoa
oh you guys are [ __ ] done
what should we do
are you seriously all [ __ ] moved as
say
[Music]
yes
[ __ ] i [ __ ] up ow he kicked me
stop kicking me i'll go up i'll go up
i'm sorry
can you go up in those moments making my
bed downtown
i [ __ ] up there i shouldn't have gone
in do you know if you've seen
re zero but it's straight fire it looked
pretty cringe honestly i saw it this
morning
cringe
[Music]
so i'm so confused i don't want to do
that i want to change
oh i got it all right
this is not going well
oh my god can you stop
nice that's how it's done
[Music]
built
yep
[Music]
[ __ ]
[Applause]
[Music]
what a fight dude i can't stop
super focused
everybody dead now
damn that was fun
stop the fight go to the boat but i can
kill everyone
it was so much more fun
[Music]
was i supposed to just sneak in
all right fair enough get to the boat
i'm sorry
okay now we sail
get to the boat kestrel i'm sorry yeah
yeah ding dong nice just gonna do
another 10 to say thank you for saying
my name
right can't wait for the next merch alex
matthews i nailed it i know
grand priest i bowed pewdiepie
there's only one verse i stood it thank
you cheryl
all right epic yeah all right it's our
ship for food
hungry gang
i can only carry one smoke bomb that's
so lame
nothing
foreign oh there's
[ __ ] there's a 500 donation from angry
stone
i'm starting youtube channel i was going
to build a background how
you had in the 2016 area with the
whiteboard spray paint because my room
is huge and
uh has a boring background how did you
make the backdrop how can i
deflect comments saying i'm copying you
if i have the 100 million chair kind of
same style backdrop
uh i think it's fine if you admit that
you were inspired by something i don't
think that matters
um damn first of all thank you so much
angry
[Music]
you mean when i sprained painted those
walls those were like um
oh god
oh god i hate the [ __ ] spear guys
they're so annoying
that was a head shot god damn
um i just wrote down
what i wanted to make on a paper and
then i made it
it was pretty easy you can do it anyone
can do it
[Music]
i think i kind of copied the what's that
artist called keith harry
is that him so hey everyone copy
oh my god this is very annoying
[Music]
oh nice all right last one
yeah that was sick dude
oh all the best angry stuff
good luck
[ __ ] yeah you see that shot
that's what i'm talking about
oh it's a spear guys i do change stands
just so we're clear they're just very
annoying
oh that was the leader [ __ ] i could have
inspected him
i should have expected the leader i want
the moon stains
i want the moon stains in my pants
nice
the leaders are too weak man i can't
tell the difference
it ain't my fault that there's some
[ __ ]
so let's not kill them let's not
assassinate people because then my dad
will be angry pills can you please tell
my boyfriend carrie
karim he's a shrimp
agreed
agreed one thousand times over
control your sim ass friend mother
jesus
that was close [ __ ] where they come from
a
[Music]
nice love your work you do thank you for
being such a genuinely good guy best
wishes p.s could you shout out a fellow
sim tyler yee as fellow sim
what do you mean fellow sim the [ __ ] do
you mean with that [ __ ]
i ain't no fellow sim keep the words out
of my mouth keep mom
oh
oh god i'm almost dead can you not
because i'm almost dead and i don't want
to die
thank you
i'm doing this zero deaths thing you
know what i mean addition to have dudes
get a tattoo of anything for years
nice nice nice oh [ __ ] we didn't go in
here my bad
well this is a [ __ ] bloodbath what
happened here
are we gonna fight
[Music]
uh [ __ ] now it's not a good time
i said now it's not a good time i was
changing stains
oops uh look away one second i didn't
die i uh tactically killed myself
because i had the wrong stance there we
go all right
oopsy didn't mean to
[Music]
oh my god you're so annoying
i'm so confused literally ran azura on a
ship in a straw is that a
one piece reference look i clicked the
[Applause]
smoke bomb it didn't [ __ ] use it i'm
so confused
[Music]
can you give a shout out to students of
belvish secondary college
go learn some [ __ ] bellevue secondary
college
go learn about math and [ __ ] and then
come back here and prove what you
learned
he's crazy
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice i must study it deeply oh my god it
keeps going what is this quest
[ __ ] what is
[Music]
foreign
my lord thanks for telling us there's
one universe no multiverse you're
welcome
just thought i'd clear that out there
pringle samurai continues
do you know how to pronounce my name
correctly malone
there nailed it you're welcome
just chilling with my home in the horse
we can upgrade one of our techniques or
stances
yeah that feels like good
how do i do the typhoon kick launch your
enemy further back and deal extra stigma
all right
i'll think i'll wait until i
do more of that then we have the ghost
ones as well
let's do that for now
this is a screenshot time
is it a screenshot time with my horse
stanley looking out
nice
nice mysterious
so so oh i like that
that's a video i don't think videos
[Music]
oh i see that's how you do that stance
this is important shut up
[Music]
shut up
so
love it
[Music]
all right let's stop sorry my bad
too dark you guys don't understand art
i'm sorry to say it
[Music]
this is the equivalent of taking
pictures of your girlfriend
no that ain't me
oh man what a game all right so
there's a we can upgrade our sword i
guess
should i do that yeah
where is everyone in this [ __ ] town
though
oh we got the grapple hook here oh okay
nice
well let's do that then
sarah that so far feels good
zero there's zero devs very good
what's this [ __ ] blacksmith guy huh
hey man
i just want to know what's your opinion
on the game so far
i love it i absolutely love it i just
uh can't really get into the story i
know i haven't really tried but at the
same time yeah it's
not it's kind of basic
everything else i love camera angle is a
little awkward sometimes but otherwise
i have no quarrel
with this game it's perfect
where is this blacksmith guy
should be here i can't see him
i could have distracted
give me the grappling hood
[Music]
foreign
go
so
damn you guys are loyal huh hardly no
one left what the [ __ ]
you knew i'd get a pair huh
i'm that predictable huh
i already
foreign
it doesn't sound ripe enough yeah well
sometimes you just gotta eat
foreign
materials did you use to build the
background
i'm singing using plywood
um make sure you fill it up with some
sound dampening material
it was a while you got purpose out of
them
[Music]
foreign
you
number two
[Music]
and excuse me snacking on a pair right
now i'm almost done
think of this as power asmr
all right now that we're done with that
we eat our third apple i'm just kidding
intensified voice yummy bear
oh she i don't know what pair is in
japanese
thought i knew all the fruit
why did you stop snoozing it isn't
terrible for you
the worst part is the cost but it's not
dangerous
yeah well i'm trying to be free from all
sensational pleasures
excuse me while i sip on this g fuel
one step at a time okay
be
i have some pear that's how you remember
that not sheet
[Music]
nah you want some apple nah she i want
pears now you forever remember
nashes pear in japanese
you're welcome unless someone's almost
trolling me
kinda wanna thank you damien forgot your
message but good to see you're here
here i kinda wanna
take a screen shot but it looks like the
game doesn't allow me i'll go back
yeah apple is ringo it's just easier to
think of ringo starr
although it's an easy one to remember in
general you don't really need mnemonics
for everything
oh we're in a fox then
that'd be so cool i could be like hey
this is where the mongols were
and kill kill
sorry what is our goal
there is a fox then right behind us i
kind of want to see if i can get it
no god damn it
we'll get it later it's whatever so it's
whatever
i want to take a screenshot
reach the cliff side
i take a different run huh
this is where we use the grappling hook
[Music]
jump and press r2
nice
sweet
cool
spooder samurai i like it like you like
it
i don't care
a man
wants to take a goddamn selfie a man
will have his goddamn selfie
do you understand
foreign
[Music]
no you [ __ ]
can i save myself good day man thank you
kylie withers god damn
can i save my settings for like a shot
so i don't have to redo it everything
you know i mean
[Music]
all right sorry i'll stop we'll take
some more screenshots later okay
it's whatever
you know what if i do a screenshot here
though wouldn't this be sick
wouldn't this be a six screenshot
this let the sun just hit perfectly
sorry i'll stop
almost died intentional
almost died intentional almost died
intentions
where the hell do i go from here
ah solano
hey
that's kind of cool
bum
just a quick one
we at the top
all right we gotta free the prisoners
good morning to you too
oh man
well they ain't here
[Music]
you can hold share button it'll take
screenshot law
sorry
can you guys stop
[Music]
[ __ ] these guys are strong
[ __ ] you don't like my clothes
the hell observe the leader all right
let's do it then
i want the moon stains
pump
this is the way
is that the leader
[Music]
where's the leader
more chicagni
[Music]
okay
oh [ __ ]
[Music]
we gotta find the leader i think he's
here somewhere
[Music]
i think they saw me
we're so close to the leader should i
just tactically die
tactical dad
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
oh
oh what happened [ __ ] i got so into it
[Applause]
oh god i'm gonna die now
what the [ __ ] oh god
jesus christ
okay here we go
whoa
[Music]
can you stop
oh god i'm almost there
[ __ ]
that was my clutch moment i [ __ ] it up
and i'm back all the way here now
worth it i think i think the leader is
still dead i don't think
this is my moment
guess they're not then what the [ __ ]
check it out check it out
can i climb here
nice okay
oh i see
[Music]
no one saw me
wow
you're free
kumasan
live a life
[Music]
go bear hey don't attack bear
hmm
they're tough i'm not gonna lie
what do i do
that's totally what i meant to do
surprise
there's the leader
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[ __ ] [ __ ] thing [ __ ]
[Music]
god damn i suck pp
i need more of these
zero dash shut up
if i can stop wasting [ __ ]
don't tell anyone
i didn't die it was a tactical
tactical peepee my poopoo
how you doing mate
i blocked that what the [ __ ]
wow
[Music]
that's how it's done it's easy
i said block but i mean dodge
yeah learn my language
learn how i speak and then you tell me
all right where are we going
i don't have no [ __ ] clue
[Music]
yeah apologize
did i actually miss
sure
he's [ __ ] crazy
those two are so tough
but not tough enough you're free my
friend
i save your life you're welcome
live a life and be free and live life
and freeness who saw me over here
surprise [ __ ]
new subscribers i like your intro thank
you guys
we gotta let the beer out
honestly i felt bad for not doing it
before
[Music]
oh he's not here anymore this is so sad
they're dead in another
beer will be my girl
think [ __ ]
every [ __ ] time i die from that
goddamn attack i swear to god i want to
die
how do i not know the controls this far
in the game
there we go
the [ __ ] is another beard
all right we did it sorry barry you
can't come with us
i thought we did a challenge thing where
are they
please use your hearing mode to find
objectives switch stances mid fight
please i do
shut up
look i found the objective thank you
i wish it was clear though like when i
changed quick it's like oh
did i do it i don't know love your
period thanks for yesterday's tribute
video thank you
shubham very nice
yeah we should really do a mythic yeah
yeah that's such a backstage
standoff food
all right smoke bomb
they're just dying what happened
how what the [ __ ] was i
[Music]
all right let's not do that
go
oops
i can't [ __ ] hit anything what the
hell
that's better that's better
make them go boom boom
you're the last one left you're
embarrassing yourself
thank you thumpy thank you
[Music]
nailed it
sorry
um
i've died uh let's see zero time so far
in this playthrough
just chilling with my horse
feet licks nice thank you
[Music]
i never heard anyone call me feet licks
before great
make sure to do all the bamboo strikes
yeah i'll do them as they come
i take it as it is i just breathe in
each moment you know
you know hey hope
why can't can someone stop me from
taking screenshots of this [ __ ] game
[Music]
i'm gonna get somewhere higher
can't get up apparently well [ __ ] it
selfie was invented in ancient japan
yes
how many acts are there and am i on act
one still
no don't stop taking screenshots i over
a thousand ghosts of
tsushima screenshots i regret none of
them
kitsune me damnit day
have you been to kyoto golden temple yet
i have
it's a bit too popular it's kind of
ruined by tourists
not sure if i would recommend
[Music]
so
hey he thought i was done with
screenshots huh
oh you guessed wrong
so
okay i'll stop sorry
[Music]
ah [ __ ] what are we doing here boys
now this is a screenshot
summer love i call this one
i call this one ow my [ __ ] foot
yes
[Music]
now we get a charm salon finally
thank you thank you you're so cute
[Music]
[ __ ] it's been so long
goals weapon deal 20 more damage
so
thank you bang
tata's armor is awesome but have you
gone
gosaku's armor no i haven't just
ordered your chair finally still on
floor gang for life though
hell you
[Music]
in
i haven't gotten soup yet no aiming not
yet i'm working on it
thank you
um
oh we progressed the story
yeah you should have killed me the daily
pills crying hell yeah thanks for being
here guys
is
yeah the characters are linked but
momentarily won't go through but maybe
now they will
a few hours later
we're close
[Music]
yeah sorry
uh
optional speak with your allies hello
this is a big quest coming up i gotta
pee then i don't know if you read super
chats
uh but
foreign
why did no one tell me my hair was so
crazy
the [ __ ] thanks for nothing
all right where did my friends go
um
so the game is in different acts if i
understand comm comments correct how
many acts are there and
are we almost done with act one then hey
i'm a big fan tier three member hell
yeah i was wondering
donation also goes to charity no they
don't uh refund if you want also haven't
seen
one of these streams in a while but it
looks like has really progressed
and it's
[Music]
yeah because like we have
the the whole yeah toyota
and kamiya
so cool man this game is huge
did i wash my hands maybe maybe not who
know
you will never know you will never know
if i washed my hands
[ __ ] do i look like a
[ __ ] that washed my hands
[ __ ]
i do the japanese hand wash where they
just pretend to wash your hands
they just say let's splurge it with some
water
yeah that's clean
that's clean now oh is it today
where you have to wear masks in uk
is it today yeah 24th right or did i get
it wrong
if you enter a shop you have to wear a
mask
where she's like finally [ __ ]
i always feel like i'm the only one
wearing a mask wherever i go and i feel
so weird about it and it's like it
doesn't [ __ ] work if i'm the only one
wearing a [ __ ] mask it's all
pointless
i'm looking stupid for no reason
everyone has to wear it that's the point
that's the goddamn boot what am i
grappling with
[ __ ]
where do i use the grappling hook i
don't [ __ ] see it
there
finally finally
yeah i might do mask merch now that
it's um
less opportunistic and more something i
just want
because legit i was looking around on
the internet for cool masks and stuff
and they seemed hard to find like
all of them are really ugly or really
cringe
do not raise the alarm all right
you guys know me
[Music]
i'm stealther number one
you're dead my dude
you dead my dude
[Music]
let me kill you in your sleep
that's gotta suck i feel bad for that
[Music]
good morning
i killed you in your sleep
[Applause]
[Music]
i feel bad okay i feel bad
[Applause]
[Music]
i could probably kill them in one arrow
should i try it
there we go that wasn't really one but
it worked
here we go it's all happening
i hope there's a boss fight it's been a
while they're always fun
yeah i'm more for simple designs as well
a lot from australia thank you ben
robinson yeah i think something
like a black mask and then maybe just
the wave pattern as a square or
something on the side
could be cool
that's all you need baby
collect arrows yeah i was literally
thinking that
definitely need it for the upcoming
battles
for the upcoming
[Music]
maybe they're in here
it
huh
every time it happens the same way that
[ __ ] guy
swings his [ __ ] thing i dodge it but
i'm don't dodge it
and i don't know what the [ __ ] to do god
[ __ ] damn it he's so annoying
i guess i have to roll away from them
i just want to kill kill killing
can i you fools
[Music]
i cannot you fool
[Applause]
they won't [ __ ] die
there we go
thank you
now give me supplies
[Music]
you want to play the flute
i want a boss fight come on
near the bridge no not now
where oh god guys what am i gonna do
what am i gonna do are you winning some
no look at the objective dad this is a
problem
oh [ __ ] oh [ __ ] oh [ __ ] uh
they didn't see me did they i don't
think they saw
oh yeah
[Music]
[ __ ]
oh we've been here before
am i out of arrows
no i'm not what the [ __ ]
[Music]
why was i not shooting before
please
all right we're almost there this is
where we died last time
hey is it echoing in here or something
will come in the last minute
ah screenshot temptation intensifies
this is the tough one guys
hmm
oh there's the leader all right we're
[ __ ] expecting him
i'm expecting the [ __ ] out of that
leader that leader won't know how much i
look at his ass
you're dead though
ugh
i'm so close god damn it
how do i know who the leader is
nailed it
foreign
[ __ ]
they're blind apparently
there's quite a few of them
oh
uh
[Music]
there it is
boom
[Music]
nice
foreign
what just happened
too strong yes i'm winning dan
look at me dad of course i'm [ __ ]
winning dead
of course of course i'm winning dad
don't you see this move son i open gates
and [ __ ]
two easy two weeks give me a challenge
he burned me in himself good job arrow
guy
more like arrow lamer
just need supplies and wind chimes and
[ __ ] you know i'm saying
you know it's good
it's hard i'm playing hard mode shut up
but the game might as well call it easy
mode
you know because i never even died in
this game
find a way faster lock gate
um
here we go
i knew he would come i told you bro
he's just dipping his feet i respect it
[Applause]
[Music]
he did not join ceiling gang no no
m
[Music]
anime betrayal
ceiling gang i spit on you
[ __ ] unbelievable
ow [ __ ] that hurt i need to learn how to
darshan do it again
oh
all right i think that was a good first
try
i can do it zero deaths though so let's
try and do then
[Music]
m
um
[ __ ] i was trying something else and it
didn't work
that was terrible
that was my move
i have plenty of health it's all good
[ __ ] come on i can do it easy
sorry it's a simp there i said it
there it is
[Music]
ah
there it is that was sweet
no i have him
no i [ __ ] up shut up about heavenly
strike that's what [ __ ] me over i used
it
it was your fault
god damn it shut the [ __ ] up about
heavenly strike god damn it it's your
fault it's your fault
[ __ ] if i hadn't blocked that it
would've been so good
[Music]
got plenty of
i can do it easy no problem
he gets easier every time i play him
[Music]
that [ __ ] thing i don't know how to
dodge and it's very annoying
hmm
[Music]
god damn it i go from slaying it to
sucking it so quick
why can't i use my [ __ ] attack over
his
you know i [ __ ] you know i [ __ ]
[ __ ]
[Music]
um
[ __ ] didn't see it and i'm dead
he's a tough one
shut up game don't patronize me i can do
it easily
easy trust me guys easy
it's a joke
you traitorous [ __ ]
[ __ ]
i [ __ ] dodged it too soon
so annoying oh
[Music]
that was close
there comes
plenty of health
plan of health
plenty of health [ __ ] i got plenty of
help
heavenly strike doesn't [ __ ] work he
[ __ ] me over
what a dick
unbelievable [ __ ] ceiling gang cringe
oh
now we're angry right
and then we die at the co this is like
the epic moment and i died
are you done thank you
[Music]
thank you for waiting
calculated
i know how to deal with these [ __ ]
are you serious i'm burning
nailed it don't hurt me don't hurt me i
can get up i can grab
can you get up from there
that was [ __ ] i hit all of them in
the head and you [ __ ] know it
[Music]
there it is
[ __ ] yeah
and i [ __ ] it up goddammit
see i dodged but it still hits me
there we go
that was some nice stance shake and
stance
change and stains arrow and
face and yeah that was cool you know
it's cool
you know you're playing the realest
gameplay of the world man
i'm the illest the realest the killers
gorillas and i think the
pillars into make a mama in the
dollar billas yeah did it
thank you
whoops
oh we got a new unlock sweet
[Music]
can i do it yep
and that's always done
you don't talk to me you don't look at
me
[Music]
give me that [ __ ] poor gang up in
ceiling gang what the [ __ ] dude the
[ __ ] though climb
climb
thank you
feels good me
you're free
oh
[Music]
it's uncle and son
time yeah
[Music]
i really wanted to fight the boss again
huh
[Music]
wow
[ __ ] i'm out of arrows this is all we
got big ones
what is happening
am i dead
[Music]
excuse me i believe i did it all
[ __ ] yeah did we do it is this act one
complaint
this is it thanks for sticking with my
channel ever since i'm with the nobody
came in the barrel
two days later far to the north
so we're in the snow gang
foreign
ah [ __ ] he doesn't look too cold
can i still travel to the south even if
i'm in this area
[ __ ]
i already read the donut
[Music]
oh you [ __ ] jesus
christ
oh [ __ ] off dude
quack
a new horizon
the plot thickens at least that's cool
foreign
you know what time it is
[Music]
you can just get her to leave that'd be
great could you get out of the shot
thank you
i like that
so
[Music]
quite like that one
the game be like bro
that's a good one awesome job playing
hard mode dude
could you give a quick shout out to my
mate cj he's a big fan happy gaming
thank you cr and cj
all right i'm gonna end the stream there
wasn't that a highlight
for me to take a screenshot at the end
wasn't that cool
i'll share these on my activities
wait i can play a little bit more
actually i'll just play a little bit
more
i'll just play a little bit more mom
i just want to play a little bit more
can i just play a little bit more
i'll just play just a little bit more
mommy
[Music]
oh yeah i remember this one that was
cool
i'll share this on my member feed
afterwards
because they're cool because they're
epic
i like them that's my wallpaper
it's weird like you're collecting
memories in the game
gotta play the flute
did i share this one
now which one of these were better quite
like this one
[Music]
i love the red filter it's so cool
can you play with the filters like can
you actually
have them on at all times
foreign
yes or no i just want a [ __ ] answer
oh hell yeah
can i play like this a little bit
oh i like this
yes
[Music]
what is
foreign
[Music]
sorry
it looks a little awkward but also very
cool
e a sports the way the game is meant to
play
shortcut
that's not a horse what the [ __ ]
can i ride the cow that's all i want
all right i'm not really playing this is
too slow i'm just gonna stay here
okay epic
did i save it i'm so paranoid that i
don't save for some reason
1941 yeah that's it
all right my fellow friends the [ __ ]
thanks for joining this early ad stream
my dudes it was fun
i like it you guys are cool sometimes
um have a good one
see you next time thanks for joining
do you like my hair do i look crazy i
might take a shower
i feel like i need to
johnny bye bye
hey dude oh we got one more donut
there's this channel called pewdiepie
nursery rhymes everyone wants you to
notice him all right
yeah i don't have time to look out of
everything but sure great
i'm glad so