what's up [ __ ]
it's me
look how pretty this place is should i
do it
start off with the screenshot
whoa that looks cool i like that
while we wait for the fox to come in
i like how we got the bird there as well
how are y'all doing fellas
it's literally one viewer in here i
don't think it's pushed
what up one person in the live
chat how are you doing
how are you
show yourself one person
reveal yourself now
reveal yourself to the jedi
cool
mori
whoa that looks pretty
i love this one
screenshot that [ __ ]
[Music]
why is there only one person in here
this is very confusing i'll just
publish it to all oh i'm the only person
have i been talking to myself
now i know how streamers that have no
audience feel like
feels bad man
all right we got some peeps in this
[ __ ]
i was taking a screenshot look at this
okay no
that looks pretty epic too
[Music]
i like it i like it
i publish a video now as well
a lot of pewdiemie at the same time
oh my god it's the best
jab at the hands
they call me job of her for a reason
here we go
love this new armor that i have it's so
cool
uh it's my dad's armor i played a little
bit offline yesterday i'm sorry
i'm so sorry okay i'm sorry
i'm sorry i played a little bit on my
own i'm
[Music]
sorry
what do you want me to say i'm sorry
[Music]
i'll make an apology it's just
everyone's so [ __ ]
far in this game everyone's already
[ __ ] finished it and there's so many
side quests and shits i was like all
right i'll do some side quests no one's
gonna care
i'm sorry
are we doing the it looks cool right
i love it i can't change color of it for
some reason
armor is the best armor because i have
that one too i did the side quest
is that better
massive increase to health stagger
damage
major increase to melee damage massive
crystal
i think sakai is better now massive or
moderate
or major or massive
which one is better
i guess i could upgrade it one more time
though
i got pretty this
i think i prefer the look of this one
i did i did some little dabbling off
stream
this morning because i just wanted to
play sue me
sorry i'm [ __ ] sorry
so i stopped snoozing right so i thought
i need to pick up something else so i
pick up christian my friend
but they [ __ ] burn through your dude
this looks so pretty
they burn through your
stomach and everything they're not a
good
i don't recommend oh this is kind of
mysterious
basically my stomach hurts that's what
i'm saying
so you can get a diet for the sakai
armor from the black dye merchant where
is he located
my father here you go jesus christ gmk
out of nowhere 100 bucks
[ __ ] yeah thank you so much
are you winning son
yes dad i donated to pewdiepie hundred
dollars and he saw it
it was that big oh there's a bamboo
strike here
where
i look handsome today well you thank you
so
much i'm using this new hair spray
that i've been drinking it tastes so
good
i think it's been clearing out my skin
can i jump down here
you don't know unless you don't try okay
i can't jump there
all right i'm just gonna do a thousand
push-ups
no problem right
now your hair looks like that chad meme
really
step by step here's the bamboo sweet
let's do it
what are you on about canis i'm not
gonna click that link can you explain
instead
um
i [ __ ] it up again my bad
there we go that wasn't difficult
a thousand percent muscle increase okay
so click click click click click click
dick
yes yes yeah
nice cool
oh i think edgar's doing something on
the door
oh god
did leg day today on workout thank you
for asking
passed out again
not epic
slept for 30 minutes my brain went bye
bye
oh you act you exercise leg bye bye
brango bye bye
there she is what's up
what's up
[Music]
oh dude they're wearing my hat this is
like my clan
40 years ago fire nation attack hey guys
what's going on
what are we talking about here
that's epic i should go to the barn
search for umig call for the pirate
what excuse me
there we go
[Music]
what's the brand of baggy trousers that
i always wear i don't remember but it's
a good brand
although i bought other pairs of that
brand and they don't fit as well
so i will not recommend them no i will
not
a good fitting pair of pants is hard to
come by my friend
and i will wear the [ __ ] out of them
is this the merchant black
white might look cool why does it take
so long to load
oh golden
a whoa
which one do we want they all look so
cool
i like them all i want to get them all
which one do i get i need help red is
pretty dope
but it looks a bit cheap doesn't it
but light is so cool too it looks so
clean it looks like a minim
like i'm on a minimalistic samurai slay
i like white a lot
i think i will get both white and and
gold
so that they're more cool
gold hell yeah
oh that looks good that looks really
[ __ ] cool
what is that mask
oh oh
oh that looks cool
oh that's cool huh
[ __ ] yeah
[ __ ] yeah oh dude we gotta change our
sword to
die now god damn it hell yeah
oh dude this makes me so hyped
you see this [ __ ] yeah you don't [ __ ]
with me
69 muscle increase from clicking on
channel what did it work
a lot of you guys so yesterday's stream
we did 10 push-ups if i die
and a lot of you guys said you joined in
as well i thought that was kind of fun
maybe we should do that again
let's get swole gamers actual muscle
percentage increase follow the guard to
meet lady sanjil
[ __ ] if i didn't pay attention
where is this [ __ ]
this is what i get for not paying
attention
doco girl you got me loco
oh is it upstair
yeah everyone's saying upstairs ipit
sent the dm an insta hope you read
promise it's not weird just a longer
thank you message for making me and my
fam smile for years anyways thank you
for helping me make it through
more than you know floor again that's so
sweet thank you very much
thanks for watching
[Music]
[ __ ] let's do the let's do ten
push-ups let's do it together
if we die promise promise you'll do it
with me
and for each time we'll add one push-up
so we start on 10 then we'll do 11. then
12.
yeah you're in you're in all right let's
do it
nice uh ooh one upgrade on swordsmith
trapper oh there's a myth sequence down
here too
[Music]
we should check out this city longbow
upgrade i don't give a [ __ ]
let's check out the city a little bit
versus swordsmith
no push-ups today cause zero deaths okay
yeah
let's make it happen then
it's probably not good to do the same
every day but [ __ ] one
this is just for fun uh
cool city can't [ __ ] find anything is
there any way to like
find i don't know why it's so difficult
to find
are you the armorer
what is this like a secret entrance
huh cool
pull ups where how
please make it five if you can't do it
do it on your knees
it's better to do something than nothing
where's the armor
quest is here
cartwheels what the [ __ ]
yeah let's do it let's do in the mythic
quest
oh god we'll definitely
[Music]
here's some charity money uh devils the
super chat don't go to charity it's only
the membership i'll refund you if you
want to
thank you anyway thank you
previous livestreams
that's cool what is the reward for this
one
should i be wearing the mask or should i
wear that it looks a bit like a corona
mask doesn't it maybe i should change it
that looks so [ __ ] scary
not that one that looks [ __ ] cool too
dude
nah it doesn't fit this is like
height beast meets
meet samurai
all right let me find the [ __ ]
privilet
is there possibility that merch and
cleveland will be delivering to
russia i sure hope it does i'm really
sorry about that
there has to be a way to check on the
map where the swordsmith is
i'm not sure why i'm struggling with
this so much
bird here
[Music]
sword schmidt
i guess i can just go to could literally
just go here at least i know where it is
let's get some presents
upgrades
hey felix you're my personal here all
and complete inspiration you are
a spark for my passion to entertain
other people i'm going to make it
personal goal to talk with you in the
last one year from now keep being great
well i guess you just did we just talked
hello how are you
nice to meet you what's up damian
when did i get that outfit uh don't ask
questions
armor like that will never fail you my
lord
[ __ ] i'm so close all right let's not
upgrade right away then i'll go soon god
damn it what a waste of time
all right so where's the mythic quest
locate the straw hat assassins in toya
toyotama toyota
um
where
is it here what is that oh i got a
technique point if i do that
gold as well
[ __ ] it i'm doing this now sorry i got a
little sidetrack
i think i really need that because then
i can upgrade my armor or sword
which i will need to not die a million
times
yeah i'm playing serious now
is this is this game better than uh
skyrim i never played skyrim
[Music]
stumble food
this guy should be weak as hell now
right
look i can do three times now one
two come at me bro
hey who's the last one
come at me
[Music]
yeah you better run you better run
don't think so [ __ ] [ __ ]
i play flute now
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry yeah i'm a bit op now
it's whatever i i also have the blow gun
now which can
poison and hallucinate people i still
don't know how it works
but yeah that move is pretty good
the armor makes it so i can do one more
extra slice and then
there's the move where i can charge uh
and then yeah let's take over this city
sorry mongols look away
but this place
try the blowgun in this area okay yeah
that might be a good time to try it
because i never actually tried it
so hallucination makes it so they go
against each other
reclaim stolen armor kill with poison
darts
i only have one [ __ ]
they never see me but here i am
these masters
you doing that bro oh [ __ ] no no no
[ __ ] i missed one don't sound the alarm
he's gonna go loco
he's about to freaking lose it guys
trust me it's gonna be insane
i really have not been looking in these
buildings good enough because you always
get the resources
for upgrades my bad
at least i know now someone sees me
that's fine where
he's in the ceiling [ __ ] cringe
[ __ ] cringe
the armor looks cool dude
oh i tried it
[ __ ] oh i did it
pretty epic
can we get this guy
[Music]
could have been cool
oh
how
here we go
god damn these [ __ ]
[Music]
[ __ ] block
there's an arrow there oh god
oh god oh god
[Music]
nice
jesus don't want to die
that's how we do it shoot his legs get
his legs
[Music]
where you running [ __ ]
the [ __ ] you going [ __ ] get back
here
ah
[Music]
how does death feel like god damn
there's so many this is insane
i'm so focused because i don't want to
die
i love it it's so fun these missions are
my favorite just [ __ ] kill everyone
what does that say about me i'm not sure
hopefully good things that i i'm kind
and sweet
in a gentle zone probably yes
so what do i have here
kunai this is the sticky bomb that's
kind of fun
how many push-ups have i done sarah so
far zero that's [ __ ]
who sees me
oh
[Music]
doctor
where is he
uh parrying and killing makes the
thing goes up like the
healing thing or whatever and i can use
that for
abilities as well so generally just
killing but a perfect parry gets you a
lot of
refill as well and that sort of stuff so
you want to time your
[ __ ] no push-ups today boy
ain't happening ain't happening
too strong yeah
should really use kunai's more because
they challenge remaining enemies nice
keep up the good work floor gang hell
yeah
what the [ __ ]
god damn mongolian
yeah i meant to do that
all right let's get this thing then do i
have any more poison darts
no i couldn't have gotten the quest [ __ ]
[ __ ] the [ __ ]
here we go
so one more banner where is it
where a bender
there it is
doing good
just wait until the mythic quest i'm
definitely gonna die all over
all right are we done here destroy black
power
cashie is it cash or cashy
now these are the real questions
[Music]
where is where's the black power
question
there it is found it
everyone's saying different now i can't
trust anyone you're liars
that's you when you mispronounce cache
right there
don't ever try and say it again cashew
cashew nuts
casheen
[Music]
damn i did a lot more damage than i
thought i'm sorry mongolians
i'm sorry about that one bro
yeah a new technique sweet
[Music]
we should have enough should i upgrade
the armor or the sword
you tell me because i should have enough
now
catch me outside how about that
what happened to that [ __ ] where is she
now nowhere
because she would die as [ __ ] bro
i can't afford it i can only afford
their samurai sword
yeah we can upgrade the sword
is this more aesthetic with our outfit
yes yes it is
let's go back to the golden temple
all right going for sword yeah but what
about zero deaths
[Music]
huh what happened to zero deaths we're
doing so good this live stream
could this be the first live stream haha
pewds go boom boom nick rother back at
it again
what a guy thank you very much nick
what is your avatar that better not be
something bad
that better not be what i think it is
yo look at that uh look at that
i saw this today and i was mind blown
i'm gonna reveal my feet
just warning
see that see that logo
on my foot see that
do you see it
it's the same logo
i was part of the clan all along
huh do you see this
it's the same logo
the [ __ ] what are the odds
those were not my legs by the way cyber
added them in this
his legs but it's still a crazy
coincidence
all right so where you got to go oh
what was it otsuna
where was it toyotama
[Music]
toyota
where is toyotama
help me
mr backseat gamers this is your chance
where the [ __ ] is toyotama
i'm not in toyotama i'm in the golden
temple
oh that's toyotama avatar
is a russian double-headed eagle just
for you nothing bad pierce epic
thank you thank you nick
okay so i need to find the straw hat
once
no i don't skip leg day my legs are
beautiful shut up
i literally did leg day today literally
like daily
look how esthetically pleasing my
character is
this is i am literally goals
there's about five of them
just track the quest and use the wind
wind doesn't help me but look how cool i
match the background
maybe maybe i'll just google this quest
this seems like a difficult one to find
so this quest is called six blades of
kojiro
uh six
plates of congee
[Music]
i look on google image search
i tried to find the code
[Music]
boo
on this guy defeat the five straw
yeah okay okay okay they're showing me
where they are
all right so there's one south of
old kanazawa march
i think i've already beaten this one to
be honest
it should be here yeah i have to beat
him again
gamer a's 18 hundred bucks pizza epic
you're epic
huge peepee god damn you guys are
generous what the [ __ ]
you know a millionaire right you know i
have monday right
thank you we'll still accept that
without shame
okay so this one is checked
i do want to do an epic
that's pretty cool
looks like death stranding
damn that looks cool
whoa not even intentional
[Music]
damn all right so we've done that one
uh there's another one north of field of
equino
flower where is that
it's next to smugglers
oh there we go okay it should be there
i've already done this one
too
okay and then there's another one next
to
kenzo's inn could have been mount umi
oh god
where's mount only
coast
gonna be here
excuse me am i even supposed to be doing
these
they're on the map
can you please give big pp blessing to
my huge people blessings
to my send huge peepee blessings from
nick rother to tecla
nick rother says you big pp i bless them
came from my mouth that sounded weird
what the [ __ ] sorry
just look at the logo of ronan with a
question mark
so they are on the mat why can't they
see them
there is thank you
we can travel there
you ready to do some push-up boys [ __ ]
i'm tired dude
i'm hungry where'd i do this
the reward is an armor then i shouldn't
even be doing this
[ __ ] all right
should we do crunches instead or
something
what am i doing crunches
shout out sloth on method streams on
weekends
shameless plug
let's do crunches
[ __ ] yeah that's too crunchy all right
we're doing crunches
how many crunches
is he down here yeah i see him
um
20 seems reasonable
uh i want to die on my way there
nailed it
whoa this is a cool setting i'm doing
this purely for the aesthetic reasons by
the way i don't need the armor
and i don't need the crunches i just
really want to kill this [ __ ] guy
okay
let's do it so that
here we go
first try
let him hit the first
see what you got
is that all you got [ __ ]
[Music]
oh wait
that was [ __ ] sweet dude
god damn he [ __ ] hit me once
that was it
i paid my respects
even though you were weak flute this boy
y'all got the flu on this beach hold
on hold on screenshot time
i'm about to flip this [ __ ]
just me and my boys there are no more
chairs at the memes hq
it's floor gang or unemployment
shameless plug but still big pp
chris roseack i'm not sure what you're
plugging but
by all means thank you
there it is
just joined this jacob ties god [ __ ]
damn it
stop daunting so much thank you very
much
thank you so much i just fluted my boy
over here
dude i'm playing on hard mode and i
don't even have the [ __ ] thing so
shut the [ __ ] up
shut the [ __ ] up [ __ ] this game is easy
and that's not my fault
all right we're going for number three
we gotta show these motherfloppers whose
vows
i drink sows
did i not track it
autumn leaves
we will study it the pee pee deeply
[Music]
it's number four oh you're right it's
number four
kill all sims
someone see me
welcome chris rosac to the floor gang
yeah this armor is so cool i agree
should we wait for it to get uh brighter
here we go
look at these mean
uh optimus mass mpp yep
that's all i gotta say sorry i'm in the
middle of something
you about to get the flute [ __ ]
foreign
sarah devs flute gang appreciate you
pissed thank you tristan woods with the
well my ass is on the shot very nice
i don't take car we don't take kindly to
sims around these parts
i'm afraid you're gonna have to get
fluted the [ __ ] out
[Music]
aah
no i didn't heal in times
[ __ ] um
crunches tell me how my form is bad
do it gamers 20 20 or
how many
did you even see me
seven ow eight nine
12 13
or 2
perfect form perfect
you did yours oh you already did a
hundred
i did mine so fast that uh
um shut up
20's too many and do 10 then
simp
here we go here we go we're about to do
20 more
trust me
i almost died i'm definitely dead
it's not [ __ ] fair when i start off
so badly
do it do it [ __ ]
then
ah oh this can be tough isn't it oh
[ __ ]
all right no more dying no more dying
no more dying
no more deaths sarah that's from now on
muscle increase let's go thank you for
joining me
bad form it was perfect for him you just
didn't see it the
great form all right all right
here we go i gotta i gotta do this for
my bros
my broskis come on come on
i did so good the first time
[Music]
one more
[ __ ]
go through
[Music]
10.
[ __ ] i missed him
[Music]
come on
he got me
god damn it this guy's so much tougher
than the other one
i really don't want to do it
five
16.
it's not too bad i don't feel that
anymore
you're counting yours
all right
12 pack incoming bros just join me
it's that easy
[ __ ] what do you know about the floor
gang
not great
i always [ __ ] that up
i had him i can't believe it
i forgot to change whatever i had him
you don't know what happened
all right let's of this i'm sick of
dying i'm [ __ ] sick of it
i'm tired of dying god [ __ ] damn me
at least i'm getting out sword out here
that's all that matters
god [ __ ] damn it come on
all right here we go no more
no more good start
[Music]
foreign
i didn't steal why did i not heal i was
saving my [ __ ]
[Music]
this is [ __ ] why am i taking so long
i was doing so well
what is happening
thank you for everything thank you right
back
what am i on i lost count
no more no more i said no more
i did 420 damn that's not bad
[Music]
here we go
nice punishment
[ __ ] i always forget that the next one
it will definitely [ __ ] block
i'm playing too aggressively
should work
nope
can i i'm tired of leaving the chair can
i just
let's do it on my chair how's this
one two
three four
six ah damn i really feel it
seven oh
hey oh
ten eleven
oh i feel it oh
oh i feel it so much i might stop
my better gonna pop my abs are gonna pop
dude
oh god oh
okay i did it thank you i'll do it
better next time
sorry okay it's just okay come on it
won't be next time
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
um
no
i'm dying again now
who clicked the button
uh
it's not even hard that's why i'm
getting so [ __ ] annoyed
this piece of cake this piece of cake
guy
he's made of cake
[Music]
[ __ ] off with your little
foreign
oh okay so you can hit through match it
it doesn't it it doesn't makes any
[ __ ] sense
because he's hitting past my [ __ ]
things and i don't even care anymore
god's [ __ ] damning it's so annoying
why am i struggling so much
do 20 push-ups i'm sorry
twelve
patience we're doing this with patience
come on
i like the patience
[Music]
oh yeah there it is
no problem at all
[Music]
uh
i was i'm ready for it but it still
don't hit it
[Music]
nice
not nice
that was easy why did it god
damn it thank you
i was so close way too many times thank
you guys for doing the push-ups legends
one punch man in the making right here
i ignored all donations because i was so
pissed off give me one second
that's how it's done petition for you to
play warzone
[ __ ] now simp game
flute gang appreciate you pewds tristan
yeah
yeah you about to get fluted
[ __ ]
you just got fluted [ __ ] you're getting
is laughing at you
you just got fluted
no one flutes me [ __ ]
[Music]
i'm the fluter flute gang
fluke gang feels good man
we all about that flute gang
me and the homie playing the flute
[Music]
i don't know why it took so long i did
the first one on the first try
[ __ ] cringe i got angry and then i
lost focus
and then i got greedy and i made dumb
mistakes
that's what happened all right we got
two more
there's another one
did i do them
oh do you guys see them
say stop if you can see one
yeah they're up north aren't they
those [ __ ] simps are hiding in the
north
not that north
do i have to unlock the map or something
right side of the middle
bottom left
stay in toyotama
wait there's one here
should i just go there
there's one there's one i've done that
one
i've done that one
there's one isn't it no
hey
done there it is
took me a while but i found him call me
huge pp my friends call me small pp
this is my redemption you should be
patrice
who the [ __ ] are you how dare you attack
here again
don't ever go near your again jurgen no
don't be scared
this is a cool area
this is a really dope one
you about to get fluted
where is he
it's down there isn't it how do i get
down
whoops
just jump
uh
oh my god is there no way to get down oh
here we go
whoa what a cool backdrop
where's the shim
there you are
i present a leaf
yo pear's big fan from montreal i gotta
say you kind of need a flute now too
i'm not gonna lie i thought the same
[Music]
homie just fishing though
come on
ah up
[Music]
theory
uh
yes
[Music]
oh i'm sorry sarah that's [ __ ]
first try that feels good i'm so
glad that we don't have to do any more
i'm so happy yeah
you about to get fluted first try
[ __ ] you get the flute
you get the flu if you die first try you
get the flu
you'll get the flu you get the float
get [ __ ] diaper try get the flu oh
get the flu [ __ ]
you get the flu [ __ ]
me and the boys when we get the flute
i can't be bothered doing a proper
screenshot well that'll do
that'll do you got fluted my dude you
just got [ __ ] fluted how did that
feel
you get the blue he got the flute oh
there's the last one isn't it
no we did that one [ __ ] we got one more
all right
where's the last one
yeah i'm still doing push-ups but not
because i died didn't die can you say
happy birthday to my brother joel happy
birthday joel
[Music]
happy birthday it's your birthday zero
dab so far
left side is that it
left side
what did we do that one no
three
i don't see him
i got him all
go back to musician first
okay so i did five now i go back gotcha
sweet
we're doing all of this for an armor
that i will not use feels good man
but we got the flu we got the flu first
try
yeah i [ __ ] love this armor so happy
with it
are you liberal if so that's bad
uh well i'm not stinky so that should
tell you no okay
dude i'll pray for your victory
all right the last one is over here
then we get the flute
this is the closest one
okay
to climb up all this [ __ ]
oh yeah we can stack loose right
i like that idea making like a giant
like you do with megaphones you can
stack megaphones
make like the greatest flute that's
everest
the world has ever seen
i always [ __ ] these up
oh
who's left
i was gonna flip them
oh they're attacking this one
[Music]
[Applause]
don't ever try me anakin
[Laughter]
nice pink scarf [ __ ] where'd you
just get it
amazon
[Music]
let me play the float who's left
that guy was cracking up over my joke
where are they
[Music]
this is the end or is this a barn
[ __ ] off i don't care save for later
[ __ ] i'm busy i just saved your life be
grateful don't be greedy
whoa look at this dude
if only i was floor gang and not
ceiling gang ah cringe
hold up hold up can i upgrade
nope definitely not not even close don't
know why i asked
[Music]
okay let's finish what we started bros
brush brows
hopefully it's in a pretty area i want
aesthetic policing fights that's all i
care about
no more abs i don't have any left
for those of you joining now we're doing
10 push-ups
no 20 push-ups no wait 20 crunches what
am i saying
help me for that so far we've done for
twenty six hundred thousand nine
billion have you read vagabond it's
amazing beautiful manga but miami
musashi sounds interesting
where's this [ __ ] place oh it's down
there
well it's a little city down here
no wait what am i looking at you're
again i don't think you can go
here you're again you're crazy
see you later
do you think we can jump in
the answer is yes wow look at this i
want to take a photo
i want to take a photo
that looks good right
what was the last time you ate a swedish
hot dog been craving one since the video
i want one too
so
there it is
[Music]
i wish i could save my settings so like
if i want to adjust something i can
whatever we're doing a [ __ ] fight
here i forgot
he's at the entrance
is this you whoa whoa it's a giant
buddha
hello you've been such an important
figure to me you helped me through tough
times i never failed to put a smile on
my face i hope you see this many things
mr mister thank you so much mister i'm
glad i cheered you up
with my domestic my dumb [ __ ]
sorry
i'm sorry
oh that looks cool
that's even better
nice all right
is do you like you lose coming this week
i don't think i'm gonna do it
i know you asked for it jose
nothing makes me laugh anymore i'm just
dead inside there's no point
where is this scent oh this is cool he
lit candles for us
that's so sweet he lit the little
candle
uh nice place [ __ ] what you live here
huh you know you're about to get flooded
i'm about to float you [ __ ]
[ __ ]
let's go no push-up coming no push-up
coming
sorry to disappoint you guys but it's
not happening
it's gotta chip them off
how do i do heavenly strike never mind i
don't need to know it
if i keep doing with the stream not from
denmark your fellow viking gang i'll
take
the last mclaren adrian grimes i'll read
you after this
sorry i gotta focus
they don't start with those what the
[ __ ]
what the [ __ ] was that
same
[Music]
nice
now
[Applause]
come on
yes
it's so tough
i guess i'm the one that got fluted
i guess i was the flute all along
[Music]
damn
what do we do now what do we do a
thousand push-ups
we do we do crunches we do crunches we
stick to it
abs will explode
two
five
four
what did i do wrong
i don't know
nice
[Music]
nice nice
[Applause]
stop kicking me
close
a simple slice and i die seriously
a simple little kick
i'm so distracted because he set up this
like romantic
area and i don't know i don't know how
to process it
you know 20 20 do 20 now
no excuse
okay this is my last try guys
but i have a strong feeling that we can
do it
because i hear food is done almost
so difficult i don't see my [ __ ]
health baby like someone asked
uh what
no more fail win win win no matter what
got money
[Music]
nice
how do i block that [ __ ] attack keep
[ __ ] it
up
[ __ ] i got so focused on something else
oh god i [ __ ] up i got permanent help
there it is
got plenty of help god [ __ ] dammit
[ __ ] all right well i'm a man of my work
and i
die now so end the livestream don't want
to do more crunches i'm tired i just
want to play
yeah i parried it all wrong so annoying
all right thanks for watching
thank you i'm gonna go see you next time
um i will study deeply
i will study the play and then i will
return again
we'll get swole next time thanks for
joining
see you bye bye johnny okay
have a good one