am i alive
my internet went down
it was like the lord
what up gamers
can you see me
i gotta confuse her for a minute
what time is it for you [ __ ]
speedy time right answer
only correct answer
i wanted to stream yesterday i didn't
have time
i had a very annoying day yesterday
where nothing was going the right way
i know boo hoo me so i thought i'll
stream today instead
even though today technically not the
streamer day
but i thought uh why waste a day away
when you can be playing video game
that's right
joe rogan you were wrong [ __ ] you
video kept getting claimed yesterday
and i don't understand why
this is one of those annoying companies
that i won't
understand fair use i guess
so shank is a really [ __ ] good video
we'll wait to see if
we can get it released my toes are
shaped like beans
that's funny marcha thinks i have ugly
toast but i think my toes are
like peak per peak physique like
perfection
i never i guess like i never looked at
other people's toes
so i always use my own toes as like the
pinnacle of
what toes should look like
so i had the perfect toes but basically
what i'm saying
and everyone else
you got it all wrong toe reveal i ain't
doing that you guys are [ __ ] weirdos
all i'm saying is just imagine the most
perfect toes of all time
hey is my [ __ ] synced yeah it should be
okay cool how you all doing this blessed
morning
what's up ethan
what is my favorite game to play of all
time tetris
every day if you could only play one
game for the rest of your life what
would it be
that's the real question isn't it try
lethal difficulty there is
how do i change difficulty
my beans toes voices are better no shut
up
they're not you can try
but i have the best toast this is a fact
fact of life
you can try i have to
when do i change the settings
gameplay maybe let's try lethal
death is always close at hand a single
sword strike is lethal
i like that that's cool
if i could only play one game for the
rest of my life
what game would that be
you'd think it's a game that you can
just get really good at
maybe chess but then i have someone to
play against
like something purely gameplay-based it
had to be i got fired today because i
chewed on
shoot a guy out for using the girls
bathroom
is that a window or an l
i'm not sure i don't know but sorry you
lost your job
all right so we die from one hit now
this is super interesting i gotta focus
all right one two
no i died oh i didn't die i thought
lethal was like you died of one
what the [ __ ]
is it did i not set on lethal
is
now felix is it better as you go are you
talking about ghost of tsushima
i love this game
because i kill kill your power is super
high lord pewdiepie your presence is
very amazing
thank you thank you finally people know
how to work this
properly and not always just roast me
i have feelings
why am i so dumb i changed the settings
two seconds ago it was in game play
it isn't lethal death is always close at
hand a single sword strike is
lethal so it's more implying it i could
die from one third strike
you play minecraft you guys are playing
minecraft i guess that makes sense
but man you get [ __ ] sick of
minecraft after a while i guess
no because it's creative and it's up to
you
that's a tough one man yeah i guess
minecraft you could sink
you could sink some hours into
yeah i played offline again but i
haven't done any main quests i literally
just like
look around this area for bits i missed
apparently there's a city here
no i'm not changing the gold armor sorry
dear
the white armor is by far the coolest
one and look
look look look look uh i really want to
get this one for
this one will look so good for jurgen
was it kami no jurgen
that looks sick
um
what's my favorite color what is my
favorite color well
if i told you i had to kill you much
love
ghost sushi is definitely my game of the
year and all right sorry i'll
have to do the stand up
you're dead sorry my dude
whoa how do you get so many of them
okay so i may have unlocked one thing
without you guys
that i probably shouldn't have unlocked
without you and i'll show you
we're still on act two don't worry
splendid the morning my lordship
[Music]
all right i need to find them okay here
we go
okay now i can do this this is so
[ __ ] cool
this is so [ __ ] cool i'm so sorry i
unlocked this without you guys
this is the coolest thing in the game
so basically if you hit forgot his own
lethalness
jesus
i bet you can't eat your toes thanks
i bet i can suck on my toes better than
you
all right what was the donation sorry
love for camp humphreys korea go army
i'm not sure what that means
i got another message where the [ __ ] did
it go how many okay here we go
ghost is your game of the year hope you
enjoy every second of it i really
appreciate
all that you do your contest made me a
happy person over there oh that's nice
mr laughable not so laughable after all
that rhyme epic can you say you are
winning harsh
so that i can watch after i finish
finals i can do the leo pointing me
oh are you winning harsh
do the meme do the meme now
yeah cyberpunk is like the next game i
really look forward to
can't wait for cyberpunk can't wait for
the cyber sex that i can have in the
game
that's gonna be [ __ ] epic apology
video for unlocking ghost mode yeah i
feel
bad i know it really upsets people that
i play a little bit on my own but this
is such a long game
and i honestly didn't mean to do it i
thought i was doing side quests i
i swear i wasn't i think i realized
midway through and i just didn't stop
but this side quest was a lot more epic
than i thought it was
i'm sorry i am a flawed human being i
don't deserve audience i'm
sorry joint floor gang tier three thank
you you shouldn't because i'm not
worthy i'm not worthy did i clear this
area
oh it's not even the area i wanted to be
in what the [ __ ]
[ __ ] am i doing here
it's such a nice game to immerse
yourself with i love the
aesthetic and style and feeling that's
what matters
what the [ __ ] i never seen that happen
on the map before
does that usually happen
if you [ __ ] these up you're so [ __ ]
they put way too much importance on
these
you really i get so
it nervous happening i couldn't see him
[Music]
who are you shooting at bro oh you
[ __ ] up
okay so if we kill three more we get the
special ghost mode or whatever
there's only one left to kill though sad
huge getting better at this game hell
yeah i'm pro i told you bro
i told you i'm slow learner
here we go one more
there we go go smoke
so [ __ ] cool
no you're ruining it ah
you're ruined you're running go all
right you're there
look at his face yeah you
oh god oh god i'm dying
nice there it is
hello dad i just want to say thank you
for bringing us great content over the
years
thank you for being real and humble but
are you winning uh
i just destroyed this whole camp on
lethal
difficulty i think that's pretty epic
let's go
yeah i didn't stream the sakai armor
quest i'm sorry it wasn't even that fun
it was really [ __ ] boring not gonna
lie
uh if you're reading this australia is
not upside down upside down
floor gang
just because you say it doesn't make it
true you understand that right
are we clear on that one chief
osaka's armor upgrade is that one better
maybe i should upgrade sakusaku
how does the hat look for the gosaku
it's hex
check them out sounds cool sounds
interesting
so what are they what do the headbands
do
nothing they do nothing
did the stream go down again what's
going on with my internet
can you just say rosa maria is a noob
yeah i just said it 3 a.m gang
no i'm still streaming it's youtube
that's now
low so lord pewdiepie i must go see
another channel soon
no no
[Music]
how dare you watch other streamers
cringe
honestly
honestly i fully get it i feel like i'm
still learning how to stream
i'm not good at it that's probably
you're dead
oh god sorry doggy
[Music]
oh god i'm stuck
i died [ __ ] you that quick jesus
this will be a challenge
all right i like it
i think that
i think that was what i realized even
though i'm not good at games per se
i think i've gotten really poor that
with them lately
oh [ __ ] that was embarrassing oh my god
i swear i hit that
alright
like if the game isn't challenging i i
kind of
lose a lot of interest in it i think
most
aaa games if you play them on normal
yeah it's not going to be talent and i
can't block these [ __ ] pools
[Music]
this is really [ __ ] tough i should
not have just spoken about this
i blocked this game sucks
i hate it it's too challenging
i'm not doing the push-ups not a lethal
mo [ __ ] that
come on i can easily do this come on
come on
kill an enemy investigating a wind chime
that's kind of it big
[Music]
sorry dog
we cool yeah we cool
that's an easier way to do it
uh you my friend are amazing let me sim
chat let me sim
don't simp for anyone forbidden
forbidden simpery
oh the enemies have a tighter parry on
lethal
okay that makes sense
that explains it thank you bro
[Music]
let's try and get the wind chime kill
i don't think that counted i don't think
that counted at all
3 a.m die must watch live stream love
you thank you guys for staying up
appreciate ya
foreign why am i not getting it
all right at least we have ghost mode
activated
jesus christ that scared me jack what
the [ __ ] is wrong with you
can i please leave my lord i have
business you're loyal okay go
it's okay to go sleep i was joking
my fiance theresa has been a fan of
yours for eight years i was hoping her
senpai would acknowledge
her teresa thank you so much thank you
eight years how are you not [ __ ]
tired
usually people watch a youtuber for like
two years and then like all right i get
it
i'll move on i'll go watch
ninja now thank you
why am opening these i'm doing anything
do you read my favorite book
three body problems yeah i've read that
random chinese dude is your name like
nice i uh it's very interesting sci-fi
it has a lot of cool ideas with it
um i think the characters were
very shallow and forgettable
unfortunately
um and it suffered a little bit because
of it but
overall if you want if you just care
about really interesting sci-fi i highly
recommend it
i'm reading a book recommended by dave
a sci-fi called recursion
which is really good so far at least i'm
only a few chapters in
hello felix greetings from tijuana
mexico
epic
nice
i kind of want to go ghost mode on these
fools
oh sleep gang sleep
forever gang
we'll go back to terraria probably after
this maybe i don't know
oh i saw everything
should we just go ghost motor in this
fool
one guy just had the most oh
nice nice
so [ __ ] cool oh god there's more
god there's so much damage
one guy is like super lethal others a
leader
there we is that go
the leader hi pids loved you ever since
playthrough of
ev we need another ebb game kayla
hell yeah thanks for staying up
i feel like undertale was kind of like
ib inspired but
yeah i want another one what made ib so
good
what made that stand out
it had that same concept of like an
older character and a younger and you
want to be protective but you played as
a younger character though which is
interesting
someone's gotta make it i want another
head
well written well-paced
what the [ __ ] did i just witness did you
guys see that
ah am i crazy
oh god that was terrifying
the hell
[Music]
i guess i'm losing my mind no one else
saw it
you probably like one shot if you like
undertale in it
alright did i clear this area out yet
two more banners
where are they
sashimono banners where are they
when pewds misses your 20 donation
message say hi to conor c
i'm sorry conor c i thought i saw them
all
all the seas hey has been a big fan for
six years love their minecraft series if
you ever in india
i can hook you up with a room in tash
mahal no sweat hell yeah
just a room come on bruh
are the banners i need the batters
someone saw me
[Music]
someone's seeing me i don't know where
they are
oh don't forget the loop
where bish where i'm wearing this sakai
armor
it's the coolest armor for sure
ain't nobody can tell me
what a genius ai we got over here oops
nice clean
clean my dude
feels so clean i got money machine
here we go find another banner i watched
you like nine years ago now i've been
watching for four years
through college love you man got me
through some lonely time
what's up alpha stud what's up oh god oh
god i'm gonna you're gonna make me die
this is wrong why is this guy running
come on [ __ ] boy
your beard's biggest here oh god there's
too many though
god it's tight
[Music]
god there we go
there's a tree in the way and then
there's the arrow guy
[Music]
sexy sexy sexy
i'll read donuts in a second
sometimes game come first i'm sorry
gamers
games over gamers bro you watch food
wars
[Music]
food
it's a line
i think out of like itchy anime i prefer
prison school so far
oh god here you are
does the enemies die quicker as well
i feel like they do on this mode
live spanner boom
no there's one more i didn't pick it up
[ __ ] sorry
all right we just gotta clear up the
camp i guess
ha ha can't go boom boom
yeah i [ __ ] love this armor it's so
cool
boom all right what's your [ __ ]
saying in the chat
damian be like hey happy birthday
there's a henry cavill mod for witcher
that's kind of cool you're streaming it
epic
when met you in 2003 you drew a cute
little picture of australia for me
where did i meet you i feel like we
talked about this i don't remember yo
pewds
okay i read that poor pest thank you
very much
okay we're back on track hey technique
point
what should we do
my dog barked when you said boom sorry
doggy
sorry
upgraded everything almost everything
i feel like i need to do the ghost stuff
yeah let's do this yeah
what is this black powder bomb uh no
that's not that good
yeah i need that i definitely need that
so cool been substance one mil
and i can prove it i got immersed since
old days two now
probably spent like three k overs i'm
your biggest simp
thank you i guess what makes you simp so
hard
i'm curious if you can simp for anyone
in the world
i'm flattered obviously thank you
but what the [ __ ]
okay we're done here let's go back on
the main quest
think it's this one
yeah let's go gamers
main quest time hey felix huge fans
since your last guardian gameplay happy
wheels love you more than anything
please say hey victoria what's up
victoria
gloria borga victoria thank you tr
unidentified
all right it's time to speak with lord
shimura
oh actually do i have enough i want to
get the jurgen armor so bad let me just
go here really quick
i need one more i need one more banner
i agree second book of three body
problem is the best one okay maybe i
should keep reading it then
you must die much
[ __ ] i need one more banner
i need jurgen to look beautiful this is
not fair
do you feel ever feel guilty for not
remembering someone who said they met
you
not really it'd be really [ __ ] hard
for me to remember everyone plus i have
bad memory as it is
conor the guide thanks for being here
connor can you help me through this game
where's the banner i need another banner
journey series and i already play that
love this community and you have been a
big part of helping me cope through
deep depression so i will support
forever all potato
thank you
[Music]
i watched this video that was so
brutally honest i don't know who it was
but it was this really buff
guy uh
and he was talking about how he was
addicted to simpery
like he was addicted to and it wasn't a
troll
i think he was serious it was so uh
brutally honest he was just saying how
is he not shimura who the [ __ ] is lord
there we go uh
he was like i'm addicted to donating to
e-girls
and how big of a problem it was now it
was affecting his life
like it's kind of thing where you kind
of want to laugh about it because it's
like haha simp but it's also like you
know
damn it i didn't get it like
what a [ __ ] loser if anything i
respect that he was talking about it
and he talked about how he overcame it
thanks to his girlfriend
she uh she helped him like recognize him
it helped him monitor him so he wouldn't
don't like monitor his bank accounts and
stuff like that
simping is an actual illness
who would have thought serious we've
been making fun of it this whole time
i wonder if the fact that it's such a
stigma to be a simple is like
actually causing more harm because
people get addicted and then they can't
get out of it and they don't
they don't want to admit it to other
people so they can't get help
hey pewds my name is miguel from la
thanks for being such a huge role model
source of entertainment i wouldn't want
to
sip for anyone else but yeah
thank you
perfectly timed you've been diagnosed
with sin
[Music]
about something in japan that sounds
interesting
there's got to be a healthy level though
it's got to be a healthy level
[Music]
guess it's better than smoking
a month or two and quitting it
feels like losing a close friend of mine
it's so crazy
it feels like i lost a good friend of
mine
it and i had a smell and i was like oh
god
i actually was like oh [ __ ]
not healthy man
but yeah i'm free from addictions right
now feels good man
just got video games left
hey pewds how's your animal crossing
island coming along i stopped playing it
i know there's a ton of great updates
i'm doing my second week quarantine
because of coronavirus luckily i was
negative your streams videos keep me
occupied during these times thank you
and never stop being epic thank you for
being epic mate
just leave okay
the smell of cigarettes is so nostalic
for me but i never smoked
interesting
doing curls should we start doing curls
that might be fun
i'm too tired right now i'm not gonna do
it
excuse me oh god i'm gonna die oh no
good night say it back no no i will not
we're doing mainline quest [ __ ] yeah i
think
are we almost done with act 2 because
this could this be the end of act 2
already
i want to see i'm curious
install tatami mats on your floors i
called them
tonkatsu mats last time
we used to have tatami mats oh god i'm
out of battery
and now i regret removing them
i could have been floor again guys
where do i charge this
are the mini ruby brofist actually lost
forever yes
but it lives on in my heart
sometimes i can't tell if i'm crazy or
if i'm going through a mid-life crisis
it's like i genuinely don't want these
items and everyone else seems like
they're so important but i don't wanna
i don't wanna
[ __ ] sake
i think youtube ruined possessions for
me
if you get everything for free then
nothing has value anymore
and items just start becoming a burden i
know it sounds super
like boo hoo or wow what a privileged
[ __ ] but that's just how it becomes
you get a package every single day
it sort of ruins the way you look at
things
but i'm charging it
the [ __ ]
hey pete's been watching for 10 years
now i was 12 when i started watching i'm
22. good day from
made quick question who's your favorite
avatar last bender character
the simp one guess i'll have to watch
avatar guys
otherwise we have nothing to in common
you and i
where's this [ __ ] camp
hey felix my entire family watches you
are they all watching the livestream
brenda much love from the lopez family
what up lopez
hell yeah
am i gonna be big sad after act two
yeah jack said he cried or he was
tearing up at least
well you ever become sick of any of your
buttons send them my way all right
fair enough
i'll survey the [ __ ] out of you [ __ ]
how the [ __ ] do i get in let me in
maybe i can get up here nope
i was wondering what your thought on joe
rogan said about gaming yeah i'm kind of
interested in maybe making a video on it
because i think it's so funny how that
became such a big deal
[Music]
can you believe what joe rogan said
about video games [ __ ] i'm dead
i nearly shat myself
does his opinion really matter i think
it's more the
other people's reaction to his opinion
patiently waiting
for my floor gang mercedes so i fight
every ceiling in australia thanks for
being my favorite youtuber
thanks for watching appreciate it
guess we have to go this way
heavenly strike your way inside
okay
yes i will
can't find a way in this fort
you even had the brofist backpack hell
yeah those were awesome
need more backpacks how the [ __ ] do i
get in
oh my god did i really run in a circle
survey
i'll just tell me oh i see i'm supposed
to oh my god why did no one [ __ ] tell
me
why did no one tell me i spent five
minutes
why didn't no one tell me my brain's
small i have to do one of these
oh [ __ ] yeah i want to blow that [ __ ] up
i'm winning dad i surveyed the kobayashi
whatever
come on
shit's about to go down
may you continue to entertain us for
many more years to come hell yeah
[Music]
oh now i enter
but where do i enter
this is where the story really picks up
oh cool
[Music]
your fourth is mine at fourth night
the night is fourth fourth
night fortnite [ __ ] you play it
make your way to the upper game
yeah i gotta kill people on the way bruh
i think they saw me no they didn't
[ __ ] that was close
can't really hear the game hippies i've
been a fan for a long time
i can't see me i'm a ghost
you didn't see me but here i am [ __ ]
oh fear me mongols
yes who's next
[ __ ]
what the [ __ ] happened there oh my god
i'm dead
[Music]
oh you guys are getting buried
there it is
i hate you so much i'm gonna [ __ ]
kill you with an arrow even if i burn
today
so annoying he doesn't pull the arrow
back
stairs god [ __ ] damn it
all right i made it out of that just
playing
lethal too easy
because i'm too good okay as you can
tell
thank you
[Music]
oh i'm terrible at this game all right
let's see your playthrough lethal zero
that like i'm doing shut the [ __ ] up kid
shut the [ __ ] up kiddo be quiet
child child no speak
looks like i took a lot of damage there
i might need some flex tape chief
i'll skip donuts for a second
no you [ __ ]
dudes you made teresa's night she was
freaking so much i thought
the cops would have called checker
that's great
i got played
no they do not take away my armor
[Music]
hardest difficulty whatever i'm a pro
gamer
man i thought we were bros i can't
believe you just betrayed me like this
yeah at least let me keep the hat dude
does he not understand that that tactic
is not going to [ __ ] work
just so no kutuba
foreign
foreign has there ever been a video game
where the
the main character died just get to play
somewhere
oh he's never gonna betray me um we're
best bros
no kill him
the [ __ ]
no we're bros red dead redemption did
that oh okay
i didn't know that never played it
yes that's my bro no
[Music]
now
jesus christ
yeah i can see that
another one went to bahamas
damn damn
taka f in the chat
at least he died an honorable death
and not a filthy stinky ceiling betrayer
see i don't understand like if your
hands are tied why don't you just double
tap
zero circle i mean
oh i'm pissed [ __ ] angry
i'm [ __ ] angry
where my [ __ ] sword at honestly where
is it
oh convenient they are all here
nice kill them all defeat
all straw hats oh we're standing
up oh it's happening it's about to go
[ __ ] down
[ __ ]
god
i totally you [ __ ] up the standoff
you're done i gotta do it right
[Music]
[ __ ] sake i can't even see when he
attacks
what how
[Music]
i used to can i it's an
unblockable attack i don't know
let's try that again bro come on
come on can i see where the [ __ ] guy
is
there it is thank you
next thank you next
next thank you next next
that's how the cookie crumble in the
[ __ ] [ __ ]
yeah you're afraid coming for all you
[ __ ] straw hat [ __ ]
he died by just looking
cringe that's how it's done
[ __ ] you straw hat traitorous
london
there we go change the title of the
stream
where did she go i wasn't looking over
here
probably
you guys see that couple coach react to
your video
he still doesn't quite get that martial
was with you regardless of money
yourself as being big
coach also simp for her
[ __ ] it's getting hot in here
don't ever say poggers in the chat it's
banned from my chat
oh
it didn't help
[Music]
dude look at my [ __ ] armor so cool
oh we got ghost mode on these
[ __ ]
even the dogs are scared
[Music]
run away little dogs run away little
puffer
[Music]
easy peasy on my cheeks
how [ __ ] fast do you die sometimes
jesus
you gotta become better at dodging for
play lee so much
[Music]
snacks
sorry
[Music]
whoa
that's better getting better
come back here fool
[Music]
i keep telling you guys feels good man
feels good to be on top
sorry for what i said before truly love
you and want you to know i feel for you
the difficulties and expectations set by
society
is unobtainable but be you and not what
society media culture expects
i don't even remember what you said but
thank you for apologizing
how dare he
[Music]
foreign
dude he's got the avatar thing on his
head he's hanged
he's hanged from dragon ball he's got
the arrow holy [ __ ]
has no one noticed that
oh you're here to cheer me up thank you
you're again
let's play let's play yeah you're right
let's play a song for taka
i don't know
let's play a song for our dude
lemon of storm yeah here we go
f's in the chair
no keep playing
[Music]
i want a flute now
so pretty with the butterflies
so the main quest continues here
fate of tsushima huh
undiscovered area here though rebels
last stand i never been here
you are the best can i get a shout out
for tick tock guys
shout out cool pro 2020 youtube oh tick
tock
hey i'm a fan a little youtuber from
czech republic your video
on how to get started really helped me
thanks a lot by the way this game is
great
okay cool i didn't realize that i should
actually help people that's awesome
daisy love from the boomers boomer gang
gang
[Music]
bird wants me to jump off a cliff
apparently what the hell
have i ever watched cowboy bebop i do
i have an anime list if you're curious
which anime i've watched
it's my anime list dot net slash beauty
you slash user slash beauty
this way you don't have to ask me what i
want wait what the [ __ ]
are there more
i almost finished steins gate
two episodes live seems really good
this is it this is the last act hope
you're having a great wednesday feelings
wanting to know from
one hundred gigs stand to another if you
listen to their new album
i haven't yet i didn't even realize it
was out
because i heard one song randomly i'm
like wait this is a new song
i'll have to listen to it later
i'm actually really looking for new
stuff
i've been listening to that meme album
that everyone says is like
the best album the aeroplane
in the airplane over the seats
foreign
me and my fiancee love you [ __ ]
watching them all the time if you could
bless us with some big peepee energy
to finish the week big dicks to you and
your fiance
zuni nice
speak with your other allies and then
speak with you
i don't have any friends the [ __ ] game
you really have to rub me in like that
shout out to my friend elizabeth she's
part of flora gang huge fan nice
shout out from me again oh god we're
getting too many donors guys what to do
what do you do suffering from success
again guys this is a big problem i'm
trying to focus on the quest but i get
too many donations stop
donating please
now i'm further away from here
she in here
oh thank god all right
have you already decided which charity
you will donate this month there's a
really cool initiative called money
makes money
don't know if squishy you know what
kelly would but they mad
it's like ugandan hollywood would be
cool to check it out all right i'll
check it out
dudes first just wanted to say i've been
substance amnesia
watching through high school my current
fiancee thank you for the long years of
smile nothing but love brofist prophet
thank you very much
[Music]
foreign
yes
this week with lord oga
big deep energy floor gang indian branch
the indian
branch it's the branches now nice
no they do not they go straight to my
pocket
it feels good man
maybe i should turn it off it is a bit
distracting but it is nice too
so
this is it wait wait what
does this take me to the other place
yeah i think i should say yes
it's optional to speak to my other
allies
here we go last question
why when i saw it
foreign
check upstairs
trolls have been giving you money it's
great right
damn
[Music]
m
[Laughter]
right there
[Music]
feel like it's supposed to be daytime
right now oh there we go okay
[Music]
oh
this wouldn't have happened
here we go oh fb
whoa [ __ ] yeah
i can't do anything there we go
hell yeah
[Music]
[ __ ] yeah this is badass
i hate them so much holy [ __ ]
okay i got the perfect
let's go
ah
i run in and kind of go smack smack god
damn it
fine you know what don't
[Music]
there he is
i missed that
[Music]
i could have been
feels good man that's how it's done
part three video what the [ __ ]
[Music]
oh hell yeah
i don't have anything good black powder
i swear to god i am blocking
they just smack smack [ __ ] sake it's
so annoying
oh
[ __ ] you and your smack smack
[Music]
hold on
my
[Music]
didn't show the red bar thing though
that's why i got confused
am i crazy it's good i use pretty much
everything
jesus they want my ass so bad dude
[Music]
[ __ ] my friends keep dying
oh god
[Music]
oh my god
oh god someone's got to deal with these
[ __ ] archers
oh
[Music]
are they fine yeah okay
nice nice nice nice
nice do we have heavy armor archer
have you taken off status bars i have i
forgot about that i wanted to make the
game as hard as possible
felix i know this sounds crazy but as an
autistic person watching videos helped
me learn to talk better when i was
younger oh that's great
it resulted me yelling like a let's play
for you but i'm thankful oh god
whoa
[Applause]
oh then what is that
they got the mean killing machine
okay
oh god
too busy
he's with me on the machine no
yes
mongol go bye-bye your plans
backfired mongol
more like a locum on
[Music]
that's a lot of mongols
i don't think so i don't think so
[ __ ]
i think we did it
it's like one guy line
[Music]
not done
all right we're done nice
well look at this dude i served thy lord
i am a trebuchet
and that's a pro gamer move forward
[Music]
don't they know you have to play dead if
you're dying
where i am
i know i'm supposed to fight enemies but
i'm also very tempted to look for loot
all right maybe i shouldn't maybe now
it's not the time
all right
i'm faster now [ __ ] burn [ __ ]
we got it we got it
yes
[Music]
this is what i'm talking about
what i'm doing
my [ __ ] phone doesn't connect all
right
sorry
[Music]
something's wrong i feel it
five versus joe rogan match hell yeah
he's too scared though
he doesn't know the real power of gamers
oh god they tricked us
[Music]
whoa
man i keep telling you bro
yeah maybe being samurai isn't so epic
after all
this is why we can't have nice things
right here fate of tsushima
boom we went up all the way
at least that's a good thing demon's
blade [ __ ] yeah that's dope
charm of hidden blades throw two
additional kunai
hell yeah that's a really good charm
um
oh
we have one two three four
five six seven eight am in my bank
account
sorry summer what upgrades do we got now
no new story okay no sir
therefore leaving 19 year old life
behind it's been a good run
sad floor gang noises oh
man we all gotta grow up one day
now you're 19 plus one
um
here since a long time really also
became a fan of brad what youtuber i
really like the relation have you ever
played dungeons and dragons
i literally said that yesterday i'm like
[ __ ] i kinda wanna try don't use the
dragons
deal bonus damage while 50 health or
less
uh which one is better
oh that's really good i never realized i
had that
i think i'll try this for now
mercer and it was so fun
i loved it
me and ken did it for the podcast
remember
have been getting into playing board
games
[Music]
if someone comes and attacks your
territory it's fair game
[Music]
if you're attacking someone else you
gotta fight with honor those should be
the rules
[Music]
do you do i get the choice in the game
if you love dna you should check out
baldur's gate 3.
nice i've heard about that game
ghost armor a gift from taka to enhance
the tactics of ghost
a good friend's final creation oh
ghost mask inspired by sakai mask
oh cool [ __ ] yeah i'm the ghost man
but i prefer my old armor should i
change it back
can i what a dick move what a dick move
he made this for me
no i can't what is the ghost armor there
to reduce it
oh okay so it is good for the mission
could i upgrade it i kind of want to
upgrade it can i go back
no
maybe i should wear charms that helps
that as well then
there we go we're going full stealth on
this
because lord knows i suck itself
[Music]
where do we go from here
i don't think i'm supposed to be here
i have this weird feeling i'm not
supposed to be here
maybe i have no
what just happened i'm so confused
i broke the game bro sorry game
they came out with a patch yesterday i
haven't downloaded it
love you so when are you going to collab
with mr beast keanu reeves and elon
those are definitely checklists
the [ __ ] did i do wrong here
i don't think i'm supposed to go on that
rock
cyber son is in the chat cyberkun
can someone help me i don't know where
the [ __ ]
um
there it is i didn't see it
thank you
i love you so much thank you for ads
i did not read that name right sorry for
said aj
here we go
nice
i did not mean to do that
uh
[Music]
oh i get ghost mode here as well
what's happening why is he running like
a fool
oh [ __ ] guys don't mind me
[Music]
don't worry about me guys
don't sound the alarm
[Music]
this is going pretty good yeah
yeah i wrote you on one time
[Music]
i can't believe i haven't failed a
mission
[Music]
oh wow
oh i'll serve away the [ __ ] out of those
mongols
is that edgar opening the door what a
little weirdo
there's more of them
thank you foreign
[Music]
sure
no one saw me right
no one saw me right you didn't see
anything right
[Music]
i can use those oh
oh my god he doesn't let me jump
[Music]
here we go i'm invisible now
44 000 people
[Music]
all right we're back
why are they running so awkward
any tips the [ __ ] do i deal with this
poison their suit
that will draw a bit of attention you
know i mean
[Music]
oh there's a crack there
you didn't see me but here i am
[Music]
coming at you live with another guild
stream yeah
you didn't see nothing
[Music]
you didn't see [ __ ] nothing
y'all don't see nothing
stealth gang stealth gang snake gang
[ __ ] elk gang
joe rogan be proud of me man ah [ __ ]
you didn't see me
you ain't seen
[Music]
you didn't see me but here i am
elk master 64.
[ __ ] i eat elk you got a problem with
that [ __ ]
how
oh i see i see the path ahead of me
watch oh god
i gotta ferment their milk
[Music]
we've all been there
we've all had that gamer moment when you
gotta ferment the milk
[ __ ] i think they saw me i had this
feeling
imran latif you got teeth bro you got a
flicks about it
damn thank you
[ __ ] alchemy isn't helping man i
gotta
ferment the milk fermented milk they
said
everything
[Music]
will be
all right i see what i must do forgive
me father
washes
they didn't see me i just want to spice
their milk up
is that too much to ask i just want a
banana milk put some piri piri in that
[ __ ]
see this is where i suck my brain just
goes [ __ ] what am i supposed to do and i
don't get it
i don't care what i'm doing is too
difficult
game's too hard i don't like it
watch this
[Music]
watch that watch me go sick mode
watch me go absolute loco
i put the [ __ ] in the chokehold
[Music]
you didn't see me cuz i'm invisible
i'm a block of wood [ __ ]
i'm a block of wood mate you go [ __ ] up
movement
i'm a [ __ ] crocodile right ring up um
i think they saw that
was i really close to it i think i was
really close
man's just trying to be block of wood
fermenting milk
camouflage hundred all right i know
where to go now this is easy
look all right watch this part of the
plan you wait for this guy
to turn around you admire his haircut
and how he has so much balls
respect him before killing him yes
we sneak epically past this guy
boom and i said boom and we take this
guy out
and then we tell this guy we'll block a
wood mate
should we poison this guy or the fancies
[Music]
i was [ __ ] killed
we're close to the milk right now
i can smell the fermentedness
can you smell it too
smells like ass boy i'm a block of wood
mate
they're about to get flooded
is this the mill
that is not the mill where do they keep
their [ __ ] milk
i can't tell where's the gaddy milk
where's the [ __ ] male frog
that the i found the milk
the milk is spicy now
but i did it they got more milk oh they
got two satchel mill
[Music]
should i play the flute see what happens
that's not milk
wind is telling me the milk is over here
there it is i see it
i got my eyes on the milk and got my
milk on my mind
probably just pour gamer girls
[Music]
yes drink the gamer girl pee yes
yes yes
you all have herpes
does ricardo ever come downstairs and
play video games with you
yes if i've been a good boy he does come
down
drink the mail yes
[Music]
64. i got milk for
days you want milk you got
milk
it's my new g-fuel flavor you're the
first one to test it
do you like it they all drank the milk
never never everybody drink milk
should be a lesson if you have a mongol
army and a bunch of milk some of you
should be like all right
maybe not everyone should drink the milk
you know what i'm saying
milk gang for lamb
[Music]
oh it's happening oh it's on
oh you're not helping me now
[Music]
oh
m
foreign
[Music]
he's not going to do that is he
all right here we go sorry let me change
the armor
uh i think probably because it's armor
would be better but i haven't upgraded
it goes match is pretty epic
oh god do i have many of them what do
they do
they must do something different
you
this does not help me at all
maybe that
you
charm of coco melon i choose thee
this is gonna be tough
[Music]
[ __ ] jesus
well that was apparently not difficult
at all what the [ __ ]
are you serious
[Music]
useful
are those heavenly strikes no
that was lethal mode what the [ __ ]
i made that was dirty i expected like a
really tough fight the
[ __ ] dude
the true power of floor gang has been
revealed
lethal mode gives extra damage
so it's easier on linkedin mode
[Music]
that's so interesting so hard mode is
harder
to follow
oh
m
there
okay
foreign
[Music]
we
what's gonna happen
damn i made him sad
samurai ugh
yo
i heart the crack
i play flute so sad
feels like a good point to end it thank
you for joining this late
night stream or early morning or
whatever it is for you
hope you have a great one hope you had
fun watching
i had fun playing isn't that the point
joe rogan huh isn't that the point
dope thanks for coming guys we'll finish
the game off
next time epic yeah
see you next time bye