[Music]
joe
rogan you have taken two steps too
far how dare you you shiny head
son of a [ __ ] credit science video
games
for those of you who don't know warning
warning joe rogan criticized
video games and this is news
joe rogan passes controversial remarks
on video games
joe doesn't really understand ninja
responds
my god you don't get it joe
guess you're not a gamer huh what the
[ __ ] joe i thought you liked quake
hey joe you may think i'm a loser in
real life but in the gaming world
you're the loser god i'm good good night
okay for those who don't know joe rogan
is
a podcast host i think it's one of the
it's probably the most popular podcast
host i think at least
and uh i mean i don't know how you even
have a podcast in 2020 without pissing
someone off every week
uh and today i guess he pissed off the
gaming community this time
you pissed off the wrong crowd mr joe
how dare you how dare you criticize
video games
so what did joe rogan say well let's
check it out
you know and then they they seek refuge
in drugs or video games or
something that stimulates them and video
games are a real problem
they're real problems you know why
because they're [ __ ]
fun yeah well i have a real problem with
them
and you you you do them and they're real
exciting but you don't get anywhere
right
it's like you could do like like martial
arts right you could learn jiu jitsu
you get obsessed by jiu jitsu and then
three years later
you're you're like an elite jiu jitsu
athlete you're like you're
what kind of beta martial arts take
three years to become an elite
they're you're entering in competitions
you're a purple belt you're moving up
yeah you're doing well
you're thinking like i might be able to
open my own school one day that
confidence yeah if i have a hundred
students and those hundred students are
paying me x amount of dollars per month
it's almost like if you have like a
stream or something like that
with like a hundred viewers and they
like pay you x dollars
why are you talking about jiu jitsu man
hey man you have heard about
i've been doing it wrong gaming money
get the [ __ ] out of here
i'm all about that jiu jitsu brain i'm
i'm quitting youtube right now
i could be making jiu jitsu money this
whole time and no one told me there was
jujitsu money laying around everywhere
make a living holy [ __ ] i can have a
this would be amazing and then you see
your jiu jitsu
school and your jiu jitsu instructor has
all these students and drives a mercedes
and he's got a nice fan
i could have a mercedes jiu-jitsu
mercedes god [ __ ] damn it
good damn it i've been sold a pipe dream
that isn't real
i make no money you're doing something
exciting and fun and you don't
or you could just be then you just say
that gaming is too fun uh
just seeing a bit of correlating message
here joe
[ __ ] video games three years later
you could be that same kid
just playing video games waiting for the
next vic's whatever the [ __ ] game is
you know next xbox game to come out and
you're going to waste your time
you have children you got to waste your
time playing video games
jiu jitsu not a waste of time i mean i i
get what he's saying though at least
with jiu jitsu you
you're building your body you're
building your muscles you're learning a
skill that you're going to have for life
instead of a video game
that comes out you know there's always a
new cycle of games even if you get good
at one
there's always going to be a new one i
guess is my point uh so i get it i get
his point it's just like the worst
example ever with jiu jitsu
and that's another thing like you
wouldn't even have to be good
at gaming to make a living obviously
right
there's compared gaming competitive as a
as a
superior job it's like the worst example
you can make
you can make analytical content reviews
streaming
youtube esports managing i like all
these so much aspects of gaming
and it's such a massive market
developing whatever you understand what
i'm saying
uh i'm curious what ninja said let's
check out what ninja said and i guess
that's the thing like
who gives joe rogan has to say about
video games like
no one cares that's like what i would
think about
i know i know everything about
everything so it's hard to think of an
example
makeup that's like me saying make up
stupid you cannot make money make a
doesn't happen but i think it's the fact
that everyone is talking about this
that makes it so interesting and it hits
comment about wasting time it's almost
like
joe rogan accidentally brought up the
discussion of what is the meaning of
life
building a career for yourself or you're
making money and
building something out of yourself or
just having fun in the moment and
enjoying yourself and
that's almost how it became such a big
deal uh let's see what
mr ninja said most recent
uh clip going on about joe rogan his
comment about video games
or like gamers and i think where he was
coming from
um or what he was talking about
specifically i don't want to put words
in his mouth but i watch the whole thing
and try to get context of it and watch
you know
i don't want to say it just say you hate
him ninja
just say gate uh i will put merch in his
mouth because uh
i want to be invited to his podcast in
the future but i think maybe like what
he meant was like that uh
i think i watched the whole clip and
like uh i don't think he meant anything
bad
to the podcast joe rogan let's talk
about games
i love you babe before and after the
clip that was just
you know being posted on twitter it
sounds like he's talking about like the
top one percent like the very odd
or one-off chance that you're gonna be a
professional player any sports player
and a successful one at that
right i mean you can be a professional
esports player and you know beyond like
a tier two tier three
or which is not maybe paying you the
most and obviously if you're not winning
and being paid a lot you're and you're
not a big streamer then you're not
really making a lot of money
uh so i'm assuming he's just basically
talking about you know the top one
percent you're winning every tournament
you're on the top point
oh my gosh all right great correct
response
uh so yeah there was a
twitter bad but yeah i saw a bunch of
comments as well quit gaming eight
months ago bought a new car
i have an amazing new girlfriend i make
it load of money
and i'm buying a house this spring i
party
every weekend i'm never home i enjoy
laughing
do yourself a favor stop trying to make
a gaming career it's crazy as
[ __ ] and of course we have the contrast
here quit my job four months ago
bought a car got out of an unhealthy
relationship i make more money now
playing video games
i also use my platform to bring
awareness to mental health and bipolar
life it's great
do yourself a favor stop being
close-minded it's creatures
i wasted my time playing video games as
a kid to such a degree that i wanted to
know how to make them
i wasted time learning some coding art
sound and music and now been wasting my
life for nearly 30 years writing music
for them and companies waste lots of
money paying me for it
epic yeah i even though i kind of memed
it already i feel like it'd be so easy
for me to
come at joe rogan's statement and be
like yeah joe you're
an idiot i make money playing video
games what the [ __ ] you talk about you
dumb
how can you be so stupid it really just
sounds like a boomer
i'm sure when i when i'm old and i'll
have my podcast and i'll just go
yeah these [ __ ] kids man back in my
day
we play real games now these kids are
playing vr smear
real men back in my day we play fortnite
god dammit
we play battle royales bet they don't
even know what that means
this is such a generational gap that's
always existed
even with novels i'm sure people said
like oh
people wasting their time reading books
huh you should be go out there in the
real world enjoy the real world
cringe it's just a thing that's always
been going on and it's always going to
keep happening
but i also find yeah i do find it kind
of cringe with all the streamers
being going after joe being like well i
make a living he's so stupid
it feels kind of irresponsible almost to
just say say that because it's
i love the idea that i can just inspire
my audience or
i don't know people in general if they
want to pursue youtube and other
gaming related things like yeah go for
it but i don't want to
sell people on the pipe dream that is
possible for everyone because it isn't
just like any sport or uh profession
you have to be in that one top percent
or 0.1 or whatever
the percentage may be to really be
successful at it and it just doesn't
happen to everyone
and that's just that's just reality of
life does that mean you shouldn't pursue
your dreams no but
i think it's important to have some
perspective of your
what you're pursuing at least and i
think especially when you're talking
about something that
is actually like what joe was saying
highly addictive
like the video games are dopamine hits
and having kids being so
exposed to them for hours and hours i
can't
honestly say that i think that's
necessarily a good thing either i it
kind of worries me as well a little bit
when we designed something to be
addicted and
even myself as a kid i was probably i
yeah looking back i was definitely
actually addicted to video games
and i think a lot of kids are
i think it's way more common that people
think so even though there's a ton of
benefits to video games like i read
studies saying that it helps with
logical thinking
like puzzle solving i guess that's
logical thinking reaction time if you
think that's important
yeah it can improve your memory you can
meet friends online
it can help you get out of mental health
situations there's a ton of
positive benefits but i think that
doesn't
make gaming above criticism it seems
like the gaming community is so
sensitive to criticism like
just acknowledging that gaming addiction
is a thing and that it is a problem
which i think is what joe is trying to
get at he's just
he just brought up a terrible example at
least i think
uh yeah invite me to your podcast joe i
love you come on
this is what it really meant guys it
doesn't diminish all the good
you can talk about both it's okay
uh you know if gaming is your only hobby
i would invite you to
try something else it's fun that's the
fun thing about life it's like what we
talked about in the beginning
is life about pursuing uh trying to
build something big for yourself or just
enjoying yourself and i think personally
the answer is just a balance of both to
me the idea of
going through life being perfect just
feeling comfortable
and feeling happy in the moment being
entertained is terrifying
i hate that idea i never want to live
life just like that
but also uh living life when i look at
people that are
all about optimizing and trying to be as
effective as possible and
and accomplish as much as possible that
makes me really disgusted as well i i
think there's just a middle ground
i feel like i i am though becoming more
boomer across the years like
i a a few years ago as you guys know i
got into reading a lot more and
[Laughter]
i god i'm such such a boomer this is
like comparing that hobby
which is something you kind of have to
force yourself a little bit to get into
if you're not used to it to something
compared to video games
i mean obviously it's different for
everyone and everyone gets different
things out of different hobbies but i
i can't honestly say i get that much out
of video games
compared to reading a book that i feel
like oh i learned something i actually
got something out of this even if it's
fiction i can still oh
cool i could immerse myself in in a
character i guess you can do that in
games but i don't think games are that
good at it
i don't think they are i can't remember
last time i played a game and be like oh
i learned something
maybe i'm wrong maybe there are examples
but it just doesn't happen as often
as what i'm saying i guess what i'm
saying is find a balance by all means
enjoy video games it's a great hobby
it's super fun
it's fun to share with other people and
that's what made my job possible and i
couldn't be happier about it but also
find a balance
i think that's what makes life fun doing
different things
i don't know i just thought this whole
uh discussion is so interesting and i'm
curious what you guys think anyway
passing on the question to you guys
and that's it for poppy somaria today
and remember
keep gaming gamers children
of nine parts
it's time to raise what was once
forgotten
what creatures fart spells and poop
troops awaits
hoopty is coming to
nintendo switch
and remember it has a very big pp
pre-order promotions i mean