[Music]
turn down your speakers now welcome to
the why I'm very excited holy cow
93 thousand up votes that's gotta be one
of the all-time highest ones okay maybe
not
youtuber consistently take a photo every
day for 10 years down I'm scared of
watching this the bear came and Vlad
that's 2017 let me serve you Sonya oh my
god 2018 this is so hypnotising 2019 no
this is 2019 damn you can actually tell
my face losing way this is insane
oh my god how long is this oh there it
is there's the shave head big oh god I
became uglier oh no happy 10 years
anniversary fit oh my god that's so nice
that provider that is amazing thank you
so much for doing that
that was to take in so long
god I love that I don't know why this is
interesting to see all the development
his hair and his beard look like they're
having a turf war alright let's see what
else we got I freaking love Becky so
much Becky being a Becky here who the
hell is Becky our PD PI and Felix
Kjellberg the same person or twins twins
might once a gamer once a comedian oh I
don't really know who they are now Felix
was in design yeah PewDiePie wasn't
scary so confusing
I've not seen either of them that's
PewDiePie that's Felix oh my god they
look just see why people get confused
yeah man weirdest wow that's so weird
unbelievable this even confused me what
the hell don't blame Becky I have a twin
what wait a tuchis miss Gloria Borger at
poppy Harlow her mind will be blown they
look exactly the same
haha you're approaching me amazing fader
record though see I said in my last
video you only workout to escape time in
death but I was wrong you work out so
Ricarda once steal your wife I'm coming
for you Ricardo bring it bring your
a-game linnaeus then your wish is my
command sensei ninjas now I'm not
singing I love this meme and I'm
definitely gonna kill it in the next
main review it's so funny
it's basically beta and Chad rebranded
but it's got some alright I'll save it
for me review Felix Kjellberg
right see I get this now because we're
watching fitness and ferb that's right
every live stream we watched one episode
of Fitness permits but it's been really
fun actually so I get it I understand me
I'm one of you guys and you better not
complain now and be like oh it's not
funny anymore because PDP knows it
become a member guys you get access to
all the offline live streams if you want
to watch it don't cry babe it's just a
movie don't cry babe it's just a third
year old man who stops playing minecraft
minecraft dungeons baby I play it on the
live streams again I don't mean to shell
for my membership live streams but all
the footage access through membership if
you want just to clarify these two are
the same person
both absolute Chad's look at them I
should probably shave pretty soon it's
probably time to let it go my head look
at that bald head that's beautiful
beautiful thank you alright we got a fan
art doh I don't favor wanted to see
myself as Garfield but I'm okay I'm okay
with it really cool fine art up bug very
nice but I just say up Potok crinch big
people ease yeah oh they're trying to
influence me boy whatever eight is an
actual sculpture this is so sad guys I
would show my tambourine but it's
undergoing surgery right now it's been a
24 hour process it's very delicate
it's very difficult I'm just praying
every single day guys pray for
tambourine in the comments down below
he's gonna be okay and now I get to know
that it's broken
that's so dope amazing fire Oh God
subscribe right now neck 20% increase
immediately lettuce makes a custom
top-of-the-line creeper PC for Felix
Felix quits minecraft let this be like
bruh hey can we talk about Linda's Chad
Linda's Chad transformation there it is
10 out of 10 now start lifting
2016 2020 2020 for 20 30 all right all
right I'm getting a new camera guys I'll
fix this I think it's time for me to fix
my car I'm getting some hints here and
there I'm getting like this feedback
from you guys I noticed just a couple
comments about it and I think it might
be time to change when enemy dudes is
about to die and then start having
flashbacks of his entire life the
villain I'll just pretend meanwhile you
go ahead have a two-episode flashback no
problem I'll just chill here homie
damn damn I got a show not sticky that's
cute that's amazing you guys are so
talented and I'm so glad I always look
so good in my fine art as well you see
pretty pie fan art might see Fame Oh
actually I found a fan art I don't think
this is on the WHI but it's made by Enzo
Fernandez art I love it so much Thanks
see I get the best stuff I know what I'm
like I get the best it's just cool that
people do it that's super dope amazing
Finny's affirm episode two lawn gnome
day there are days that was a great
episode
you did it you crazy son of a you're
dating it's a good show it's a
legitimately good show
I drew PewDiePie dragon find out for
Puetz baby by dragon damn the textures
are amazing kind of what I like you know
what I mean you know what I mean I want
to put my pee pee okay my mom look at
shooting star make a wish if it will
come true me done Papa Gloria she'll
come back one day I actually been
waiting to confirm this but Papa Gloria
just like tambourine is undergoing
24-hour surgery there is a possible that
she might not make it the treadmill will
hit her very hard but pray for Papa
Gloria she might come back how to change
a tambourine head I need to look into
this how is it done this is the live
footage of the 24-hour surgery or you
can use that rubber band if you have two
people
the uploader is wondering what's going
on in the comment section one picture a
thousand words behold my husband
six-pack
behold everyone great lightening is that
what that is
lighting nothing else 20/20 can't get
any worse 20/20 bye-bye my trip bye-bye
I'll still play it okay I will never
stop playing mine cry that's a lie I
just feel like I can't do them weekly if
they don't update the game but I'll
probably makes them I'll make some more
episodes stop crying
there it is listen before people
challenge me for boxing match I say no
I'm tired hold me I'm just chilling now
bring it I'm ready
81 I challenge everyone in the world oh
that is so cute huge PP ginormous oh my
god it continues okay so good I love
spending most stuff okay we gonna beat
up eat the soup that Alabama hug
king of the underworld your get three
paint
I can't bird poop oh baby baby no hug oh
my god it's the father sleepy smelly cat
what is all my pet died hey buy a net
get still alive no problem guys
this year can't get any worse oh god mr.
beast let's start a gaming channel and
play minecraft pity pie pie pie
minecraft
mr. piece this is so sad mr. piece is
shaking and crying tweet streamers you
guys need to donate Felix stop jumping
hey this is sometimes people donate to
me be like this is the last bit of money
I'm like dog doo it's what are you doing
stop simply for me alright you're doing
it wrong look at the size of those legs
so here we have a photo unedited so this
might be a good reference point so I
hear towers roughly 6
hundred one kilometer Paul I'm half the
length so I should be around ten
thousand meters tall something like that
that's just an estimate
rough estimate could be anywhere between
ten thousand meters and zero okay we
have the wrong way it's that one punch
man before he
oh really I didn't know that there it is
there it is
thanks for all the support on my workout
review video that was really nice I'm
glad you guys enjoy that you can't
recognize somebody just from their torso
bare a days when you're a girl and get
rated big peepee you're welcome everyone
you're welcome girls hey
I don't discriminate on this channel
alright i'll all exclusive exclusive
that's right inclusive women can have
big peepee - i said it multiple times
might safe manner
Felix pair that Wow thank you guys so
much for this fan art there are many
hours it take oh here it is okay fine
now I am married man and I've got Ripa
death rippled ABS ripped ABS PewDiePie
then oh no barrels this big BP maybe
laughs very nice goodbye my friends
quick banner oh so good fan art big
peepee he's that paint which one is
bain't do oh I like that
cybers my stand that's pretty cool
actually that's a cool idea that's the
real reason to work out so you can look
like a Jojo character so many people
when they saw that photo there like he
was Jojo I understand even though it is
a bit silly to have a goal even if it's
like not even possible cuz no one's more
buff than to you it doesn't hurt to have
a an image of a goal I'm not gay but
damn Sam said it was like father to me
Denver inside he's in surgery
pray for tambourine I'm in the
tambourine finally fresh Marcel was
devastated aha I'll let you know I'll
have you know Marcel was not happy
teacher today we're gonna talk about how
glass is made me after five
plus hours of Minecraft I already know
puke is a sheep everyone else hey I've
seen this word no you haven't
no you haven't stop lying he's not great
it needs to be a great sheet that's not
what they're sheep I would but that
would cost a deep cost here's me
shilling for a new to bridge content in
the new update it's cool check it out
game is so fun not gonna lie
Felix bye bye minecraft minecraft
dungeons you guys called what is with my
boys I record and I recorded yesterday
singing that's that's why okay
I have always this is my voice this is
my real voice this is a voice reveal uh
hey guys it's me big-time Tommy we need
Koreans in their 30s playing Minecraft
[Laughter]
good babe big peepee leaks email it's
okay I have another one
mix it join livestream for me making
more royal cups burp good times good
times are ahead bro you should give
people a copy of your worlds and see
what they do with it
okay I like that idea I like that idea a
lot it's fairly big though where can i
upload it like a big file for many
people to download it come join us
tambourine no no yeah no he's alive he's
fine
pray for tambourine one like equals one
prayer anime Netflix had her touch
I was just trying to get it that's a
tough part to get over it's a rough one
before Joe Harry days before Joe Joe
after Joe Joe goal after Joe Joe go
Felix upload a video while
live-streaming me and intellectual
parody the subreddit when Felix made
Sven and deep have Alabama the subreddit
when Felix made literal sex chamber for
some villagers in which generations
so the he could have slaves would give
but no now you've crossed the line Felix
you made the dogs go peepee inside be
deep I'm not playing mind if terraria
yet I am the worst oh god I'm sorry
actually I should write it down so I
don't forget it I keep forgetting play
Terraria you now now I won't forget it
that was the Karen haircut first it
confuse me are you waiting Felix no no
next year I win the tambourine challenge
oh wait yeah sure that we'll call it
that from now on the smell of vanilla
extract that takes the vanilla extract
so true this is so true should I make
one more video on whatever his name is I
kind of curious what happened afterwards
no one fifteen year olds in enemy yes
finally I've reached the body were
fifteen you're all oh no it's true there
I'm also pissed off by it they practice
for like a week and then they're like
muscles muscles now roses are red boots
amps have been seen but all pay respect
for his dead tambourine he's not he just
got hit by a treadmill it's not his
fault
use code PewDiePie for discount that's
right I didn't talk about this in my
video I don't want to get too much in
diets but yes I only eat G fuel that's
my entire diet nothing else before G
fuel after G fuel very nice
Felix do your dream in Swedish or
English people keep asking this I think
it's very contextualized I big word okay
epic for example if I notice if I write
a note I was right in English but if I'm
writing a note related to Sweden or
something regarding my parents it just
naturally it switches to Swedish and I
think it's the same with their dreaming
if I mean somewhere in Sweden in a dream
I dream in Swedish and yet this is how
it is Alabama Lord of nether Reve please
accept these melons please bless my safe
travels across your Lancer amazing
resting paste Emery I told Jack he
should sacrifice his Bell to resurrect
tambourine
but he refused can you believe this
Mojang Studios new name logo and trailer
so long old partner so long I don't like
the red but I like the font that they
picked I think it looks better Hospital
gang ow confused noises thank you for
the sacrifice the predictive recovering
you clay disturbing our vote Dodd very
nice yeah oh my god I forgot tooth that
was like here so I just edit this Amy
think about it he has to watch all these
awful Shh
other worse I'm sorry sighs thank you
for editing that video
it is really Simon had to blur the
footage and solve the awful stuff I'm
sorry I I didn't even prepare I'm sorry
Oh God hey sweet and seventeenth-century
hippity hoppity your land is now my
property now
don't hit me I'm Swedish play hates oh
no no oh now it changed
sweet good now oh we take back Finland
out we take back Norway out Denmark I
don't really want it you can go you're
free to go
anime characters at the start of
training montage enemy characters at the
end of there it is I just needed real
sensei then we'll see some real progress
how to change a tambourine head someone
get this man in the VOAD felix leg
fighters pets in Minecraft I love the
hammer did I not see by Alabama nah
google has removed 8 million reviews
from tick-tock what the hell
pewds microjet terraria this is so sad
I'll probably live stream terraria but
I'll still upload it as a video on its
own because it's been so long that I
played and I feel like I need some help
oh you're challenging me you're
approaching me Ricardo you're
approaching me you protect the attack
but most importantly he will be there
waiting for you when you get back when
your friend were sponsored by Mojang
that's dope I'm proud of them that's
really cool no it's evolving just
backwards what comes to my brain when
Pete says huge PP o join floor gang 20%
PP increase instantly female or male it
will happen look at those curls
incredible the PP is strong with this
one the people are strong with this one
Jack and Felix during the 50/50
start the Minecraft series unmarried
nine-year-olds did not have unrevealing
subs chair gang crinch and the minecraft
series married to merge 19 year olds
reach 100 mill floor gay al um 20
percent muscle increase our we're not
gonna add that the smell of vanilla
extract that taste of vanilla extract
extract yes I said that right thank you
Felix identity breaks his tambourine
nice 19 year old dear Felix now that you
have seen Phineas and Ferb properly how
do you feel its pictures I get it now
haha I can let this haha I get it
goddamnit just when this was getting
wholesome it just ended just want to
thank Peter pie for helping me at my
lowest lows oh I hope you recover soon
there's no need to thank me hope you do
better soon yeah that's right Felix 2025
oh no no Felix 2021 baby let's get it
alright guys thank you so much for all
the memes fanart and all the lives
appreciate it it's really fun
remember to become a member and I see
you guys tomorrow I think I'm not sure I
might take a day off actually okay see
you guys
brofist
[Music]