oh oh here we go
it's a Pierre I'm so gross and fat you
okay well so far nothing bad is here how
do I get in there maybe I can get like a
vault
oh my god there is a ball ah huh dude
people say this game is hard pathetic
I love how you see looking at you hey
buddy why did you come down eh mate got
forgot about that
god dammit I know there's like an area
in the beginning that you can kind of
choose your way through right oh can you
jump down there right
it looks like zero dancer one all right
so we're starting up the lights from
here I know what happened though either
you crazy son of a snake what the who
threw that
who's ever doing that you're gonna be
pissed off that you did that
oh I don't remember how I beat this for
us to be honest oh [ __ ] Kevin jump then
you little [ __ ]
how did I not hear clearly the strategy
is working out impeccably very good so
far he's Bozek claiming me he better not
be fast go go go go go go don't hit me
don't even know us finish at my camera
get up please
all right so that's how you do it on the
first try whatever come here
this guy's so annoying oh there's the
kick EEP ash what do you learn to aim in
R at school idiot she look at my bony
ass I want to have a thick ass it's not
pop all right all right he doesn't
actually go inside the fire oh he does
ha ha ha
he's gonna fall for it three times don't
call pizza don't go beat the bleep no
all again I get one mole again that's
right pretty bad
to Milligan's you get to Mulligan's ah
what I'm like ah
oi oi he's all you're gonna die or you
can't die
goddamn stop it away boy is my new best
friend oh god this this is a bad idea
here we go it's a party yeah yeah
Oh where's your friend huh yeah thank
you ollie zero Depp's pretty good so far
slower roll is good for this fight do
plays there's [ __ ] how long does this
happen
keep presenting yourself that's right
that's right come to flat feet double
hit no oh oh god oh oh you can't hit me
I'm Swedish listen meatballs all come to
poppy we have to go friend
so this is where you meet a Dark Knight
that can actually drop a really good
weapon cuz this is how the speedrunners
do it right they just run here cool so
literally he doesn't know how do I do
the thing how do I do the thing oh oh I
get the Black Knight Halbert we have the
Hulbert so it should be really fun
strong let's go gamers zero that's okay
here we go
Oh fight day we week
gaming week let's do this gamer to gamer
I feel like I'm not prepared at all
okay starts off with that I'm stuck
that's all right
it's gaming week count them for me boys
count them for me
can I just one shot it nice knowing yet
I remember this oh that's why I remember
it 9 year olds look away oh wow it's a
cute little snake what an easy boss oh
my god
go for the knees boys here oh that's
this place sucks it feels like actually
going down sewers Oh God look at these
big boys whoa
welcome to Blighttown maybe try and
fight him over somewhere else that's
what I think of you and your shitty town
cool so we're still at the beginning of
this god-awful in place I go down there
there's a guy there let's go gamer time
don't use those giant rocks Emmie all
right Jay says cool
are there enough noted noted all right
kayo some cool lug more like ugly girl I
forgot about the explosion it doesn't
count if you're eager 'ls kill you it's
the first rule of Dark Souls can you
freak off with the stones literally no
more stones see you don't have stuff
where did he get this from I don't know
when they're throwing them it's really
stop with the stones please oh no it was
poison I wasn't paying attention it
doesn't count if you were not paying
attention look at that oh yeah getting
them good over here doing a lot of
damage big on talked zero deaths that's
how it's done
thank you very much jump here what look
at that I ride the ferris wheel this is
epic one time epic a bee bee no one asks
clearly no one asked me and now we
climbed very epic bush alright alright
buzz off
he pushed me to be pushed me how can be
push how can be pushed I'll get it up
how I wear skirt you know what's the
lamest animal ever made that's right
ah no not again God not like this oh
it's okay okay just keep
keep running
all right we jump here it's cool boys I
just want to talk
skirt gang skirt gang this time I'm
ready while you sit hello
oh my god what onion got me killed you
idiot
wait was I not supposed to kill him trap
ahead huh
what's happened to me ah no skirt get
hurt oh wow
I don't know if you guys noticed but
he's bombing the place
he's farming the play
he's bumping the game a way
scart game all right I've had enough of
your balls
skirt gang
why is his weapon so overpowered no no
no oh my god dude chill
oh my god there's two of them oh you
can't hit me skirt they're shooting for
her boobs dude how is that even legal
you see that deaf counter we played so
far I don't know how many hours but the
lot of hours have been playing no dice
zero death has occurring that's been
occurring has occurred bottom got the
gamers what are you gonna do there's a
pillar there that's so embarrassing
he's so embarrassed
I missed you call that a swing oh god oh
god
first ripe pictures
what is that weapon and how did you get
it
Oh old strength no skill this is the
best part big titty and him a girlfriend
hallelujah
they are so large she's so largely the
sad part about this is that all thoughts
must be exterminated F's in the chat
so [ __ ] anime I'm sorry
oh no what it died
No oh my god I was trying to hit Pat it
Keanu Reeves wants to know your location
Oh God we're a better bounce bonfire
ahead where oh hey check back I don't
remember this he's sucking me oh my god
is ever old three or four of them gonna
suck me oh my god it [ __ ] suck again
you get this son now eyes gonna jump me
ah it doesn't count if the treasure eats
you that's the number one rule of dark
so you have to destroy oh yeah hahaha oh
it's getting chopped oh it's getting
chopped oh it's getting chopped
oh it's chopped gamers jump jump to pay
to win weapon oh you can do a shortcut
here watch this gamers
just as planned gamers oh yeah that's a
shortcut baby oh god it's the wheels oh
it's the wheels
it's the wheels oh it's they goddamn
wheels oh they don't stop Oh God oh we
did it thank God that was close
ah all right hardest boss of the game
here we go gamers oh my god oh god
hmm No oh god are there other things out
there hello hey get out of the way get
out of the way get out of the way get
out of the way gamer he's slapping my
ass ah I have a lantern no lanters are
for [ __ ] oh yes I remember this bald
son of a [ __ ] oh thanks
how about you go first I'll follow you
look how much treasure that's awesome
why I pushed him that makes no sense I
just got on my why oh god is there
anything down here oh well what the hell
are you doing down here
there gamer get out of here it's
dangerous oh god I killed her I'm sorry
ah hey look guys there's a way ah okay
how do I fight neither I completely
forgot what bad no not now I'm drinking
slurp woo it's called timing
Gaming week by all right gamers
it's card time
[Music]
bedlam chaos more like my bed
Oh God
oh that
now imagine having 20s this blast is
still fine I'm almost a gamer they left
to fight hand just go down - damn it no
[Music]
are you getting
maybe a week is over get me with you
some game a way
Gaming got to be careful we have zero
deaths are you kidding are you all right
guess I got a restart okay so we're back
I replayed the game
Jamie wig gang
praise the Sun my gamers hope you guys
enjoyed this video
smash like if you enjoyed subscribe if
you haven't
we're almost at a hundred million I
wanted this video to mark the end of
gaming week we've been live streaming
this as often as I can it's been really
really fun
and it's been fun to bring back gaming
to this channel but all things must come
to an end so therefore that's it game a
week over