that's right
spend this year it's a beautiful day and
we're gonna play Minecraft how did I
become a Minecraft channel and everyone
is important with if this video gets a
million likes we're gonna make it
minecraft month no I'm kidding
or a bye okay so first of all we have a
look to stuff to do today aren't miss
when I broke my ankle spent coming down
from there I've been getting a lot of
tips from you guys from on the reddit
and one of them was how you change to a
Swedish banner flag so we're gonna make
that because I made a lot of epic
upgrades to the house isn't that epic
Sven he's so excited he's leaving me
look at that that's beautiful his friend
hey he doesn't he want to look at me I
accidentally killed his boat cows friend
he's like I'm not making eye contact I'm
sorry he had to die right sin sin agrees
okay so we're gonna make the banner
there's one thing I want to do first is
because as you can see
[Music]
let them free God it's lagging there's
always something else to do in this game
god damn it and also this series got a
shout-out from the god of Minecraft
notch himself thank you notes for
watching okay I'm done I'm done okay you
get gamers get to eat now here you go
here you go you get to eat you get to
eat you all get weeks
you all get week just calm down I know
it's very look there plenty of space but
come on space they're moving if they had
if they didn't have space they wouldn't
be moving am I right gamers I almost let
them out okay so I have this new system
double gate gamers get out of the way
cow double gate ok gamers you're free
you're free be free oh my god oh my god
there's so many of you look there's
plenty of space I'm so generous now
where were the ones I let out I want to
kill them look at that beautiful
beautiful it's not beautiful deer again
you're good I'm speaking to you hello
what are you doing Oh God okay I'll kill
the mom okay so there is actually a
reason I did all that which we'll get to
in a second I just need to organize my
inventory oh wow this is look good Felix
and I also built a fence so Sven can't
die from the lava
don't worry gamer if Sven dies this
playthrough is over okay so the reason
why we need it's because apparently this
is redstone which activates stuff so if
I happen to put down a dynamite it would
activate the dynamite and therefore my
house would blow up which is not good in
Minecraft generally you want to avoid
blowing up your house that's the pro tip
from a veteran gamer you guys are
welcome if we cut the sheep we can make
wool which we can make I'm like doing
the Swedish accent on ironically at this
point chop chip chip chip chip chip chip
chip chip chip chip chip chip chip chip
chicken come on we would all ship ship
ship ship
I don't care what Peter says I don't
care you will ship your Winship don't
God delight now God the leg oh god the
leg this is what you create Nikita if I
can't kill them
overpopulation will happen don't escape
no one escapes if anyone else tries it
that's what I thought okay gamers now we
have wooden what the Frick are you doing
that's what you get and that same thing
will happen to you one day if you ever
make it out of there wish you won't by
the way your doom there for eternity
that's right let's also make sure we pay
our respects ok ok gamers ok so now we
have a Frick ton of wool but we need to
dye it obviously I think you use flowers
to die so we need yeah we need blue and
red yellow obviously and I think I want
to make the carpet black which will you
get from why am I talking on ironically
about this and why are you on ironically
my cheek I think you get the black from
the squids which I will kill now watch
me gamers do you swim faster next to
dolphins I didn't realize that there
used to be a million squids here what
the Frick stupid fish ruin my life but
you get fish show me where the squids
are what are you doing smash got a mate
alright fine fine you can just take over
why are you not dead go away
I will trick you I'll freak a skeleton
you have bones I like it
oh yeah and I caught a dolphin I
remember is it still here what the
dolphin escaped it was down here I swear
what the hell it why did the dolphin
escape - why my dolphin not working lol
ok gamers this is an epic moment is an
epic moment uh-huh
he agrees hello there fellow tradesmen
what are you selling
whoa I need those God don't spit I think
I need the time but they're so expensive
shut up Jo - shut - I'm thinking I'm
thinking okay how much do they cost a
bucket of tropical fish dude I can get a
tropical fish I go get a tropical fish
be right back
yeah man I can't play this game for two
seconds without getting distracted I
have other stuff planned this episode
they wasn't supposed to go this way Oh
God get the money get the money I feel
like I just ran into the ice cream truck
or some thing I'm gonna get a goddamn
bucket of fish and it's gonna be awesome
bucket of fish bucket of fish bucket of
fish bucket of fish bucket of fish come
on bucket of fish oh he's still here
thank God I got a piece so bad weird
bucket of fish is waiting all right
bucket of fish man I can heat cheap
gravity I get two bucket of fishes and
I'll get these because I know I can do
something with them two bucket of fish
and now comes the best part the
murdering that's right give me back my
money oh god they're spitting stop it
stop it I didn't do anything I'm
innocent I am 100% innocent what you
just witness was he hacked your eyes god
damn it why would you spit on me why
would you spit on me
I spit on you I took filthy collections
I spit on you and your mother Jurgen
would never spit on me okay so we're
gonna look at four squids that's why I
came here
stupid squid DDD where are you I will
find your squids whoa what is this whoa
this is literally in my house and I've
never seen it
Nunnally freaky-deaky what is this okay
I'm running oh god I keep getting
distracted we were supposed to make a
Swedish banner god dammit why is this in
my backyard who put this here I've never
seen these blocks before Allah what
there's people down there ah what there
people why you live there however never
noticed this back off what they're
people
[Music]
all right what do people got pooped on
is there a chest down here or something
and it's garbage although there is a
Trish man they might actually fall again
I don't need that what was I doing the
flag Felix okay fine we'll do the flag
all right you're gonna you come in with
me we're gonna pick flowers it's picking
flowers with my best bro Jurgen time all
right I need you did why can't I go oh
he's on the leash I'm sorry again I was
like why is it not working
there you go now we can go oh my god
nothing like picking flowers with your
best bro in it okay blue is well perfect
absolutely epic if we could find red as
well that'd be oh yeah oh yeah there
again today's are they it's gaming week
possibly gaming month year again think
about that like minecraft is probably
the only gaming where I would actually
enjoy picking flowers
but it's so nice isn't it
you ruin everything don't ever look at
your again again okay we got plenty of
rest time this is perfect
stop stop in the name of Lord you don't
want to go to my prison I did you a
favor
oh it's Enderman oh it's no dammit I
know I'm supposed to kill them because
of the ender dragon but that's all I
know
the pearls are something anyway I think
we have our stuff we'll head back
it's gaming week I thought they looked
cool okay they're like glowing stuff
it's epic carpet right so how do we okay
just like that cool we're making the
dyeing youtube de monetization bought
just picked up me saying the bad word
okay cool so now we have red wool this
is epic do I know how many I need
absolutely not
we'll just go buy the floor
bing-bam-boom bing bang bong Bing bong
you know I need your knee when BIM BAM
boom next we make the bender okay so I
have to follow the tutorial you guys
made first we make a bender and it has
to be blue so we need six of the blue
light blue no dark blue Frick it I need
three more I have two more Frick it
oh yeah the reason about the shells
because I know you can combine it with
heart of the sea that's all I know
clearly all I know oh yeah these can
make blue dye perfect ah that's not a
design flaw that's a feature thank you
one two three every gamer can't you see
I make me a blue flag II epic okay so we
do one two three one two three and then
stick BAM we got ourself a banner now we
have to do ruling what is it called
ruling yes looming
okay we need ship chop your horse nope
Oh loom I told you loom okay we can loom
here this will be looming station very
epic I need to see well to do looming
epic we need a yellow dye okay okay okay
okay yellow dye we got it all gamers
Swedish flag time so we put this here
and we put this here and we click the
key and BIM BAM beem beem boom boom boom
go away ugly banner by the way ugly what
banner go away shoosh shoosh bender oh
there it is okay it's gone and it's gone
and boom
yeah yeah oh that's epic I love it
that's cool oh god I should have gone
with you I should have done yellow here
that oh my god I got it
alright gamers then no I did not just do
with a diamond pickaxe don't worry about
it you guys have to worry about every
detail whatever I use a shovel Bing bong
Bing Bing bong damn this looks good
damn that looks good okay alright I
[Music]
think we should do blue here actually
this is what minecraft is all about
color coordinating something only gamers
will understand
[Music]
bing-bam-boom yeah it's got to be like
that gamers we got to make the bed match
of course and spends sickening pad throw
my old bed in the fire no big deal man
dark wood bed that might be epic alright
there it is I'll hide when you hold that
it's so tiny and then BAM beautiful
let's not forget about Sven sitting
cushion bean bomb joke ifs when would
leave the boat you could actually enjoy
it so the reason I kept this is cos it's
a burek and it's a very Swedish famous
tree I think
maybe not I think every country has a
killer okay well whatever gamer oh right
I forgot about my bucket of fish there's
too much happening in this game I can't
keep up where should I keep my bucket of
fish maybe here in the little pond
there you go bucket of fish all right
I'll find a better use for you later
oh god don't tell me this runs out in
the water no it isn't I don't I don't
trust you guys now now now now but now
tropical tropical tropical tropical
tropical no I punched a fish I'm so
sorry what do you have the one go come
back here you tropical son of a snake I
pay good money for you fish I will do
with you as I please all right I won't
go here for now okay so if you thought
that was it that was not it okay we have
many epic things to do because I'm so
obsessed Jesus Christ
amazing they set up a trap you go to
sleep go to sleep go to sleep it's
really cool Easter egg just click on the
bed just click on the bed ha ha he did
it idiot a pig on top ok so I'm a I
figured out since you guys told me but
there's eight blocks in the narrowed
around in IRL that I can make a portal
to new places that I want to go to I
know I cube five thousand as long as I
don't get attacked here we should be
alright so we have this portal which
goes to epic plays hello thanks for
welcoming me so I found this city
I never explored it yet but it looks so
cool they got like houses in the
mountains and they are all depressed
it's awesome they're just like me we're
totally fitting in hello
okay hippity-hoppity your money is my
property as we say in sweden this is why
they depress everyone's taking this
stuff I didn't do anything I swear I
didn't do anything all right what else
more money it's poor people oh poor
people don't worry if you're matter but
if you're mad at me oh they have
Garrigan's
is there no one to trade here there's
really then there's no reason for me to
build that portal thing but I spent so
long
hello so anyone that want to trade
they're all just a bunch of poor people
oh my god it's a tiny alcohol - a creepy
notch would not have come up with us not
saying I don't like them all I'm saying
it's not should not have made them all
right what about the ones in the
mountain maybe that's where the epicness
you guys do anything any day all day
pop-pop yep hippity-hop Vinny hey look I
have the bucket I don't have the bucket
all right you win this time cat you win
this time look how cute they designed it
that ones have a hat maybe that one can
train hello hat man ow
broke my leg it's fine hat man hat man
treats wait I have so much weeks I'm
gonna be rich
okay the portal was worth it there's one
thing I thought about because I always
have to look for them right is it mean
if I lock them in so I don't have to
look for them all the time right okay
cool so now I'll find him easier more
easily perfect you just stay there
epic all right let's check the top you
bid to help but really hopefully whoa
all right
better not be a trap okay flowers for a
year again it's actually a nice house
like I would like to live here maybe
will will emigrate the uragan one day to
a new place all right we're going to
sleep because there's another thing
around here that I have never seen
before and that is my gamers we'll get
to it in a sec it's got oh it's a is
that a church does I mean that there's a
god of Minecraft of course there's notch
must be inside here no Chi hello what is
this brewing stand what pick out torches
this is awesome the city's cool I like
this city Oh
epic I want to
lock him in as well actually when I just
dig underneath him no stop don't escape
there you go enjoy enjoy the whole since
but this here so we find you enjoy the
whole have fun I'll trade with you later
I'll let you out if you trade with me
hippity hop with a hello you're against
here you go have Apple there you go
enjoy see they have a road and stuff
it's awesome as gamers know whenever
there's a pretty utopia there are other
people that want to take part of it
where is it there it is see they have
the this is I never seen this but it's
an enemy camp look at them so we're
gonna go absolute sicko mode right now
I'm gonna set up a little defense maybe
here oh god they're coming don't shoot
don't shoot you will never get past my
defenses ah how can you shoot backwards
oh thank you coming Wow ok easy there's
a lot more of them though
come on gamers
like I just try to 360 sicko mo sickle
bow all your Chargers ha ha gamer beat
gamer weird kill them all
I don't care what it takes you're all
gonna die
[Music]
if you guys get on then maybe you can
kill me [ __ ]
oh yeah should we blow it up
do I have TNT I'm tempted to just go
back and get oh god there's more this
must be good either
where you from leaving
dude he dropped the crossbow I never had
them look at me haha oh I hear more of
them okay we've got it we've had our
advance our way inside
alright pirates bring your A game or
your B game actually don't think no
think just kill bye oh whoa Bop the
love-in shunting what is that okay I'll
take a game oh damn the old respond
oopsie I think they're angry can I blow
up their place though i legit want to oh
he's getting dangerous oh oh oh time to
bounce later gamer
home sweet home okay so I have all this
rotten flesh I knew i hain't knew saving
up all this useless stuff what's gonna
be worth it I just realized I googled
how to make dynamite FBI is gonna find
me guys
oopsie gunpowder which I have oh my god
oh my god no wonder my game is lagging
all right I just needed to do a dynamite
test so I think if I remember you could
use redstone that's like a fuse do I lit
it or hmm maybe I can is it one of these
the torch and I hit it with the torch Oh
yep okay wait what
what is happening
read I think I'll read a comment about
this I didn't think it would happen oh
god guys were raided what is happening
is it hard
I think people said it was hard you guys
will help me right now they're all
freaking out they don't want to trade
with me now Frick I'm not ready for this
I'm ready to pull up oh there they are
there they are oh wow stone guy is
killing it Duke don't worry guys don't
worry eye protection oh sorry I let him
did it
wait what it continues oh god charge my
crossbows oh god they mean business
chief says oh my god dude they got axe
people oh my god oh my god I'm dead
there's only one way out this is not
even my city oh god I swear I had so
much food God the iron golem is not
helping well thank God I protected them
yeah what'd I say
you thought it was cruel bring it it's
gone that deuces Lauda Tammy it's a
leader
bring it
thank God the baby made it I'll
barricade him so no one can kill the
child oh my god he's alive thank God all
right goodbye the last oh god it's
another raid I can't deal with this
we're gonna have to get the big guns out
oh they're coming from the other side
holy freaky Mickey what is that oh it's
gonna have to go boom
whoa whoa relax I'm not I didn't sign up
for this I did not sign up for this I
did not sign up for this this is not my
city this is not my battle
no one said anything about giant
freaking bulldozers just want me to come
on Raiders oh it's only the bulldozers
are left oh god how how how
okay range range battle
Oh God it seems me
I'm sorry sorry poori
oh god it's got a lot of help
and I'm gamers a holter oh this is bad
you're getting audio I'm out of arrows
freaky okay I have a gamer plant I have
a given plant Oh God
gamer oh wow you're really angry aren't
you
[Music]
ah oh my god yeah oh my god Oh
all we died
god it keeps going I can't do more
they got wizards and stuff this time I'm
sorry wizard actually gonna die
how long does his last how do I care
poison
this is the most intense battle I have
ever done in my life
No damn it why am I here oh because I
slept in the bed oh my god I'm an idiot
or a genius question mark freaking one
shot at me dude oh my god that's where
it went
Oh No
are you kidding me
these freaker's are correct they're
crazy they one shot you go oh he went
through two that's
kidding me my stuff is right there she
says price luckily I do remember the way
home it's just very far oh boy what a
day it's not over yet
the battle is still on all right I have
to make so much new stuff oh god if only
the pigs could help me okay they should
be over there oh my god they are look at
that butt dude okay maybe I can push him
off you kidding me and I respawn here
because I forgot to sleep
oh my god yes yes that's the best thing
that could ever happen oh no I'm so out
of logs dude he's blowing up my bridge I
want my stuff back yeah
no another I can't do another I'm done
how long this is keep going oh my god
what they're writing them now they
really want they really want blood I'll
give them that
this is a bit more than I bargained for
she says Lord
it's over Anakin I have the high ground
don't do it we can be friends don't
shoot
[Music]
[Applause]
if I stand really low
he sticks out yes yes gaming I did it I
did it
Oh free you're free to go you're free to
live you're free to you're free I save
your people
ow the child Oh No
well your again is Jurgen Czar okay what
the Frick is this I'm fun in hell
what the Frick and we're back home very
epic that's it for me for now smash like
for more minecraft and I'll see you guys
next time
what you never played super simulator
you know it's fun right I'm not supposed
to give my opinion but give it a try and
then you can tell me if it's good or not
not convinced yet okay I'll cut you a
deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]