thanks that's right we're continuing
Minecraft and Jurgen is back I had to
make some adjustments but the Sheep is
back - hello sheep ap you're again I
swear to God stop me scaping why does he
do this it's a lot of you were saying
that I can make like a lasso or leash or
something I will but apparently I need a
slime so we're gonna go find some epic
slime no we're gonna go back to the
pirate ship we have a lot of epic stuff
to do today but everyone kept saying and
there might be another treasure map in
the pirate ship okay I'll go back I'll
go back gamers gamers speak I listen
vote pity pine 2020 gamer imagine a
society run by games alright you're
gonna I swear to God
I'm gonna go off why is it white day oh
god damn it keeps happening alright so
if I save and then go back he should be
there yeah okay so he was a glitch and
that was a glitch too everyone was like
oh how can you not understand it was a
glitch oh I'm sorry the game that has
been out for nine years still has basic
punches in it oh god it's getting dark
no I can't do this hey sugar we're gonna
make cake bros oh sorry I think if we go
along the seashore we should find the
ship oh god creepers it's fine gamers
I'm not afraid
this is a terrible idea oh god there's
monsters everywhere Jernigan but as long
as you're is you are close to me we'll
be okay uragan okay there it is found it
Oh perfect we'll put your gun on the
plateau stay stay thank you
so apparently it's really rare to find a
pirate ship in like above the water
someone said I don't know people can
tell me anything I'm supposed to look
for a treasure man
oh god I'm drowning damn I'm bad at this
game
what if there's a treasure map on this
boat find it so why can't I not brave on
the water it's the easiest way to find
it maybe going down I can't breathe that
long I'm not a fish where is that you
guys are trolling me again
God let's take forever come on it's so
obvious as that would say look it's the
only part that goes down - all right
after mining and the whole thing all
night I have deduced that there is no
treasure man thanks gamers it's fine we
have other stuff to do it doesn't matter
it wasn't even important let's get out
of this place here again whoa dolphins
that's epic
a sheep we're back wow what an adventure
go in Juergen go in thank you I got
noses in the bear dark wood now where
did he go God it happen again all right
we may not have gotten a treasure map
but at least we got a dark the world
yeah look at that beautiful carpet it
looks so nice now I know I know
well well well okay step to get Gucci
pants all right who's the gucci mane
you're the gucci mane why oh by the way
I might steal that looking for a Gucci
guy where's the Gucci
tear this is such a failure what are you
doing
maybe I give him they're gonna pay for
this I can make leather horse armor what
you never played to for simile
I can make armor for oh my god I can
make armor for four year again you're
again look I have present for you
Oh your dork at night let's lit you up
yeah shut up shut up everyone quiet
Jurgen this is a special moment you are
getting leather armor you look so fancy
dude oh my god that's awesome I love him
let's go good night okay you're again
wish me good luck we're going to the
nether cuz everyone said there's a
secret achievement if you sleep in the
nether why would anyone do that
god this place so creepy dude why on
earth would I sleep here this is awful
all right fine we'll make a little
NetherRealm house how about that it's
gonna be so cute oh god I'm scared all
right good night my own audience my own
supporters can you believe this scared
me dude I know what I was expecting but
not my house no oh my god God aah damn
yo give me back my stuff there if I
don't get back my diamond pickaxe we're
through okay I'm done I just serve
better than this my house blew up are
you kidding you're like half my stuff
dude
help me look peg people if I can you
slice it how do i oh I can chop away the
flames there we go
go away cool I'm glad I brought back
gaming week to get epically trolled and
lose half my stuff sleep in the dead
there Bailey
I missed I lost my pants do you feel
good about yourself
what's a block of quartz it looks
prickly I liked it goddamnit I lost my
shield too
so someone said I can actually go to the
nether round with Jurgen I just have to
like I want to see if that's possible
it seems like a terrible idea ah you're
against drowning
what no your again went through your can
come back come back come back
damn it god damn it you're getting you
crazy
alright so does the combos work here no
it doesn't great on second thought no
the hell I got a teleport yard kid
it was here a second ago maybe he went
through to the other side
no no I'm not crying shut up you are oh
my god
he left us way too soon Jurgen was like
a father to me I loved him like my son
you never know when the ones that love
you are gonna leave you I never thought
this day would come
he left us too soon rest in peace Jurgen
rest in peace if I die fine I can
respawn uragan can't respawn you have to
get uragan number two now of course now
of course there can only be one year
again but there is Jurgen number two
here you go your again have it all okay
hopefully this one hopefully your again
the second won't be such an ass like I
just bought myself a new pet it will
never be the same I'm still hurting wait
there's one thing I want to do here you
go you're again he loved melons I'll
plant the tree for New York and I plant
as many trees all right things happen we
must move on we have our the things to
do okay we're gonna kill the Ender
Dragon let's go you're you what is your
gonna have more life you're gonna the
second oh I never been in the desert
before there's bunnies there's freaking
bunnies can I put them in the bucket
damn it you're back buddy what's up
hello what are you doing into the desert
can you go in the bucket what where do
you go
mysterious all right I'm gonna have to
kill someplace I'm sorry look away
children
look away children I'm sorry uh-oh
oh he's back what the hell what wow this
place is cool
whoa another house what is there it's
got a creeper phase on it what whoa what
is this whoa whoa whoa whoa what my god
minecraft if your game could see this
he'd be freaking out yeah he better not
run away this time yes really deep oh it
goes up as well that's so cool how do I
go down there scared okay here we go
whoa oh no oh no I set off a bomb didn't
I if I could take it all away if I could
do what why did I do that I could have
gone I bet there was like awesome stuff
in this some murderers it's my evil Ark
beginning all right if anything else
happens
whoa whoa whoa whoa I'm just confused by
everything first of all we need to get
your again the second bank
second of all oh god what did they you
ever had a bad day in Minecraft never
had a pet they will imagine having a bad
day in Minecraft okay okay I see her
again this good I thought this was a
kids game okay
why are there actual traps in there oh I
got you now oh I got you now oh I got
you now oh I actually got him oh no I'm
sorry
my trusty horse uragan ii my man I
missed you poop thanks I guess now we're
gonna need a lot of sand so we gotta go
down again damn it
it better not be any more traps in here
oh my god ha oh god of course there's a
creeper there as well what are you doing
go away oh my god guys I am having a bad
day okay you're not going after me oh my
god
all right we keep on gaming its gaming
week it's Gayley week and so he kept
walking with no armor no skill and no
hope
he just wants Jurgen back and all his
stuff to would be great
play minecraft they said sleep in the
nether they said you can enter there
with your horse they said I can never
trust anyone ever again
not even myself at least uragan the
second actually is cool here we go again
I'm getting my stuff I don't care I'm
getting my stuff
maybe whoa what a cool room maybe they
surely they're gone now right look at
the damage alright if I find like a
sword or anything I'll take it I see
stuff down there oh my god that's my
stuff that's literally my stuff this is
good okay this is just the first stuff
there's nothing you drop the phone come
on come on come on
surely my diamond pickaxe is here right
look at this explosion dude you can all
gone cool let's never do that again
epic did you find the treasure yes what
did it cost everything okay
okay Jurgen imputes for more adventures
I am genuinely upset over minecraft is
that another one or the same one okay no
it's the same one is that another
shipwreck
it is isn't it damn it's far your again
will you be good
sorry hundred fishes in Sweden hi yep
oh my god it worked okay we're going to
the pirate thing and maybe we finally
get some good news this episode god damn
it
there better be epic treasure oh this
one looks bigger I see a treasure okay
okay well what is this whoa looks like
an air hole cool paper hey you want some
paper here you go Felix oh there's
another one
potatoes Oh another one
whoa okay rich boy rich boy I could get
good cheap ants oh okay epic Jurgen it
was awesome
oh my god very dude we found it use your
map Oh what do I do with it
what I do with buried treasure map Sun
is setting let's go back home you're
again it's been an adventure you're
getting a second
all right time to go to sleep I'll dream
of yet again the first forever
one thing that I'm curious about is yeah
I hope you're dying what happens if you
build another nether portal in the
nether realm question mark so let's
explore that question okay I never
actually done this how do I do it
what are gamers here we go oh yeah
gaming time hey someone's shooting me
this is my gaming town if I remember
correctly I had an obsidian down here
yeah there it is
just be careful cuz there's freaking
lava everywhere this is always fun what
the hell is that
what's bad dumb back haha I would never
make that mistake okay we have 10 all we
need baby now if we enter the nether
what a pig
now let's say we walk a bit further god
it's so hard to walk in there where
would I go either you guys have nothing
better to do Jesus Christ dude oh my god
fine let's just build a bridge lives
gives you lemons build bridges over them
so what is that down there is that worth
mining I wish I knew
maybe I'll explode out of nowhere or we
can just clog this what's that sound
I think we can stop this as well oh yeah
Noboru lava
don't worry piggies I won't charge in
okay what is this nun Dakota whoa he
looks cool Wow all right don't walk on
them
guarding I can hold them I can't walk on
him
I mean I guess it makes sense they're
hot dude there's so many what's
happening with the music hello
little too epic for my taste thank you
alright alright you can come down
minecraft magma block okay Eppie why do
I feel like my whole life is flashing
through my eyes
holy moly macaroni
Patroni this better not kill me I'm
gonna be pissed okay let's go what's
gonna happen I don't know that's the joy
of mine crap so it does take me to
another place what
don't case no take me back to Netherland
why is there under water things there uh
hello
what is it a glitch Oh what okay that's
scary Mac my blogs oh god there's
LARPing
that's so confusing so those lit up
don't explode my llamas I will kill you
how the shield can tank them how they
talk to big noises
gunpowder break break break break
they're so cute
I want to take you home oh my god you're
so adorable oh my god they're still
coming from this one's gonna Bowl dude
it's a swamp monster these guys are
strong dude
I want the llama what do they eat so you
saw anyway I can breathe on the water
easier Oh what is this I don't know
there better not be tramps that's no
Elena this stays
oh there's Ches the better not be sharks
in this game then I'm quitting I did
just want the chest are you kidding me
that's it
oh it's his what blue eyes so if I kill
him can i still islamís cuz I will do it
don't you spit on me okay I see a lot
more stuff to explore but I'm gonna have
to end this episode here guys because I
need that comments to help me actually I
can't trust you smash like let's see you
guys next time bye oh you never played
super simulator you know it's fun right
I'm not supposed to give my opinion but
give it a try and then you can tell me
if it's good or not not convinced yet
okay I'll cut you a deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price