welcome to Hawaii everyone's favorite
show of the week let's prick and do this
oh boy
can't wait to read a bunch of James
Charles memes that are gonna be slightly
outdated yay
[Music]
fatality it makes me so mad that British
people say the c-word in every sense
like oh that one is actually awful
please stop what consent how to spot a
slime bag people that tweet this things
there you go it's always the one that
say these sort of things that are doing
it to cover up from something else I've
no one asked the fat rat is that it
again YouTube's suspended my channel
with three point six million subscribers
without any explanation or warning and
without having a strike this is so crazy
I don't even know what to say wait
didn't something else happened to this
guy already we're by like a copyright
strike alright this is still down though
it's it's back up we did it reddit good
job ready just got the message that my
channel has been reinstated it's been a
rough mother staying sleepless night but
girls have been heartwarming see all
this amazing Gordon thank you so much
see this is crazy to me
kissy YouTube's algorithm it's like
strike first ask questions later
he might have waken up one day and then
you're live what your livelihood depends
on is just completely gone this happened
so many times as so many channels how is
it possible by the way guys the
PewDiePie glow-in-the-dark shaker cups
have sold out I'm so sorry this is you
when you realize you never bought one
[Music]
five million in six months never done
before 30 million in six months never
done before - three million this is so
outdated I can't believe you lost three
million in two days never done before
you did it James Charles congratulations
it's crazy
Logan pole gained subscribers out of his
controversy can you I don't know it's
it's insane
oh my god boy I spent 24 hours in
straining slime I spent 24 hours in
slime and it was a huge mistake
it's like be original and then the
cancer version of it I spent 24 hours
straight in an insane asylum I spent 24
hours in insane asylum challenge I put
100 million Orbeez in my friends
backyard I put 100 million Orbeez in my
bed mom's backyard Frank Frank
mr. bees caught on I spent 24 hours
straight in prison challenge Oh God and
he just copied it Jesus Christ dude I
think I I pointed it out in my video I
don't know if it made the cut but I was
like wait is he just copying mr. bees
well I guess he is 100% does he at least
acknowledge it because otherwise it's
pretty messed up dude
oh my god that's beautiful thank you old
house Pedro and at attack Jesus Christ
he's staring into my soul
suckee can see my beauty and love it
when you notice how irrelevant T series
is after the meeting most people didn't
even know who they were before all this
honestly
best roast ever Tati congrats on 50
million been here since 16 can wait for
James Charles to hit 10 million so he
can get his diamond plague button
Cleveland James Charles next video 5
subscribers oh my god thank you so much
I mean it is kind of funny as much as I
don't like to admit it
the means are good Fame power and fat
bank and cat will change almost anyone
not me I sell all that it's a fine car
than its own it is a fine vehicle to say
the least
oh my god brofist statue finally done
you got to get a read though it looks
like a brain I mean it's amazing I love
it thank you so much
finalize my prom outfit today damn hell
yeah it is oh my god let's make out
may 9th Pro Jared became the first
person to lose hundred K subs in a date
may 10th James Charles became the first
person to lose 1 million in a day
poor Jared lost his marriage dignity
career and now he lost his Saab lost
records yeah
god dammit I we shouldn't read it before
ok pubsey apex let's grab the powder you
picked the wrong house boo am I allowed
to do a black man voice but he says it
that way Brad will decide Pano's goes to
Mars without Elan and they talk about
memes while smoke what in the world ok
cuz all the different endings yeah I
guess that's good when you go against a
whole class and your answer turns out to
be correct
they called me a man me when I went
after Tati ever when everyone wanted
blood for James oh my god you see in my
artificial links we've now introduced so
I can feel pain in them my pee pee hard
Ricardo Milla's James Charles JK Rowling
turning straight guys game hey maybe
just maybe I have this crazy idea maybe
if you can be convinced to sleep with
another man or make out then maybe
you're not straight it's my cake day
fred is gonna cut the hat please can
this get to the why this will probably
get 7 upvotes beards needs to see that
20k effort see
that's usually when I cut the episode
cuz around 20k it's all it's the wealth
in ways can you not repost for five
minutes the subreddit is fine did you
get to bird simulator yes what did it
cost nothing and that's a great price
that's weird I don't think this
character is in Toomer simulator hmm
[Music]
that's strange ending this subscribe to
p defy me I broke my ass I broke my boss
like I would premiered it as well and
the chatters went F the whole way four
hours
oopsie-doopsie James Charles kind of use
his fame and power to get straight
people into gate also pretty but sorry
guys someone makes an oopsie Gloria
Borger
Gloria Borger is fired I'm sorry guys
she didn't do enough research I had to
let her go a royal wedding the Royal
Wedding like a this is full bloom summer
and my face could not be any more white
I had not
I'm literally spent the whole summer
just making videos I remember it so much
when you're fat a failure in school and
don't have a girlfriend but you're mean
makes it to the why I'm still worthy
yeah okay sure whatever you gotta say to
yourself
worst YouTube channel man your homes
assembled this is made like five years
ago when people used it and hate me oh
how things change oh wait nothing's
change we've gotten some requests by our
fans to have you on the off the pill
what are you saying you're down well
there's never been a more convincing
arguments of other people want you to be
on our show so I mean how could I refuse
other people have told us this so
therefore I suppose we will ask Wow
really guys you want me on the show
why thank you so much I'm joking I would
like to be but a podcast is like a
double-edged sword
okay I committed to this analogy I guess
I don't want to do them and I'll
probably just get say something that
gets me in trouble there you go mom can
we get home we have mercy at home I
can't even read marzia no oh she looks
so much better
Wow got a feel gotta feel good to be
like the the ugly version of the meme
the ugly version of the joke how does
that feel faith Dave you're beautiful
though they said I broke my boss hey I
remember touching your balls lol thanks
ball doctor friendlies remembering fame
power and fat bank account will change
what's anyone hello how that's a meme
now oh there it is again
fame power and fat bank account will
change almost everyone anyone I'm a
freak now it's rare to see 96 million of
anything I saw that video and I remember
the title as well I think it is like 96
millions I'm speaking the language of
guards 6 3 3 6 3 3 it sounded like I
almost got it whatever that's not what
it is anyway I got sidetracked
oh god damn it god damn it I'm so stupid
good day edit that one out Bryan Beauty
pie Felix Arvid Ulf Shelley boot again
congratulations for a surprising 100
million subscribers hashtag thank you
Peter pie shell boutique I'm a booty
gear this is the final draft okay is you
might want to do just another draft
maybe just maybe just one more can't you
do that I mean I don't want to criticize
it but like why the yell of fun and like
the phone itself is kind of ugly I'm not
being ungrateful and also like the
brofist logo I know that's very popular
but generally use it that much anymore I
think in this is certainly interesting
2016 2019 you know that there's a
problem in the video quality from 2016
is better than the quality now that
can't be right tell me what isn't better
haircut I went to this in hairdresser
that was like hey let's do something
avant-garde and I'm just sitting there
like okay why does it look so bad you're
right it does not look this bad when I
sent up the footage it does noise it
does not I created 100 mils of spray but
in concept for Pierce as a 3d model took
me two seconds to second what that's a
lot of little seconds that was cool
though I liked it
why is millennial humor so weird why is
dr. Phil so beautiful 2016 Pete by every
company that makes a game free is just
stupid the game is available for free
and that's a great price well I talked
about this before but everyone was so
pissed that we charge money for legend
of the brofist and we thought we did the
right thing we're like hey it's a full
game you can just play right away and
then it was like it's not free so it's
like well Frick it then we'll do make a
free-to-play game
Peter PI I see you follow me that's good
because I saw your video the day it came
up I love to do this on a commuting
review I'll send my skype April Oh
okay let's get the ball rolling I'm
sorry I've been very busy it's happening
my mailman is showed up okay that was it
for this week's live live thanks for all
the amazing memes and all the amazing
times and all this amazing support and
most of all thanks Brad for editing this
video that's incredible that he does
that and I see you guys tomorrow
that's right tomorrow I'll be here
tomorrow I don't know why every time I
do the outer I'm like I just want to sit
down why do I even film these standing
up it's very tiring to stand up I don't
like standing up okay
end of video see you bye bye a hundred
mill soon so make sure to subscribe it's
over there
what you never played tuber simulator
you know it's fun right I'm not supposed
to give my opinion but give it a try and
then you can tell me if it's good or not
not convinced yet okay I'll cut you a
deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]