how's it going brauch my name is Pierre
Pam and let's find out why my channel is
dying Google Trends everyone a wonderful
tool that seems underutilized have you
ever looked on Google Trends as I know
what ever done this video before am I
the first one
oh my god did I just have an original
idea that's all so few days ago me and
Jack did a video where we looked a
little bit into Google Trends but I want
to really dig deeper
I want to truly understand why everyone
else is doing so goddamn good and now me
so let's find out
cool maybe my channel is dying cuz I
can't ride it PewDiePie oh my god
well it looks like I'm not the only one
with this problem by type you who the
hell is pie type you know reading
youtuber pie dipu he's my favorite he's
so funny he's so good alright let's just
go into this so here we get an interest
overtime grant pretty interesting I
would say you know it's it's there you
don't really get the full picture unless
you hit the whole graph so let's start
up here in 2012 this is where I'm nice I
guess I started becoming more popular
I'm not exactly sure what they represent
what but I hit my peak at 2014 what
happened in 2014 I need to understand so
someone made a playlist I guess I played
games in 2014 no controversy no nothing
huh I'm actually in the same room
nothing's changed five years Jesus
Christ when did I become the biggest
channel in 2013 damn it's been a long
time it's 2013 and then I I peaked in
2014 and then it all just it all just
went down I think it's interesting to
note at least for me cuz anyone that
came before me almost every single
channel that has been before me has is
disappeared okay everyone that's been
bigger than me they've all they're all
gone because of this fact I've always
just looked at YouTube like it could end
at end
like I should just be ready to pack my
dad bags out any day
I actually oh wait let me see if I can
find that sorry I'm this is video is
just gonna be one giant engine so I did
a I think in 2012 I did a I did a
presentation do not google it for the
love of God but I I found the pictures
and I talked about you know doing Let's
Plays as a job people didn't really know
anything about it at the time look here
I'm showing off my stats being like hey
guys it's going pretty well
there was one information that I I was
really interested by sick of boring
Let's Plays I am you're salivate er I
found the presentation where is it
beautiful faces of horror okay so how
did I get to where I am full time job to
videos every day do something different
let myself into the game blocks so what
happens in the future I thought it was
interesting how I kind of questioned how
it was something stable or not with laws
and regulations and copyright I thought
these things would hit quicker I really
I was so unsure whether he would even be
allowed to monetize the gameplay on
YouTube I think it's it's one of those
things where people really fought for
and to try and convince companies as
well that it's benefit fitting for them
like these big cup publishers like EA
but that's that whatever they benefit
from people playing their game and they
them understanding that has really had a
huge impact on on YouTube and gaming I
can easily see it go in another way
where gaming would just not be allowed
on YouTube and I that's always been in
the back of my head you know and now in
the future 2019 nothing's really changed
its article 13 all these stuffs
happening I think this is where wall
street journal' happened I think it
happened in February because it was
literally on Valentine's Day
it was here so this is a Wall Street
Journal and then Barbara Babbitt above
just been kind of stable for a long time
and then Jay says Christ
t-series but my favorite part of this
graph is when I go hey guys let's end
this subscribe PT pi meme like we
shouldn't do this anymore okay
skydive graphic you know this is the
kind of reports you want to see a
full-on economic crash thank you guys so
much I can't wait to hit a hundred
million subscribers in a couple of years
no one cares Felix fine you know what
this is just America what if like in
Afghanistan I'm actually popular zero
what about Chad what about Chad
goddamnit Chad so according to this
state of America I am most popular in
the state of lova what the Frick is that
with the dumb name of a state lova what
do you love so much
which country am I most popular in they
give Sweden very cold
too bad you're such a tiny insignificant
country come on Annie imagine if I was
the biggest one in India oh my god
this is so sad I am so oppressed if I
was born in any other country everything
would be different
Norway come on what is this despite
years of abuse Norway's Norwegian bras
are still here thank you guys
very good New Zealand Australia Estonia
what what is this Philippines is my
second biggest country damn Philippine
iam bros thank you okay so what are the
most search related terms for PewDiePie
PewDiePie Swedish youtuber I don't
understand why people make it all about
me being Swedish I never make my channel
about being Swedish of course TV series
number two so this is what most people
have searched and related to me I think
that's what it is and then the third
most related is my net worth
sorry mics yeah you're not as important
by sitcoms forth my net worth
PewDiePie net worth so basically what
this means is that most people that
search PewDiePie PewDiePie net worth so
really in reality what I should do is I
should title this video P PI net worth
and I will inevitably give me a lot of
views based on search terms according to
this I am my net worth is 20 million 20
million dollars
it's more I am sorry but it's a bit more
than that I don't know exactly how net
worth is mentioned measured but if it's
based on how much money on my bank
account then I'm sorry you're coming a
little short there buddy oh god damn it
it turns out I've already done the net
I've already done the net worth me Marge
the abyss of mean Italian internet
personality let's look at how Martha is
doing Oh projection that he might go up
well that's good
Connecticut okay happy wheels video game
guys happy wheels video game I can't
believe that's the fifth highest people
always associate me with horror games
but I guess happy wheels is bigger
markiplier
that's insane so many people Google me
and markiplier we barely done any videos
together we did this one as no one
searched there it is scare PewDiePie
scare PewDiePie at a hundred million
let's get it please alright so let's
compare it to another youtuber what's a
youtuber doing well mr. B's nevermind
wait okay he's doing really well okay
never mind Jesus Christ Australian New
Zealand do you do anything but watching
youtubers mr. B's network meth worse me
mysteries p5 good back how are they how
are the pole brothers doing look at this
dude holy look how much bigger they
were than me at some point that's crazy
so Jake Paul is technically been bigger
than I've ever been
none knee alright who's bigger than
Logan and Jake Paul holy dude holy
okay so Logan is blue I'm red look at
Logan holy Sh that's nuts
so the suicide forest was literally four
times as big as the diversity series
that that's nuts
that is crazy am I the only one
interested by this okay so we now know
we're failing but that doesn't mean we
give up goddammit
subscribe god damn it I need a hundred
million there's another website that
lets you look at statistics and
analytics of course socialblade I used
to be obsessed with social Blaine and I
think a lot of youtubers are a lot of
youtubers go on social blade and they
look at their own stats and they compare
it to other people and they they
frantically I think that makes a lot of
people really really depressed why my
lack Finke what's wrong with me
it's just that imagine that you have a
job and how well you are performing in
that job is 100% public and 100%
comparable to all your peers like
there's some deep psychological
emotional stress that is always
lingering for a lot of youtubers I
literally have not gone on social blade
in like four years I just stopped I
don't know why what happened
after a while it just luckily it just
ironically it hit me it doesn't matter
like I don't care how many subscribers I
have it doesn't matter and I don't have
to waste time just obsessing about this
stuff but I do remember I used to obsess
about this stuff and I think a lot of
youtubers do especially comparing
themselves so my views are up yay my
subscribers are doing estimated monthly
earnings it seems about right I used to
complain so much when I saw these
estimated monthly earnings but like
that's ridiculous
how can I possibly make that much money
and then clearly I have been very poorly
monetizing my channel like before I
would make 4-minute videos you barely
make any money on those like that's
impossible how can everyone make so much
money oh oh I'm not monetizing my
channel oh okay cool well maybe that's a
part of the reason 21 billion views
that's nuts dude okay so what I
really want to investigate here is the
top
subscribers who's gaining the most
subscribers right now okay 300,000 in a
day Jesus Christ
knowledge TV teach me clearly I need to
become Indian I'm beginning to see a
pattern here okay well that was
analytics with PDP I hope you guys
thought this was interesting I've
literally uploaded every single day for
as long as I can remember taking minimum
breaks as much as I can possibly take
take it's crazy to me how I still enjoy
it I don't get it either
why am I here it's fun I don't know what
to tell you one thing that I am thinking
about is like I've never had a proper
break like I never had a long break
where I'm just a normal person
that isn't constantly thinking about
YouTube but literally if I took a break
it would kill my channel the way YouTube
is shaped at this point it's like you
just have to keep making videos
otherwise there won't be anything to
come back to we've seen this happen
through so many youtubers they go on a
break and then hey guys what's up Oh
everyone is gone oh no didn't light and
leave the algorithm made it so you know
that's always a fun lingering fact at
the back of your mind bring youtuber
it's such an easy job you guys don't
understand it doesn't even matter we're
all gonna be replaced by AI in the
future this has been PewDiePie analytics
subscribe goddammit
goodbye what you never played super
simulator you know it's fun right I'm
not supposed to give my opinion but give
it a try
and then you can tell me if it's
not convinced yet okay I'll cut you a
deal the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]