I might have to pull my age can we can
say PB chemi-con say baby Oh beauty pie
truck patty pie truck what's up everyone
we're playing cross now you may haven't
seen this game before I I at least have
seen where some guy literally slam-dunk
two other vehicles in this game
[Music]
we're not gonna do that today however
the gist of this game is that you can
build your own vehicles and then you
fight against other people and depending
on how much parts you put into the
vehicle you'll fight stronger or worse
people I'm kind of new to this game but
I'm really drawn into the creative
aspect of it so I'll build some quirky
little stuff later but for now PD pie
truck and you get a bonus if you check
out the link for registering you get
three weapons or a van cabin guys this
game is super fun check it out it's free
you can download it right now it's out
on Xbox Playstation 4 PC and it's right
there look you can see what other people
built Tesla cyber truck wow it's so tidy
oh yeah and you can also fuse vehicles I
love how this game is a meme if you have
a bunch of friends you can merge your
vehicles together as one unfortunately I
have no friends 30pi truck
yeah PD PI drug what do you want huh ah
get out he's crazy man if I slammed up
move it down that make up yeah stop this
is God you know what I don't think we to
play trucks strong in it whoa there's
how how how would these even work it
doesn't okay cool
come here come here it's time to dispose
trash come on
this is so sad what the hell is that
surprise some of these are really cool
I'm sorry what what is this who made
this and why oh yeah
wait what if we change it and on the
front it's just a spike instead we just
put Alliance online yes I call this one
pp mobile oh just wait until I poke
someone with this
I feel very alpha right now I'm not
gonna lie oh god it's a little hard to
steer there we go our first target come
on PP don't touch my peepee
don't touch my baby what are you yelling
oh you rub a back I'll never forget I
just need no one to touch my peepee
except the tip difficult be VP judge oh
my gosh I first amazing hey come back
here let me poke you
yeah BP BP attack too strong BB too
strong yeah
Oh God Oh
no no yeah he doesn't have a gun man
yeah
get away Paul I may be small but I still
have strength come back here this is my
kill this is my time yup yeah oh stop
stop stop stop stop stop all this bad
this feel bad I might have to pull my
age can we catch a PB Tammy got a baby
o.o can't believe i lost
oh man I love this thing it's beautiful
let me touch you let me touch you
come on from coward oh I missed the tip
stop this is not how the PB machine goes
what are you doing
drive around the PP idiot
what are you doing get off get off my
peepee thank you thank you have some
respect baby
ah nice are you kidding me yeah yeah
yeah that's a lot of em that's a lot of
damage no you can't kill what this
alright you can't kill it whatever
whatever you prove nothing
who's shooting me don't you dare the
blockade it works yes yes oh I think I
have still one PP charge I am still one
BB charge
oh yeah
nice that was my best game
flying machines dude you're not supposed
to fly in this game okay so if I boost I
assume it will fly scare me okay I like
that all I want to do is fly shooting it
Wow nah nope nope I need help i need
help God maybe I shouldn't try and
change now I feel like I've proven how
is strong the PP you
[Music]
damn look at this boy oh nice oh my god
what the hell just happened
hahahahahahaha the evil laughter did I
actually build a machine that isn't Van
Damme all right oh look at the Arabic
look at Eric he's spread wide open what
the hell is that you know what I won't
even ask
I shouldn't be judging people for their
different sizes okay so this is the
people mobile obviously the greatest
bill of all time I think that I didn't
show you guys that is so cool is that if
you use the link in the description to
download the game you can get Swedish
lasagna both old and new players will
get this my god that looks so much
better and epic brofist very nice
although this is not really my creation
I have an idea to make it even better
that's right
legs it has peepee has legs this is my
fantasy come true at last
at long last oh it's actually not bad
be be strong let's perfect it yes that
looks scared I have an idea
there we go it's the brofist PP mobile
2.0 there it is Swedish lasagna live
step we'll just be to add something that
does some more damage to Melly right
which one knows it there it is so
another cool thing about this game is
that they have a bunch of not just PvP
but PvE stuff as well like raid vs
bandits let's try this out oh my god
it's so good I love this design yes the
brofist pp hey hey get out don't touch
it don't touch it don't touch my bro
face a man can I get it bro yeah yeah oh
brofist that's what I'm talking about
Oh too strong you can't handle the power
of the bro face ruff it's coming through
excuse me so now we can save this
obviously I did still some ideas but I
think there's an improvement if you guys
want to download this one it's called
bro fish there it is if you guys want to
check it out it's the ultimate killing
machine I guarantee it
alright here we go I'll never see this
coming
I guess that could work too slam dunk
oh yeah flip them kind of work alright I
got to find like a light vehicle
you ready put your slam slam dunk are
you kidding me
oh my god I can't drive too fast hey I
don't need judgment Malik I don't need
judgment come on help out Molly can't
help out come on oh yeah come on come on
Malik please have a brother there you go
thank you
I got you Malik
oh no my peepee 2.0 rolling out no ya
got game dammit I can flip myself up
there we go
I feel good about this one does this
thingy oh he shot off my pic starting to
think peepee isn't a good idea
no society that isn't a good idea help
help
just help me thank you
this thing doesn't steer it doesn't
steer steer I think there's there's a
slight design flaw on but I think I'm
able that yeah I think I'm able to work
fast thing breath yeah help me thank you
thank you I spent a lot of time on this
thank you thank you
oh yeah come stand to me all right I got
him
got him
oh my god peepee gotta kill yes it was
worth it
alright that was me playing cross-eyed
it's a really fun game I highly
recommend you download it no if no maybe
the game is free check it out it's out
on PlayStation for PC and Xbox one it's
free