how's it going bros my name is ohmygod
peered pie wreaked paid the price so
strong this has basically been all over
any form of social media oh my god ah
it's basically being plastered on my
subreddit
they even had to close send the
subreddit because people kept posting
about it this isn't the why however but
54,000 people want a workout review so
that's what we're gonna do today I'm I
wasn't planning to talk about it or make
a video like this in a long time at
least I don't know six months a year to
for me to actually gain some muscle
I'm not ripped okay I'm just lean or
what there's a difference I I feel like
I still have a long way to go but what
happened was I was putting up some light
outside I mean that was challenging
ceiling game as you can see my workout
routines hundred tambourine hits add a
hundred mics it came out and she was
like damn so she's not the photo of me
and they should we both looked at it
like what the even I was shocked I had
any workout that day it's not like I was
pumped up or anything so she shared it
on her social media because you know
it's lame if I share it and goddamn
people freaked out did not expect that I
guess since people always I've always
been very skinny for a very long time
and people always see me that that's oh
do you gain any form of muscle it and
people are like what yeah this is me
before yep oh yeah there it is I'm glad
that photo exists and yeah this is me
now I guess at the end at the end of the
montage I need a couple more montages
come on I saw people online debating if
I'm using roids or any sort of
supplement it's like I don't even know
what they're talking about I don't know
what it means I'm not that strong and
other people were just going like oh oh
he's got a super-rich he's got like a
super good trainer pumping him every day
and he's got like this insane gym at
home he can afford it so I thought why
don't I just start off by showing what
my gym looks like welcome and here's my
gym set it Eggar spots me thank you very
much
so basically it's just as what is it
call Finch it's garbage it's so bad it's
so bulky I swear to God I feel like if I
ever die it's because this thing
collapses on me half the time the screws
are coming off and I have to keep
screwing them in so they ignite these
are super nifty and the way they work is
that you can very quickly change each
weight that you want you want 30 40 60
50 70 it goes up to 90 actually I have
90 here that's why and even ten without
anything okay for 130 BAM lifts up ready
to go and that's why I have this risk
protection because it hits my wrists
sometimes and it hurts a lot so I got
these I actually recommend it if you're
using these let me feel more badass
somehow I don't know why it does have a
problem which is that if I want to make
a jump it's a high jump to go from 80 to
90 pounds that's from from 36 kilos to
41 instead of going from 36 kilos to
maybe
38 or 39 it takes me a lot longer to
jump in in weight basically that's the
problem I have with these but it saves
you a lot of money and a lot of space to
not have a whole rack with dumbbells
which would be nice I should probably
get that but these are cheaper I also
have these which are good for it's good
for extra grip when you're doing pool
exercises they're okay they're not that
great it's just very frustrating
again I'm filming it is very frustrating
when you're trying to hit away and you
know you can do it but you're losing
grip I hate that so much so these help
and that's pretty much it
I put my workout Journal here next to
all day all the chemicals so I write
down all the this is me day one I was
doing flat press 50-member soon cemani
and then I could do it's not that bad
actually
I haven't improved that much it's just I
hurt my arm recently so I haven't really
I'm careful I'm careful what the show
here cuz sometimes I write down I get
angry and I write down about your show
do it [ __ ]
so it's notes for me for the next week I
always go through what I did the
previous week so I'm like yeah next time
do this [ __ ] you wimp
right arm weak very compared to left
yeah this is two weeks ago I hurt my arm
this is probably dumbbells and don't
make the mistakes I made properly
warm-up make the right movements because
if you get injured you're you're out for
three weeks at least it takes that long
for the muscles to recover it it's very
easy to get damage with dumbbells I also
hurt my back from lifting down the
dumbbells which is equally important so
if you're working out with dumbbells be
careful I'm saying it to myself in the
past it's not worth it to get injured
just take it slow but yeah I think it's
cool I like the idea that anyone can
pick up this with in their house it's
very small it doesn't take up a lot of
space and it's fairly cost efficient if
you have if you don't have access to a
gym this is a pretty good space I would
say gym is always better because you're
gonna have machines and you're not gonna
hurt yourself like I do like a skinny
again that's my setup setup for I know
my my setup is and I know I could get
more but I just really like the idea
that I can move it anywhere
it feels very liberating to have that
kind of set up and you can do a ton with
dumbbells like I said in the video so
just be careful that's all
so I've never actually spoken about my
workout history or whatever in 2016 I
had never been to a gym before in my
entire life and I I didn't know anything
I don't know how to properly squat I
didn't know what reps meant I didn't
know what sets meant I but I wanted to
try and get in shape in better shape at
least so I kind of forced myself to go
to a gym I I was terrified I had no idea
what to expect and it was just the
overconfidence in me
just said I'll cage you just go in there
and just how hard can it be you just put
up and down weights anyone can do that
don't be me basically what I'm saying if
you've never been touching before ask a
friend to introduce you or or even
better and ask one of the personal
trainers at the gym they'll definitely
be one and they'll help you out I keep
seeing the sentiment that people that
are maybe overweight or don't feel
confident about their body or I feel
like they're gonna be judged or
something like that that you just
couldn't be further from a true and I
gotta say the personal trainers that I
worked with have just been the most
motivating and supportive people because
that's their job you know it's so
definitely don't be scared to do that
and to just get started a lot of gyms
will offer one personal trainer for free
so it's a hundred percent worth it
absolutely you need to know what you're
doing going into a gym so I surely after
I switched gyms and I got started with a
personal trainer which was really good
he taught me to how to really push
myself how to workout with dumbbells
ironically this is me after going to the
gym you can tell there's some muscle
yeah okay maybe I don't know I think the
most strong I was at the time was in
this video you can sorta tell there's
some muscle there but not a lot this was
really good the problem was that I
didn't have a goal with my exercise I
just sort of went with it which was a
big mistake and I knew you know at the
back of my mind I was working myself to
the point where I was throwing up you
know I was really almost I wasn't
actually throwing up but when you feel
like oh god I cannot give any more which
is common when you start off and you
haven't worked out before but in the
back of my mind I was like there's no
way I can maintain this for a long time
you know so lo and behold I got sick I
got a stomach flow that was really bad
and they knocked me out for two to three
weeks and after that I just I just never
picked it up again and any sort of
progress that I've gained from from
those months at the gym after a year you
know I was still fit but it most of the
games were gone
and so I decided to myself okay I'll
just set up a bench I'll set up some
dumb little side home and I can just
work out from that you know and this
time I'm not gonna make the same mistake
I'm just gonna be consistent and I'm not
gonna overdo it so I did that for a year
this really measly workout just to be
consistent because you know I've been
consistent on YouTube and that sort of
been my success so that can translate
into exercise and yeah it just got to a
point where I was fed up and I I wanted
to really start pushing myself and I did
that two months ago and that's when I
really started to notice the big
difference that you've seen in the
photos today and this is after reading a
lot of books reading a lot of philosophy
you guys know I'm a fan of Mishima so if
you know Mishima that's pretty
self-explanatory for those who don't
know Mishima was an author that was
absolutely ripped he talked a lot of my
body and action wishes a message today
that seems completely lost and I read a
bunch of other books as well that helped
me develop my philosophy around exercise
which seems kind of cringy and and like
it doesn't match no work at it that's
for dummies which couldn't be further
from the truth if anything body and soul
are are deeply connected and I wanted
them to match and that's why I really
wanted to start pushing myself with my
work AB so this time I had a clear goal
what I was getting into so I just needed
to push myself this time but how I
didn't have it I don't have a personal
trainer anymore so I sort of became my
own personal trainer I knew which
workout that was needed to be done I
just didn't know how to not slack off
because it's easier to slack off when
you work out on your own it's totally
possible to to work out on your own but
it's always better with a trainer or a
friend or with someone else so I started
tracking down my training I wrote down
in a journal which you saw earlier my
reps my sights the weights and how much
rest time I would keep and I would
really try and push myself each time to
make sure I was making progress
in retrospect I don't think that was the
most important thing to do their most
important thing is to really do it until
you fail like you can't push any longer
that should be the goal instead but it
worked out for me
so my workout routine finally we got to
it I'm sorry for so much talking
so Monday's I do push exercises I do
chest heavily on chest everyone keeps
making fun of my chest in the in the
photo but it looks better in person
trust me it's massive I got a huge tease
and then I finish off with shoulders I
don't remember it in my head but it's
something like that and then Tuesdays I
do leg squats deadlifts yada yada lunges
and then Wednesday I do pull exercises
then Thursday I do leg a and leg again
and then Friday I finish with a mix of
push and pull I know there's other
variations of this sort of workout that
are more efficient and I'm probably
gonna change my workout pretty soon but
it worked out for me so far I literally
just googled online like five day
dumbbell workout and you could probably
find it yourself and follow it so or
maybe I'll leave a link to an in
description if you want to try what I
did the most important thing is to
really push yourself until you fail but
the next thing which is very important
and people always say that it's
important but then they just ignore it
anyway but it is equally important
because when you're lifting weight
you're only burning so many calories no
matter how heavy of an exercise you
don't really lose weight more in lifting
weights ironically you have to change
your diet if you want to lose body fat
and the probably the biggest difference
for me was cutting out alcohol which is
something I talked about before I'd say
maybe a year ago I quit alcohol for the
first time yes you guys know I like my
whiskey too much I like my whiskey too
much which was not healthy I didn't feel
good about it so I quit alcohol
completely and I did that for a couple
months and I felt okay great you know I
can actually do this but then afterwards
I just fell back into my old habits and
I felt you can be and terrible about it
like I was slowly killing myself it's
great so I so I basically made the same
mistake I did with my workout as I did
with my eating or drinking rather and
there was obviously a lot of calories
and drinking that's not the reason I
quit but it helps to have another reason
to quit it I decided to just cut off
hard liquor from my palate I just
realized it's not for me if other people
like it that's great I just know I'm not
never again I do drink maybe like a pint
of beer once a week if I'm hanging out
with friends online or whatever I drink
socially basically if someone saying hey
as so as services and talk about how
it's important to let your spirit loose
and I kind of agree with that I was I
think the problem was before when I quit
drinking is that I was too strict on it
I didn't want to be that person in the
friend group and I think this way I'm
just gonna be able to to stick with it
and honestly quitting drinking it it was
hard it was a habit that I had develop
and like you probably have some food or
some craving that you really feel
strongly about maybe you don't realize
that you're addicted to it but once you
cut it out of your your diet that's when
you realize that you are addicted to it
and you sort of just like you trained
yourself to like that food and depend on
that food you have to train yourself to
not be dependent on it and that's really
tough in the beginning but once you get
out of it you've gained a whole
different perspective and youie even me
looking back on my old drinking habits I
have really looked back on it with the
test and in the shame of my past self
you have to realize that sensational
pleasures
don't bring happiness and as soon as you
take that first wipe it's already
fleeting it's not gonna make you happy
now I feel like there's almost a social
idea that you need food to be happy oh I
need these food because they make me
happy or whatever which isn't true
recently there was a comedian Kumail
Nanjiani who got really really ripped
for Marvel role this is really
impressive Jesus Christ those veins
breath and I saw he went on the Kimmel
show and they had prepared this like
funny idea where okay so you reached
your goal now now we're gonna set you
off with a bunch of cakes and a bunch of
pizzas
yeah something special for you please go
ahead and be careful
[Music]
and I get it it's it's just a funny
thing but I also feel like this shows
the to me at least the idea that oh you
like these sort of things are dependent
for for becoming happy or it reinforces
it at the very least it doesn't state it
necessarily gonna happen and I remember
very specifically the day we were like
is she gonna make it is she gonna make
it and I remember when I got to the
hospital one of those days and went and
she was up and sitting on her bed I'm
happier right now sorry this video just
became me ranting about different topics
hopefully it is helpful for people to
understand my mindset because I really
think mindset is one of the most
important things if you want to work out
you can obviously anyone can pick up
working out for a little while but
unless you have the right mindset you're
not gonna be able to be consistently
pushing yourself for it one of the best
things I done out of all of these and
and the change in my life that I'm the
most happy about is I looked up how much
protein I needed you can do this as well
I'll link a little website down below so
you can put in your weight you can put
in your height and then you can put in
how much you work out and then it tells
you okay well this is roughly what your
daily protein intake should be and mine
was just way off so I started just
stuffing myself with a bunch of protein
snacks you know protein bars nuts that
have a lot of protein it's not as great
but it's if you want something savory
it's good
this was life-changing for me because I
used to struggle a lot with anger I
never really I talked about actually my
sources and video about anger and I have
made the habit of being very angry often
and very confrontational and aggressive
at first I liked that part of myself
because I thought oh this is another
sort of image of a man kind of like
whisky is seen as manly you know it's
it's society looks at anger a lot of
ways as something manly as well and I
think recognizing these things as just
that and I started meditating on it a
lot
I was able to control my anger much much
better so this doesn't really help with
that as well but I would still you know
feel it I would still feel that anger
even though I didn't act on it the same
way I used to I will feel happy now with
virtuous by the fact that I wasn't
acting on my anger anymore but I wasn't
my happy self that I would you normally
used to be and as much as I would like
to at least but protein makes you self
so much fuller and it doesn't make your
at least for me my blood sugar spike is
much so if that problem for me which was
a big problem just completely
disappeared just by me trying to eat
more protein so I'm so happy I made that
change it wasn't intentional but it's
just something that just worked out
really well for me I guess last thing
working out will not solve all your
problems it will not fix any sort of
issues there's obviously many reasons to
work out that are very positive you you
will you'll look better you'll feel more
confident you'll be more healthy but
these are obviously degenerate reasons
to work out you exercise you extra lift
weights for Mishima okay you lift
weights for homework you lift weights to
escape abstract concepts like time and
death that's the only acceptable reasons
and just lastly if you feel good about
yourself already there's there's no
shape whatever size or shape you are I
don't care all right if you feel good
about yourself all right great excellent
this is not a video to make it like you
have to be like this or you have to have
this mindset to be happy then this is
just something that worked for me and
I'm very happy about it and it's been
really motivational as well to see so
many support around it I think that's
great
and I really appreciate it I really feel
like jimbros are the most supportive
people out there so yeah this is my
partner so far maybe in a year I'll make
another video when a more in depth on my
workout once I actually know how to do
it properly I don't want to spread
misinformation and stuff like that but I
I feel confident in what I said today at
least so there thanks for watching
brofist
[Music]
[Applause]