oh good morning its gaming week gamers
and grab your pickaxe cuz it's minecraft
time isn't that right smell cement
agrees excellent we made a lot of
changes to the not really I just got
these items on the wall so like now I
know what's in each thing pretty epic
thank you guys for giving their tips
also I'm freaking rich now isn't that
right Sven we are super rich yes we are
you're not getting anything all right
there's one thing I wanted to do yes yes
wait it's coming so and don't worry you
guys told me you can dye his color if
you just add a dye on it and click on it
so like oh my god Sven you look amazing
seriously so good here you go love you
uh what else what else we got llama and
move and water cow what their sheep is
still here of course what their sheep
you wouldn't think about escaping would
you wow you look so sexy Lisa that's
what I thought you never speak until s
spoken to be quiet garbage you trash
your subhuman trash your I've been
making sure to feed him so he doesn't
despawn just enough to keep him alive
there you go don't give me hearts what
else your guns here cow is here llama
here very epic time oh yes you guys told
me you can just place a carpet you're
not to have a gate and you just put a
carpet nice nice job notch
you dummy thick we also have papers now
I guess I don't know this is pretty
boring there you go here you go
also chickens hello chickens sorry I
forgot your food oh no you're gonna
starve all this is so sad oh yeah and
you guys told me how to fix the farming
with the pumpkins and the cactuses
because you have to place a block spare
one so now business is good this is good
I'm not gonna lie this minecraft veteran
knows what it's doing
oh yeah I remember I want to burn down
this tree because it's in the way and
it's super annoying hello
there you go burn
epic burn time oh yes I wanted to do
this as well so you guys told me you
guys still be sad what are you doing
there you guys oh god I shouldn't be
walking around with this in my head
Sven come in please
I need to make a banner Oh perfect I
have six okay uno dos tres Quatro says
your mother is a place sexy ladies okay
give me cocoa and then Bing bong Bing
bong listen I remember because I
minecraft before you be quiet
what oh we work okay cool yellow dye
yellow dye yellow dye where is my yellow
dye hello how are you
that's not gonna be enough where is it
hi how are you is this gonna be enough
Bing bong huh what happen are you okay
huh eat potato
say brick oh there you go okay okay gosh
be careful it's a court I'd put a carpet
here just sit sit sit good boy
okay and we make Swedish banner and then
apparently I can do this oh oh yeah
gamers oh yeah its gaming week god damn
we look good can I see it yeah me and
the boys me and the boys oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah x-men please look at this look
at this dude that's awesome
thanks for all the tips guys now we do
have some plans for today and it's gonna
be pretty epic because if you remember
last episode we had a little problem
with some Raiders they're gonna die
basically and I might make dynamite okay
I think I remember a
Bing bong Bing bong bong and Bing bong
bong bong be okay cool
then I would bring you with me but it's
gonna be pretty dangerous
all right gaming week let's freakin get
it should I make Gucci pants everyone
keep saying I should make Gucci pants
all right let's make Gucci pants I
didn't want to make Russia pants for a
very long time
what's a green guy kelp maybe your nose
oh hello kelp is kelp a green guy let's
check it out no it isn't
I need the green Gucci pants I can't go
on an adventure without Gucci pants how
to make green Gucci pants green dye
cactus oh I have those Bing bong Bing
bong let's get that mill and die wait
what you never you cook the cactus so
this is a Gucci visit huh
whoa you can cook cactus blast
protection fire protection okay so how
do you make leather armor boom okay
gamers
okay okay okay gamers bing bang bong my
fat slum here we go why did I make it
green blue would be so much cooler what
am i doing I mean it is Gucci though
fine okay fine I'll change them in I'll
change I'll change I'll change okay okay
all right me and the boy ready for some
adventure Oh red around all right we'll
see how this guy's
hold down the fort for me Sven oh there
it is we're gonna blow it up gonna blow
it to smithereens baby with this fish
that's right
okay so maybe if I run okay the plan is
I Russian I block out all the exits I
set up the bomb and then I blow it up in
front of them so I can see their tears
while I do it
look at them look at idiots but they're
talking about dumb stuff okay here we go
which way to get out of my way gamers
boom don't think so the back Oh Joe tada
okay so we want one on each floor right
Bing boom boom BAM Cheney ah what slight
problem in the matrix I can't put
redstone downward gamer week kidding me
yeah yeah it works
look gamers it works okay
we've got to get rid of this stairs now
I've got angry they're dumb nothing's
gonna save you nothing there's another
bomb here then I don't know how about of
redstone it's gonna be a short fuse boys
it's gonna be if it's gonna fit your
feet okay okay all right gamers it's
gaming week what happened nothing
happened
Bhandari defense defense II Oh God I
thought I blew it up
we've been set up it was a trap cheap
subscribe that's a lot of them it's
alright it's gaming week
ah cricket okay
oh my god there's so many she believer
Swedish feedback she says okay okay okay
new plan new plan the plan new plan
I'm scared Thanks so many okay here we
go here we go
they didn't explode
[Applause]
let's go
Gaber got rekt give me all your stuff oh
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa look they
dropped cactus i gamers time to bounce
hoes mad hoes man okay I think that was
pretty successful Jurgen it was amazing
I wish you could be there so much okay
we're gonna stock up on hay and meat
because we are gonna head out I really
want to go on an adventure with Jurgen
and Sven together and you guys told me
that you can put then and Jurgen with
you on a boat so I'm like okay well
that's a big so Sven
pack up your best smile cuz today we
ride together let's see is there a
direction I haven't had it yet like a
headed sow
maybe we should try this directions so
when you come up with us right what are
we gonna find who knows epic gaming
adventure water awesome so I think I
have to put the leash on Jurgen okay
spent in the boat in the boat you go go
in the boat Sven it's safe don't worry
there you go yet come back gosh damn it
okay and now I go inside is he still in
yes oh my god does it work oh my god yes
oh heck yeah me and the boys own
adventure I think I've been there maybe
I should just head south you okay you're
again let me know if you won't break
Swedish Viking discovers new lands oh
man I want to find our underwater temple
that was so cool I know they are in the
game but I never found one
again you're getting no no you're
getting here again here again what are
you doing the lasso Oh God but yard
again please I thought you were safe
like God
at least when stays in the boat can we
get a lifejacket for cement please we
found the sunken ship gamers with magma
blocks we found a sunken temple okay
this is perfect then stay in the boat do
is practice you're gonna stay in the
same first we discover the what oh my
god
whoa it could be dangerous inside well I
never gotten these materials before
could this be a water temple man I'd be
so happy this is a ruin isn't it no
treasure if I can't get every gamer loot
then don't waste my time isn't that
right here again yeah there we go - see
this is what I'm coming okay all right
it's good for your again maybe not for
me anything else there's usually two all
right gaming must go on loot or without
load it's not about what we find it's
about having fun guys don't worry we'll
find the gamer Lou oh epic oh heck yeah
all right
Jurgen you can come with me Sven stay in
the boat
guard the boat Sven so this is how I got
so rich because these you can get a ton
of hay from a wreath or whatever I just
stole I just sold everyone's wheat and
sold it to them and they paid me bunch
of money stinks everyone hi gamers
just want your stuff you see we grab
these and we resell them just give me
one moment hello sir wanna do business
okay epic pleasure doing business with
you god damn these guys are rich unlike
these poor cities I keep going to oh
look the stoners having a bat that's
cute
are you enjoying okay never mind then
it's getting dark maybe I should sleep
here
what up gamers did you sleep well here's
okay alright we head out you're gonna
see a little scared of the water but
it's safe don't worry we're looking for
water temple we will find water temple
Oh
found one it's your again gonna be okay
if I leave him in the water what happens
to your again does he go down with me
let's swim here again our car is
dangerous Jurgen back off back off back
off
whoa
get him Sven oh he dropped gold heck
yeah just here for the loot gamers out
there there is none y'all get my god
yeah you're scaring Sven here again
come back boy even in the water
that's literally physically impossible
what you just did come here we're not
leaving Jurgen we're not leaving it's
better if you've got you know what
you're getting one would never do this
subscribe hey looking at a city we can
do stinks in alright gamers wait by the
boat Jesus Christ the rich now okay now
I can afford buying Gucci pants instead
of making them instead of making fake
ones this is amazing what is there a
pirate ship in your city what this is
even oh my god that's crazy
boners mean there's a cat oh my god yes
I've been carrying our fishes just so I
can tame you
hey kitty you're going in the bucket I
see you got to sneak up to the kitties
hey hey kitty kitty kitty kitty kitty
kitty what this maybe we need to
paralyze it first hey kitty kitty kitty
kitty where do you go
[Music]
you didn't see anything it can't be no
witnesses so it's dark now but I think
that might actually be better because
now we can see the water if it lifts up
whoa look at that dude
whoa whoa okay it's a harpoon guy oh god
I can't deal with harpoon guy Oh God
all right it's gaming time Oh God you're
again be brave be brave uragan Jesus
Oh we'd actually hit me damn it
Rosie come up coward Oh God hey you're
good I'm done I'm done
this is not okay okay all right gamers
first first you're again there you go
second-year again I'm probably the only
one dumb enough to do this okay his help
is full
okay another water temple this one
doesn't look so bad
juergen what are you doing get up there
no no no no no no Jurgen Jurgen swimmer
swimmer swim up swim up though I can't
do this I can't see where they swim up
swim up
you made it yet
[Music]
eat my gamer dude alright we're going
home we're gonna help no treasure is
valuable more than you're getting and
you spend you're not a submarine McGuirk
again I don't know what gave you the
idea
whoa what's happening what's happening
spit spit
swim [ __ ] oh good duh son
[Music]
let go of the leash Fred where is he
stay there Spain Spain it's fan
he must be here spent you wouldn't just
disappear you can breathe in the water
yo again I can't find him
[Music]
you can stop swimming away you heard him
right I'm not crazy right go down where
are you sad what if I build a plateau
maybe he will teleport no why do I hear
him
I see him still he's out there how do I
get him back it's not over here again
where is he I don't care how much these
are worth
I'll save Jurgen for any price can you
teleport here teleport yard again
teleport
oh yeah during it oh you're okay nope
[Music]
oh we're gonna get you out of here buddy
we're gonna get you it's not a good
place to me it's not a guy
baby oh god all right
I might have to build like a tunnel
don't know how to do this you must be so
scared you're again you must have been
so scared as long as we don't run out of
the air so you could just swim here no
but the bubbles might grab him right so
let's set up a defense it will not take
me or you're getting worse man can he
swim boy I put the leash on oh god no no
no not work Oh God's men okay okay okay
let's cover up this hole oh god he's
struggling
okay okay hey I got an idea I got an
idea again I found him I found in Jurgen
he's safe you're getting at least
pretend that you were happy okay we're
going to grab you carry that you don't
like water here again we have to write
like the wind year again write like the
goddamn win
come on come on come on come on stay
with llama oh god I messed up all my
materials spend it all alone in a cave
under water this when was like the
father I never had it was like a child
to me he was like my own son
okay gamers I need your help any tip I
can get you get thrown out of this cave
I will take gladly help a gamer out
don't worry safe they're gonna the nine
year olds the nine girls are gonna save
us oh it hurts to stop here