article 13 has passed everyone what we
feared all along has to become a reality
the Internet as we know it is gone it's
obviously really upsetting I think a lot
of people don't know what's gonna happen
but people have been saying things like
now memes will be banned
now all this content from Europe will be
banned YouTube have been saying that
they might remove content completely
from EU it's obviously a big change
coming and that's why I have a great
deal for you guys honestly we didn't
know that article 13 was gonna pass but
I've teamed up with Noor VPN which is an
amazing VPN I use it myself
article 13 pad gets past my VPN this is
America that's right there's a simple
solution to all this article 13 mumbo
jumbo VPNs baby in case you don't know a
VPN lets you browse the Internet as if
you were anywhere almost anywhere in the
world
joke's on you European legislation I
already said so no VPN it's a great
service you can use it on your even on
your phone it's super simple to use I
and right now we have a great deal that
you don't get just 50% off you don't get
hundred percent off you get 75% off if
you entered the code PewDiePie
Nord VPN commerce as PewDiePie it's only
$2.99 a month that's a great price
I mean honestly that is pretty cheap and
you get one month for free because you
entered the code PewDiePie so good for
you what a way to troll the European
Union there's obviously other reasons to
use a VPN especially for security
reasons what you don't care about
Internet security what a loser pathetic
okay you need to care about these stakes
you know all your data could easily be
stolen just like that if you have a VPN
it's protected its protection Thank You
Nord VPN for sponsoring this video and
now let's get on with it
[Music]
welcome all new subscribers ever since
these t-series vs. PewDiePie thing my
channel has just been abundantly
inflated with subscribers but really
this is it it's just me in a bedroom for
looking at stuff on the internet I want
that to be clear here I don't want there
to be any higher expectations this is
all that we're doing we're gonna go haha
over a bunch of clips today now since we
have so many new subscribers I decided
to create this new show called you my
you lose we're testing this out it's
please be patient a we'll see how it
goes but basically they're really simple
your life you lose let's freaking go hey
look it's me it starts with me t series
35 years how long is trash live thousand
years we don't need to cry anymore we
are winning thanks right everyone I
don't know if we still are it's ironic
how we made the chrome graduation song
to wrap up the meme to stop the meme out
go there break relations that's great we
finally did it we we persuaded
nine-year-olds from saying he gay -
congratulations instead amazing well
done comeback of the goddamn century
we'll go for another thousand years
another millennium easy
Adi Adi Adi oh yes monotone why do your
monkey now
[Music]
I Jesus Christ I still haven't watched
Jojo but I feel like with all the memes
it will just never live up to the
expectations low quality yet hi dear oh
it's another one of these huh dr. Phil
dr. Phil Kuwaitis named sequoya
either sure dr. felassan he's so
beautiful
absolute beautiful man I miss him you
know I miss seeing him I mission making
video of him I wake up sometimes at
night wet
thinking about dr. Phil Wow
well guess I'm gonna show it myself the
heck that's funny do people buy those
cookies and just to put their [ __ ] in
when why are they so convenient to use
for sewing stuff pathetic what is
happening here what is this
[Music]
see all these life skills that parents
try and emit upon their children that is
never gonna give them anything in life
beyond just random memes I really
appreciate that you know this kid I have
to go to like thousands of dollars of
lessons just led up to this moment
oh no I mean I'm sure it's an hour to
play but still no no kid wakes up one
day me like I want to play that big
weird guitar looking instrument cello is
that what it's called no it didn't shut
up I know what it's called never touch
Jimmy Fallon's a man okay we played the
piano laying upside down you were laying
on the ground playing with your hands
cross oh sorry that was something
Freddie good point played the piano
laying upside down you were laying on
the ground playing with your hands cross
spoiler alert oh sorry
something Freddie did she be always
laughs what happened Jimmy why was that
not funny
look like he just got his whole life
ruined another three months of heavy
drinking memory-wipe therapy got so he
has second emotion besides laughter I
won't know that was something Freddie
here I've never seen another emotion for
this man
[Music]
oh my god a it's just one mm oh that's
creepy
oh it's be some ice okay okay I got it
okay that's funny I still haven't seen
that movie ah that that actually makes a
lot of sense now
now it's a joke
[Music]
don't take a man's waffle wait Logan
took his waffle that's totally justified
then don't eat Logan's waffle everyone
knows this never touch
Logan's waffle I really expected it to
be a I did not hit her I did not know
just me okay moving on yes oh you know
they're coming you know exactly what the
joke is but it still makes you laugh
because goddamn if ass good old Scrat
day isn't worth it oh my god oh wow
you know whoa oh my god is he drugged
what is happening you're terrified I
like this I just look at the cow and
Peter pie is losing dump start
subscribing Thank You Faye fabulous
bacon for doing your part everywhere I
look now tilt that
Joanne
when does this
thank god that's insane how is that real
i goddamn just the beginning plays
everyone god damn that was amazing I
mean it wasn't funny but it still made
me laugh I guess that means I lose a
life oh no what am I possibly gonna do
akward Disney Channel wand IDs with
graphics hey and you're watching Disney
Channel this is real this is outtakes
then someone decided to draw over the
eye and you're watching Disney Channel
let's see the mouse Wow incorrect
how do you see Chad oh is this real
please tell me this is real you're
watching the Disney Channel all right
let's see it let's see if I can do it
it's a part of you but exploring is not
a game we've Dora the explora look
before you leap it's like a fan main one
this is real so goddamn bad well at
least that in life
goddamn Sam's meme in 2019 Jesus Christ
why never yield kids learn some
triggered Nintendo switch user going
around saying that you take Xbox
controller and a Playstation controller
and hook them into the memory card slots
of an old Nintendo wheat what I'm saying
the external DVD drive into the USB in
the back along with a [ __ ] disc drive
a floppy disk adapter right here uh-huh
and then you attach it to the extra USB
cord on the back of it uh-huh you can
hook this flash card reader up the
screen right here connect an additional
USB to the second port then plug that
into a Bluetooth headset that's a wall
adapter to this one right here then plug
it into a pumpkin nutmeg pie candle and
then you can play two British simulator
insert a spare GameCube memory card you
know okay this chip reader then punch it
that's right bada and allowed to take
harmony memo let's see if it work oh my
god I knew it
mom we're buying an Xbox controller and
a Wii my mom is not even here I don't
know why I said that
unbelievable
Oh God yes but have I seen this Resident
Evil 2 but 1000 facial animations
[Music]
okay 200% burger that's not too bad wait
I'm cutting to the good stuff 300% site
that's how I eat all right all right all
right
thousand percent let's go that's a tasty
burger right there it's not too bad oh
the burger just that good bye your whole
face melts
hey look it's another peeling hi there
only stuff that makes me lioness mom are
you subscribed to PewDiePie I'm going a
little dead good ask you should get your
mom and make her to subscribe right
freaking now I'm waiting hi mom
subscribe please thanks did that work
incredible almost all 9 year olds have a
mom right if we can get all the 9 year
olds mom to subscribe then we have
double subscribers all right that was it
for this week's your life you lose smash
like if you laughed and smash like if
you lose and I see you brought skis
tomorrow
you remember check out merch check out
Merce remember and brofist at 100
million very nice look at this merge
support the channel see you guys
tomorrow bye what super simulators
becoming relevant
no no don't leave
no please sponsor Eagle please do
something
yes yeah this game is still relevant God
dear me
[Music]