it's Tuesday my dudes
[Music]
and you know what that means
cringe to state time yeah Tuesday's is
Tuesday
that's right everyone and today we're
looking at probably a video that a lot
of you have already seen I'm probably
one of the last commentary channels I
guess that's what I am to comment on
this but it's just too good to be true
mogs pause video now morgs Canada Sapir
for a while I don't know if you're
familiar with this kid but he came back
he came back with his family and it's
just it's as weird outside all day
you don't have to do anything so the
gist of these videos is that you can
polish someone with a remote control at
any time now what the rules are beyond
that it's never explained who has to
controller how long do you get to use a
controller can you pause anyone at any
and all I need to know the rules
otherwise how the Frick you my supposed
to understand but all you need to know
is of course the mom really likes to
make that face and it makes me very very
very very very very uncomfortable
there's $10,000 on the line it's like
the perfect example of youtube these
days you can't do anything well there's
not $10,000 on the line well why should
I care then huh why should I you can't
start a video without a giveaway first
this is 2019 god damn it we gotta do
yeah cuz liking doesn't do anything you
just have to subscribe talking about
iPhones where is the iPhone I want one
Shh
um pause I don't know what happened did
he get the iPhone what is happening
that's why I liked most about these
videos this is super thick accent for
some reason they're all just yelling
constantly I don't understand him
everyone is his family's death
apparently Shay she always does that
face and I don't like it I don't like it
no what a beautiful face to pause on
what am i watching here like what is
this I don't know I don't understand I
don't want to watch this anymore
I really the editing it's like hyper
dramatic background music every time so
I got head brush in every single one of
my videos I mean I guess this is
literally me in 2013 I can't really be
too harsh
Oh balls why are you laughing damn
that's some cruel anime laughs it's your
t-shirt all along Morgan it's not just
any old shirt it's your brand-new black
cow Angie's not the apron you black out
NGC merge no not the new mg said black
head merge stop making that seriously I
can't be sure about that Jesus Christ at
least you guys can still copy right now
Molko just make sure you keep your eye
on Zoe oh god don't zoom in on that oh
god the cold sir
oh why would you in the nails like dude
take care of your nails from a brother
from another
you gotta get those nails manicured
brother
we better unpause those nails if you
know what I've got a limited edition
only available for seven are you serious
he's using this marketing employer oh
it's gonna be gone forever only seven
days that is shameful how could he do
that
you know some people just turn their
videos as ooh one giant advertising
campaign that's so sad and that's
honestly just shameful description do
you think they talk like this all the
time or it's like okay now we need to
shoot this for you all right okay so you
understand here okay so what was my line
check out the mark she's making you
juice guy he's just making juice just
like when I pour milk out of the
cartridge I'm just making milk I don't
know what to tell you she's barefoot for
this as well I mean I can't shave it I
do the exact same thing you want to do
something annoying you always set it up
like oh yeah I should probably remove my
socks oh yeah we should probably shoot
this on the floor that's easy to clean
up I don't know how to tell you this
guys I know this might come as a shock
this is fake all right if you point the
remote at someone and say it doesn't
actually work okay
bra bra bra you know the only thing this
video is really missing to fit any sort
of cliche it's fortnight in the meantime
Brad let's play some ball tonight we're
only five minutes in guys I'm running
away I'm good in a way I'm getting
chased Jenny's
oh my freaking God this is a gamer
moment don't don't do it morgue this is
definitely a oh my god eliminated anyway
hope you win
Brad this next clip is me every time I
lose in the video game what am i
watching this is just a normal scenario
for those of you who don't know what
it's like if a girlfriend interrupts you
in a video game I had the exact same
reaction she went too far this is the
first time I've ever seen you on the
treadmill okay I definitely did not need
to see that how is she being careful not
to fall off shame if you go
oh yeah let's watch that again
[Music]
oh this is so awkward
getting imagine filming this with my mom
just have your mom laying there on the
floor like how they went through all
this and then they thought hey Liss that
was awesome we replayed the clip three
times but we should do to get she's
getting back on she's getting back on
wow that was just how she was running
she's right dude running like this dude
her head looks like a freaking bird bird
moorage hands mom confirmed
oh now she's dead okay oh my god I
thought for once they wouldn't scream
Jesus Christ damn it don't say I didn't
warn you
Oh No did she call her husband bald
Martin that's awesome babies Doc's
himself as well can you imagine being
neighbors to this family I guess
actually it's probably not worse than
being a bag of ice jokes over me
I think I am too pushy yeah oh my god
it's not like you could have done that
anyway why do I care it doesn't matter
it's
[Music]
he got destroyed that's some pause
action right there that's what you get
for killing him in fortnight these
girlfriends got to learn like how now
after they've done the groceries they
had their food they come back and they
thought to themself in the car hey
wouldn't be epic if we like pause in the
car since you humiliated me in the shop
Morgan no Morgan no don't do this mold
and it's crazy no Morgan we're in the
car oh my god Morgan you can't do that
if she dies we die because we are in the
car we're all sitting in this car
together so if she crashes then we all
crash
I think Morgan you can't do that I bet
you weren't expecting male ones on your
these are the stinkiest bugs I can find
and honestly I don't even know what I've
eaten those they're not that bad
they're like dry it out they don't I'm
just saying it's not that bad okay yeah
I've had live ones on scare PewDiePie
season one
Thanks gross okay this is nothing shake
my head you call this a pause challenge
know what miss buck and also it's no one
gonna point out there they're not
actually pressing the pause button
they're just pressing the off button
okay see that's not the pause button
alright so I think that finally confirms
that the pause challenge is actually in
fact fake once and for all
leave your comments down below what you
think is it real it like how are they
doing this his mom just walking I mean
naked in the shower no one sees a
problem with this you look fancy
everything you never straighten your
hair well Kara I'm sorry about this I
didn't want to have to do this after
what you've just done to me no other
choice okay I'm really sorry but you
just bought yourself a pop is no no
excuses you got morgues killed in
fortnight you went too far you now you
pay consequence kara I'm gonna sit here
all day until the hair turns off the
only way you can stop me is by giving up
you've made
me do this didn't Berta
cut us and then you stick to it as well
I think one thing's for sure
Martin is not gonna give up so i forfeit
three forfeits i guess alright that's
cool I'm really glad I watched this this
is a journey to say the least
I mean I'm in front of most before he
clearly doesn't care it's just really
weird seeing a whole family do this at
the same time it's clearly just like a
kids show at this point it's surreal to
me seeing how these things are still
happening on YouTube and doing very
successfully at it I mean 21 million
views that's well done what can I say
family-friendly PG clean okay well how
do you explain this huh I feel so bad
for Martin like if you agree his facial
expressions are hilarious so people are
actually watching it alright fair enough
to you what can I say that's it for
cringe week let me know what you want
next time and there's always smile and
happy what you never played super
simulator you know it's fun right I'm
not supposed to give my opinion but give
it a try and then you can tell me if
it's
not convinced yet okay I'll cut you a
deal the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]