lame review saying Wow why do you do
that
middle of you YouTube's favorite show
everyone say it with me you to to
favorite you bro show everyone say it
with me I am so excited guess why
because this week's we have a lot of
plentiful memes oh boy I'm excited let's
begin meme number one JK Rowling
she's back at it again remember when JK
Rowling went on said her Mohnish e can
be black it's canon totally white skin
was never put specified I am such a
progressive person I thought about this
literally years ago before it was
popular to be an annoying verified
Twitter on Twitter and then people
pointed out wait a minute JK Rowling it
says right here Hermione has a white
face you even wrote it yourself
I mean JK Rowling has already been made
fun of for this no one JK Rowling
Dobby had a 10 inch [ __ ] remember that
everyone well she went out again JK
Rowling and said that Dumbledore and
Grindelwald had an intense sexual
relationship JK Rowling reappearing
every two months to save something
literally no one asked about is me
adding more random details to my as a to
up my word count
listen it would be fine if the
characters were like this originally but
it seems like you're changing them after
the fact so you could see more inclusive
and get good press oh okay I'm sorry
I'll stop okay thank you
wait just one more thing what is it
guess um guess which character is
actually gay what I said guess which
character is actually gay I don't know
all of them JK Rowling confirms that
Dumbledore had long ill JK please no one
asked JK Rowling reveals Dumbledore a
gay
JK Rowling reveals Dumbledore Lindgren
devil had
incredibly intense sexual relationship
or JK Rowling reveals your mother is a
homosexual
JK Rowling confirms that the readers
were gay all along
joke's on you I never read harry potter
because i'm not gay
I do like dick though JK looks up fan
fiction about Dumbledore and Ron having
unprotected sex while Dobby is watching
JK Rowling my goodness what a great idea
why did I not think of that at this
point yeah this seems like she's just a
fanfiction writer at this point I mean
it worked for Fifty Shades of Grey
it's literally a Twilight fan fiction
even Elon Musk himself confirms JK
Rowling is gay now we know everyone
which Harry Potter character is gay
Harry Ron Hermione LML all of them all
of them are gay nobody JK Rowling the
following wizards like fisting Jesus
Christ stop she's like George Lucas and
Steven Spielberg editing their own old
classics they just can't keep their
hands out of it JK Rowling after
accidentally stumbling onto a Harry
Potter fairy fanfiction write that down
JK Rowling when she announces the
characters in Harry Potter are gay after
20 years of existing as well as there
being evidence of characters are
straight I'm gonna be all that me be gay
I gotta relearn yeah how does he have
that voice JK Rowling reveals that
Hagrid was black all along how could we
uh miss the Sun sure integral part of
the story you're a wizard mother why it
was played by samuel l.jackson all along
now i'm gay and i agree with that don't
be fake and with the moon landing Thank
You JK Rowling Thank You Harry Potter
characters JK JK Rowling her mony is
black also JK Rowling her white face
though characters from Harry Potter
clearly isn't gained any book that
they're in JK Rowling reality can be
whatever I want all right we get it
Felix there's an abundance of JK Rowling
memes I'm sorry I just
okay this means we'll get the
seven-point gay good joke Felix thank
you next name also related to someone
making em alright let's just read what
shane dawson tweeted I didn't Mike hey I
didn't come cat
I didn't put my peepee anywhere near my
cat I never done anything weird with my
cat I promised myself I wouldn't go in
to make an apology videos at the last
year's thing so I'm just trying to be as
short and honest with this as possible
thank you for your honesty Shane Dawson
a guide to YouTube stars Shane Dawson's
viral apology about his tan this is why
I tell you guys if you need help writing
your apologies
just let your boy know cuz you might end
up like I mean this apology is 10 out of
10 I don't know the world so what
happened was basically Shane on a
podcast it said that he came on his cang
and he sounds pretty sincere when he
says it but I used to watch him Donathan
like way back in the day and I know he
had with like really edgy and strange
sense of humor it was always really
overly sexual and I always thought it as
a way of Shane dealing with his own
sexual frustrations he hadn't come out
as bisexual yet so in retrospect it
actually makes a lot of sense so while a
lot of people might be shocked by this
it's obviously just Shane making a joke
but the fact that it says it in such a
serious tone I also understand why some
people think it's real although it's
clearly not real okay but the most
important thing out of all this is of
course yes that's right everybody the
memes I mean this just brings whole new
meaning to sad cat means I can't look at
them the same way I just know Shane did
something bad to that sorry cat why did
she go to you ah oh they're so sad and
cute
Shane hurt you didn't he just point out
the GP way to chain touch you the only
reason I'm bringing this up is to
deflect from this story that I brought
up on a podcast and I thought it was
hilarious like but apparently he was
more like shocked by it so the day at
like he went to tell everyone in school
that I didn't masturbate in my cat and
I'm like that's not what I did but then
I realized that first of all all right
let me just say guys in case you're
listening to this podcast footage in
your website and you're hurt which I
honestly you should be just know that I
didn't my can I didn't come with my cane
I didn't put my dick anywhere near my
cane I never done anything weird with
Mike hands and I promised myself I
wasn't going to Thank You Shane awesome
just for making that easier for me why
did both me and Shane have the same
history
listen you I literally just had to rub
my calves belly and his dick would flop
up and I was a kid and I thought that
was funny all right stop it please
Wall Street Journal box news playing
hates Shane Dawson's cat tomorrow on
Good Morning America those poor kitty
know everyone bangs his pants me no way
come on I can't believe everything you
hear
oh yeah daddy likes okay
all right let's move on Shane Dawson I'm
warning Sheen does his cat she says
Christ I oh god absolutely no one Shane
Dawson Jess I think we need Shane a meme
review at this point oh my god everyone
3-chain damn I thought he'd ask you
skank Shane Dawson he said yes okay now
you've gone too far
chucky cheese when they find out Shane
Dawson was effing his kin Chuckie Cheese
I bet they're the ones that discovered
this the Shane Dawson meme gets a
7-point gay cats by the way the cat is
Dave I feel bad like honestly a lot of
people are memeing this but a lot of
people are actually taking this very
seriously and are actually mad at Shane
Dawson and going after Shane Dawson and
attacking him just for this you know in
a way I can really relate to him because
you know he had an energy pass that
obviously follows him around and it's
not who who he is anymore so I can
relate and I feel bad so it'd be nice
and support chain everyone and also
Shane happy marriage that were you
saying happy marriage next me deaf
people that's right everyone the
internet has discovered that deaf people
exist they do in fact exist you know
when you watch something on
flicks and then the subtitles just shows
up being like noise in the background
like an audible sound or like music
playing well that's become a meme now
subtitles music deaf people it's there
has to be an old name this cannot be
subtitles outside sounds best people Wow
I can truly experience this thank you
subtitles and Netflix thank you so much
I was wondering like how did they react
to that they're like um okay now this is
no weighing shape or form making fun of
bad people of course I just want to make
that clear before box rights or not an
article this is just a way to
acknowledge and understand them trying
to learn each other trying to make a
place better world
subtitles cool jazz music that's people
I wonder if it does it say that in
spider-man that would make me happy
subtitles scary sound deaf people
Felix now you stepping a little too far
on the toes here okay but let me just
ask one simple question what language do
deaf people thinking they never heard
language then how do they think a very
philosophical meme indeed captions
yes when the deaf person asks you what
time it is but you don't understand sign
where's language and it's 8:54 so you
have to improvise that relatable moment
when it's 5:23 and you don't know the
time okay alright I'm sorry for being
insensitive
I had gomennasai alright sumimasen
but let me ask you another question if a
deaf person goes to court it is still
called
a hearing
top five comments do I have the green
screen on what the hell why is it on ah
deaf people exist reddit right now I
mean I think that summarizes it pretty
well this mean gets a gay deaf person I
don't know last name that's right we
have time for one more meme everyone
hope you guys are excited about this one
it's gonna be very epic now this Ralph
meme has become popular and thank God
I'm not supposed to give my opinion but
thank God I really wanted another
cartoon meme Family Guy Simpson punch
Bob there's just not enough cartoon
names
Ralph can't be in another meme his last
one got too popular
Ralph Ralph please World War 1 soldiers
in 1918 we survived the Great War
Spanish flu just came out of nowhere
mediocre action movie director I don't
really like this me mediocre action
movie director we need an actor to play
the main Cara main Joel son Dwayne the
rock Johnson I can appreciate this one
of these lava exists your dog no okay
that's good whatever I start my PC yeah
why does Skype keep thing existing Jesus
in Christ and discord don't even get me
started a finished program I don't know
why it happened I cannot launch discord
unless it launches itself at startup so
if I close it and then try to launch it
again it doesn't work and I can't even
uninstall it and stay if I want to play
games team I'll just start you when I
dig straight down in Minecraft oh god I
know the feeling small game developer
stars relatively successful game
seriously eh quentin tarantino's so i'm
making this new movie white actors who
want to say they okay alright okay okay
one more your kids gets one more famous
pulls down pants to take a
mein I rate this meme a four day round
thank you guys for watching another
episode of mean review blue shirt kid
Willie he hosts meme review the real
question that everyone asks at the
beginning of this video now smash like
if you want blue shirt kid to host min
review and I will see what I can do all
right but for now what super simulators
becoming relevant no no don't leave no
please sponsor eagle please do something
yes yeah this game is still relevant God
dear me