supergirl band who funds these shows why
are they sinking so much money into
these TV shows that I don't understand
why anyone would watch I don't even know
this show existed apparently it's been
running for all those five years and
they went from ten million viewers to
now going on 1 million viewers let's go
through some of my favorite scene from
Supergirl this is called the worst CGI
in TV series so prepare yourself and the
best part about this clip is that they
use this as their promo this is what
they want to show what Supergirl looks
like to people that haven't really
watched Supergirl prepare yourself
now
the thing is like even just even just
this special effect are so bad by water
it's happening one person that's one
thing and then there's another thing and
then good switch it to another thing and
it catches a bullet and then just she
changes her beep alright I'll break it
that evil the space alien Supergirl was
actually construction worker why Donna
oh it's so good let's wash it on slow
speed Oh God what a hot mess look at
that that's why it's like that really
feminist empowering moment in Lord of
the Rings when she's like I am no man
it's a super speed punch what is
happening here are they're supposed to
walk through glass or something they
look like crystal meth or something look
at that yeah they are they're walking
through that wow this guy says we came
prepared and prepared immediately gets
shot
prepared I will have a good clearly
there's been some budget cuts going on
here
and I understand this is just one scene
they probably have better CGI this looks
like some PlayStation 2 level of CGI
honestly it looks so bad what's really
confusing cuz I kept trying to find like
alright are there any more like bad CGI
but they actually have like a ton of
these where they break down the CGI for
the films and just like how much effort
and time they spend on it so what
happened they're like yeah this looks
cool this doesn't look bad I'm not I'm
not the gonna just like blindly hate
something that would be foolish
I wouldn't do that but yeah super girl
sucks it sucks it really sucks as you
can see by these numbers like just don't
take my word for it
just take this drop out alright so
here's a cursed video that I loved so
much
I shouldn't this video before it's
superheroes without special effects look
super silly alright here we go
maybe Cara Danvers is tougher than you
think
we're not gonna win this today ah dang
it better flow away oh wait what she
doesn't fly away are you serious
she doesn't actually have superpowers
this is crazy what is your superpower
this wears his hands in circles really
fast you don't want to mess with me boy
you know they are really pros if I was
there I would be laughing non-stop right
props to them honestly I could not do
that no way alright service was FX
I mean now I kind of respect the CGI
team for making those goofy ass scenes
look actually cool so great I love it so
much
doesn't look like silly with the fact I
think it best it's still kind of silly
damn this makes me realize how much a
real life sucks it sure that thank you
super a girl for nothing now the reason
that my attention was caught piqued by
whatever sense I have to say you
understand what I'm trying to say Oh
recently they did another promo
I guess because their viewers are so
high that they just some I need more so
again this is them showing what's cool
about the show this is to get more
people involved
what is it budget I want to know how
much they're spending on this what are
they fighting little toy figures what is
that wow that's so cool is this stream
available in this location asking for a
fandom wait there's an actual Supergirl
fandom even they have given up hope that
me must be really bad then I kind of
want to watch Supergirl now I'm not
gonna lie it seems to me little hope
island good this is where I was watching
bird that make it looks like they're
fighting Bionicles what is he this is
not the clip though the clip because
clearly the rightest is just giving up -
they're just posting at this point
[Music]
that's right a character from Supergirl
just yelled Leroy Jenkins unerotic Lee
in 2020 it might be time to cancel the
show guys I'm sorry I mean I appreciate
it I'm not gonna alight that makes me
laugh the fact that they did that but
it's also very cringe you can't do that
you can't just do that so apparently
people are actually watching the show
why why why it's like you can do
anything anything else yeah why are you
watching this you could shoot anything I
was trying to understand why people
don't like sight as Supergirl cyber girl
whatever
apparently Supergirl husbands like
sneaking in social justice propaganda
what and fans aren't happy about it so I
obviously I need to investigate what is
it what I why our fans upset about this
we have this clip here you believe it a
female hero lass for my daughter to have
someone like that to look up to yeah
real nice the characters basically me
when you really want to say no that bit
but you have to go a lot that's so cool
here yeah real nice on my planet see
most bow before males this is not your
planet that's kind of anti-immigration
message really why so it's not just cuz
he's alien he's not allowed to be on the
planet that's not cool man
she's not strong enough why I guess
she's just a girl no because she will
actually die why why so you're saying
it's because she's a woman
is that why for a cool powerful kick-ass
woman instead of a bunch of angry old
white men hey that's me
shoutout to me in the show awesome
I'm sorry I have difficulty making
conversation with men under six feet
tall we woman strong man short this is
all women have to have short or tiny
penis
that's all they have on us nothing else
I hope that but making me dead do you
think that's how the writers went when
they wrote that also small penis nobody
is calling me the most powerful woman in
National City I believe they are calling
me the most powerful person I know this
is a minor detail but clearly like her
suit is making her look more buff right
it could be kind of cold to get like an
actual really strong woman like that
Korean chick from that video that I
reviewed that I had to edit out is
actual Superman the guy to play Superman
is actually really involved like I'm not
against the idea of a super female oh
god this is so hard to say I'm not
against a soprano Fullman that empowers
women I'm not against it I know that's
gonna sound like a lie but I'm not
against it we could really use your help
here it has to be you
why cuz I'm black he's black too why
would you say that what oh man is this
really who you want to be
testosterone-driven windbags boasting
about your big guns surely we don't need
to measure phoenix ball be that small
your short invaded small that's all they
had yeah well your CGI stinks
Supergirl huh get a new team of CGI it's
in a week Amy at all it might Oh No
no I was at full strength and you beat
me these strings are measuring capacity
must have been jammed or something cuz
that's no way that would happen courage
man this is a good cringe it's horrible
I'm terrible it's like it's such a guy
thing to do I am a horrible terrible oh
that's right only guy have sex one time
when they can't do that well I am a
horrible terrible
that pretty much summed it up right
there guy bad girl good well super girl
rating bad once you throw in another
reference how about uh how about some
chocolate rain reference in the next
episode okey I'm pretty sure I can help
out the writers I know all the memes how
about this alright super girls this is
super tall man it's like the mega chat
of all time it's like 12 feet tall and
you have Supergirl go like this then she
says megusta that was for free that was
for free smash like if you enjoyed this
video check out the merch if you support
channel subscribe if you are not already
and see you tomorrow
Hado I'm a horrible terrible