[Music]
good morning gamers welcome back to
another beautiful day in Minecraft I had
a live stream yesterday and someone told
me to plant 4 spruce trees next to each
other and bam whoa whoa whoa
why do I feel like it's challenging I
can power don't worry IKEA tower you are
beautiful forever if you didn't catch a
live stream don't worry you didn't miss
much I just walked around and it was
very peaceful and very nice
I can crit with the Trident jet oh my
god Bank can you get out of the boat
you're not supposed to aah
sorry how do I get him out oh my god
they're stuck forever
lishus gets them out I keep forgetting
oh oh
so someone told me they go to sleep
underneath trees that is so cute oh my
god I'll put a little lantern oh okay
sorry sleep sleep just go to sleep
thank you I don't know if this is true
or not but apparently you can give them
a sword as well cuz they keep stuff in
their mouth just like Dark Souls oh my
god okay thanks
come on you can be just like Dark Souls
eat it I can give him my badass sword
and it will give him like fire aspect
and stuff
this sword is very important to me but I
want you to have it because you are
important to me - I need him to drop the
leash some of it maybe if I give him
porkchop there we go
he just spits it out oh he's eating it
oh my god yes that's so cool
so apparently he gets the enchantment we
need to try this at this is so cool
alright who wants to volunteer all of
you that's very well I'm just gonna
leave a look at him look at him look at
him beg this going crazy oh my god
alright alright I'll just leave these
guys here you can do whatever you want
them kill them kill them now well the
backwards attack look it's cooked
chicken because my sword that's so
awesome
well I guess you two are the lucky ones
oh my god he killed them as well very
very interesting technique that Bank has
using is why is the chicken just not
running away incredible technique all
their friends
oh and now he went to sleep with little
chickens now obviously I'm still
homeless I've been trying to figure out
what I want to build and we'll probably
build something or at least started
today I'm really excited for what our
new house is gonna be but this time I
want to go big I'm always such a Swedish
loser and I always like oh I just want
to build a small little home for me and
my pigs no not today today we go big we
go all out but first of course I have to
terrorize my villagers yes I have this
new system set up which I think you guys
are gonna really like swine has been
guarding them to make sure good jobs win
so I have a I have a very well-hidden do
what is it absorber here which if you
can see there's a line of thread here so
if anyone passes this thread observer
will notice and the trap will activate
now so far not a single soul has managed
to escape this prison right Sven yes
but just for a safety mesh no the boat
is not for you Sven you want to be the
guard boat fine okay fine
all right let's remove this and let's
watch them walk into the trap you're
free Oh anyone else want to be free is
that so funny you guys are free you can
run look you can play both with sweat
you know what to be honest I think I
only need one right now let's actually
feed them a bit more I need more babies
keep eating and keep fricken oh it's
working excellent I have to cover up the
whole thing because babies can still
crawl in through tiny holes
which is kind of an oceans and I haven't
made this with babies and oh well how do
you do okay this is perfect so this is
my new transportation system oh yeah I
showed her already
well the reason you featured to it you
see the track doesn't go up now I put
the track over here and then it will go
up up into there was that which so oh my
God where huh in my spawner so I
improved my spawner based on one of you
9 rolls oh it works I'm supposed to me I
made it one by one but it's better if
you make it 2 by 2 so now you can see my
training is a little broken I get the XP
bang bang BAM it's full and the loot
gets dropped in here excellent well what
you nine year olds told me are one of
you is that you may think this is a fun
roller coaster ride well I guess in a
way it is they get their final final
ride before the before the eternal
suffering Oh God oh they're all in here
huh so I will they will be placed here
forever and that will make more mobs
spawn if there's a villager and they
will move more towards the center as
well I think I know one of those things
is true at least so it's time for our
annual lottery that's right Sven one of
these lucky contestant will be randomly
picked they look like one giant guy hey
hey sorry sorry sir one lucky contestant
will get chosen as tribute I think this
will go pretty fast but I'll try and
follow three actually I kind of want to
see them getting pigs okay so when are
you ready here we go three two one three
[Applause]
two one here we go and there he goes
lucky wither let's follow him Sven see
I'm so nice to my villagers they get a
lucky chance to live a new life
there he is perfectly placed excellent
why I'm actually gonna keeping them in
the minecart for now because I think I'm
supposed to get two or three of them you
know it's it's not really fair like I
haven't even written this I just let
other people have fun it's really not
about me all right one more lucky win
there here we go three two one people
and we have a winner congratulations sir
sorry I haven't really outfit y'all get
you a job eventually so how's married
life Sven hi how is it I'm about to get
married myself you know cool that's good
to know
hey hey get off my property
oh sorry it was me damn smells boyfriend
Loki Savage all there's Swensen so cute
so you guys said that I should make
Svensson purple because red plus blue is
purple but I wanted spends boyfriend to
be yellow so that makes green so he's
green just so we're clear this is matter
to anyone No oh right I forgot what I
was doing completely I forgot about them
people up here there should be two of
them up here oh no did he push the other
one down why am i laughing that's awful
so now zombies will spawn on these
squares they'll they'll be like oh I
want him I want his sexy body
he looks so nice oh god I'm about to
fall in the hole but I also still want
him
oh god that hole is really coming closer
but I love him he's so sexy but oh my
god I'm about to fall into giant [ __ ]
maybe there's more of them down there
okay see you later
that's how I envisioned it have fun now
cool so hopefully it works better now as
you can see I put IKEA bird on my
shoulder
as honor of Ikea bird thank you for your
service IKEA bird never forgetting my
spaghetti man Bank looks so cute next to
dinner bones what who left the door open
bank who left the door open
where is dinner bone oh my god alright
watch this tonight by the way
right in his face so I had this thing
for a while in the background a lot of
people seemed curious about it
I literally Oh God oh no I wanted to try
out because you can make like elevators
with kelp and Minecraft I actually want
to try that for a very specific reason
okay so if I remember correctly you do
this yeah but so we have this water
flowing in our beautiful goddamn that's
annoying but if we put one ah no that's
not what I wanted to do wait how will is
too strong I mean my shovel ah that's
not what I wanted to do either okay you
place old son here and then you're like
oh it does it creates bubbles not all
the way though oh my god what is
happening flip flop flip flop flip flop
flip flop flip it flip flip flip flip
flip all the way up baby
when zooming same since wincing then you
take the soul sand did I do it is that
how you do it No ah oh it's working I
did it I did it how do I get down from
here
Yelp do I have a bucket of water yes I
do
okay watch this gamers this is an old
veteran minecraft trick you jump and
then you drop the water right before you
fall good thing I don't have legs cuz
otherwise I would have a hurt let's try
that again I never actually managed to
do it here we go yeah you see that
that's so cool
Oh smooth yeah ah the idea behind this
is to have a sniper tower because oh you
see that creeper over there watch this
he despawn are you kidding me alright
watch this first try got'em moving
target no problem
and another one bites the dust
ah but I wished men could see me I got
him look at Bengt
don't worry Bank I got you oh I hit the
pig sorry see I swear there's a witch
spawn like oh that's far oh my god
I am the lord of Triton okay it's time
gamers time to build our new house are
you excited you should be right banked I
got a lot of spruce wood and I got a lot
of stone and a lot gotten a lot of
patience this time when I build like I
said I'm gonna go figure
[Music]
all right not a bad start right banked
oh yeah I'm building another Japanese
temple whatever they just look so
awesome it's kind of cozy underneath as
well meanwhile there's one thing I
desperately forgot to do last time which
was building a freaking snowman let's do
it right in front of Bank I think he'll
like this I don't know if this oh my god
that's it ha ha ha what why does it look
like that oh oh that's creepy
Sven is scared Sven don't worry it's
safe what are you hello that is so
creepy why does it is a joke like am I
getting this is the texture pack why do
they look like they are they evil are
they able to spend oh my god they're
leaving trail of snow what he's peepee
pooping himself
you see actual peepee poo-poo aaaa not
too close so yeah my plan with the
building is obviously finishing the
temple I might have to move I might have
to move Council of water sheep which is
obviously very controversial oh it looks
like they have a what the Sheep is
riding the pig
it has been done my lord yeah I might
have to move a little bit it's fine
oh no he's dying now Daniel what their
shape oh my god so I don't know if this
true or not but I heard that you can oh
my god is stunned there okay okay I'm
going back
Oh big this scared
oh no he's scared of thunder don't worry
you're safe in here don't worry don't
worry buddy you're safe in here so it is
my channeling work or does it have to
hit something to do it oh it still works
baby oh so what happens if you do it on
different things like sheep
they died okay cool that's good to know
is there anything else that I can use it
on like a spider no zombie
it's so badass I love it so much
creeper oh man whoa what is happening
why is he blue what
what's a blue creeper
well it's so cool look at you huh oh oh
they make bigger eggs whoa
he dropped the head what wait so if a
creeper blows up other mobs then they
drop in Ida question mark blow up blow
up do a creeper oh man what they drop
hints stop hitting me
stop I'll take their heads I say I don't
know I so many of them
back off children
oh no you're deadly deadly I'm too
strong Swedish Zeus did it drop yes ha
ha oh man do I want to Enderman head ooh
let me go to sniper tower
can I wear their heads oh my god that
can shred boom oh my god spendings gonna
freak out hasten out
hey Sven bear who never eat that it's me
hey slim boo-yeah okay cipher tower
let's go all right it's sniping time all
right you see that zombie so this is
what it's like to be a god among some
more thoughts
why is this so funny
it's rafita
[Music]
whoa hey hey you can't do that that's
illegal
Oh
why are there so many of them here
strike them strike them all I'm one of
you guys I'm one of you guys I swear no
head all right that was fun though him
people hoped would be like what hey Sven
oh my god oh no I'm sorry
oh oh oh swear I'm sorry I'm sorry it's
me it's me I promise look look look
it's me PewDiePie Oh
[Music]
Oh God okay what happened here I'll let
you guys free and this is how you repay
me I need to do fishing go in they've
turned my dock into a freak chamber it's
not big I need something to calm me down
I need something to cool my dad a good
old fishing what very sit you can have
the dragon's head you have a human head
how sorry I'm learning about the game
while I'm playing it's really weird but
you can make fireworks out of the heads
so the creep red is a fire oh my god
that's so cool can you build a snowman
in another
now does it have to be snow sorry I'm
sorry what did you leave a snow trail
okay I just Google you can make you can
make a fire assist potion and then they
will survive in the nether obviously I
have to do that I want to build one
that's just stays here cuz I like that
he was just putting snow anywhere
yeah just keep keep doing you you're
doing great buddy you're doing great
make Mars snow okay and then we turn it
into a splash potion I guess we'll have
to be really fast what should I name the
snowmen dumb ball yes okay let's see how
he fares against some enemies of the
nether should try and make that potion
land on me as well okay we're gonna have
to be really fast
first cut the pumpkin Oh God
okay well well the snow just not melt
wait how do I throw the potions again
right clink okay okay come on come on
gumball okay okay I gotta make the
hotkeys come on gumball
you got it it's working
he's throwing snowballs at them
get him Dumbo you got this man yeah you
got nothing on us no ah dumb ball nah
he was like father to me it was like my
own oh god I'll take that
the Triton rules all yes
rest in peace dumb ball okay there's one
final thing I want to do so this is a
regular fireworks but then now it
becomes a creeper shape what okay so I
want one blue one and one yellow one
all right gamers follow me I spent I
brought all your friends
spen look they're so happy all right
guys get your seats
Spence boyfriend there we go oh that's
so cute all right guys you ready for
this
it's that creeperface it's still Apes
Wow thought it would be a little bigger
[Music]
they lob a mail Ave thanks for watching
another episode gamers hope you enjoyed
smash like if you did
check out the merge to support the
channel Sven uragan whatever you want we
have a ton of great options and I really
appreciate it that's it for me for now
see you guys next time bye bye