but here it is Oh
[Music]
before we get to going on this video
here's me hello I have a question you
ever bought something online to then
real nice you could have gotten it for
Less that is literally worse than
accidentally killing your dog in
Minecraft okay not really but luckily I
discovered honey honey is a free browser
extension that lets you save money
online the way honey works is that it
scans the internet for coupon codes
whenever you checkout and just like
unicorn wizard magic it pulls it out and
saves you money amazing
honey literally knows about every single
coupon code there is you know those
weirdos at the mall with all those
coupon codes that's honey imagine having
an army of those working for you
filigree Brooke that's honey honey knows
about over 20,000 web sites such as
Amazon Alibaba game shop your gamer
razor it works on razor when you buy
your PewDiePie headphones honey will
save you money and you don't have to do
anything extra honey will do all the
work for you when you check out and I
gotta say it feels amazing it feels
almost as good as hitting 100 million
subscribers the feeling is actually
completely mutual I usually use honey
for amazon because I buy a lot of dumb
stuff or my videos or suffer my home and
it's just nice to save extra money
because then I have more money to buy
more dumb stuff that I don't need I
think it's just a good feeling knowing
you're paying the absolute lowest
products you can for something honeys
for everyone and it works for anything
you buy online go join honey calm slash
PewDiePie I know other youtubers have
promoted honey but if you haven't
downloaded honey now now it's the time
to do it it's free it doesn't cost
anything and it saves you money now why
am I getting angry about it I am
literally getting angry about it because
it's so easy it's such a win-win service
you literally can't lose anything from
using it it takes two clicks to install
link is in the description do it it says
mr. B says unless you hate money you
should have down a little honey join on
it Kampai also big thanks to honey for
having me salad
this huge milestone of 100 million let's
get in with a video nine years ago I
uploaded my first video onto YouTube
this is what that video look like it
blew up
I got millions of views and I was big
ride away
no instead of twelve million views this
video had about three or four this is
what my content actually looked like
back in that day and I am back with
black ops with an awesome game of Search
and Destroy it wasn't good it wasn't
engaging it wasn't even original but I
loved it it took so when he uploads just
for me to hit even a hundred subscribers
and hitting a hundred subscribers was
huge huge for me
and yeah today we're gonna celebrate cuz
I have 100 subscribers oh my it's funny
looking back to that video and what I
said I obviously had big goals
I liked aim even that big goals even
though they might not be relevant at all
but no no I don't want to I don't want
to be famous but at that time I was 20
years old I was living in Sweden in a
small flight I had just moved away from
home I have no idea what I was doing I
just knew I enjoyed it I was also
studying at University at the time
industrial economics and management my
calling in life thanks to what I want to
do so I decided this YouTube hobby I'll
probably have to set aside because I
should probably focus on my finals so I
upload a video saying I was going on a
break but in reality that was I was
quitting it was it for me just can't but
my hobby and from
that right now so I'm sure a lot of you
I'm sure most of you will understand
that and I'm gonna miss you guys a lot
actually which was a pretty reasonable
choice to make considering I had about
five people that actually watched me
during this time but luckily the break
didn't last long just a few days later I
was back uploading videos again I had
found what I was actually passionate
about and I wasn't ready to just let it
go
I knew that a career in YouTube was so
far away it was more of a myth than a
dream at this point because people
didn't even know if it was possible but
it was always at the back of my mind
that there was a tiny chance that this
could actually happen I was back
uploading videos and I tried out this
new horror game that had just come out
called amnesia and it was scarier than
anything that it didn't even compare and
the top comment of this video really
says it it it is what started it all for
me at least I wasn't popular as soon as
I played amnesia but for the first time
the five people I watched my videos they
really enjoyed it and I could tell I was
on to something and this wasn't just new
for me it was a new thing on YouTube as
well and I had never played horror games
before it was genuinely horrible I made
montages and compilations of the best
moments where it's really just me
screaming they're kind of loud they're
kind of obnoxious but you got a charm to
them
[Music]
eventually I had grown a thousand
subscribers but it was also clear I had
grown an audience that really cared
about me I used to be an introvert and
but YouTube really helped me open up
because on the other side there was
people that really appreciated the side
of me that I didn't show to anyone at
this point I had completely failed
school I'm sorry mom and dad
my passion was somewhere else and I
famously started selling hot dogs to
sustain myself but I look back at this
time with great memories because I was
finally pursuing my goal my dream not
selling hot dogs but making videos in my
spare time that is at this time I
managed to meet a girl online who later
became my wife I won't bore you with
every step of the way of the journey it
it's been long it had its ups and downs
I made a lot of mistakes on the way but
I've grown I feel like I have at least
and I feel like I finally come
internship with the responsibility I
have as a creator about a hundred
million subs too late but you know but
the channel has done a lot of good to a
lot of things I'm truly proud of we
literally raise millions of dollars to
charities and I'm really proud of my
audience for helping me do that looking
back at myself in that flight in Sweden
it's a very surreal experience I would
never ever have imagined this outcome
beyond my wildest dreams came true ten
times over a hundred times over I'm nine
years old there now I'm still awkward as
[ __ ] but I finally got confidence in
myself and I'm really proud of Who I am
today and instead of a hundred subs we
had a hundred million subs
[Music]
we did it I want to thank all the people
I work with over the past couple years
you know who you are I want to thank the
people I collaborated with I want to
thank all the great friends I met along
the way I want to thank my previous and
current editors Michael bride sigh I
want to thank my family for supporting
me in doing something that I didn't even
know what it was and I want to thank my
dad for being by my side every step of
the way
but most importantly I want to thank the
Prowse I don't need to tell you about
the journey you already know it brofist
got a ladder in the post hmm what is
this I like the color scheme YouTube
very nice it even got a ladder from
Susan I won't read the whole thing but
it finishes with congratulations again
on becoming Marcia's husband and please
give Sven a big hug from us Thank You
Susan
now if you've been on Twitter you've
seen this already but here it is oh my
god I've smudged it already but
PewDiePie congratulations on passing 100
million subscribers and a lot of people
wanted a custom with reward but I don't
care this is awesome and of course thank
you YouTube where would I be without you
that's it for me for now please
subscribe we're trying to hit a thousand
million is that a billion oh my god
let's get it we have to beat I'm just
kidding see you gamers tomorrow
you