welcome everyone look who's here brought
her back baby to play the greatest game
of all time what your hit you never play
minecraft so when you look at that when
you look at that meatball what is that
what does that tell you use this to look
right
well that's my giant meatball this is my
world in Minecraft marks here we have
this really awkward setup and your name
is James Charles fan because that's my
secret my cat
oh no they will know now I'll change it
it's fine yeah I do I'm wearing the set
I'm wearing this spooky helmet you look
cute
you're wearing it you're wearing a
diamond helmet see if you press I think
f5 you can change so you see yourself oh
that's how you look what yeah you're
wearing diamond armor you should be
happy with it all right
don't break anything nah hey hey hey hey
relax yeah you're in creative mode I
don't know how to get you out of it okay
I got to show you stuff okay so this is
yeah
Mott's yeah what come over here okay
that's my slave I mean my worker I
paying minimum wage so there's just that
this is my automatic farm you come over
here and press his bun yeah he's doing
the machinery don't worry about it the
presses button no just right click on
the bun yeah starts to farm and if you
follow me here now you're doing good
maybe the farm isn't that impressive
okay
it's just like I'm getting stuff follow
me this is council of water she yeah oh
my god no you like council of water she
get back to work Council all right quick
quick quick
there council of authorship thank you no
okay
so I'm building this like oh I got sure
you IKEA Howard follow me look at that
get our look at look at that get our
yeah this year good that's very good
that's the agency what they're sure you
turn a grief water sheep follow me to
the meatballs okay we'll do our own
leveling the second I just really want
to show you like what I mean why you
haven't seen me the best as a creeper
not bad
oh that's s Quinn's I anything what
happens even boiling the water they'll
eat you so don't fall in the know you
can actually breathe in water cuz I am
this like things set up
whoa what are you gonna be to me I don't
know what do you want well you can ride
horses and stuff
but now you can't write squinch my see
ya no one's ever tried it I like the
thing with my crap everyone these things
you can do different things
alright you should come up over here
yeah go up thing now ignore the city
okay this is a my Japanese house that I
built for spend oh yeah you can fly cuz
you're in creative mode okay down there
this is Sven and this is men's boyfriend
and this is friend's son oh [ __ ] yeah
come on that's Q and then there's a
liberal wait oh he didn't name yeah
boyfriend I haven't named the Sun yet I
need a name tag but it's gonna be
sensing
what are you doing Tim well everything's
judging you right now let me take you to
my freaked onion hey what's that
attacking me oh it's a fan thumbs hurry
up okay oh yeah they're so annoying it's
cuz I haven't slept in the game these
annoying things come from the sky hey I
gotta get my training back no it comes
back after all okay so wait wait wait
where Specter
that's pinky comes and goes so this is
what their sheep and dungeon you press
this it opens up that's tower a llama
she likes tower I'm impressed by
Minecraft fiancee this is nips finally
tower love let me show you Tara llama no
one likes tower llama
it's alright so this is all the my
workers so after they in the freak
dungeon after they they are done
freaking thing I release them hearing
hey guys you're free activated my own
tribe by accident okay look look look at
him and then I send them up with a thing
they go to work
it's great Oh up there is do you want to
try it you can try and go into tribe
making sure he's fine he's fine yeah
yeah gonna trap the Travis to good she
can't find it it's it's a that's not
that is not the trap you want you mixed
it it doesn't matter yeah oh look you're
one of the workers yeah what job do you
want
[Music]
[Laughter]
you can be whatever you want Spence
mother that's so you
okay well that bets it then Wow why is
he doing in my bed
get out is my bag
you're not gamers good night gamers all
right we should play our own world up
okay what should we name our seed it
should be called like if we have a
sanctuary what would it be called bug
lion so I'm creating a new world front
this is gonna be our world but now no
more fun and games Marzia we have to
survive no fun we have to serve oh my
god sheets someone do that please for us
oh here we are mines yet oh you're so
kawaii
look you have lazy old outfit now what
are you looking at we have to survive
this is important oh my god there's for
arrogance you're James Charles man you
can talk to me their donkeys look a baby
thank you so cute okay well hmm you can
get only if you right-click it but it
will kick you off cuz you need to tame
it well it looks like you're doing more
than k me right please there is not work
like I can get out you just hit me
you're in it oh yeah you did he totally
just pushed you on down but okay what
about Beast
you can try the sheep's as far as I know
you can do other things frickin stay
yeah that's a button so the world is
completely like random randomly mates
and this is our world night will come
though I see if you look at the sky
so we need to make our farts home yeah
yeah so if you follow me
the first thing you do in Minecraft is
cut down a tree with your bare fists to
get some wood it's a pick a pick a tree
that you hate and just start punching it
thank you
well we can replant the trees which one
are you going for so you just hold you
just hold down that button and you see
it started decreasing yeah you know you
got your first block in Minecraft yeah
that's how they work
that's how signs work notch made this
game he decides if you press e you get
like your inventory okay okay after you
and then you have like this crafting
area right yeah if you bring the blocks
there you can make them into wood we're
more wouldn't like planks or whatever so
you just right right click there yeah
yeah and then place them in with your
Eamon turn and then you have more and
then now you can make other things so
this is like log and now it's like
planks and then you can take the planks
to make other things for example you
could grab more yeah you can do that and
then you place one right click in there
and then click left click in the
different spaces if you place one in
each thing you make a workbench which
maybe isn't that important or orange
steak sticks are good too okay yeah it
makes sticks and I'll make a workbench
you know we have to make a well well we
can make an axe so you can break us up
faster so if you give me your steaks I
can make you an axe
alright I'll make your necks anyway you
click on the crafting table and you make
this pattern well I can tell maybe if
you watch my let's place there you go
there you go she's making workbench next
up you'll make a cobblestone generator I
think you have enough sticks okay so
come over come over to your boy hello
stop don't punch me you know I have an
x-ray
Wow Wow I wholly say that you need an
axe to we're gonna build a house Marzia
don't eat the mushrooms your point
they're poison mushrooms no they're not
you can make mushroom stew if you want
I'd say we have to build a house zombies
are coming at night
here grab his hands grab that axe I give
you an axe just keep chopping yes
chop wood might see a chop shop you have
to say reach yeah you break faster if
you say chop chop
okay once we get it enough wood we
should pick a spot no they can drop like
apples it might be good to have a little
snack you know I was just gonna murder
one of the cows what did you say nice
murder
nothing what I would never do not do not
are we doing a vegan let's play but then
we have to it's so much harder
hi all right well eating mushroom we're
eating mushroom tonight gamers okay I
think we have enough wood I think what
we can do now is we can find like a nice
spot where we want to build our house I
up we're underwater or whatever you want
okay maybe not underwater that's a good
idea okay I like that I like that see
this is where do you go are you going up
okay I see I see
yeah so 200 part let's play incoming
Peter pine James Charles fan
do you like to any Charles well no I
don't like you don't like this is so
cool this is incredible
[Music]
all right you pick a spot whatever you
want but it doesn't work if you're gonna
break up Emma we can replant trees
there's flower biomes eyz okay you're
using an axe to cut down PP which is not
very efficient so here you go use this
for the dirt stuff and use this pickaxe
to cut down the gray stuff are you doing
good yeah yeah but here I'll use this
one I sent it this one is prettier I
made a better one for you if it gets
dark we can let up this place oh my god
it's getting dark real fast Marcia oh my
god they quicker my Zia is getting
darker I'll make torch are you blind
oh my god there we go what should we
name our home potato I like that we
should build a giant potato that
shouldn't be potato and then we only
grow up with paedos wait what are you
doing I'm helping you excuse me
oh sorry sorry I'll be right back if I
die Marcia just no what do you mind I
just know that that is dad abandoning me
I'm just gonna I'm coming back I'm
coming back we just don't have any food
where's the hole oh here we go
you pick that you pick the good home
yeah I did this so now we can put so
evil people don't come in for the door
here perfect
you like that okay I have a bit and then
Fedor here that's good I like this I
thought it would look good together just
like using different you know what
nevermind that's yeah they don't have
them they don't have big doors in this
game careful making the Lord make a door
I did can you make yes yes cuz I want to
keep them the natural effect that's
right yeah you can make how's this
yeah and we can have a little how many
years of Minecraft experience did this
whole is like the night it's kind of
cool if we murder a couple of sheeps we
can use their wool to make bends and we
can sleep sleep oh we don't have to
marry anyone of course I'll guess I'll
make a mushroom stew instead because
we're poor my say wants to be poor yeah
yeah I'll give you some torches you can
place them hey wait watch this I never
done this before
that's so cool oh I have to dig holing
dang it you're very demanding lady but
of course of course here it is
you're my minecraft girl and I do
anything right a right-click there you
go say anything any block you have you
can replace I gotta say this is a nice
hole yeah hi Sue why do you have so much
food why am i dying and you're not are
you still in creative mode no I'll make
a mushrooms some what you said that you
have perfect yeah yeah but then I need
to kill some enemies
I need to kill spiders
what about chickens yeah no chickens you
want to head out then no one died maybe
I should make a sword actually they just
cleaning up okay here's something yeah I
protect you my dad don't worry
yeah take the sword ah behind me there's
a baby killing kill the baby Marcia yeah
I hate them
oh my god please kill it it's gonna it's
gonna kill me all thank God
you'll learn where's my sword
uh it's probably new inventory I really
want to kill the cows Marcia no I won't
do it oh my god I thought that was you I
almost died
Oh careful and you wait for the sword to
charge up you look like you've taken a
couple punches thing okay okay Polly all
right Oh
it's full of people there's so many my
dear where did you go oh my god you're
so far away how did this happen the Sun
is back okay that means the zombies died
when the Sun comes up just keep living
keep living for me Marcia and the
animals Internet are you stop that I
don't think there are crocodiles in
Minecraft
the fishes yeah you can use a bucket no
we just started might see one step at a
time
you didn't hit it with the ax
oh you drown no but yeah we do we look
at our fishes oh my god I'm gonna die
too
well you you can respawn you just lose
your items but it's okay oh we have a
trader here oh my god the llamas are
gonna kill me oh my god I got killed by
llamas don't tell anyone
okay I'll find him one second I was
surprised nothing I just killed it I
killed a traitor and I have a present
for you it was further north so where
are you right now hey oh yeah I see you
I see you with stained water hey yeah
there you are here my dear hey macho you
must be so scared
ler I have a present for you Marcia you
have it follow me my dad this is our
home
I was close you were close we can old I
have a lead now so we can also take
hostages like this chicken can come with
us and be our house pay but we kidnap in
you don't want to chick in months my sir
doesn't want you sorry
he says he has nowhere else to go his
family abandon him he says please
maybe one day might say will change her
mind about me he said he loves your
YouTube channel Hey fake sad
fake bad okay so what I'm good how do I
get stuff back your meter would away I
can't breathe right I can make us some
beef it fell on the ground ha ha
it fell on the ground in front of me
look I make flour in front of my house
I'm tired of being hungry I'm starving
literally starving there was a cow and
nothing the cow had to go I'm sorry I
don't eat a spider
alright so what do you want I can make
you a wooden sword what do you want
anything you want like anything you want
anything
make me a cow I'll make you account yes
do yes damn you
sure you have good intuition how I go
where are you you keep disappearing
everywhere what are you doing I'll leave
you for two seconds two seconds you want
more snow you want a house full of snow
you want to eat glue you're an eagle
yeah at least changing yeah look at
these mountains they're sawsan aren't
you your feet cold so am i saying you
wanted more snow what are you laughing
yeah yeah okay so you can make snow
blocks let me see I don't remember you
used to shovel so I hear use the shovel
to get the snow so we should have a
location you know it's like the hole
[Music]
yeah you can go as tall as you want so
wanting the clouds
yeah I never thought of that I shouldn't
do that on my own No why not what do you
want to do oh you need you need me to
help you out okay okay okay let's just
make like a cute and called it an igloo
I would make it a little bigger that
would make it like bing bang and I'm
like pushing you away cuz you're in and
I look like a clown and I don't make it
a little like a little yeah and then
leave one open so we can see the skies
and stuff
hey James Charles fan here you go more
we don't have a lot of time Isaiah
zombies come soon soon chop chop chop
chop chop chop chop
now don't panic don't panic you'll be
fine you'll be fine
[Music]
I would like get on top of it and then I
would put one more up and then like
maybe like that you say I'm saying oh
god we have a visitor Marzia boise ones
oh he's outside our house no go away
I'll push him up the moon okay
look at our beautiful igloo look at that
thank Martha it's a beauty a truly a
spectacle to be absurd it's lovely what
matters is the insane all right what
else do you want see you know I protect
my ground
run that's yeah yeah yeah hey I just
saved you a lot of offense a wot a
bridge here out you can put the fence of
you on oh yeah good fence what why what
did I do
I'm trying over a year all right I'm
doing the bridge building a bridge for
your minds yeah this is minecraft we
build bridges oh god it's so far no that
is actually not bad
ah I never build anything it's not
before we should yeah we should find it
in our hostage dogs do you have any
bones I have a dog bone we can tame one
I don't think you like that we tame him
he's ours now this one is he tamed I
can't tell even plot I need to cook the
food maybe dawn budge him he's gonna
kill you mind that you're sorry about
that why again you were trying to give
him a flower good dog
all right well guess it's just me and
Sven to Anam thank you for joining my
Zia it smash like subscribe hundred
million merch
cool all right well you haven't tried to
pursue Malaysian citizen II after 50
million app troops much just now it's
still relevant just download it