no you laugh you lose let's go gamers
dinosaurs when they see the asteroid
coming down oh look it's the loud mic
guy oh god stop buying the blue Yeti
microphone my god it's like oh I got a I
got a sales stream I guess I'll buy the
mic that everyone has stop brother
that's Larry from VeggieTales oh my god
it's him oh I cannot unsee it now that's
Larry from VeggieTales even have the
teeth and everything how did he figure
out how to dream justin trudeau when a
bottle of black paint is within his
proximity come on he even covered his
hands who does that it's so many times
you know if you do a mistake once fine
a couple of times fine but enough times
and it's just become real Oh God
Oh No I take back everything I just said
okay you can make as many mistakes as
possible it doesn't mean anything I
swear it means nothing
coincidence a society if society ice
tell you at least you won't catch me in
blackface it's my only track record so
what good things have you done Felix
well I didn't lmf oh eh oh I can't read
cross console play is toxic
wait this cross console play now who
thought that was a good idea
they got ranch damn I love that that's
hilarious
it's like we're bringing gamers together
finally Xbox in place that you can play
together it's we're doing such a great
thing for gamers United reality we got
ranch I wasn't doing a black man voice
bye
just super clear that was just a random
voice I would never ever imitate black
man voice that's racist
my gamer Danny DeVito better make me act
up Danny DeVito more like Danny don't
wanna Vito Vito is Latin for look so now
that's not Danny devotion he's way
hotter than that
Danny devotion I'm not gonna lie I'd
freak Danny DeVito as long as he covers
up anything from neck to bottom I want
to see that
that's disgusting don't tell my SIA but
I would break that individual this is
peak comedy care we'll start with the C
and E Chipotle's a form of self-care I
know you can't tell me different also
guac back I loved wok and bring this
whole thing in Guam because I'm an adult
and I can and South Carolina pack you
can use your leftover Guam as a facemask
I guess you can see I walk a little
something on my face did you like that
pun because I did not only will the
avocado make your face feel better and
this is what some care looks like I'm
sorry I'm sorry you had to watch that I
apologize
fact well we do have this little bit of
a second I want to I've seen that this
is a classic monster right here
that's right while you could no don't no
I recall it that : Duncan you got a
problem do you like the taste of that
monster let's just go to the game this
is getting out of control just getting
out of control was that set up it was
too good you got a problem do you like
the chest if he hasn't tasted yet and
then he goes in and then it registers
it's so funny
[Laughter]
this is why you drink G fuel I don't
know how many times I gotta say it
drink G fuel code pity pie there's the
discount I'm in charge I'm in charge I'm
the only one with a gun I'm in charge
and it looks like a critic a thank you
take your shirt off
okay yes to meek come on down kid
let's have a drink here that's it
you saved me now yeah feel like I've
seen it yes Kevin told me don't make
don't make me you done this isn't the
drinking room don't make me look like
Meyer domine the master of puns
absolutely incredible delivery come on
dr. Bell you can get up
the effort that went into this she says
[Music]
okay that was impressive
okay you saw that was that big
everything's swell in there or something
that would be beautiful that's right Oh
No what do you weigh down Thanks look at
you go Wow nice cash three thousand
pounds 40 miles an hour
Wow hello when these just become me
going haha funny haha oh wait not
supposed to laugh
Oh shame ah I guess I lost
[Music]
okay Jesus Christ top-notch 10 out of 10
that was beautiful I want water that
[Music]
damn to be here baby so big yeah
cold-hearted killer but what is this new
filter that real how can you get scared
of that well these are pretty cool blue
arrows
goodnight go I see you tomorrow hmm
like I want to laugh but they're so bad
no no stop stop trying to do loud is
funny okay I would never do that
oh man oh man you already know man it's
cool
you don't know why well you feeling fat
out with your barbeque boy sunday school
special sure there's booked like an
exotic cricketer ugly what tap dancing
frog looking as well and you're on it
with them roof are red violets are blue
my boo square-looking mother fat pan
says I don't know you guys but I'm
frickin villager what are you gonna do
sue me
you can't I'm Swedish it's the only good
thing we have
here comes - oh no no now that mixture
with family guy for been an illegal okay
that was that big oh no no no don't feed
rook to me
stop he doesn't want it Oh Oh God
much like if you're crying - that was
incredibly sad I was gonna say so sad
but then I realized I was dead mean
so I said incredibly sad instead big
brain
oh my god
Russell well technically if he has clean
rush so then he actually made a bigger
mess because he made balloons on the
floor so if anything you shouldn't be
sharing his thanks actually I felt like
a boys locker room girls be like again I
gotta change tampers boys be like clean
Russell No ah so sad
the [ __ ] live out of patient thanks
Abby I I really really swear to God here
[Music]
sound like he started me I I really yeah
got here live we will have much more
from the tiny community of Rachel Nevada
at 6:30 reporting live Joe Moore tells
13 Action News everyone's getting so
good at editing bro what is this Mara
days
[Music]
oh my god I've CIS
that's illegal you can't do that anymore
[Music]
still funny though a membership figures
stood at 169 810 you could do it Jacob
700 listen properly seven hundred and
sixty nine thousand eight hundred and
twenty
all right gamers be honest did you
scoffs a-- or did you flora let me know
in the comments down below and also
raise it a hell anymore the baby edits
are so good I love this meat hamburger
hamburger that's hilarious
okay that was good I like that one
[Music]
what is it
oh it's Peter graphic yeah that's right
gamers thank you for watching this
episode of scatter their falooda dude
happy to love you yes but did you live
let me know in the comments down below
and see you gamers next time hey doll
Hey whoa you haven't tried to Bruce
emulator City after 50 million out
troops by ouch Miami down just down it's
still relevant just down a bit