annoying things youtubers do what's up
everyone it's me the least annoying
youtuber there is
I just wanted to ethically rant today
about some stuff that I noticed
youtubers do that is kind of weird
there's a lot of it that doesn't
necessarily get addressed a lot it
probably does but regardless I'm gonna
go through it and then I'm gonna ask you
guys what your pet peeves I guess we can
call it our and we'll compare if we have
the same ok number one this is very
specific but I find it as a perfect
example of youtubers have no idea what
they're doing so they're just copying
everyone else we have Sniper Wolf with a
tiny tiny bit of red than the in the
thumbnail for whatever reason people
think this is something worth
replicating this tiny bit of red in the
background of the photo that's what's
gonna get you views apparently people
just should I pick any other color than
this shade of gray red now now it has to
be that one oh I tried all other colors
they don't give use ok sure
I like how this started as well with
sniper wolf and was a Z who practically
looks so similar anyway and they have
the exact same thumbnail you know that
photo of a human where it's like all
faces combined this is gonna be every
youtuber eventually what is that yeah
this is how all youtubers are gonna look
in the future I know not that important
Felix no one cares it just showed so
much to me alright bringing up the
second point which is the description of
videos I hate the description of videos
I don't care about it but it's one of
those things as a youtuber you have to
write a description because it's so
important for people to find your video
a lot of channels will I mean I don't
even know how it works to be honest
previously used to be tanks as a way to
find a video through searches and it
didn't have to be in your face you can
just put in a bunch of tags yadda yadda
yadda no one cares
but now everyone just put the same tags
in every video so you're kind of lost
this effect so now what YouTube wants
you to do is to write a description in
your video and it's so obnoxious look at
this I mean clearly it works view rise
but after child well clay made the video
spining just rock band signs record deal
at the product says Oracle rose music
video goes viral
by quaint created our Regina and pc-9
brothers and sister Kris my test results
from upgraded hacker PC 7 1 P 1 5 to
reveal sibling true that was a quote ok
and then you'll upload it quote upgraded
hacker defeat it's a way to get all the
videos recommended by putting the title
of other videos in this one searching
for technology to destroy projects or go
on the expulsion project Soria YouTube
channel example project circle member PC
9 and also named merit started big and
I've read half of it
watch my awesome friend videos know
they're teaming up now oh no I think
this annoys me so much because it's it's
not about the content it's more about
how you can optimize your videos in a
way that people will be will watch it
it's loud it grabs attention and people
don't question why they watch it it's
just there in front of you because it
hits every single mark or what YouTube
is asking for if we click on any video
that just starts immediately super
intensive then it's a it should be
assigned to just click off immediately
you're not gonna get fulfilled from this
[Music]
I'm told by YouTube as well that I
should write a better description and I
just cannot care less I told boohoo
right it's just so lame which brings to
the third point which is YouTube
thumbnails I mean this has a long
history back with like I think Tobuscus
and with like same face every single
thumbnail for whatever reason having
just this face in the thumbnail will
will do the trick do you know how
annoying it is I'm so sick of it but
it's so useful for people to know hey
it's you in the thumbnail you know what
from now on this is gonna be my
thumbnail for every video because that's
how I feel inside when I make these
thumbnails so awful it's so cringy I
like this david dobrik one as well just
like just mirror the image I can't be
bothered
it's too soul-crushing to take another
photo I'll just mirror the photo
I like that clearly it works no one
cares I think after you it's fine but
after you've done like a thousand of
these stupid faces in the thumbnail it's
like
I'm done I'm done I'm officially done
I've done too many number four videos
that have a question that I could not
give less [ __ ] about but I'll watch the
whole thing and I'm thoroughly enjoyed
it always annoys me like I've learned a
lot but I will never need to know this
it's the world running out of helium I
don't care but it was a great video okay
I want to see what shows up if I search
why why Costco is cheaper than Amazon I
don't care just don't click on it Felix
you clearly don't understand my
impulsive habits that I can't control
okay why Joe Rogan won't do hot ones I
mean I want to know but I'm sure the
answer is pretty unimportant why planes
don't fly I don't care stop stop roping
me into questions that I don't care
about stop giving me knowledge and stuff
I don't like it it needs to end what is
his budget v socks why doesn't the heart
get tired I don't care I don't care I
don't care
stop asking questions in your titles I
don't care I don't care do I have to say
it more why your aim still sucks I don't
want to know I don't want to know I
found this when I accidentally clicked
on this video and it's number five
pointless or rewards for videos no
Daniel or Regina the winner will get
oh cool why it's almost like this night
you need to know you can't just do
anything now there has to be like 10
grand on the line or something when
there gets 5 billion and they're never
satisfied in the end when they win
they're like oh cool this is awesome
it's the same video regardless it's not
like it's amping up anything but oh my
god they win ten thousand so I have to
watch the video and see what their
reaction is reaction alright cool thanks
what are you gonna do with this I'll
maybe pay off student loans okay cool so
many youtubers do this now with like pay
ten thousand pay ten thousand all right
don't get me wrong I think people can do
it right and a lot of people do but it's
one of those concept that clearly works
on YouTube and everyone just take that
concept and they do it so lazily lazily
is that a word I don't know what did I
see recently oh yeah morgues does that
in line last two life wins twenty
thousand it's like it's like the bank
gives out loans to its elves yeah I won
twenty thousand from my own money that's
awesome cool number six
I think I'm we're up to six likes on the
screen it's the thing that's happening
now and it's one of those things where I
makes me feel so [ __ ] old leave a
like liked subscribe cool the video just
began why stop it I get it it's like a
way less intrusive way to get people to
like the video this is another one of
those things that clearly works and
everyone just does it and now it's a
standard and it's just annoying and I
don't like it
boomer this is a Boomer wrenched by you
to basically which brings me into the
next one is when a lot of times you'll
watch like a video just to understand
how to do something an instruction video
and for whatever reason they'll still
tell you okay maybe it's like how do you
fix how do you download this app on your
phone or something stupid I don't know
and by the end that I follow me on
Instagram guys no no I'm not gonna
follow you in Instagram I mean I could
just ignore you saying that but why
would I know your place if you make text
tutorials then maybe people don't give a
[ __ ] about your Instagram Jesus Christ
the same with podcast everyone has a
podcast now this is such an epic rant
why does that Noah
not everyone hates a podcast if they're
sitting on problem number what are we on
eight or nine
it doesn't matter red shadow legends
have you guys heard about raid shadow
legends but don't take my word for it
take all the reviews that are it has
5-meter million reviews and they're all
5.9 average and her weight if you
download now you get 50,000 gold
whatever that means and you can also
read shadow legend with me maybe you can
find me in the game if you play an
average shadow legends listen I'm not
gonna hate on people getting bright on
YouTube I think it's great but for the
sake stop everyone that does raid shadow
legend shoutouts it's the same script
for everyone they've literally just said
okay you need to say all these things
and then every raid shadow legend shout
out sounds exactly the same it is so
annoying what's this the most immersive
RPG experience you'll find on a
smartphone its most immersive experience
your final smartphone I bought another
phone with my sponsorship money so I can
do we literary buyout for folks three
dedicate for raid regions
hmm sleep sleep the greatest ugly
Christmas sweater of all time we got
shoes and get this we got legs all the
way baby alright sure check out the ugly
Christmas sweater calm / pewdiepie order
now to get it in time for Christmas
let's get real let's get some mad push
for Christmas gamers let's get it check
it out we even got thongs that's right
PewDiePie thongs are fake check it out
ad sponsored gifted gamer red shadow
legend it's game where you can pick
class and play game and graphic good
alright
those were my pet peeves about YouTube
do you agree with them do you not let me
know in the comments I'm not gonna read
them anyway I'm kidding I do read
comments okay so I asked them Twitter
what your pet peeves are about youtubers
which I think it's pretty interesting so
let's see talking super slow and it's
noticeable they're trying to make the
video longer
some people on YouTube speak so slow
I always watch videos on times to speed
and some people speak so slow that even
times to makes the video dreadfully slow
this is a problem with YouTube in
general that YouTube ones longer videos
so people drag them out for no reason at
all and it's very obnoxious I can't say
that I'm entirely guilt free on this but
I've seen the worst examples and it
blows my mind that people are okay with
it they never really help small
youtubers oh I remember when I used to
do that remember that and then people
started calling me Nazi for it it's epic
that this is why I don't do good things
any more unnecessary interest and
background information yes this is don't
care about your car accident that left
you without a left head just show me
that a clean bird so here's the tutorial
on how to fix your makeup eckel also
guys sorry about the background already
in this video we got a little bit of
construction going on outside hope that
isn't too annoying for you guys in the
background anyway also when they have a
camera for three years can't the relate
can't relate to this at all I also think
that I know this is kind of a stupid
argument to make but when people get too
polished of a setup like a studio and
and like super crisp quality camera and
and their everything is amazing which is
nice don't get me wrong and they fit
certain channels but it almost feels
like you kind of lost touch with what in
my opinion YouTube is when it's too
polish it's almost like I know it makes
no sense to say I don't know it's like
I'm justifying me being a cheap ass and
not buying a proper camera alright it's
not a pet peeve really but chorded big
digital put an ad timer in their videos
if i want to watch an ad and i can and
if I don't want to I can skip to exactly
where the video ends more YouTube
versity should do that a great way to is
to if you're on your phone you can just
double tap on the side of the screen
most ad reads are either 60 to 90
seconds
so you just DoubleTap six times and if
their ad is still going double tap three
times and you're good to go
you're welcome gamers starting a podcast
there it is for no reason I don't know
why that annoys you so much I like
Podcast as much as the next guy but why
don't half the people I follow feel like
they need to have their own aimless
podcast I ain't got time for that I like
this because clearly you can just ignore
it you don't have to consume the podcast
it doesn't hurt you in any single way at
all but it still annoys me I am still
bothered by it this does not affect me
whatsoever but I'm still very bothered
by it stop it I don't like it
skip over really important items in bit
on video games well when you're doing
commentary and you're focused on keeping
it interesting it is hard to play away
as you do when you just watch a video
and you just it is different I remember
when I play with friends and and one
person has to control it it's so much
easier to be like you missed that you
missed that you missed that I get that
it's still annoying but yeah I don't
know talking over dialogue in games well
it's that dialogues weren't so boring
Jesus Christ I gotta say as someone that
has played insane amount a story-driven
horror and sorry story driven games most
game developers aren't writers and the
writers that game developers hires are
so bad they cannot write it can't it's
awful and he just feels like you're
having your time wasted I remember
watching the documentaries of the of the
how they made the halo cutscenes and I
find it's so interesting how they kept
revision doing it it's a really good
service if you watch actually how Bungie
did the original Halo games because
their approach to storytelling in the
cutscenes were we are wasting people's
time we need to make this as interesting
as we possibly can and I think that is
missed on a lot of games it just feels
like they need to drag out the game to
be as long as possible which kind of
ties into YouTube in a sense asking
people to like and subscribe to their
Channel ten seconds into the video this
is one of those things that just doesn't
go away because it clearly works despite
how cannabis it is I remember when I
started doing YouTube videos and I felt
awful just asking for subscribing at the
end watch it watch some of my earlier
videos I'm like if you've made it this
far in the video then maybe consider
subscribing and I remember I remember
like getting like two or three more
subscribers because I used to do that
I'm like holy [ __ ] I found a gold mine
subscribeto pretty recorded videos maybe
it's just me but I don't like the vibe
of pre-recording yeah I get this a lot
since I do daily videos why don't why
can't you just work ahead or why can't
you just do that I really don't like it
either I think it shows immediately when
a video is pre-recorded and it makes it
less interesting in a sense I don't know
why cuz it's such a subtle thing I only
really work ahead if I have no other
choice leave your opinion in the
comments below
never reads comments this actually
reminds me of another thing I always
read the comments I think I think it's
super fun if I don't care about the
comments it probably means I don't care
about the video I just created to be
honest so I think it's a good way to
know if you made an interesting video or
not I first thought the whole like a
common thing was interesting but now I
just find it a really annoying way for
youtubers to shell-like positive
comments because they all get bumped I
wish I could like a comment without it
getting bumped up because now it's like
I want to find out what people thought
of a video like what the actual
democracy opinion of ideas are but then
I have to feel like I have to scroll
through yeah there's a surgeon out
problems I am aware but it's like I have
to scroll past all these like like the
Creator like comments to get what two
people are actually saying do you
understand what I mean so that's why I
find myself not even using this feature
another one makes a 15 to 20 minute rant
about some other creator how much they
hate their content and despite their
views and then say please don't send any
hate as it ends as if that's gonna stop
the hate well it's kind of annoying as a
creator how you can't criticize another
channel without a lot of dumb idiots
following along and just taking it too
far so it's almost like you have to say
it even though it's not gonna have any
effect I think that's another pet peeve
I have too is like these channels that
are purely based around calling out
other channels that's all they do and
then they get called out and it's and
it's the biggest drama ever how could
they say this about me but I think you
have a point here with this cuz it's
like you're creating this atmosphere on
YouTube where it's being overly critical
and and things like that putting more
emphasis that being overly critical is
important when it really isn't oh god
I'm a giant hypocrite
starting an interesting sentence about
themselves or their own life experience
then gets distracted and then they never
finished and finished sin
yeah going on tangent is something I see
a lot of youtubers do especially when
you're new because you think it's like a
quirky way to speak but it's just really
really really really annoying if I ever
go on a tangent you may have noticed
this I always acknowledge that I go on a
tangent just so people know that yes I
am aware this is a different topic but I
will get back to the point later a
little tip there for newbies and I'm
working on something really excited but
I I can't tell you yet yes the
announcement of it the announcement
that's always very interesting just shut
the [ __ ] up then I hope I haven't done
this I don't think I do
doing too much of it at once and I can
lie but pushing games merch and hardware
and drinks and figures and a sponsor all
in one video it's kind of much in one
video I think with games I have another
one coming out poopd on 12 of December I
don't give a [ __ ] if you have a problem
with it games is really hard to time
with other things a lot of times you're
working with different people in it I
mean it is fair criticism but at the
same time games specifically it's very
hard to time say might seem like oh
you're pushing a lot right now but it's
literally just a coincidence and I think
it's cool stuff too like I don't know I
don't care when they try to act poor as
familiar I can relate to someone working
two jobs and living paycheck to paycheck
it like some of them hi there well I
mean meanwhile we're all aware of it I
think it makes it worse when they try to
hide it and relate to us to some level
yet see this a lot youtubers obviously
pop off I think it's less than obnoxious
than shoving it in your face we'd like
look at the car look at the house wait
and when that becomes your content
that's a lot more annoying than trying
to hide your wealth but I also think a
lot of youtubers are scared of showing
that they have money to lose that sort
of connection with their audience and
that's what people do it when I think in
reality it doesn't matter what level you
are on as long as you're honest about
what you're doing and can express what
your fears are people will still
understand it even if they can't relate
to it I'll really complain about YouTube
and how bad it is to point where it's
not just venting their frustration
anymore it's very tense of complaining
for no reason
you have a great house expensive
equipment and an amazing car like a stop
I actually disagree with this to a
certain extent because I think I find
myself being more critical about things
that I care about and that doesn't mean
I think it's all bad but it's it's
things that I think can make improve
it's just giving constructive criticism
or pointing out things that I'm annoyed
with because I really care about you to
me if I bribed by youtubers because I'm
I really want you to do well but I think
it's small things right I think the
thing with YouTube is said eventually
because it's ridiculous to care about
these tiny little promise all people are
stupid thumbnails and blah blah blah all
these all these things they don't mean
anything by themselves but after year
after year after year after year
each progression of all these things I
think we'll find it maybe it's not
entirely possible that we find ourselves
looking at a YouTube that has been
shaped in a way that we don't want it at
all and I think that's my concern when
addressing these things not so much each
like I couldn't give a less [ __ ] about
what someone uses I said thumbnail well
yeah that's my YouTube pet peeves
do you agree disagree I read the comment
actually that's a lie
actually no it isn't like I got it you
know when everyone's spanned the
comments and it's the same one I just
sort by knew all right that's how I read
the comments you're not slick okay all
right that's it
bye-bye
[Music]
you are entering a new era where you
shall craft thy own
the hour of our spells and poop grades
is coming marzia Edgar and buttons need
you
the timer you will face but crawlers is
all about
when you are seated on the porcelain
throne Bertie is the game to play I'm
not supposed to have my opinion about
that but the prizes
[Music]
you