Hey Jake.
I made one phone call.
I got the same house as you,
Same cars to, It's really not that hard.
Oh hey, by the way welcome to the top little brother,
Feels good heh!
But, Let's not forget how you got here (uh!)
YAY YEEHT!
Little brother jakey try to roast me?! (WHAT!)
Little brother standing on his own two feet?
(Not For Long!)
I'm a dog, You're a puppy, Call you kong (WOOF!)
Let's talk about your garbage that you call a song.
(TRASH!)
It should be every other day, Just some strong advice
i made you famous once, It's about to happen twice
yeah you on disney, but who helped you read all your lines?
(THAT'S ME)
Don't forget boy, You were my shadow on vine.
Now you got a few subscribers,
And you think that you're the s***
I'll admit, you got money, you got bars, you got chicks
But you're a d***
You ain't thankful for your fans, It's kinda funny
do your investors know team 10 ain't making any money?
See, it starts with the talent,
But it's hard when you got none
I think you kinda salty 'cause
I'm the favorite son
I'm a maverick, You're a sidekick,
Yeah i brought you to LA
If there's one thing you should know,
YOU DON'T F*CK WITH THE LOGANG!
Hold up, I'ma throw up, looking at your face,
You don't know what it means to glow up.
Tryin' to dance and acting class,
It's doing nothing, now you try to rap
Come on, hold up.
Catch the flow, you can't oh no,
Maybe Team 10's got it?
I mean, that's how you grow.
But you still can't sell out any shows.
No, you still can't find some matching clothes!
(YAH YEET!)
You just killin the vibe, yeah, (fact)
You ain't doin it right, yeah, (double fact)
Trying to play ball with the dogs,
You don't know what you've done,
You just ruined your life, yeah,
You're killin the vibe, yeah,
You ain't doing it right, yeah,
Trying to play ball with the dogs
You don't know what you've done
You just ruined your life, yeah!
What happened Jake, man, we used to love each other...
After all, we came from the same mother.
Biologically you know that makes us brothers!
So much negativity it really makes me wonder.
(Why?)
I feel like you need a maverick shirt.
(link in description)
When you insult me Jakey, it really hurts.
Sometimes I wish my real brother was Dirk.
But now I gotta go and PUT YOU IN THE DIRT!
Yo wait what hold up... HOLD UP, WHY THE MUSIC STOP?!
UH OH!
THAT'S ALISSA VIOLET,
USED TO BE YO CHICK!
NOW SHE IN THE LOGANG,
AND YOU KNOW SHE ON MY...
TEAM.
THOSE CARS AIN'T YOURS MAN,
THAT S*IT WAS JUST FLOATED!
GUN TATTOOED ON YOUR LEG,
'CAUSE SHE KNEW YOU WEREN'T LOADED!
I ACT IN MOVIES THAT YOUR FANS WATCH WITH THEIR BABY SITTERS.
(airplane mode)
I THOUGHT YOU WERE MY BOY, GUESS I HAVE A BABY SISTER!
(YEET)
YOU'RE TRYNA BE A MODEL, SHOULDA KEPT NEELS VISSER.
(HAHAHA!)
GO MAKE ANOTHER VIDEO 'BOUT WHO'S THE BETTER KISSER!
Is it called team 10
Cuz you take 10 percent of your friends?
(That's f*cked up, Jake...)
When the contract dies,
So does their career, it ends!
(That's... also a fact.)
Are you mad just cause you couldn't sign the Dolans?
(They're smarter than you...)
So you had to replace them with SOME SPANISH TWINS?!
(Haha, WEAK!)
It's everyday bro... DO YOU GIVE UP AT NIGHT?!
WE 24/7 MAN, YOU PICKED THE WRONG FIGHT!
I'M A SAVAGE,
YOU ARE AVERAGE,
I'M A BEAST,
I'M GOING WILD!
THIS SONG WILL BE THE DEATH OF YOU,
I'M 'BOUT TO BE AN ONLY CHILD!!!
*Music*