Where's logan?
you found your balloon didn't you buddy?
hey what's up? that's me, logan
I used to be a regular kid from Ohio
You know i love sports payed attention in school and was always a bit awkward
But then when I was about 10 years old, I picked up a video camera and became Logan Paul. and your address? butthead street.
wow your a jerk don't call back again
Yup I've always been a bit of a troublemaker. Fast Forward.
**Fast Forwarding**
This was me in 2016, which ended up being the best year of my life
(Music)
Then this was me in 2017, which was an even better year of my life
(Music continues)
So what the Fuck happened in 2018
that made the world quiver when they heard the words - *Logan Paul*
Obviously, you know the answer, but let's rewind for a second
After becoming one of the top vine stars in the world, Rest in Peace Vine, btw
I hopped from platform to platform shooting viral sketch comedy bits. Some of which you may have seen
After about a year, I have gained about 25 million fans between Facebook, Instagram and Twitter
And then I heard about this thing called daily vlogging
What is up
People of the internet. My name is Logan Paul and welcome to my vlog channel. That's right
I'm vlogging now you get to see more of me. hahaha
I began, my youtube journey with a bulldozed mentality
I was gonna work my ass off to overtake this platform with fresh explosive quick pace and outlandish content.
I wanted to conquer and destroy
sometimes quite literally everything in my path. The bigger the faster, the louder the better.
I wanted to make noise,
So... I did
We became the fastest channel to hit ten million subscribers in the history of YouTube
And I told myself that I was gonna blow any competition I had, out of the water which at one point became my own brother
And that got ugly
**Chanting** LOGAN LOGAN
And slowly but surely in my endless pursue of more views and more subscribers
It was becoming clear that the vlog mentality was getting out of hand
But, I did not see that
Here's what I saw
Oh Mamma Mia take a look around Oh! yoo look so good at night! boy just dropped 40k on a presidential rolex
so how about that vehicle though
What's in the bags eleven thousand six hundred dollars worth of Gucci clothes. Oh! is this solid gold, solid gold. twenty thousand dollars
It is yours. That's my boii
The machine was beginning to take on a mind of its own
As my hunger for success was growing exponentially. So was my ego.
The line for what was acceptable, became more and more foggy and the disrespect began to skyrocket
And it's not that I felt the rules didn't apply to me I knew they did
I just didn't care about the consequences if I broke them. I didn't even consider them
You can't stop logan fucking paul
I Wanted to entertain my audience every single day with, out of this world content and behavior that they could only find on logan paul vlogs
Consequences were rarely even an afterthought
logang going to the top
And not to mention I was the 22 year old
blond haired, blue eyed kid from Ohio with 45 million followers on the internet. Every single day
My actions were validated by five to seven million viewers
and as long as I wasn't doing any harm
No one was trying to stop me now my peers not my family not even members of my own team
And then in December of 2017 I went to Japan
It was the perfect storm of circumstance ignorance ego and downright stupidity
The backlash against the social media star who posted a video of an apparent suicide victim is intensifying
The video viewed over 6 million times in just 24 hours
Youtube star Logan Paul is facing the fallout after posting a video that showed the body of an apparent suicide victim
The backlash was
massive people and creators of all sizes
Denouncing Logan Paul and this video actor Aaron Paul saying Logan Paul go to hell so many people sharing stories people they lost due
of to suicide and some specifically hanging
I obviously as a person as a human being I was
frustrated and pissed off and offended by his actions a hero for a lot of kids is to logan fans and
when I see that I
Care so much
I'm so disgusted
how could somebody not realize how fucked up this is this crosses the line and I am NOT surprised that he would do something like
This it doesn't make any sense to me whatsoever
As a human being how about a little bit of empathy like a normal human being instead of being a moron go to a morgue
If you're that fucking morbid he thought that that was a cool thing to do
in
Less than 24 hours. I became the most hated person on the planet. I
Had made an inexcusable mistake
completely destroyed my image lost every
Professional relationship that I had became the Internet's favorite meme and most importantly had my eyes opened wide to the consequences of my actions.
I felt every ounce of disappointment and hate directed at me and while it was a hundred percent my fault
It was critical that I felt all of it
Now here's where I made a significant mistake. I went into panic mode
Being disliked was my biggest fear in the entire world
So in a scramble to try and reverse the past I asked myself
How do I fix this when instead the question I should have been asking was how do I fix me?
I took a month break from the internet and attempted to bounce back with an anti suicide PSA and a donation
But I was still moving too fast.
I didn't fully understand the significance of my actions the depth of the pain they caused and was literally becoming my own worst nightmare
Pretty much. I know for a fact everything I do from this point on will get criticism
It will get backlash. So internet, please don't use me bro crucify me vilify me
As I fell more and more out of touch with reality. I couldn't trust myself. I wouldn't send my team the videos for a review
I didn't listen to my friends and I refused to adapt my content. It was the highest degree of self-sabotage
But finally after nearly running the rest of my life into the ground I received a blessing in disguise
True Geordie: You said before this fight you have something planned
Is there anything you want to say to someone out?
KSI: Obviously man's got this belt right now and if any YouTuber wants it. You can come get it
Jake Paul, Logan Paul, any of the Pauls I don't care bring it
I saw this as an opportunity to turn my disoriented emotions into fuel
After everything that had happened since January
This was my chance to truly TRULY take a step back from the internet
and focus on something else with the unrelenting passion that I knew I had
I knew that I had more to offer in this world, and I did not want to let my failure define me
Little did I know, I had been preaching this message the whole time
And if you lose if you fail fine, in fact, please let me fail
Let me let me lose. If you can take a hit in the face and get back up and learn from it
That is a win consider that a win because you are now better and stronger than you were in the past
It's just like working out. You work out. You work out. You work out you deplete your muscles
You take your protein shake and then your muscles heal and you're stronger than you were before. It's the same exact thing...
During the six months of four hours of daily training I rekindled my relationship with my brother
I fell in love with a girl who
Absolutely changed my life and I restructured my business and focused on my mental health and emotional growth
This is weird bro, I didn't think i'd cry right now
Thank God for the people around me in the support of you guys because I don't know how else I would have gotten through this
Year or out of my own way
It is a majority draw
And although the fight was a draw (whack as fuck)
It turned out to be the biggest event in internet history, and I'm looking forward to the rematch next year
I told myself at the beginning of the year I was not going to let that become my legacy
and that I was gonna not ask for forgiveness but earn a chance to be forgiven
Have I earned that? not yet, not yet
But it is a start of a new Logan Paul
where every fucking day I craft a better version of myself and KSI for that I owe you a thank you brother
Rematch is gonna be fun
True Geordie: Ladies and gentlemen KSI and Logan Paul!
As I've matured this year I've gotten to exercise my creativity in different ways with the number one podcast in the world called impaulsive
A documentary about the Flat Earth, which is coming in January, And
I'm hitting 2019 hard by releasing a show called best friends that I shot with Evan
big things come in small packages
An animated storytime series about crazy shit that's gone down in my life as well as reviving the vlogs.
I'm growing into who I am and what I want to make versus trying to fit into the mold of YouTube
Personality or be someone who I'm simply not
The things you've been went through this year
Have you shared yet on this podcast or on your vlog - three biggest lessons you learned from this year. What's that?
What's the one you share? The one is slow down. It is the first thing that comes to my mind and I can
not
Point to that as the reason for what happened the singular reason for what happened, but that is a that is HUGE
What would be less number two the biggest?
lesson of the year lesson number two
listen...
Listening happen what way listen to the people around you?
Listen to what they're saying
Listen to your audience. Listen to your friends. Listen, you're family. You're not right about everything old Logan what will be a third one
Biggest lesson that you think will transform not only your business your brand your Empire, but also your life
In 2019 and beyond I think empathy
I think I think being aware of people beyond just yourself
Granted I'm still young and I still have a lot to learn and by no means am I saying I've learned everything and
I'll never make another mistake
Because I'm far from perfect and I'm nowhere near the man I want to be
But the best thing I can do is keep striving to listen, learn, grow, feel and adapt.
Now one year later, although I can't say 2018 was the best year of my life
I can absolutely say this has been the most cathartic and important year of my life
This year and how I move forward will forever define the type of man that I am in the mission I'm on
I'm blessed to be able to continue doing what I love and I want to thank all of you for your support
and if you're like me and you're ever feeling low, like the weight of the world has been stacked on your shoulders
Even if it is a fault of your own, just remember
It could always get worse
But it will always get better
Who knows? 2018 might end up being the best year of my life, but I got a lot more to go.
Peace!!!
Captions Made By: Dion Perera http://dionperera.com