Jake hasn't changed at all dude... he still thinks he's a thug and he's a still a whiny ass bitch
AYO~ Good Morning Logang! WHASPOPPIN'!
Yo~, we just set up a wall of merch for a photoshoot that we're doing
Getting right into the day, I'm heading to set later BUT, look at this bro~ this is DOPE.
We got everything guys... If you don't know, we are having a pop up shop in New York this weekend
Details will be on my Instagram, but like exclusive stuff like this backpack, we got v-necks, we got LOGANG4LYFE.
We got everything bro~ YA~ YA~ YA~ I think it's time for a montage
OGH~
SIK MONTAGE DHUUD.
Alright, we're back at the crib, my roommate, young Evan, yo, first off, no one leaves my shoulder without telling them.
You bro~ HOW?!... Yo. OK, just one sec.
HOOWW?!~
Just give me one sec, Maverick. Thanks~ OK, HOW?!~
Can I tell you something?
I am Jesus.
But.. But.. They were a lot shorter back then, so that's why people like...
I was still vlogging this whole thing.
Awww~ S£$%.
Hey, Jesus bro~, I shouldn't of vlogged that, I'm sorry... Bro, come on, I have something to show you, just trust me.
Come on.
*Heheheh* Are you good bro~? Why you taking Jesus's bed dude?
SOOOO CUTEE~
Are you mad bro?~
Evan: GET THE F#£$ OUT OF MY BED. Logan: OH S"£$, JESUS IS ANGRY
He didn't mean it Kong, he was just kidding, he's just short... tempered.
Yo.. no. stahp, stahp, ow, ow, ow.. F#$% me (?). Ow, OW OWWWW
POWER OF CHRIST COMPELS YOU!
ALRIGHT WE'RE GOING TO SET, WE'RE GOING TO SET.
Y'ELLO, OK guys, I'm in my trailer... I just realised something OK, like *BRRAGUHSUGHUH*
I've been on set for like 4 hours, and vlogging on set is hard BRO~!
I GOT NO CONTENT!~
Luckily, this is my last day, then back to the epic savagery that is, Logan Paul Vlogs.
But right now, I'm looking around and.. oh there it is, yup.
Yaaaa~ this is happening, right now.
Good ol' Tabasco sauce, going down the hatch.
Wait, hold on, I got distracted, this is not yours?
No, no, It's yours.
They just left a box of... potatoes?
They dropped my burrito, and they only gave me hashbrowns...
I'm going to eat it, 'cause I'm fat.
You want some Tabasco with that?
*UUHGUGHGUH*
(nice...)
*BAUHAUABAUABAUHAUBAUH*
That made me sick... I need more potato... *AHUAAMAUUM*
D'you need this? A FWIRER EXSTWINGWISHER
I'm OK, honestly, I missed my mouth... I just wanted to spray.
Well, that's a good start to the vlog... what do you say?
Alright guys, given the beef that's going on between me and my brother right now...
I figured it'd be interesting to go back and watch the videos that we made when we were kids.
Bro~, we've been making YouTube videos since I was 10.
Yeah~, no.. OK, story.
Those ones... like the super young ones, I actually deleted when I was like, 15.
NOOOOO~
Yeah, like the really young, pre-puberty. I know bro... here's why.
I wasn't a full Maverick back then, I was like 16 years old, and I had a crush on this girl.
And her younger sister watched our videos.. because Jake and I were like the kids in town that made videos.
and everyone pretty much knew us... oh hello~~
Hey guys~ what'dya doing in here?
Just vlogging, step in the frame
just vlogging... ma nhams Jheff.
Anyways, I had a crush on this girl, and she saw these videos that I made when I was really young
and she was embarrassed by me, so I got embarrassed, and then I deleted all of them.
I'm an idiot! If you ever post videos on the internet, keep them there, no matter who makes fun of you, just keep them there.
Anyways, there still are videos online of us when we were younger, so we're going to watch them
I just want to say, like, you will see the difference, of like, what we were like back then and what we're like now...
I actually love Zoosh(?)
Zoosh, is what we called, by the way, could you just step in frame, or just hide in the corner
Yeah, thanks bro. <3
So we called ourselves 'Zoosh', because, Smosh inspired us when we.. we were..
*NNHGNHGGGEEEEE~*
When we were younger, which makes me, it makes me curious as to who am inspiring right now,
that will become the next me, in like, 10 years.
Zircon!
MUUUHBOIII ZIRCON!
OK, without further-a-do, let's watch some kid videos bro~
Younger LP: 'Alright everyone, with profits decreasing and sales tax sky rocketing... we're facing a standstill..'
WHAT THE F#£$ WAS I DOING?!~
Question is, who wrote the script?
I DON'T KNOW! I think I wrote it, I thought it was funny...
Younger LP: 'Sure, blame the economy, blame the president, but let me tell you something...'
'BLAME THE PRESIDENT', Donald Trump, what'cha doing? Profits decreasing, sales taxes sky rocketing!
Wait... who was the president when you made this?
Don't know...
(at least he didn't smash plates..)
Younger LP: 'My lil' Timmy's lost 8 pounds, a'ight? We better step it up, or I'm laying down the hammer.'
YEEEEEEEA~ Till this day, I lay down the hammer.. we laid down the hammer on Jake bro~
Call us the Ogang, because he took the L, YAAAAAAAA~
You get it? Yeah I get it, he took the L... 'cause he took the L from the Logang...
They need you in there to actually shoot something... NAAAOOOOOOOOOOOOO~
The life of a vlogger/actor... a'ight guys, I'll be right back, quick cut.
HEY GUYS, You recognise this place? WE'RE BACK HOME. YAAAAAA~
It's not my home.. It's MY home, YAAAAA~
Logan: Alright so... what? Jeff: Can I go home?
Alright you guys, he wants to go home because it is 1:39AM, look at that... YAAAAAAA~
Anyways guys, they kept me on set, obviously, a lil' longer than I would've liked..
And now, we're here and...
Logan... can I go home?.. D:
Jeff, no, you gotta vlog with me bro, reaction video... come on Jeffery.
Logang, I've been vlogging for 308 days straight, no way I'm going to stop now.
Daily content, I don't care what it is or what I'm doing, I'M PUTTING IT OUT BRO~
Jeff has been my manager, throughout my internet career, 4/5 years maybe even.
So, these are going to take us back, getting into the young, young, young... age videos...
You can actually, a good fun fact... but you'll probably cut it, we go all the...
OK guys, I'm kind of an ass-hole, I've been an ass-hole my entire life, including when I was younger...
I did a lot of prank calls... This is one of those..
Look at those braces... ahhh F#£$..
Oh... Good one, Buttski
You had a friend to help you spell that...
This is savage... YO.. I was a savage... I love how I thought.. Butts were so funny...
'Buttski is so funny~'
Little kids love buttski?~ How old were you in this?
I was probably 11... keeeh... Buttski...
Jeff still thinks it's funny..
Right now, I was thinking of a joke, because like, I wasn't sure what to do, I wasn't quick-witted...
I wasn't that funny, I was a goofball, so I just did this.
HAHAHAHA~ Butthead, that's a (inaudible)
And the foghorn! And the foghorn~
Bro~ everyone loved butts, 'Butthead Street' dhuuuud~
Definitely could've though of something better.. Bro, look, it took time to craft this piece of perfection you're looking at now bro...
We also... sold merch... What da heck? In the day, we used to... how many did you sell?
2. And they were both from my cousins... Here's what that looked like.
No, I don't know.. Look at it!.. WHATTTTT~?!
Why did I think that was cool... I didn't even design it myself...
On Word-art?... Yes...
Bro, but look at it, the merch is on fire today, look at the logo behind you...
May favourite hat, I don't wear anything else. Its the best.
Look, it takes time to progress guys.
Here's a fun fact, you guys see like the...real life fruit ninja videos on the internet...
and not even kidding... before that was a thing, I literally made the first one, I swear on my life...
5 years ago... Check this out.
Oooooh... what a face~ THE INTENSITY.
How'd you make those faces?
I'M A BEAST! I sliced the cucumbers bro!~
That's all I can show... Because of music copyight purposes, but I hope you enjoyed...
Oh no... Wait! Yeah, yeah... when I first got Maverick. This is like when I first got Maverick like 5 years ago.
What am I doing... What am I looking at? Wait for it...
MAVERICK THE PARROT!~
Yo~ guys... look at his wings, Maverick's wings were green when I first got him...
We're just going to skip to the end here...
Maverick... waves.. and I lose the staring contest.
Yo... are you F#£$%@& kidding me bro~? Like.. this was like 4/5 years ago...
You had a lot of time on your hands... I had a lot of time and I got to say... Things have chaaaanged~
I don't even know what I was saying bro...
Yo, you know whats crazy... this was after puberty, like this... you can tell it's me...
2013... I was just wasn't funny... That's all. I thought that was pretty funny...
Wha... wHA... WhAt Do I dO?~
Here's the background, I told the guy my bird flew into the wall and his eyeball fell out from its eye socket...
So... let's watch...
I'm a F#$%^&@ idiot
This guy is still on the phone... I don't know, but you don't want to know right now...
I'm going to do a little throwback and call someone that's open.. prank call them a little bit...
Open for business? Yeah... like... Taco Bell is definitely open, right?
I don't think they take calls bro...
Yo~ an emergency vet, Jeff says this is a 24 hour emergency vet clinic...
Open till 7AM bro~
Opens AT 7AM you big idiot... Open 24 hours you big dumb dummie...
Oh, what the fu...? Oh...
F#$% MAN I CAN'T PRANK CALL A ROBOT!
That sound like me...
I'm going to go balls deep... I have no patience right now.
*My bird's eye, has fallen out of its socket....*
*He literally, got one eye...*
*I can bring him there, it might take a bit.. but I don't even have a skateboard*
I can't do the same voice... I can't do the same voice...
*Is there anyway you can put his eyeball back from over there?*
*Do you have... Do you have bird glasses?*
*I dont eve have healli?*
I'm still not funny... this poor girl...
*OK, I'm just going to have to put it back myself... Bye!*
F#$%!
I'M NOT F#£$%@% FUNNY STILL GODDAMIT.
Poor lady... she just wanted to help get my bird's eye back in its socket...
OK, lets what another video~
So guys, like I said, I made videos when I was younger.. and I made this like..
'big' comeback when we were older, and had gone through puberty.
Well... maybe not Jake... but me...
This was like.. our announcement video.. like, 'WE'RE COMING BACK'.
Look at Jake~
I was such a bad actor...
I think you're going through puberty, not, went through it.
Yeah, I know... Definitely. I was in a weird phase, my face was swollen, my nose was big..
Jake hasn't changed at all dude... He still thinks he's a thug, and he's still a whiny ass bitch...
I'm just kidding guys, I love Jake. He was a whiny bitch, he was a little thug dude, like... this kid was the baller...
You were kinda awkward... I was awkward
How can a human being go... 'We're really excited...'
DO I LOOK F#£$%@& EXCITED TO YOU BRO?~
This video is bad... This video is... Goddammit...
Here's the moral of the story... We're done watching this.
Please, I want to go home and watch them.
I'm removing them right now... I'm deleting them.
It's got 70,000 views... and it's gone.
OK, this vlog's done. COMEON....
Here's the moral of the story guys... If you work towards a goal and you keep doing it, even though right now you might now be good at it...
like, as you just witnessed, one day, you can be famous on the internet.
You can be a star too Johnny!
If your name's not Johnny, I, Uh... F#$%.
I literally can't make jokes at this hour, my mind stops functioning... OK!~
Keep on pursuing your dreams Logang, that's what we do, we are Mavericks~, you guys know I love you...
New York pop-up shop, we are coming this weekend... the epicness is real...
we get to do good vlogs again in the next few days..
Subscribe if you're not subscribed, join the fastest, the strongest... the.. uh...
The fastest growing... and the strongest family on the internet, the Logang...
I love you all Logang, I'll see you all tomorrow, take it easy fam... PEACE!
(so f#£$%^@ awkward...)